<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 06:57:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Wash your new clothes before wearing them!]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: Many textiles are treated with
chemicals including formaldehyde resins to prevent mildew and mold growth on
clothes during transport as well as dye fixatives, fire retardant and
antibacterial treatments, and treatments to prevent wrinkling and…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rap5y5/ysk_wash_your_new_clothes_before_wearing_them/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rap5y5/ysk_wash_your_new_clothes_before_wearing_them/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 06:40:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Many textiles are treated with chemicals including formaldehyde resins to prevent mildew and mold growth on clothes during transport as well as dye fixatives, fire retardant and antibacterial treatments, and treatments to prevent wrinkling and shrinkage.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You may be able to smell it on your new clothes. It&amp;amp;#39;s recommended that you wash all garments that will come into direct contact with your skin. Any remaining resins will come out as you wash them. At the acceptable levels present in clothing, the main risk to you is contact dermatitis. But you should still wash your new clothes.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m sharing this because I bought new pajamas and they reek.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.co.in/books/edition/Principles_of_Textile_Finishing/p_9PCwAAQBAJ?hl=en&amp;amp;amp;gbpv=1&amp;amp;amp;dq=finishing+textiles&amp;amp;amp;printsec=frontcover&quot;&amp;gt;Principles of Textile Finishing&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gao.gov/assets/gao-10-875.pdf&quot;&amp;gt;Formaldehyde in Textiles&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007%2Fs40521-019-0197-5&quot;&amp;gt;Textile Contact Dermatitis&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2010/12/11/your-money/11wrinkle.html&quot;&amp;gt;NYT Formaldehyde Fumes&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK the gov-run Unclaimed Property Program holds money YOU are owed]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: it&#39;s free, it&#39;s legit, and
it&#39;s your money</p> <p><strong>This program exists in the US, Canada, and UK
AT LEAST, so while I&#39;m talking about the US, your country probably has one
too</strong></p> <p>Let&#39;s say 8 years ago you quit a job.…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/raizy7/ysk_the_govrun_unclaimed_property_program_holds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/raizy7/ysk_the_govrun_unclaimed_property_program_holds/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 04:42:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: it&amp;amp;#39;s free, it&amp;amp;#39;s legit, and it&amp;amp;#39;s your money&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;This program exists in the US, Canada, and UK AT LEAST, so while I&amp;amp;#39;m talking about the US, your country probably has one too&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Let&amp;amp;#39;s say 8 years ago you quit a job. Later, that business discovered you were owed $50 in overtime. Legally, they have to get it to you, but realistically they aren&amp;amp;#39;t going to hire a PI to find &amp;amp;amp; verify your identity. Maybe you inherited some stocks/bonds and weren&amp;amp;#39;t notified. Where does the money go? Why, the Unclaimed Property Program! &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://unclaimed.org/search/&quot;&amp;gt;https://unclaimed.org/search/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Government-run and totally legitimate, it&amp;amp;#39;s free to search your name, your business name, your sister&amp;amp;#39;s name....anyone&amp;amp;#39;s name, and see if they are owed money. I found I was owed hundreds of dollars from my college apartment. My best friend was owed about $75 from an old gig. My current employer had cash from an overpaid utility bill.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s your money and it&amp;amp;#39;s free to get it back. There are BILLIONS OF DOLLARS left unclaimed in the US every year.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is not a scam. I get nothing from this. You won&amp;amp;#39;t be asked to pay a dime - if you are, it&amp;amp;#39;s a scam website. Every state has its own. You can search anywhere - make sure to search in states you&amp;amp;#39;ve lived in the past.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Steps:
Search name - find $$$ - fill out form - get a check in the mail a few weeks later&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;GET YOUR MONEY Y&amp;amp;#39;ALL!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: When planning a trip to see a national forest/park, forest/park rangers can provide loads of info on nearby lodging or transport]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: Planning a trip to another state can
be daunting. All national forests and parks are operated by one of the
forest/park services. All of these services have sites with contact forms. The
rangers are like librarians but for the land.</p> <p>They have all…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rad2oo/ysk_when_planning_a_trip_to_see_a_national/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rad2oo/ysk_when_planning_a_trip_to_see_a_national/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 23:45:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Planning a trip to another state can be daunting. All national forests and parks are operated by one of the forest/park services. All of these services have sites with contact forms. The rangers are like librarians but for the land.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They have all been in the area for a long time and are very familiar with tourism to their park. And they typically are very kind and informative and don&amp;amp;#39;t mind helping you out with the info.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It makes planning a trip so much easier to have all of that information up front.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK cut nails straight across to prevent ingrown nails]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: Improper nail trimming is 1 cause of
ingrown nails.</p> <p><a
href="https://puretherapyclinic.files.wordpress.com/2017/01/infection-after-ingrown-toenail-1.png">Here&#39;s
an example of how to cut them</a></p> <p>Causes:</p> <p>The etiology of…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rabskj/ysk_cut_nails_straight_across_to_prevent_ingrown/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rabskj/ysk_cut_nails_straight_across_to_prevent_ingrown/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 18:42:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Improper nail trimming is 1 cause of ingrown nails.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://puretherapyclinic.files.wordpress.com/2017/01/infection-after-ingrown-toenail-1.png&quot;&amp;gt;Here&amp;amp;#39;s an example of how to cut them&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Causes:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The etiology of ingrown toenails includes direct trauma to the toe that forces the nail corners into the surrounding nail fold, genetic predisposition, improper nail trimming, poorly fitting shoes, and constant and repetitive microtrauma from normal day-to-day activities. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After a painful procedure this afternoon and now typing this with throbbing pain, I wish I have knew about this MUCH SOONER.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC1472971/&quot;&amp;gt;Source&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/d5qh3a/&quot;&amp;gt;Old YSK post&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://theawkwardyeti.com/comic/ingrown-nail/&quot;&amp;gt;Comic&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK there is an app called Be My Eyes that allows visually impaired people to video call volunteers to ask for visual assistance]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: The app is free to download and you
can sign up as a volunteer or a visually impaired / blind person. If you need
visual help (examples given are picking the right colour of an item of clothing,
or the right brand of product when shopping) and you are…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r9lzqz/ysk_there_is_an_app_called_be_my_eyes_that_allows/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r9lzqz/ysk_there_is_an_app_called_be_my_eyes_that_allows/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 04:48:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: The app is free to download and you can sign up as a volunteer or a visually impaired / blind person. If you need visual help (examples given are picking the right colour of an item of clothing, or the right brand of product when shopping) and you are visually impaired, you press a button on the app. The app will call multiple volunteers (volunteers do not need to have the app open to recieve a call, they just have to be logged in) , and whoever picks up the quickest is connected by video call. The volunteer can then assist you in whatever task you need help with.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thought it was a great idea and a helpful app. Currently there are over 4 million volunteers signed up, but only 310, 000 visually impaired or blind people. Thought I&amp;amp;#39;d share in case anyone would find this useful.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: You should regularly pour white vinegar into your toilet's water cistern/tank to avoid calcium buildup in the toilet's flushing system, which can damage it.]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: Tap water, which is used to fill a
toilet&#39;s water tank, can contain a lot of calcium hardness in it. If left
unchecked, over time, calcareous buildups will form pretty much everywhere in
the toilet&#39;s flushing system, which will damage the gaskets…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r9tj6r/ysk_you_should_regularly_pour_white_vinegar_into/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r9tj6r/ysk_you_should_regularly_pour_white_vinegar_into/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 02:52:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Tap water, which is used to fill a toilet&amp;amp;#39;s water tank, can contain a lot of calcium hardness in it. If left unchecked, over time, calcareous buildups will form pretty much everywhere in the toilet&amp;amp;#39;s flushing system, which will damage the gaskets and other components in it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This also goes for pretty much anything that has tap water running through it in your home. Faucets, dishwasher, washing machine, kettle, shower head, etc. A little bit of vinegar is very efficient at getting rid of calcium deposits.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Steps:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Turn off the water&amp;amp;#39;s supply to the toilet&amp;amp;#39;s water tank, there&amp;amp;#39;s usually a knob or valve on the wall next to your toilet that you have to turn.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Open up the water tank/cistern by removing the top lid. (You may need a screwdriver to do this, depending on the model of your toilet)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;If the water tank is full, flush the water and empty it. (Because you&amp;amp;#39;ve turned off the water&amp;amp;#39;s supply, it shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t fill back up again)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Pour white vinegar all over the flushing system and fill half of the tank with it.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Fill the remaining half of the tank with hot water (not boiling, slightly hot, max 50°C/120°F temp) and let the mixture do its thing for 15-20 minutes. You should be able to see small bubbles, that&amp;amp;#39;s a result of the white vinegar dissolving the deposits.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;If you have thick hard deposits, wear latex gloves and use a sponge to scrape off the deposits.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Once all the deposits have dissolved, flush it all down the toilet.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Turn the water&amp;amp;#39;s supply to the toilet&amp;amp;#39;s tank back on and put the lid back on.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Do this once a month, or maybe even once a week, depending on how calcareous your tap water is.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ve just had to clean mine thoroughly because my toilet&amp;amp;#39;s flushing system stopped working properly, the water kept flushing/running. When I opened up the lid of the water tank, I was pretty horrified by the state of the flushing system. I had to replace the gaskets and had to scrape a lot of thick deposits. It was a real pain to clean... So, I now have a reminder in my phone to pour white vinegar into the toilet&amp;amp;#39;s water tank once a month to prevent this.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hopefully this is useful to someone!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Bleach expires and becomes almost useless]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: Bleach degrades over time into its
constituent parts. It doesn&#39;t become more dangerous but it will absolutely
lose its potency, thus limiting it&#39;s cleaning capabilities. If you&#39;re
having a hard time getting bleach to work as you&#39;d expect,…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r9ef6v/ysk_bleach_expires_and_becomes_almost_useless/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r9ef6v/ysk_bleach_expires_and_becomes_almost_useless/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 14:44:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Bleach degrades over time into its constituent parts. It doesn&amp;amp;#39;t become more dangerous but it will absolutely lose its potency, thus limiting it&amp;amp;#39;s cleaning capabilities. If you&amp;amp;#39;re having a hard time getting bleach to work as you&amp;amp;#39;d expect, think back to how long ago you bought it, as it could be almost completely inert if it&amp;amp;#39;s a few years old.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Afrin Can Cause a Serious Medical Condition Called Rebound Congestion]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: &quot;While it’s not considered an
&#39;addiction&#39; in the usual sense, your body <em>can</em> become dependent
on the drug. Doctors call this phenomenon &#39;rebound congestion,&#39; or <a
href="https://www.jacionline.org/article/S0091…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r92nwx/ysk_afrin_can_cause_a_serious_medical_condition/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r92nwx/ysk_afrin_can_cause_a_serious_medical_condition/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 13:46:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:  &amp;amp;quot;While it’s not considered an &amp;amp;#39;addiction&amp;amp;#39; in the usual sense, your body &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;can&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; become dependent on the drug. Doctors call this phenomenon &amp;amp;#39;rebound congestion,&amp;amp;#39; or &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jacionline.org/article/S0091-6749(06&quot;&amp;gt;rhinitis medicamentosa&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;01370-4/fulltext), and it is a very real problem. In fact, it could be responsible for up to 9% of visits to allergists and ENT doctors. &amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.singlecare.com/blog/rebound-congestion-nasal-spray-addiction/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.singlecare.com/blog/rebound-congestion-nasal-spray-addiction/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Ceiling fans have a winter setting.]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: Most ceiling fans are capable of
warming a room which is counterintuitive. On a lot a fans there&#39;s a switch
somewhere on the side that can be either up or down, flipping this switch will
switch the blades rotation so instead of blowing air down, it…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r91xer/ysk_ceiling_fans_have_a_winter_setting/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r91xer/ysk_ceiling_fans_have_a_winter_setting/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 09:26:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Most ceiling fans are capable of warming a room which is counterintuitive. On a lot a fans there&amp;amp;#39;s a switch somewhere on the side that can be either up or down, flipping this switch will switch the blades rotation so instead of blowing air down, it sucks air up (so having some space between the fan blades and the ceiling is ideal) which moves the cool air from below disturbing the warm air above which warms the room. (This is probably common knowledge that is worth repeating for those who didn&amp;amp;#39;t know)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: Really important point not in my original post brought up by a smart comment: Vacuum/dust the top of your blades before doing this! (thank you aquaman67!)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: teach children how to be around dogs safely and appropriately. Dog bite injuries are some of the most preventable injuries in childhood.]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: as a caregiver it is incredibly
important to keep children safe. If you want to have a dog in your family it is
important to teach kids how to interact with dogs safely.</p> <p>EDIT: Yes!
People should train their dogs! But also it’s really important kids…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r911j3/ysk_teach_children_how_to_be_around_dogs_safely/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r911j3/ysk_teach_children_how_to_be_around_dogs_safely/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 00:56:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: as a caregiver it is incredibly important to keep children safe. If you want to have a dog in your family it is important to teach kids how to interact with dogs safely.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT: Yes! People should train their dogs! But also it’s really important kids are taught certain elements of how to protect themselves. These are what I teach kids with families with dogs to work on safety. I am never excusing untrained dogs. I became a dog trainer because I care about dog training and well trained dogs. I am not blaming children for dog bites at all. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;One thing I routinely see as a dog trainer is how many dogs are absolutely terrified of children. It’s not necessarily due to bad experience. Rather, kids move sporadically and unpredictably; they vocalize in unusual patterns. Dogs are used to human movement but children do not move in ways dogs can easily read. Many dogs will not chase an adult out for a run but will chase a child that is skipping or sprinting down the side walk. This is partially due to the unpredictable nature of the way kids move; when dogs see those kinds of movement patterns instincts to herd/chase can be activated. To keep children in your care safe around dogs here are a few simple rules I used to explain to children I worked with:
1) If you see a dog, stop running. Try not to run or skip around dogs. A lot of dogs have herding and chasing instincts, and they may see these sudden movements an invitation to run towards you. They do not want to hurt you but they may also not want to play with you. It is safest for you to never run around when you see a dog. 
2) If a dog is scared of you, it does not mean you have done something wrong. Lots of dogs have had different experiences and do not know whether strangers will be nice to them. 
3) Do not scream or shout near or at dogs, try to lower your voice if you are playing with a dog. Screaming may scare them and many dogs will act defensively when scared. They do not want to hurt you but they may be concerned that you may hurt them.
4) If you want to say hi to a dog and the owner says it is okay, make sure the dog can see your hand. Instead of reaching for the top of their head see if they will let you pet them under the chin. Instead of approaching them from the front, you can try approaching the dog from the side with your hand extended. Dogs will approach each other from the side to indicate non threatening and friendly behavior.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Most corporations and ISPs track you through DNS and by using open source servers like Adguard DNS, you can block ads/trackers/malware on entire devices]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: DNS servers are required for anyone
to connect to the internet. Corporations and ISPs like to track you as much as
humanly possible within the law. They do this mostly through the DNS servers
they automatically configure your devices to use. By switching to…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8wdhg/ysk_most_corporations_and_isps_track_you_through/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8wdhg/ysk_most_corporations_and_isps_track_you_through/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:42:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: DNS servers are required for anyone to connect to the internet. Corporations and ISPs like to track you as much as humanly possible within the law. They do this mostly through the DNS servers they automatically configure your devices to use. By switching to an encrypted dns server with filters that block these tracking/ad domains you won&amp;amp;#39;t see any more on your entire device. DNS is being used for tracking/ads more than any time previously in the last twenty years. It&amp;amp;#39;s only a few numbers, it&amp;amp;#39;s an easy and effortless switch. Adguard is open source and free to use like Bitcoin and Ethereum, Linux, Firefox and Tor for example.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit (for no confusion): &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://adguard-dns.com/en/public-dns.html&quot;&amp;gt;https://adguard-dns.com/en/public-dns.html&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit 2: May not work with streaming services or youtube on phones or xboxes, play stations. Google loads all their ads on one domain, so to block those domains you&amp;amp;#39;d be blocking youtube itself, alas. You can sideload cercube youtube through altstore on IOS or use youtube vanced on Android to get premium for free though (I myself use altstore, also have spotify premium for free)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Some hospitals in the USA will offer significant discounts if you can prove your income is low.]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: Healthcare in the USA can be very
unaffordable and has the potential to financially ruin people. Not many people
are aware that <em>some</em> hospitals will offer discounts to your bill. You
MUST ASK for these discounts, they aren&#39;t handed out like…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8qwut/ysk_some_hospitals_in_the_usa_will_offer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8qwut/ysk_some_hospitals_in_the_usa_will_offer/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 20:36:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Healthcare in the USA can be very unaffordable and has the potential to financially ruin people. Not many people are aware that &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;some&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; hospitals will offer discounts to your bill. You MUST ASK for these discounts, they aren&amp;amp;#39;t handed out like candy. Some discounts may be applied simply because you asked and were polite in doing so. Other potentially larger discounts may be applied if you can prove your income is relatively low and you are unable to pay in a timely fashion. Generally speaking, some hospitals will prefer to lower your bill and get you to pay that amount rather than send the full bill to collections. You might want to seek out hospitals that offer these discounts as opposed to ones that do not. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As an anecdote, I had low wages and a hospital bill a number of years ago. I asked for a discount and got 45% off the bill, as well as 35% off any future bills for a whole year. I did have sign a document attesting to my wages. I had insurance at the time but the bill was slightly less than my deductible.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK, wary, weary, leery are all different words]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK, wary and leery both mean
&quot;cautious about a potential problem&quot;. Weary means &quot;tired&quot;.
</p> <p>Over and over you see people say they are &quot;weary&quot; of a
problem, that&#39;s because they are conflating wary and leery, two words…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r5rb87/ysk_wary_weary_leery_are_all_different_words/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r5rb87/ysk_wary_weary_leery_are_all_different_words/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 18:37:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK, wary and leery both mean &amp;amp;quot;cautious about a potential problem&amp;amp;quot;. Weary means &amp;amp;quot;tired&amp;amp;quot;. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Over and over you see people say they are &amp;amp;quot;weary&amp;amp;quot; of a problem, that&amp;amp;#39;s because they are conflating wary and leery, two words that means roughly the same thing, but combining those words leaves you with &amp;amp;quot;weary&amp;amp;quot;, which, again, just means tired. You are not tired of the problem, you are sceptical of the problem, so either wary or leery is what you mean. 
Unless the issue has exhausted you, you aren&amp;amp;#39;t &amp;amp;quot;weary&amp;amp;quot; of it, you&amp;amp;#39;re &amp;amp;quot;wary&amp;amp;quot; or &amp;amp;quot;leery&amp;amp;quot; of it. Learn the difference and you won&amp;amp;#39;t sound like a tool.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Most dish soaps (like Dawn) are designed to be used in a filled sink, not directly on the sponge.]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: Some soap companies are changing
their formula because so many people wash dishes now one by one, by putting dish
soap on the sponge and then scrubbing with running water, rather than filling
the sink. If you don’t have a 2 part sink, it makes it harder to…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8f5fq/ysk_most_dish_soaps_like_dawn_are_designed_to_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8f5fq/ysk_most_dish_soaps_like_dawn_are_designed_to_be/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 04:58:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Some soap companies are changing their formula because so many people wash dishes now one by one, by putting dish soap on the sponge and then scrubbing with running water, rather than filling the sink. If you don’t have a 2 part sink, it makes it harder to wash by hand (maybe consider using a tub), but if you do have 2 sides, fill one side w water and soap, soak dishes, scrub them while submerged, and then rinse them in the other side of the sink. It not only saves on both water and soap, but will get your dishes cleaner.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: There's a free and easy way to automate routine office tasks.]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: Nearly every office I&#39;ve ever
been in has done so many boring, repetitive things by hand. Spending just a
couple of days learning the basics of a scripting language like Python can cut
hours of tedious work out of your routine. Computers are really good…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r85t6g/ysk_theres_a_free_and_easy_way_to_automate/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r85t6g/ysk_theres_a_free_and_easy_way_to_automate/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 03:52:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Nearly every office I&amp;amp;#39;ve ever been in has done so many boring, repetitive things by hand. Spending just a couple of days learning the basics of a scripting language like Python can cut hours of tedious work out of your routine. Computers are really good at monotonous things, so if there&amp;amp;#39;s something you do the exact same way every day at work, there&amp;amp;#39;s probably a decent way to automate it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A good resource for this is &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://automatetheboringstuff.com/&quot;&amp;gt;Automate the Boring Stuff with Python&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; by Al Sweigart. It&amp;amp;#39;s free to read online.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Dating files using YYYYMMDD format will keep them in chronological order, leading to better file management]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: This is especially useful when you
need to save multiple versions of a file over time and can quickly reference the
date from the file name instead of “date modified” or “date created”. For
example, if I save a file today, I would name it “Example Text…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8dg01/ysk_dating_files_using_yyyymmdd_format_will_keep/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8dg01/ysk_dating_files_using_yyyymmdd_format_will_keep/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 02:57:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: This is especially useful when you need to save multiple versions of a file over time and can quickly reference the date from the file name instead of “date modified” or “date created”. For example, if I save a file today, I would name it “Example Text 20211203”. If I needed to save a new version in the same day, it would be “Example Text 20211203v2”.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Putting the date at the end instead of the front allows your files to be sorted alphabetically&amp;amp;gt;chronologically. Putting the date at the front will sort your files chronologically&amp;amp;gt;alphabetically.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: the artificial sweetener Xylitol, found in many common household items/food like toothpaste and even peanut butter, is extremely toxic to dogs. If your dog ingests even a small amount, they can die.]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: with the obesity epidemic and Keto
craze happening in the US, Xylitol use has been on the rise, significantly. It
is safe for humans (but will cause diarrhea in large amounts) but CAN kill your
dog very quickly unless taken to the vet IMMEDIATELY. When 5mg…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8bg42/ysk_the_artificial_sweetener_xylitol_found_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8bg42/ysk_the_artificial_sweetener_xylitol_found_in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 02:57:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: with the obesity epidemic and Keto craze happening in the US, Xylitol use has been on the rise, significantly. It is safe for humans (but will cause diarrhea in large amounts) but CAN kill your dog very quickly unless taken to the vet IMMEDIATELY. When 5mg per 1lb of body weight is ingested, it quickly causes liver failure followed by death and the effects will begin 10-15 minutes after ingesting. Any amount less than this can cause liver cirrhosis, seizures from severe hypoglycemia, tremors, and coma in under an hour. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This sweetener is found in most “sugar free” snacks, gum, toothpaste, candies, and if you know anyone who follows a Keto Diet or is just simply diabetic, they most likely have a whole bag of the stuff in their cupboard because it tastes and bakes very similar to regular sugar. It’s even in some brands of peanut butter. With the holidays going on and everyone baking sweet treats, I thought I would mention this because until my own dog ate toothpaste with Xylitol, I had NO idea it was so dangerous. She’s fine, now. Thankfully she threw the majority of it up herself. It’s extremely easy for a pup to eat this amount of Xylitol. If you bake a sugar free cake and your dog eats it off the counter while it’s cooling, or you forget to put your toothpaste in the drawer and your curious puppy eats it like puppies do… you could have your heart broken in under an hour. So please be careful! Also never give your pup a homemade treat that you didn’t make yourself!! This info is not well known at all and a good-intending person may use xylitol in place of sugar to make the treats “healthier”. So just be careful, fellow pet owners :) &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here is some more info! &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://vcahospitals.com/know-your-pet/xylitol-toxicity-in-dogs&quot;&amp;gt;https://vcahospitals.com/know-your-pet/xylitol-toxicity-in-dogs&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: driving slow isn't always the same as driving safe]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: there are a lot of situations where
driving fast is safer than driving slow. </p> <p>For example if you&#39;re
passing something, especially something like a truck with high winds, it&#39;s
safest to pass it as quickly as possible. I always use the rule of…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r85o02/ysk_driving_slow_isnt_always_the_same_as_driving/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r85o02/ysk_driving_slow_isnt_always_the_same_as_driving/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 22:42:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: there are a lot of situations where driving fast is safer than driving slow. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For example if you&amp;amp;#39;re passing something, especially something like a truck with high winds, it&amp;amp;#39;s safest to pass it as quickly as possible. I always use the rule of thumb that passing should take 10 seconds maximum.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Another example is with weather that causes bad sight (think heavy fog or rain) a lot of people just slam their brakes. But it&amp;amp;#39;s way safer to just keep driving the recommended speed, since that makes you predictable. If you don&amp;amp;#39;t trust the poor vision, go to the right lane and gradually lower your speed, if you plan to go slower than 80 km/h on the highway turn on your hazards.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Read the situation on the road, sometimes speeding up/not slowing down is the right course of action. (Note: read sometimes. Don&amp;amp;#39;t go blasting 200 on the daily just because of this post)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Tortillas are NOT fully cooked yet]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>TL;DR: Tortillas fresh out of a bag/package
are not fully cooked. Heating them on a hot non-stick, flattop, plancha, or well
seasoned cast iron pan for 30 seconds to a minute on each side until light
browning and warm/hot is essential for enjoying the tortillas.…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r85ye9/ysk_tortillas_are_not_fully_cooked_yet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r85ye9/ysk_tortillas_are_not_fully_cooked_yet/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 21:42:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TL;DR: Tortillas fresh out of a bag/package are not fully cooked. Heating them on a hot non-stick, flattop, plancha, or well seasoned cast iron pan for 30 seconds to a minute on each side until light browning and warm/hot is essential for enjoying the tortillas. Store in a clean folded towel or aluminum foil after cooking before eating to retain heat/moisture.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;[ EDIT ] The way this is going, I should have posted this on &amp;lt;a href=&quot;/r/unpopularopinion&quot;&amp;gt;r/unpopularopinion&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; lol. You can still have your &amp;amp;#39;not fully cooked tortillas&amp;amp;#39;, I understand they are also delicious and &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;safe to consume&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. Hopefully, my internet opinion does not take that joy away from you. We can all unite knowing our fiery passion for tortillas, at any stage of their beautiful lifecycle. &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;But cooking them again is better and since I must find at least one hill these days on which to fall on my own bayonet, this will be it!&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After moving from a town in the southwest United States to a more northern, college town it has become abundantly, even PAINFULLY clear that this is not common knowledge. After seeing scores of undergrads, graduate students and grown people alike reaching their clueless hands towards a half cooked, chewy bitter tortilla for their burrito/taco/etc needs, I have elected to take a stand.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Tortillas are not fully cooked. Corn, Flour, or any other grain that has been wrangled into a circular shape under the name of tortillas do not come fully cooked. If they had been fully cooked prior to being packaged, they would be stiff, crunchy and frankly some unholy center point between a tortilla chip and a malleable, fresh tortilla. Thus the onus falls on you, the consumer to bring these glorious circles of flavor up to the correct temperature, finish the cooking/rising, and bring a bitter/raw flavor of uncooked corn and flour to their glorious savory and delicious conclusion.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How: The best and most traditional way would be a &amp;amp;#39;plancha&amp;amp;#39; (think: a flat top griddle that gets exceptionally hot), but a non-stick pan or well seasoned cast-iron pan will do the job just as well. Get your choice of heat delivery device rippin&amp;amp;#39; hot (mid-high) and start dropping tortillas. Times will vary based on heat of your burners, type of pan etc, but you should look for some light to medium browning and spots on each side. Tortillas are cheap! Try a few different levels of done-ness to see how you like them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;NOTE: Huge bonus points to use your fingers when grabbing a flipping tortillas. You will make a Mexican/South American grandmother very happy somewhere. The technique varies from surface to surface, but my preferred way is a light pinch to flip, or using the curved edge of the pan and my four fingers to draw it up, allowing my thumb to get under the tortilla and toss it down on the other side. Obviously, don&amp;amp;#39;t do anything you are not comfortable with, and this technique benefits from both speed and the presence of &amp;amp;quot;kitchen fingers&amp;amp;quot; (Where my food service people at?). This saves scratches on a pan, and is much faster/efficient than some metal tool or spatula.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As soon as the tortilla leaves the griddle, you should be tossing it somewhere that helps it retain its heat and moisture. My personal favorite is making a small foil pouch, pinched on 3 sides with a fold on the forth, that can perfectly be sealed and unsealed as I build a stack of hot and steamy tortillas inside. The same technique can be done with a clean, folded towel. This steam is part of the cooking process, it softens to tortillas up a bit, and helps retain moisture, and finishes the cooking process with the heat. (In fact this is a great technique for many other foods. ever wonder why ballpark hotdogs, wrapped burritos, wrapped burgers taste so good? Part of that process is letting the heat from the steam and meat flow into the bread and keep it warm and moist. A good technique for other items too!)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Take these tortillas out as you are ready to eat them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;BONUS:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;carniceria/tortilleria : While most places may not have access to one of these stores, it is worth a quick map search. Tortillas from actual Latino/Hispanic grocers are much better than anything from a grocery store. Same rules apply for finishing cooking these tortillas. Plus, you will be supporting small businesses! These stores additionally often have a plethora of other Latin/Hispanic ingredients, seasonings, meats, pastries etc. and are often cheaper than chain grocery store equivalents (and better tasting!). Be kind and respectful of culture and language here too. I have never had a negative experience even though my Spanish is &amp;amp;#39;mierda&amp;amp;#39;, and the same service industry rules apply here: Hardworking people deserve respect and empathy, so don&amp;amp;#39;t be an asshole. Should go without saying, but still.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: When frustrated with a company, instead of telling the CSR "YOU did XYZ bad thing to me," say "COMPANY did XYZ bad thing to me."]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: Customer Service Representatives
(CSRs) have an unbelievably difficult job. Framing your frustration as being the
fault of the company, and not the CSR personally is not only the kind thing to
do, it also increases the odds that the rep will go above and…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r83u0x/ysk_when_frustrated_with_a_company_instead_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r83u0x/ysk_when_frustrated_with_a_company_instead_of/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 20:42:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Customer Service Representatives (CSRs) have an unbelievably difficult job. Framing your frustration as being the fault of the company, and not the CSR personally is not only the kind thing to do, it also increases the odds that the rep will go above and beyond to help you since you are not being unduly adversarial.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: If you have a CareerBuilder account, even if old and disused, they have started applying for jobs on your behalf even when not relevant.]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I started getting emails thanking me for my
application to jobs I don’t want and am not qualified for recently. One of the
recruiters was kind enough to respond to my follow up and informed me:</p>
<blockquote> <p>Thank you for Emailing me about this. I received an…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r81h2u/ysk_if_you_have_a_careerbuilder_account_even_if/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r81h2u/ysk_if_you_have_a_careerbuilder_account_even_if/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 18:49:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I started getting emails thanking me for my application to jobs I don’t want and am not qualified for recently. One of the recruiters was kind enough to respond to my follow up and informed me:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thank you for Emailing me about this. I received an application through Career Builder for a Truck Driver/Warehouse position yesterday. I spoke with the manager of my company and she advised me that if your resume and information is on CareerBuilder; CareerBuilder will apply on behalf of the candidate. I greatly apologize for the mix up and inconvenience.  I have deleted your information and you will no longer be contacted by our staffing company.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: If you have received similar notifications, you did not have your identity compromised, apparently CareerBuilder is just resorting to desperate measures to increase their numbers. Time to delete!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK starting a workout regimen requires more mental gymnastics than physical. You need to establish mental structure to stay motivated and push through the drone of doing it every week of every year, forever.]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: This popular New Years resolution is
just around the corner. Too much focus is put on the workout itself without
addressing the real problem of why so many start and then quit. Everyone
struggles, but some have sourced the key, the right mental gymnastics…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r7xqkx/ysk_starting_a_workout_regimen_requires_more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r7xqkx/ysk_starting_a_workout_regimen_requires_more/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 17:47:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: This popular New Years resolution is just around the corner. Too much focus is put on the workout itself without addressing the real problem of why so many start and then quit. Everyone struggles, but some have sourced the key, the right mental gymnastics to continue the regimen despite regular life pressures getting in the way.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After a lifetime of joking the #1 cause of injury is exercise, I found myself at a crossroads when I had to run about 30 meters (100 feet). I was a mess, barely able to breathe. I loosened my shirt and my pants. I knew i wasn’t in good shape but I hadn’t considered I was in terrible shape.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I started walking around the block, then longer, then jogging small parts, then jogging most of it, then moved on to hiking. I learned my body prefers Interval training, so I focused on this whether it was around the neighbourhood or into the woods.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After 3 months I was noticeably more fit but I was still struggling mentally with just getting out the door. I always had SO MANY reasons to not exercise today, mostly related to urgency of other matters. Put simply, I would find important distractions and then convince myself it was “too late” to do it today and to try again tomorrow.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It took about 6 months of mental retraining to stop this bad habit while also convincing myself I enjoyed it. Some tricks I used:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;1 - Whatever other urgent thing you have to do, don&amp;amp;#39;t argue with yourself on the priority  If you have a nagging mind like I do, I found it easier to just agree with the thought to skip today and then just do the exercise anyways.  Its like the old adage of not what you say, but what you do.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;2 - Any opportunity I had to talk about my training, I did so and said how much I loved it. Even though I was lying, I said I loved it and I said it to myself regularly as well. Weirdly, after awhile you start to actually love it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;3 - Meditation, It helped a lot learning how to “let thoughts go”, even important valid thoughts. Just because something is important, it doesn’t mean it’s more important than your health. Let the valid and important thought go along with any other thoughts and do your exercises&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;4 - Find anyone to do it with. Your friends keep you honest. Or get a dog. That sad look they give you, or excited when they hear keys, it really works. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;5 - Upper body and general muscle development are key not just for balance, but muscles burn more calories. You may not be as toned as the person putting in a couple hours a day, but any increase in muscle makes a better working body that burns more calories for the same amount of work. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;6 - Even if its just 5 minutes. This is my go to when nothing else is working. It&amp;amp;#39;s amazing how taking 5 minutes can turn into 15 and then into 30. And you feel like a boss afterwards.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;7 - Keep mixing it up. I go one day at the gym, then a neighborhood walk, then Beat Sabre, then a good hike, and then just drive somewhere new. I found I failed when it&amp;amp;#39;s just the same thing over and over, every week, forever. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It’s been 4 years now and I do love it and look forward to it each week. BUT!... I still mentally struggle with it. Or I should say the desire to skip it is always on the perimeter trying to get back in, and when it does, I just take my toolkit out and use one of my tricks to get back into it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Make this the year you make it stick. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nbcnews.com/better/health/6-mental-tricks-tricks-help-make-exercise-habit-ncna914386&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.nbcnews.com/better/health/6-mental-tricks-tricks-help-make-exercise-habit-ncna914386&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: when you buy digital media online, you don't own it, you're just licensed to watch it. that can be taken away.]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: just because you &quot;buy&quot;
something digitally, doesn&#39;t mean the same when you physically buy
something. you are buying ACCESS to the content. don&#39;t be surprised if the
company revokes access. </p>…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r7tija/ysk_when_you_buy_digital_media_online_you_dont/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r7tija/ysk_when_you_buy_digital_media_online_you_dont/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 09:43:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: just because you &amp;amp;quot;buy&amp;amp;quot; something digitally, doesn&amp;amp;#39;t mean the same when you physically buy something. you are buying ACCESS to the content. don&amp;amp;#39;t be surprised if the company revokes access. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnarcher/2018/09/17/apple-responds-to-disappearing-itunes-movie-purchases-issue/1&quot;&amp;gt;A user lost access to his movies in apple&amp;amp;#39;s ecosystem&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. it was a &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.macobserver.com/analysis/apple-isnt-deleting-itunes-movies/&quot;&amp;gt;licensing issue&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you look at amazon&amp;amp;#39;s policy for the content providers that want to use Amazon&amp;amp;#39;s platform: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://videodirect.amazon.com/home/agreement?ref_=avd_hm_ft_la&quot;&amp;gt;https://videodirect.amazon.com/home/agreement?ref_=avd_hm_ft_la&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Under Section &amp;amp;quot;6. General Description of the Service; Distribution Modes:&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(a) &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;purchase a license to access&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; digital copies ...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(b) &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;purchase a license to access&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; digital copies ...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(c) &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;access&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; audio visual content via ...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(d) &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;access&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; audio visual content ....&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Nowhere does it mention you own a copy of the audio/visual content. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://screencrush.com/do-you-own-movies-you-buy-in-itunes-forever/&quot;&amp;gt;A lawsuit against Apple for using &amp;amp;quot;buying&amp;amp;quot; when you don&amp;amp;#39;t really buy anything&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;Apple tried to get the lawsuit dismissed, claiming that consumers know that buying something on iTunes doesn’t mean buying it forever.&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://tos.ea.com/legalapp/WEBTERMS/US/en/PC/#section2&quot;&amp;gt;You don&amp;amp;#39;t own games from EA, only a license to the content&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;The EA Services are licensed to you, not sold&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. EA grants you a personal, limited, non-transferable, revocable and non-exclusive license to use the EA Services to which you have access for your non-commercial use, subject to your compliance with this Agreement.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that button batteries (the batteries that look like coins) of swallowed can burn the inside of a persons esophagus and is a life threatening emergency.]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: children find these batteries and
swallow them. We especially see these batteries around the holidays as they are
in decorations, cards, toys and all sorts of other things. I work as a nurse and
have seen several children need to be tube fed for the rest of…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r7p2js/ysk_that_button_batteries_the_batteries_that_look/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r7p2js/ysk_that_button_batteries_the_batteries_that_look/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 08:23:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: children find these batteries and swallow them. We especially see these batteries around the holidays as they are in decorations, cards, toys and all sorts of other things. I work as a nurse and have seen several children need to be tube fed for the rest of their lives and/or have permanent vocal damage. Please keep items with button batteries up and away from toddlers and young children. And if it does happen (happens to the best parents so don&amp;amp;#39;t freak out) get your kid to the emergency room immediately. If the x-ray shows a &amp;amp;quot;coin with a halo&amp;amp;quot; get your kid into surgery asap.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that you should always ask before introducing yourself or pet to a dog you don’t know]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why ysk: even dogs with good owners can be
aggressive or in bad moods. Many dogs are rescued from bad situations or had
unfortunate experience that cause them to either not like new people or other
dogs. </p> <p>These dogs still have every right to be walked around…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r7f7wm/ysk_that_you_should_always_ask_before_introducing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r7f7wm/ysk_that_you_should_always_ask_before_introducing/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 23:53:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why ysk: even dogs with good owners can be aggressive or in bad moods. Many dogs are rescued from bad situations or had unfortunate experience that cause them to either not like new people or other dogs. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;These dogs still have every right to be walked around as long as the owner is conscious and doesn’t cause danger to anyone else, but if they are out of the way and you come up to them without asking you are putting yourself at risk.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also, not all dog owners are good owners and always use caution with dogs you don’t know. Be ready to remove yourself or your dog from their reach if nescessary &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source: experience and friend with rescued bait dog&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK A team of researchers are using a choose-your-own-adventure game to allow you to change your inner dialogue – and the study is still open for participants.]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: We’re beginning to realise the
importance of self-care and investing in our mental wellness early enough,
instead of reaching for treatment when things have already gone awry. While
professional help is probably always the best option (if you can afford…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r76qnq/ysk_a_team_of_researchers_are_using_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r76qnq/ysk_a_team_of_researchers_are_using_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 15:40:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: We’re beginning to realise the importance of self-care and investing in our mental wellness early enough, instead of reaching for treatment when things have already gone awry. While professional help is probably always the best option (if you can afford it), technology can surely play a role in terms of education and prevention.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Games for Emotional and Mental Health lab is a group of behaviour change researchers and game designers, pioneering a model that combines evidence-based wellbeing tools with play and storytelling, because they’ve found that most existing apps fail to engage people long enough to deliver any benefits.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The lab recently opened a &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://utwentebs.eu.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_9uwhwDopngYIocu&quot;&amp;gt;study&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; that you can take part in, focusing on a new iOS game that teaches self-awareness through a choose-your-own-adventure story. If you’re the kind of person with a more creative mind, it could be worth trying this approach and push science forward while you’re at it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that 6% inflation in 2021 to 2% inflation in 2022 is “transitionary” in relative terms, but an actual increase in absolute terms]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: make sure that your yearly salary
increase is at least that of inflation. Otherwise, it’s a pay cut.</p>
<p>Inflation is often shown as year over year percentage change. Do not be
fooled by the government when the inflation is “transitioned” into 2%…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6q20e/ysk_that_6_inflation_in_2021_to_2_inflation_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6q20e/ysk_that_6_inflation_in_2021_to_2_inflation_in/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 02:45:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: make sure that your yearly salary increase is at least that of inflation. Otherwise, it’s a pay cut.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Inflation is often shown as year over year percentage change. Do not be fooled by the government when the inflation is “transitioned” into 2% the following year.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For example, an item that costs 100 dollar in 2020 will cost 106 dollar in 2021 with 6% inflation, but will costs 108.12 dollar in 2022 with 2% inflation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK The build-up of black soot on the bottom of your pots and pans is not normal. It can be a sign of excess carbon monoxide.]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: Carbon monoxide (CO) is known as the
&quot;silent killer&quot; for a reason. It&#39;s odourless and colourless, so
it&#39;s very hard to detect. For this reason, it&#39;s always a good idea to
ensure your fire detector/smoke alarm also has CO detection…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6su7n/ysk_the_buildup_of_black_soot_on_the_bottom_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6su7n/ysk_the_buildup_of_black_soot_on_the_bottom_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 01:38:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:   Carbon monoxide (CO) is known as the &amp;amp;quot;silent killer&amp;amp;quot; for a reason.  It&amp;amp;#39;s odourless and colourless, so it&amp;amp;#39;s very hard to detect.   For this reason, it&amp;amp;#39;s always a good idea to ensure your fire detector/smoke alarm also has CO detection  (most of the newer fire detectors come standard with this nowadays).      &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m making this post because I noticed a lot of black soot (black powdery substance) building up on the bottom of my girlfriend&amp;amp;#39;s pots and pans when we cook at her condo.  I also have a gas range stove at my place but have never seen build-up of soot on my cooking equipment.  This soot will come off as black dust on your finger if you rub the bottom of a pan after it cools.  Recently, the CO alarm went off on the smoke detector at my girlfriend&amp;amp;#39;s place, which obviously caused some concern and I started to look into the potential causes while she called the fire department.  Be sure to get out of the house and/or ventilated it by opening the windows.  Getting out of the home right away is the safest option and highly recommended. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;One of the best articles I found was this one:   &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.abe.iastate.edu/extension-and-outreach/carbon-monoxide-poisoning-checking-for-complete-combustion-aen-175/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.abe.iastate.edu/extension-and-outreach/carbon-monoxide-poisoning-checking-for-complete-combustion-aen-175/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The article shows that soot can be a sign that your natural gas stove is has an incorrect mixture of air and gas, which can lead to an incomplete burn.  This incomplete burn can cause the build-up of soot and carbon monoxide in your home.   While this typically creates CO in amounts that are not deadly, they can cause a lot of health problems over time and if the ventilation in your home is poor, it can potentially be fatal. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some symptoms of CO poisoning are headaches, shortness of breath, dizziness, weaknesss, confusion, and nausea.  If you have any of these symptoms that seem to clear up when you leave home, check the bottom of your pots and pans for clues.    The article above goes into a lot better detail than I ever could, and I&amp;amp;#39;m definitely no expert in this field.   I figured this could be life-saving information and was worth a share.     If anyone who&amp;amp;#39;s an expert in this that has corrections for my info and/or more information on this, I encourage you to share it in the thread. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Stay safe out there,&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sillyist&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that Revolut shares your private data by default with third parties]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>In case you‘re using Revolut, I recommend you
to take a look at the app‘s privacy settings. The third point under the
„marketing“ section allows them to share data such as „name, email address and
app events with social m*dia and advertising platforms“, and the…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r513bd/ysk_that_revolut_shares_your_private_data_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r513bd/ysk_that_revolut_shares_your_private_data_by/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:43:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In case you‘re using Revolut, I recommend you to take a look at the app‘s privacy settings. The third point under the „marketing“ section allows them to share data such as „name, email address and app events with social m*dia and advertising platforms“, and the toggle is turned on by default.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: The concerned data, especially in context with your bank activities, tells a lot about you and your behavior, it should therefore be treated confidential. I strongly recommend to turn off that setting.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK - As weather gets colder, it is absolutely vital you are careful with antifreeze; making sure it is kept safely in your shed and clean up any spills. Antifreeze kills cats in tiny amounts, and most taste good to kitties (and dogs) so they will continue eating it.]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK:</p> <p>The smallest amount of
antifreeze can kill cats, and kill them horribly. Signs can show within 30
minutes of ingestion; they begin to stumble like they are drunk, start to find
breathing difficult. They vomit, they can have seizures. Finally, their…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r5spih/ysk_as_weather_gets_colder_it_is_absolutely_vital/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r5spih/ysk_as_weather_gets_colder_it_is_absolutely_vital/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The smallest amount of antifreeze can kill cats, and kill them horribly. Signs can show within 30 minutes of ingestion; they begin to stumble like they are drunk, start to find breathing difficult. They vomit, they can have seizures. Finally, their kidneys give out. It is absolutely horrific for pet and owner.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know this from experience, having lost &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/gallery/4ZzwTLh&quot;&amp;gt;two cats&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; to antifreeze poisoning in the space of one week.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;*The worst thing about antifreeze is it&amp;amp;#39;s active ingredient, Ethylene Glycol, has an appealing, sweet taste. Once found, your pet will continue you eat it. Not knowing they are killing themselves.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s also vital to know &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rspca.org.uk/adviceandwelfare/pets/cats/health/poisoning/antifreeze&quot;&amp;gt;the symptoms&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; of antifreeze poisoning, as depending on dosage it only takes 2-3 days for your kitty&amp;amp;#39;s kidneys to fail, and the cat to pass.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please please please, save a cat this Christmas. Store, dispose of and use any antifreeze safely, or buy pet-safe antifreeze (that doesn&amp;amp;#39;t contain ethylene glycol).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that browsers have limitations when it comes to streaming quality. For watching shows or movies, Edge and Safari actually provide a way better experience than Chrome or Firefox.]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: Especially if you&#39;re subscribed
to a high-quality streaming plan, you should consider your go-to browser (at
least for your streams). Otherwise you basically have zero benefits from the
extra money you&#39;re paying if you&#39;re not just out for the…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6h98n/ysk_that_browsers_have_limitations_when_it_comes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6h98n/ysk_that_browsers_have_limitations_when_it_comes/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Especially if you&amp;amp;#39;re subscribed to a high-quality streaming plan, you should consider your go-to browser (at least for your streams). Otherwise you basically have zero benefits from the extra money you&amp;amp;#39;re paying if you&amp;amp;#39;re not just out for the multiple profiles in order to split the costs.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;These are the resolution limits of the most common browsers:&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Google Chrome:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Up to 720p (although you can get 1080p using Chrome OS)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Firefox:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Up to 720p&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Opera:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Up to 720p&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Safari:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Up to 4K (requires a select 2018 Mac or later with an Apple T2 Security Chip and MacOS 11.0 Big Sur or later)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Microsoft Edge:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Up to 4K (requires HDCP 2.2-compliant connection to a 4K display, with at least Intel&amp;amp;#39;s 7th-gen Core CPU, plus the latest version of Windows)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.digitaltrends.com/home-theater/getting-hd-netflix/&quot;&amp;gt;this site&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;Why you’re not getting Netflix in HD or 4K and how to fix it&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(Also, just to clarify: 720p = HD, 1080p = Full HD)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;[Please keep in mind that this post refers to streaming as in Netflix, Amazon Prime, etc. and not e.g. YouTube videos. Also, this isn&amp;amp;#39;t meant to promote or shame any particular browsers. They all have their benefits/downsides and in the end, everyone should decide for themselves which browser suits them and their needs best.]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that taking a deep breath to calm down works better with diaphragmatic breathing]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: If you’re trying to calm down,
especially during a panic attack, diaphragmatic or belly breathing is what will
help you relax. Thoracic or chest breathing is better for physical exertion and
may actually make you more tense.…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6bw6t/ysk_that_taking_a_deep_breath_to_calm_down_works/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6bw6t/ysk_that_taking_a_deep_breath_to_calm_down_works/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: If you’re trying to calm down, especially during a panic attack, diaphragmatic or belly breathing is what will help you relax. Thoracic or chest breathing is better for physical exertion and may actually make you more tense. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/stress-management/in-depth/decrease-stress-by-using-your-breath/art-20267197&quot;&amp;gt;(Source: Mayo Clinic)&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; Knowing how to use diaphragmatic breathing can help you calm down in stressful situations and potentially avoid a panic attack. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;From the link above, for those who don’t want to read the whole thing: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;•Get into a comfortable position. Close your eyes and bring your attention to your body and breath.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;•Inhale deeply through your nose, allowing your abdomen to fill with air, gently expanding out. Exhale by relaxing and releasing all of the air through your nose.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;•Place one hand on your abdomen, right below your navel, and the other hand on your upper chest. Take a deep breath in through your nose and out through your nose. Feel the coolness of the air as it enters in and the warmth as it flows out.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;•As you breathe in and out through your nose, focus on shifting your breath so that you can feel the rise and fall of your breathing in your abdomen more than in your chest. In other words, make the hand that rests on your abdomen move more than the hand on your chest. Take a deep breath in through your nose, sending it through the back of your throat and down to your belly. Let your abdomen slowly deflate as you exhale through your nose.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;•Take three more slow, deep breaths with conscious focus on the rise and fall of your abdomen. Continue to breathe fully and deeply, allowing and trusting the body as the breath slows and becomes more relaxed.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit 1: Thank you to &amp;lt;a href=&quot;/u/inspirationisagift&quot;&amp;gt;u/inspirationisagift&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; for adding this info in a comment, because it’s actually really useful!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Using a breathing method like box breathing/square breathing has been empirically supported as an alternative method that helps with panic attacks and times of high stress/anxiety as it brings the oxygen level down. This method deactivates the &amp;amp;#39;fight flight freeze&amp;amp;#39; stress response which relies on increased levels of oxygen.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Deep breathing can sometimes give the body that extra oxygen which keeps the body in a stressed state, wheras by reducing respiration/oxygen intake, it helps to activate the &amp;amp;#39;rest and digest&amp;amp;#39; system instead. Just in case anyone has found deep breathing to not be helpful 🙂&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Houseplants go dormant in winter, so reduce your watering.]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: As the cold weather slows down their
metabolic rate, plants will require water less frequently than in the summer. It
is important to not overwater your houseplants as they can grow mold, mildew, or
be susceptible to fungus and other diseases with excessive…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r5ooh7/ysk_houseplants_go_dormant_in_winter_so_reduce/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r5ooh7/ysk_houseplants_go_dormant_in_winter_so_reduce/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: As the cold weather slows down their metabolic rate, plants will require water less frequently than in the summer. It is important to not overwater your houseplants as they can grow mold, mildew, or be susceptible to fungus and other diseases with excessive water. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A good rule of thumb is to touch the soil with your finger to see if the substrate is moist, and avoid watering again until it is dry. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also, leaf tips can go brown from cold. Do not cut these off until warmer weather arrives, as this is one of the plant’s protection against frost. They essentially write off a part of themselves to take the damage from the cold in order to protect the rest of them. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Good luck, and happy gardening!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: SciHub is a free recourse to get access to the majority of research papers]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: So many journal articles in science
specifically are locked behind extreme paywalls, especially recently published
papers with exciting information. I&#39;ve seen paywalls that range from
$50-$200 just to get access to one article. SciHub was founded by a…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r69hrq/ysk_scihub_is_a_free_recourse_to_get_access_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r69hrq/ysk_scihub_is_a_free_recourse_to_get_access_to/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: So many journal articles in science specifically are locked behind extreme paywalls, especially recently published papers with exciting information. I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen paywalls that range from $50-$200 just to get access to one article. SciHub was founded by a Kazakhstan woman, Alexandra Elbakyan, to make scientific information more accessible to the general public. As a STEM major, I look through tons of research papers every week and a friend of mine recently told me about this, so I wanted to share incredible resource for anyone who is unaware, especially people in the scientific community.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: So glad to see everyone sharing additional resources &amp;amp;amp; information about the inner workings of publishing research in general. I had no idea that it was such a monopolized industry &amp;amp;amp; scientists actually have to pay if they want people to read their research. Thanks to everyone &amp;amp;amp; please continue sharing this vital info! - signed a future scientist.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: There is an extension that lets you see the number of dislikes on a youtube video]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Not sure about the policy of linking directly
to things, but if you just google: &quot;Return Youtube Dislike&quot; you can
find the right extension. It works for Chrome and Firefox.</p> <p>Why YSK:
apparently I have to explain why youtube dislike counts are…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r63i5k/ysk_there_is_an_extension_that_lets_you_see_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r63i5k/ysk_there_is_an_extension_that_lets_you_see_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Not sure about the policy of linking directly to things, but if you just google: &amp;amp;quot;Return Youtube Dislike&amp;amp;quot; you can find the right extension. It works for Chrome and Firefox.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: apparently I have to explain why youtube dislike counts are important. Well it&amp;amp;#39;s helpful when you&amp;amp;#39;re trying to sniff out a scam, or maybe it&amp;amp;#39;s helpful when looking up instructional video&amp;amp;#39;s or DIY stuff. It&amp;amp;#39;s also amusing to look at youtube rewind and see how many dislikes it gets.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Basically you should know because youtube took away it&amp;amp;#39;s functionality and this brings it back.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK the lyrics to a much better birthday song for all ages.]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p><em>Futurama</em> ep. 2:14 features an
original song recited for Lord Nibbler&#39;s birthday. It uses roughly the same
melody as &quot;Happy Birthday&quot; for the same eight bars, but with much
better lyrics. The original lyrics are as follows:</p> <p><em>What day…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r55xiq/ysk_the_lyrics_to_a_much_better_birthday_song_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r55xiq/ysk_the_lyrics_to_a_much_better_birthday_song_for/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 15:19:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Futurama&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; ep. 2:14 features an original song recited for Lord Nibbler&amp;amp;#39;s birthday. It uses roughly the same melody as &amp;amp;quot;Happy Birthday&amp;amp;quot; for the same eight bars, but with much better lyrics. The original lyrics are as follows:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;What day is today?&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s Nibbler&amp;amp;#39;s birthday!&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;What a day for a birthday!&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Let&amp;amp;#39;s all have some cake!&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;These lyrics were written for TV in order to avoid infringing the copyright for &amp;amp;quot;Happy Birthday&amp;amp;quot;, but they are good enough to replace &amp;amp;quot;Happy Birthday&amp;amp;quot; entirely if adopted by the public.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Saying the phrase &amp;amp;quot;Happy birthday to you&amp;amp;quot; four times in a row is boring and embarassing for everyone involved, and is often thought of as the least fun part of a birthday party. These lyrics are more fun and creative, and they touch on the most exciting themes for a child: special occasions, attention, and cake.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that the color of the warning lights on your car's dashboard indicate the urgency of the problem]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Some cars have weird, confusingly shaped
lights on the dash, or maybe you just didn&#39;t read the manual. Either way,
you don&#39;t necessarily need to know what every light means as long as you pay
attention to the color.</p> <p>Green: Non issue, just a…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r58u24/ysk_that_the_color_of_the_warning_lights_on_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r58u24/ysk_that_the_color_of_the_warning_lights_on_your/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 02:51:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some cars have weird, confusingly shaped lights on the dash, or maybe you just didn&amp;amp;#39;t read the manual. Either way, you don&amp;amp;#39;t necessarily need to know what every light means as long as you pay attention to the color.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Green: Non issue, just a notification. Things like fog lights, or ready to move on hybrids.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Amber: Non urgent issue. These are for issues that are OK to continue driving with, but should be fixed soon. Things like check engine, ABS failure, traction control failure, tire pressure, etc.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Red: Urgent issue. These are for issues that pose an immediate serious danger to you or the car. If a red light comes on, stop immediately. Things like no oil pressure, overheating, or brake failure, or charging system failure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Charging system failure may sound like that should be an amber light, but there&amp;amp;#39;s a good reason it&amp;amp;#39;s red. It&amp;amp;#39;s rare for an alternator to just die all of a sudden, so that could also indicate a broken serpentine belt, which would also stop your water pump and power steering pump. It could also indicate an electrical fault that could, in serious cases, start a fire. Even if it&amp;amp;#39;s neither of those, when your battery dies, you are stranded. So that&amp;amp;#39;s why it&amp;amp;#39;s red.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:  If you don&amp;amp;#39;t know what all the lights in your car mean, just knowing what the color means can save you a lot of money and avoid dangerous situations.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ysk Ceiling fans have a summer and winter setting.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: There is usually a switch on the fan that changes the direction the fan
spins. Due to the pitch of the blades this changes the direction air flows. In
summer, blades are supposed to spin counter-clockwise and this creates a
downdraft to help cool. In winter, blades are supposed to spin…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r51r1p/ysk_ceiling_fans_have_a_summer_and_winter_setting/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r51r1p/ysk_ceiling_fans_have_a_summer_and_winter_setting/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 19:51:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: There is usually a switch on the fan that changes the direction the fan spins. Due to the pitch of the blades this changes the direction air flows. In summer, blades are supposed to spin counter-clockwise and this creates a downdraft to help cool. In winter, blades are supposed to spin clockwise to circulate warm air around for more efficient heating. This is especially important in homes with high or vaulted ceilings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that apostrophes are never used to make a singular word plural.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Many people use 's to pluralize words. This is incorrect. The only time
you should ever use an apostrophe is for contractions (don't, haven't, she's) to
make something possessive (Dave's), or for pluralizing lowercase letters (dot
your i's).]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r4zsyl/ysk_that_apostrophes_are_never_used_to_make_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r4zsyl/ysk_that_apostrophes_are_never_used_to_make_a/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 18:54:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Many people use &amp;#39;s to pluralize words. This is incorrect. The only time you should ever use an apostrophe is for contractions (don&amp;#39;t, haven&amp;#39;t, she&amp;#39;s) to make something possessive (Dave&amp;#39;s), or for pluralizing lowercase letters (dot your i&amp;#39;s).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK That Police Stations Are Probably The Safest Place To Meet Up With Strangers When Buying/Selling Over The Internet]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: If you're looking for deals from private parties, or selling something
as a private party, the meeting place for the transaction should be somewhere
safe. Police stations are just about the safest place you can meet publicly, and
also act as a filter against people with bad intentions.

I'm…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r4qgsn/ysk_that_police_stations_are_probably_the_safest/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r4qgsn/ysk_that_police_stations_are_probably_the_safest/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 11:45:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If you&amp;#39;re looking for deals from private parties, or selling something as a private party, the meeting place for the transaction should be somewhere safe.  Police stations are just about the safest place you can meet publicly, and also act as a filter against people with bad intentions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m currently selling a high-priced item as a private party, and told a prospective buyer who wanted to see the item that he should meet me at my local police station.  He refused, and suggested a McDonald&amp;#39;s parking lot in a sketchy neighborhood instead.  His refusal to meet at the police station sounded my alarm bells, especially when he couldn&amp;#39;t articulate his objections to meeting there.  I called off the deal with him, and instead went with the next prospective buyer who not only had no objections to meeting at the police station, but expressed his appreciation for doing so at such a safe place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S.  Many police stations not only support this activity, but some will also provide a police officer to be present during the transaction upon request.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that alcohol is extremely addictive, and kills approximately 3 million people worldwide each year. The severity and potential of alcoholism has been downplayed by the media to increase sales.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK - to all the teens and young people out there reading this, you don't
need to consume alcohol to socialize and have a good time. Advertisements will
try to convince you otherwise, so that you become addicted to their product.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r4hzyw/ysk_that_alcohol_is_extremely_addictive_and_kills/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r4hzyw/ysk_that_alcohol_is_extremely_addictive_and_kills/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 02:07:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK - to all the teens and young people out there reading this, you don&amp;#39;t need to consume alcohol to socialize and have a good time. Advertisements will try to convince you otherwise, so that you become addicted to their product.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Most fire extinguishers are single use ONLY, and will be leaky after use.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: It can be tempting to use a fire extinguisher for fun, and just put it
back when you're done, but most fire extinguishers don't seal completely once
the handle has been pressed, and will continue to leak until they eventually run
out of pressure. You should always get a new fire…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r4h1q9/ysk_most_fire_extinguishers_are_single_use_only/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r4h1q9/ysk_most_fire_extinguishers_are_single_use_only/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 02:07:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It can be tempting to use a fire extinguisher for fun, and just put it back when you&amp;#39;re done, but most fire extinguishers don&amp;#39;t seal completely once the handle has been pressed, and will continue to leak until they eventually run out of pressure. You should always get a new fire extinguisher when you&amp;#39;ve used it, even if it was just to put out a small fire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that automated telephonic solicitors (phone-bots) are extremely easy to detect for a reason -- and -- just like a real salesman -- they don't actually want to talk to you unless there's a possibility of a real sale.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Phone solicitors -- automated and otherwise -- aren't interested in
wasting time keeping someone on the line who isn't likely to actually spend
money. So if you receive a call from an unknown phone number which sounds like
it might be a recorded advertisement, then turn the tables on them…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3p10x/ysk_that_automated_telephonic_solicitors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3p10x/ysk_that_automated_telephonic_solicitors/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 01:08:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  Phone solicitors -- automated and otherwise -- aren&amp;#39;t interested in wasting time keeping someone on the line who isn&amp;#39;t likely to actually spend money. So if you receive a call from an unknown phone number which sounds like it &lt;em&gt;might&lt;/em&gt; be a recorded advertisement, then turn the tables on them by intentionally providing an unconventional response. Even if the computer on the other end doesn&amp;#39;t bail, it&amp;#39;ll still reveal itself as such pretty quickly, giving you the opportunity to disconnect from an obvious unsolicited phone advertisement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An example: I just received a call which started out with, &amp;quot;Hello! My name is Andrew -- how are you?&amp;quot; No identifying company, no identifying purpose... just those words and nothing else. Of course, that&amp;#39;s not the way a legit phone solicitor starts a conversation, so I already suspected that it was a recording. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thus, I responded by directly asking, &amp;quot;Is this a recording?&amp;quot; My confirmation came in the form of a very brief clip of the first word that the recording was going to say next, which was abruptly interrupted by a line disconnection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So either I confused it enough to force a bail-out, or (more likely in my mind) my question was flagged as the type of thing that &amp;quot;non-spenders&amp;quot; tend to say, triggering the bail-out. Either way, I didn&amp;#39;t have to waste my time listening to the rest of their ad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK products with down insulation (coats, jackets, vests, pillows, comforters, etc) may use feathers from live-plucked duck and geese.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK:

 * You may be considering purchasing down-insulated products during the holiday
   season
 * You may not know that the geese and duck feathers may be plucked while they
   are still alive, often several times over the course of their life.
 * Even if you aren't vegan, you may not want to…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r489d2/ysk_products_with_down_insulation_coats_jackets/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r489d2/ysk_products_with_down_insulation_coats_jackets/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 18:52:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You may be considering purchasing down-insulated products during the holiday season&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You may not know that the geese and duck feathers may be plucked while they are still alive, often several times over the course of their life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Even if you aren&amp;#39;t vegan, you may not want to support this painful and inhumane practice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A single down coat can require feathers from 10-20 geese or ducks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There are alternatives or more ethical sources of down you can consider purchasing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alternatives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many companies offer alternatives (and many have even banned using down altogether) There are several ways to search for down-alternative products. Usually they will have keywords such as:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Synthetic Insulation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;Down-Alternative&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;Featherless&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recycled Insulation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cotton or Rayon Filled&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ethically-Sourced Down Options&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are currently 2 certification standards for ethical down retrieval that work to combat this issue, RDS and GTDS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RDS -&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://certifications.controlunion.com/en/certification-programs/certification-programs/rds-responsible-down-standard&quot;&gt;Responsible Down Standard&lt;/a&gt; is utilized by most ethically-aware companies, however even this standard has many flaws.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Farm inspections are announced in advance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;RDS allows for parallel farm operation (RDS and non-RDS down produced on the same farm)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;RDS does not consider the parent farm (where the geese are hatched and raised)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GTDS -&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://d2evkimvhatqav.cloudfront.net/documents/su_traceble_down_infopaper.pdf&quot;&gt;Global Traceable Down Standard&lt;/a&gt; is only utilized by Patagonia in partnership with the NSF, and is a much stricter certification.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: BlueLab is closing down and all their VSTs are now free]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Finding high quality VSTs can be a pain for producers, especially ones
that don’t break the bank.

BlueLab is shutting down and all their VSTs are free until the site closes down.
This is a great opportunity for producers to jump in and get some high quality
VSTs for no charge at all.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3w9st/ysk_bluelab_is_closing_down_and_all_their_vsts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3w9st/ysk_bluelab_is_closing_down_and_all_their_vsts/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 11:42:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Finding high quality VSTs can be a pain for producers, especially ones that don’t break the bank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BlueLab is shutting down and all their VSTs are free until the site closes down. This is a great opportunity for producers to jump in and get some high quality VSTs for no charge at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that on Android, if you put a file called .nomedia in your music folder, it will stop showing you album cover art in your gallery]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: For years you have been annoyed at all the album art in your phone
gallery. But no more! Just paste a blank file called .nomedia in all the folders
in your phone you don't want to show pics of in gallery, and your gallery will
finally make sense! Works for getting rid of other app pollution…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3kyx5/ysk_that_on_android_if_you_put_a_file_called/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3kyx5/ysk_that_on_android_if_you_put_a_file_called/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 03:54:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: For years you have been annoyed at all the album art in your phone gallery. But no more! Just paste a blank file called .nomedia in all the folders in your phone you don&amp;#39;t want to show pics of in gallery, and your gallery will finally make sense! Works for getting rid of other app pollution too. My life is improved. Yours can be too!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that your rider rating is delayed]]></title><description><![CDATA[I've seen several people on here talk about changing their rating of drivers
because they were given one star, so they "one star back".

YSK: Uber delays rider (and driver) ratings updates to "protect anonymity" and
won't say how long the delay is.

But they do a shit job of communicating that to…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3epke/ysk_that_your_rider_rating_is_delayed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3epke/ysk_that_your_rider_rating_is_delayed/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 23:32:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve seen several people on here talk about changing their rating of drivers because they were given one star, so they &amp;quot;one star back&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;YSK: Uber delays rider (and driver) ratings updates to &amp;quot;protect anonymity&amp;quot; and won&amp;#39;t say how long the delay is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But they do a shit job of communicating that to riders. So when you see your rating go down and then downrate your most recent ride because of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: you&amp;#39;re actually retaliating against the wrong person, when it was really the driver maybe 10 or so trips ago that gave you a bad rating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please don&amp;#39;t do this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: When looking for a college, if you are intelligent and have a *very* good high school resume you can use the offer given to you at one college to negotiate a better deal at another preferred college. You can negotiate a better deal for yourself in many circumstances.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: You could save thousands upon thousands of dollars by negotiating with
potential colleges. Of course, this is all predicated on how valuable you are to
them but kids with very good marks should be aware that they have negotiating
power.

If your preferred school does not offer what you want…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3czx2/ysk_when_looking_for_a_college_if_you_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3czx2/ysk_when_looking_for_a_college_if_you_are/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 16:54:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: You could save thousands upon thousands of dollars by negotiating with potential colleges. Of course, this is all predicated on how valuable you are to them but kids with very good marks should be aware that they have negotiating power. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your preferred school does not offer what you want use all of your previous offers as leverage and try to negotiate a better deal for yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK That Tipped Wages still have to be compensated up to Minimum Wage.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: If you work in a career where you earn tips as a wage and are getting
short of your full minimum wage pay then your federally entitled to it. Many
people get absued in the system, and if you are fired for asking for that pay
you can report it.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3bvmh/ysk_that_tipped_wages_still_have_to_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3bvmh/ysk_that_tipped_wages_still_have_to_be/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 15:51:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If you work in a career where you earn tips as a wage and are getting short of your full minimum wage pay then your federally entitled to it. Many people get absued in the system, and if you are fired for asking for that pay you can report it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK about the "Mother's Kiss," a technique for removing an object from a child's nostril by occluding the unaffected nostril and blowing into the child's mouth.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: This technique is a useful and safe first-line option for the removal
of foreign bodies from the nasal cavities of children, and it can save you a
trip to the ER/urgent care.

Source [https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3503923/]]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r32v27/ysk_about_the_mothers_kiss_a_technique_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r32v27/ysk_about_the_mothers_kiss_a_technique_for/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 15:51:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This technique is a useful and safe first-line option for the removal of foreign bodies from the nasal cavities of children, and it can save you a trip to the ER/urgent care. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3503923/&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>