<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 06:37:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK if you're a smoker, non-smokers don't want to be trapped in your house or car with you while you are smoking, but we're too polite to tell you that to your face]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: so many times I've been in friends houses or cars with them while
they're smoking cigarettes and it's honestly the worst thing, it makes me not
want to hang out with those people or go to their houses at all. That kind of
thing could be affecting your friendships and you may not even know…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mhgxvi/ysk_if_youre_a_smoker_nonsmokers_dont_want_to_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mhgxvi/ysk_if_youre_a_smoker_nonsmokers_dont_want_to_be/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 23:48:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: so many times I&amp;#39;ve been in friends houses or cars with them while they&amp;#39;re smoking cigarettes and it&amp;#39;s honestly the worst thing, it makes me not want to hang out with those people or go to their houses at all. That kind of thing could be affecting your friendships and you may not even know it. Most people don&amp;#39;t want to tell you that your smoking is grossing them out because they don&amp;#39;t want to offend you or cause a fuss. I&amp;#39;d rather come outside and stand with you outside while you&amp;#39;re smoking than have you light one up indoors with me in the room. Sure it&amp;#39;s your house, but don&amp;#39;t be surprised if no one wants to come over if you smoke indoors around other people, it should be common courtesy not to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK Richard Jewell was arguably a hero who was vilified by a media and government who needed a villain]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: it is important to remember that we can not rush to judgement with
people and must be smart and objective. Richard Jewell was a hero whose life was
ultimately ruined by a combination of irresponsible reporting and government
officials needing a "quick win" to get people comfortable with…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mh65fn/ysk_richard_jewell_was_arguably_a_hero_who_was/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mh65fn/ysk_richard_jewell_was_arguably_a_hero_who_was/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 21:27:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: it is important to remember that we can not rush to judgement with people and must be smart and objective. Richard Jewell was a hero whose life was ultimately ruined by a combination of irresponsible reporting and government officials needing a &amp;quot;quick win&amp;quot; to get people comfortable with returning to the 1996 Olympics. Due to the FBI being so focused on Richard Jewell the real culprit was able to continue to wreak havoc in Atlanta &amp;amp; Birmingham.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Richard tragically died at a young age, but if it was not for him having an unbelievable amount of courage to keep fighting and not give up that his name was ultimately cleared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to learn more the film by Clint Eastwood &amp;quot;Richard Jewell&amp;quot; and the Netflix series &amp;quot;Manhunt: Deadly Games&amp;quot; are great sources. The article that inspired the Clint Eastwood movie &amp;quot;American Nightmare: The Ballad of Richard Jewell&amp;quot; &lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.vanityfair.com/article/share/1fd2d7ae-10d8-474b-9bf1-d1558af697be&quot;&gt;https://archive.vanityfair.com/article/share/1fd2d7ae-10d8-474b-9bf1-d1558af697be&lt;/a&gt; is a fantastic read.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also the 60 Minutes interview with Mike Wallace was the first time America saw that Richard Jewell really was innocent, and provided an objective look at the evidence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qbx50Gsi9g0&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qbx50Gsi9g0&lt;/a&gt; (original 1996 interview)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hJiottNlPIY&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hJiottNlPIY&lt;/a&gt; (5 year follow up)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We should be teaching children that he was a hero who saved countless lives that night. He may not have been perfect, but none of us are. He was just an every day man who did the right thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: How to get scientific research papers for free.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: The $35 that scientific journals charge you to read a paper goes 100%
to the publisher, 0% to the authors.

If you just email the authors to ask for their papers, they are allowed to send
them to you for free and will be genuinely delighted to do so.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mh093h/ysk_how_to_get_scientific_research_papers_for_free/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mh093h/ysk_how_to_get_scientific_research_papers_for_free/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 13:03:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  The $35 that scientific journals charge you to read a paper goes 100% to the publisher, 0% to the authors. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you just email the authors to ask for their papers, they are allowed to send them to you for free and will be genuinely delighted to do so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that in parenting, HOW you talk to your child matters - it changes their brain. Talking TO or AT your child, even if you are exposing them to many words, is less important than having engaging conversations WITH your child, ideally where your child takes the lead.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Parents should know this because there is a widespread misunderstanding
about the connection between parental education/income level and child brain and
language development. Namely, that higher income parents teach their kids more
words, and this then leads to better brain language…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mgwzwi/ysk_that_in_parenting_how_you_talk_to_your_child/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mgwzwi/ysk_that_in_parenting_how_you_talk_to_your_child/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 06:32:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Parents should know this because there is a widespread misunderstanding about the connection between parental education/income level and child brain and language development. Namely, that higher income parents teach their kids &lt;em&gt;more words,&lt;/em&gt; and this then leads to better brain language development. Knowing about this misconception is important for many reasons, perhaps the most important being that the science-backed solution to helping grow your child’s brain development in this area is actually very simple and doable for &lt;em&gt;any parent, regardless of socioeconomic or educational background.&lt;/em&gt; It has nothing to do with dumping fancy words at your kids.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d safely assume that most parents know that talking - and teaching verbal communication - to their children from a young age is vital. But, there is a widespread misconception that parental income or education correlates to a child’s ability to develop strongly in this area. Notably, since research has shown that, on average, children from higher-income families hear millions &lt;em&gt;more words&lt;/em&gt; during their first three years of life, somehow that means that such children are set up for better brain development than children from lower-income families. &lt;strong&gt;This actually isn’t true.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1995, a research study came out that found that children from higher-income families hear about &lt;strong&gt;30 million more words&lt;/strong&gt; during their first three years of life than children from lower-income families.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So was coined the phenomenon of the “&lt;strong&gt;30-million-word-gap&lt;/strong&gt;”, at the time correlated with significant gaps in tests of vocabulary, language development, and reading comp skills of kids from lower vs higher income families as they matured. People ran with this idea. Claiming essentially that kids from higher income families, who on average heard and were taught so many more words, were somehow set up as they got older to have a more &amp;quot;highly developed&amp;quot; brain in terms of language capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More recent science has debunked this correlation, pointing to a very different reality. MIT cognitive scientists have now discovered that &lt;em&gt;it is not the number of words&lt;/em&gt; a parent says &lt;strong&gt;to&lt;/strong&gt; their child that can change their brain (for the better), but instead &lt;em&gt;the nature of open-ended conversation&lt;/em&gt; a parent encourages &lt;strong&gt;with&lt;/strong&gt; their child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Creating lots of opportunity for this kind of open-ended, back-and-forth conversation is actually more critical to brain and language development than the findings of the &amp;quot;word gap&amp;quot;.&lt;/strong&gt; This research from MIT applied to children &lt;em&gt;regardless of parental income&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;or education.&lt;/em&gt; The finding suggests that &lt;em&gt;any&lt;/em&gt; parent can have considerable influence over their child&amp;#39;s language and brain development by simply engaging them in daily conversation where the child has space to drive the conversation and create conversation turns as they please. Encouraging turn-taking conversation, as opposed to one-sided conversation, can be implemented by any parent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key finding from the aforementioned research is that parents should understand they should not just &lt;em&gt;talk to&lt;/em&gt; their child, but instead should consistently &lt;em&gt;talk with&lt;/em&gt; their child. Being interactive is what matters. Creating time and space for casual, story-oriented familial conversation, where there is less talking at or to your child by the parent and more talking with and listening to your child, changes children’s brains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe using excessive flashcards and talking at our children with many words, probably just frustrating or confusing them, should be a thing of the past. Maybe the solution is really as simple as focusing on fun conversation that genuinely encourages children to participate. Not just listen and memorize.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MIT study: &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/0956797617742725&quot;&gt;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/0956797617742725&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1995 Word Gap study: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aft.org/sites/default/files/periodicals/TheEarlyCatastrophe.pdf&quot;&gt;https://www.aft.org/sites/default/files/periodicals/TheEarlyCatastrophe.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK "Burger Den" and "Melt Down" on food delivery apps are "Dennys" in disguise.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK - "Dennys" is re-listing portions of thier menu virtually as "Burger
Den" for burgers and "Melt Down" for sandwiches to trick you into ordering
"Dennys" in case you thought you were trying something new or supporting a new
business.

Can confirm the quality is still "Dennys" quality.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mgtuci/ysk_burger_den_and_melt_down_on_food_delivery/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mgtuci/ysk_burger_den_and_melt_down_on_food_delivery/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 03:12:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK - &amp;quot;Dennys&amp;quot; is re-listing portions of thier menu virtually as &amp;quot;Burger Den&amp;quot; for burgers and &amp;quot;Melt Down&amp;quot; for sandwiches to trick you into ordering &amp;quot;Dennys&amp;quot; in case you thought you were trying something new or supporting a new business. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can confirm the quality is still &amp;quot;Dennys&amp;quot; quality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK if you’re a college student, make sure you set up your student email address to forward to your personal email before you graduate/leave.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: because in many cases you won’t have access to that school email
anymore or will just forget to check it but you’ll often receive emails to it
from the school long after you’ve left.

And sometimes these emails are VERY important (example: “you actually owe us
more tuition and if you don’t…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mgikth/ysk_if_youre_a_college_student_make_sure_you_set/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mgikth/ysk_if_youre_a_college_student_make_sure_you_set/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 19:58:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: because in many cases you won’t have access to that school email anymore or will just forget to check it but you’ll often receive emails to it from the school long after you’ve left. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And sometimes these emails are VERY important (example: “you actually owe us more tuition and if you don’t pay we’re sending it to collections”) and the school can hide behind “we informed you” because they sent it to your student email account. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully forwarding your email will just let you find out about alumni events or other benign emails that you would have missed otherwise, but if there is something important / dubious like above example, you won’t miss it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Some people are covertly abusive, manipulative and controlling]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: learning to recognise the techniques and patterns of behaviour will
help you protect yourself and better support friends or family suffering
psychological or emotional abuse. A significant amount of harm has already been
done if you have to learn this the hard way.

Abusive power and…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mg2jgk/ysk_some_people_are_covertly_abusive_manipulative/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mg2jgk/ysk_some_people_are_covertly_abusive_manipulative/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 01:12:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: learning to recognise the techniques and patterns of behaviour will help you protect yourself and better support friends or family suffering psychological or emotional abuse. A significant amount of harm has already been done if you have to learn this the hard way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Abusive_power_and_control&quot;&gt;Abusive power and control&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.verywellmind.com/identify-and-cope-with-emotional-abuse-4156673&quot;&gt;What is emotional abuse?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK There is a website called haveibeenpwned which monitors all databreaches and give you a chance to find out if your data has been lost or stolen.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK, lots of people don't know what companies have leaked or lost your
personal data, including email-address and passwords. This way you can check if
your data has been leaked so you can change passwords if you use those passwords
on other sites in combination with that email-address. It won't…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mfk5da/ysk_there_is_a_website_called_haveibeenpwned/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mfk5da/ysk_there_is_a_website_called_haveibeenpwned/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 13:22:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK, lots of people don&amp;#39;t know what companies have leaked or lost your personal data, including email-address and passwords. This way you can check if your data has been leaked so you can change passwords if you use those passwords on other sites in combination with that email-address. It won&amp;#39;t stop databreaches, but at least you know that it happened to your data. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://haveibeenpwned.com/&quot;&gt;https://haveibeenpwned.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: When a person cuts out someone from their life, it is usually the LAST effort that they have made. Normally they do everything else before cutting them out]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Everyone comes from a different background.

Sometimes if you come from a good family, you can't understand why someone might
cut out a relative. "You'll regret it when they're gone!" Is a pretty common
sentence, for people who don't understand.

It could stem from different variety of…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mfguip/ysk_when_a_person_cuts_out_someone_from_their/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mfguip/ysk_when_a_person_cuts_out_someone_from_their/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 07:51:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Everyone comes from a different background. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes if you come from a good family, you can&amp;#39;t understand why someone might cut out a relative. &amp;quot;You&amp;#39;ll regret it when they&amp;#39;re gone!&amp;quot; Is a pretty common sentence, for people who don&amp;#39;t understand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It could stem from different variety of abuse, narcissism, parentification, not respecting boundaries, etc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just respect the person and don&amp;#39;t try to guilt them into contacting their relative, if they have cut them out. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/narcissistic-personality-disorder/symptoms-causes/syc-20366662&quot;&gt;https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/narcissistic-personality-disorder/symptoms-causes/syc-20366662&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.verywellmind.com/how-to-recognize-a-narcissist-4164528&quot;&gt;https://www.verywellmind.com/how-to-recognize-a-narcissist-4164528&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://wingsprogram.com/what-is-domestic-violence-blog/&quot;&gt;https://wingsprogram.com/what-is-domestic-violence-blog/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/living-emotional-intensity/201912/did-you-have-grow-too-soon&quot;&gt;https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/living-emotional-intensity/201912/did-you-have-grow-too-soon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.newportacademy.com/resources/mental-health/parentification/&quot;&gt;https://www.newportacademy.com/resources/mental-health/parentification/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://psychcentral.com/blog/how-to-respect-other-peoples-boundaries&quot;&gt;https://psychcentral.com/blog/how-to-respect-other-peoples-boundaries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://livewellwithsharonmartin.com/set-boundaries-toxic-people/&quot;&gt;https://livewellwithsharonmartin.com/set-boundaries-toxic-people/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Your mom was right. Staring at a screen all day is really unhealthy]]></title><description><![CDATA[Yes, those sweet times sitting in front of our TV or PC. Ignoring our parent's
calls to go outside. 20 years later I work on the medical research team for
pupillary.org [https://pupillary.org/] and read a lot of papers on this
topicbehavioral. And, oh, boy, were they right. Here're just a few small…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/meyjbn/ysk_your_mom_was_right_staring_at_a_screen_all/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/meyjbn/ysk_your_mom_was_right_staring_at_a_screen_all/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:25:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes, those sweet times sitting in front of our TV or PC. Ignoring our parent&amp;#39;s calls to go outside. 20 years later I work on the medical research team for &lt;a href=&quot;https://pupillary.org/&quot;&gt;pupillary.org&lt;/a&gt; and read a lot of papers on this topicbehavioral. And, oh, boy,  were they right. Here&amp;#39;re just a few small quotes out of a lot of studies:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot; One-quarter of the students studied experienced physical complaints, and one-fifth had behavioural problems associated with the use of electronic devices“ (S L Ting et al, 2020)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot; The magnitude of arteriolar narrowing associated with each hour daily of  TV viewing is similar to that associated with a 10-mm Hg increase in  systolic blood pressure in children.&amp;quot; ( Bamini Gopinath et al 2011 )&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;longer screen time (≥2 h/day) was associated with lower levels of satisfaction with life and optimism, and higher levels of anxiety and depressive symptoms; shorter screen time (&amp;lt;2 h/day) was associated with favorable mental health and wellbeing&amp;quot; (Eva Oberle et al, 2020)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: A symptom of depression is pushing people away.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: To help stop a friend’s depression becoming even worse.

If you have a friend who may be depressed, it’s natural for them to ignore texts
and cancel plans. The golden rule is to never take it personally. Keep on
trying. It’s no time to lose friends. Getting angry or thinking ‘well fuck…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mf3vjt/ysk_a_symptom_of_depression_is_pushing_people_away/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mf3vjt/ysk_a_symptom_of_depression_is_pushing_people_away/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 18:52:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: To help stop a friend’s depression becoming even worse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a friend who may be depressed, it’s natural for them to ignore texts and cancel plans. The golden rule is to never take it personally. Keep on trying. It’s no time to lose friends. Getting angry or thinking ‘well fuck them if they’re not making an effort’, is only helping the depression win. They’re not pushing you away, their depression is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: joking about suicide is a sign of a crisis point in a medical condition]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: it's rarely a joke this is a sign that someone is reaching out for
help, they don't necessarily want to die but may not see a way out and are
looking for help but with all the stigma associated with mental illness it can
be hard to come out and say exactly what's going on.

It's important…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mf001z/ysk_joking_about_suicide_is_a_sign_of_a_crisis/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mf001z/ysk_joking_about_suicide_is_a_sign_of_a_crisis/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 15:52:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: it&amp;#39;s rarely a joke this is a sign that someone is reaching out for help, they don&amp;#39;t necessarily want to die but may not see a way out and are looking for help but with all the stigma associated with mental illness it can be hard to come out and say exactly what&amp;#39;s going on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s important to remember that some who is considering suicide likely has a medical condition which affects their thinking processes so someone should not be dismissed or told to get over it (they would if they could) -- it would be equivalent to telling someone with a broken arm that there was nothing wrong with them. (Note how I phrase it as a medical condition instead of mental illness specifically to remove a sense of judgement)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What can you do? Ask them straight whether they are considering suicide and if they are find out if there are family or friends they would feel comfortable knowing and able to call if they feel suicidal. They may not feel comfortable reaching out to family or friends and that&amp;#39;s okay. Instead or as well as that there are divided prevention hotlines in most countries who will help.
Ultimately you want to speak calmly with them and see if they will agree to contact a trusted family member or friend or a suicide prevention number before enacting any plans to die by suicide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t worry, you won&amp;#39;t make someone consider suicide by asking them about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may not be comfortable having this conversation, suicide prevention websites and numbers can often advise on how to have this conversation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also if you notice someone on Reddit with these signs, use the report option and select other and select &amp;#39;someone is considering suicide&amp;#39;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other warning signs: giving things away, seeming hopelessness and despair, seeming flat in mood, drastic changes in weight and apparent signs of insomnia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Source: I am a mental health first aider, see also &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.beyondblue.org.au/the-facts/suicide-prevention/feeling-suicidal/suicidal-warning-signs&quot;&gt;https://www.beyondblue.org.au/the-facts/suicide-prevention/feeling-suicidal/suicidal-warning-signs&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.choc.org/articles/9-signs-your-child-may-be-considering-suicide/&quot;&gt;https://www.choc.org/articles/9-signs-your-child-may-be-considering-suicide/&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also YSK: helping other people through this kind of situation can be draining on ourselves as supports, be sure to be kind to yourself and take time to recharge, you too matter and are important&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay safe&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Friendship is a 50/50 relationship. We understand that depression and real-life problems are a thing, but if one person does all of the connecting and gets ghosted, please contact them.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: No one likes being ghosted. Though I can understand why you might.
Feeling guilty about not talking to them can eat at you, ironically enough,
making you not want to contact them. But you either need to end the friendship
peacefully or make more of an effort. Even if all you do is text and…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/meoks1/ysk_friendship_is_a_5050_relationship_we/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/meoks1/ysk_friendship_is_a_5050_relationship_we/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 05:04:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: No one likes being ghosted. Though I can understand why you might. Feeling guilty about not talking to them can eat at you, ironically enough, making you not want to contact them. But you either need to end the friendship peacefully or make more of an effort. Even if all you do is text and say: &amp;quot;Sorry, I haven&amp;#39;t been talking to you lately, I just haven&amp;#39;t felt myself&amp;quot; Or something similar. Otherwise, the person that is always the one to try and get in contact with you, might feel like they aren&amp;#39;t appreciated/feeling used, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK Storing your potatoes next to your onions will make them go bad faster]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: I just recently learned that onions produce a gas that makes your
potatoes sprout eyes and go bad much faster. I had to get a new bag ever 2 weeks
before I moved them, now that they are located elsewhere I'm going over a month
and a half and they are still fine. Don't waste your potatoes,…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mejddq/ysk_storing_your_potatoes_next_to_your_onions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mejddq/ysk_storing_your_potatoes_next_to_your_onions/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 20:57:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I just recently learned that onions produce a gas that makes your potatoes sprout eyes and go bad much faster.  I had to get a new bag ever 2 weeks before I moved them, now that they are located elsewhere I&amp;#39;m going over a month and a half and they are still fine.  Don&amp;#39;t waste your potatoes, locate them away from your onions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that the FTC has a webpage to report fraud and scamming solicitations received via email, phone, and text.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: it assists them in tracking scam and fraud trends, aids in better
preparing the public to protect themselves against fraudulent solicitations, and
in some cases helps victims get lost money back.

If you’re a victim of fraud and lost money, you should definitely report any
information you…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/meg435/ysk_that_the_ftc_has_a_webpage_to_report_fraud/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/meg435/ysk_that_the_ftc_has_a_webpage_to_report_fraud/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 18:46:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: it assists them in tracking scam and fraud trends, aids in better preparing the public to protect themselves against fraudulent solicitations, and in some cases helps victims get lost money back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re a victim of fraud and lost money, you should definitely report any information you have and the amount of money lost. This increase the chance you can recover what is lost (though it isn’t guaranteed).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve all received fake emails and phone calls and text messages. Some of us know how to recognize a scam, or are knowledgeable enough to know how these guys try to get your information. Unfortunately, a lot of people still lose hundreds, if not thousands, of dollars to scamming activities. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you receive communication from a scammer, you can report them and it will be sent to several law enforcement agencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://reportfraud.ftc.gov/#/&quot;&gt;FTC Report Fraud/Scam&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: didn’t want to sound like I was calling to arms!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that your music taste may change fundamentally with changes in your life situation]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Often times, people listen to a specific type of music to compensate
certain feelings. Me for example liked to listen to latin beats and sea shantys
during months when I suffered from depression because those kinds of music were
very uplifting and helped me forget the grueling everyday…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mednvq/ysk_that_your_music_taste_may_change/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mednvq/ysk_that_your_music_taste_may_change/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 18:09:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Often times, people listen to a specific type of music to compensate certain feelings. Me for example liked to listen to latin beats and sea shantys during months when I suffered from depression because those kinds of music were very uplifting and helped me forget the grueling everyday life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After getting rid the causes of my depression and helping myself improve, I lost all interest in sea shantys and latin music. I still sometimes listen to the music from back them, but usually only when I feel sad and need distraction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Eliminating the words "so" and "very" as adjective modifiers will expand and improve your vocabulary and writing.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Words like "so" and "very" are intensifiers and don't carry any real
meaning or further description.

Something "very hot" could be anything from a hot day to the center of the
Earth, so be specific to say what you mean! Instead of "very hot", try
"boiling", "searing", "baking", or…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mdxlzh/ysk_eliminating_the_words_so_and_very_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mdxlzh/ysk_eliminating_the_words_so_and_very_as/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 13:53:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Words like &amp;quot;so&amp;quot;  and &amp;quot;very&amp;quot; are intensifiers and don&amp;#39;t carry any real meaning or further description.    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Something &amp;quot;very hot&amp;quot; could be anything from a hot day to the center of the Earth, so be specific to say what you mean! Instead of &amp;quot;very hot&amp;quot;,  try &amp;quot;boiling&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;searing&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;baking&amp;quot;, or &amp;quot;molten&amp;quot;. Each ones evokes a very &lt;em&gt;specific&lt;/em&gt; type of heat, making your  making your writing more concise, erudite and powerful.    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A character shouldn&amp;#39;t be &amp;quot;very happy&amp;quot;. They should be ecstatic! &amp;quot;Very sad&amp;quot;? Nope! Try &amp;quot;depressed&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;despondent&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;grief-stricken&amp;quot; instead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that you’re worthy of love, and who you are right now is more than enough]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: because it is easy to forget this, no external validation will
compensate for a lack of self-love, and no matter what mistakes you think you’ve
made you are beautiful and wonderful and I love you]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/md6g9a/ysk_that_youre_worthy_of_love_and_who_you_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/md6g9a/ysk_that_youre_worthy_of_love_and_who_you_are/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 13:40:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: because it is easy to forget this, no external validation will compensate for a lack of self-love, and no matter what mistakes you think you’ve made you are beautiful and wonderful and I love you&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK about doesthedogdie.com - You can look up books, movies, etc and it will tell you if there are any unpleasant scenes without spoiling the plot.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Some scenes can be distressing, especially for people with PTSD or who
have suffered a loss. Googling a work of fiction is a good way to have it
spoiled. This site has a list of trigger warnings for works of fiction and won't
spoil anything.

https://www.doesthedogdie.com

The site tracks…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mdx4az/ysk_about_doesthedogdiecom_you_can_look_up_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mdx4az/ysk_about_doesthedogdiecom_you_can_look_up_books/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 21:54:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Some scenes can be distressing, especially for people with PTSD or who have suffered a loss. Googling a work of fiction is a good way to have it spoiled. This site has a list of trigger warnings for works of fiction and won&amp;#39;t spoil anything. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.doesthedogdie.com&quot;&gt;https://www.doesthedogdie.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The site tracks 70+ categories like slurs, car crashes, dogs dying, spiders and cancer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK just saying "there is a big surprize / shocking ending" regardless of telling the details or not is already a SPOILER. If you suggest someone a film/tv show/game/book etc. please DON'T DO THAT!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Because although you want to attract their attention by increasing
their expectations, you'll ruin their experience. When some idiot tells me "you
will love it, you will not guess the big twist ending" I immediately find myself
thinking about the finale instead of focusing the moment and…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mdj0ml/ysk_just_saying_there_is_a_big_surprize_shocking/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mdj0ml/ysk_just_saying_there_is_a_big_surprize_shocking/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 11:25:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Because although you want to attract their attention by increasing their expectations, you&amp;#39;ll ruin their experience. When some idiot tells me &amp;quot;you will love it, you will not guess the big twist ending&amp;quot; I immediately find myself thinking about the finale instead of focusing the moment and enjoying it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK it's okay not to like any kind of music. 3-5% of the population can't experience emotion from it.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: many people with this condition feel permanently left out because they
can't relate to having a favorite song or a playlist for a particular mood. I
think it's important for these people to know that it's okay.

The condition is called specific musical anhedonia. it affects anywhere from…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mcrnc0/ysk_its_okay_not_to_like_any_kind_of_music_35_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mcrnc0/ysk_its_okay_not_to_like_any_kind_of_music_35_of/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 07:31:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: many people with this condition feel permanently left out because they can&amp;#39;t relate to having a favorite song or a playlist for a particular mood. I think it&amp;#39;s important for these people to know that it&amp;#39;s okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The condition is called specific musical anhedonia. it affects anywhere from 3 to 5% of people, about as common as color blindness, yet hardly anyone has ever heard of this condition in the vast majority of people who have it don&amp;#39;t know that they do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s a neurological syndrome that can occur either through genetics or as a side effect from brain injury. Through some means or another, the part of the brain associated with music comprehension is not properly connected to the part of the brain associated with reward and pleasure. Most often this occurs in the form of an issue with someone&amp;#39;s dopaminergic system, often defective D2 and D3 receptors or interrupted dopamine pathways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The result is a person who doesn&amp;#39;t have any emotional response to music. As you can imagine, it&amp;#39;s sometimes very difficult for this kind of person to fit in with the rest of society, especially considering that despite every culture&amp;#39;s differing religions, laws, traditions and languages, all cultures share music, and this is something that these people just can&amp;#39;t relate to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I always felt left out and as though I were missing something as a kid, before I knew what I had and came to terms with it. Loud noises in the background of someone throwing their voice around while they repetitively recite a crappy poem is weird anyways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can read more here:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Musical_anhedonia&quot;&gt;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Musical_anhedonia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pnas.org/content/113/46/E7337&quot;&gt;https://www.pnas.org/content/113/46/E7337&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Starting 4/24, 988 is the US national Suicide Prevention hotline number]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: the suicide hotline is now easier to remember (similar to 911), which
means it will be easier for people to access when they need it.

How I know. Literally got this message 5 minutes ago:

> T-Mobile: The FCC has adopted 988 as a 3-digit number to be used nationwide to
> reach the National…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/md2q9i/ysk_starting_424_988_is_the_us_national_suicide/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/md2q9i/ysk_starting_424_988_is_the_us_national_suicide/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 21:25:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: the suicide hotline is now easier to remember (similar to 911), which means it will be easier for people to access when they need it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How I know. Literally got this message 5 minutes ago:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;T-Mobile: The FCC has adopted 988 as a 3-digit number to be used nationwide to reach the National Suicide Prevention &amp;amp; Mental Health Crisis Lifeline. Eff 4/24/21 impacted area codes will permit 10-digit dialing. See &lt;a href=&quot;https://t-mo.co/T988&quot;&gt;https://t-mo.co/T988&lt;/a&gt; for more info.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK your cars side mirrors are probably not set correctly!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: It can save you from an accident!!

Your cars side mirrors are not for seeing behind you, but to cover your blind
spots! If you can see the driver behind you at a red light, they aren't set
properly.

To set them correctly get into the car while parked. Look in the rear view
mirror while…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/md21p2/ysk_your_cars_side_mirrors_are_probably_not_set/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/md21p2/ysk_your_cars_side_mirrors_are_probably_not_set/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 19:58:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It can save you from an accident!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your cars side mirrors are not for seeing behind you, but to cover your blind spots! If you can see the driver behind you at a red light, they aren&amp;#39;t set properly. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To set them correctly get into the car while parked. Look in the rear view mirror while sitting as though you are driving. Look for an object just at the left side of your rear view mirror. Now adjust the left side mirror to have that object just in view on the right side of the side mirror. Now look back at the rear view and find an object on the right side. Adjust your right side mirror so the object is just in view to the left edge of the mirror. This gives you the widest field of view with no gaps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I work in a garage and see this on almost every single customer car.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that if you're watching a YouTube video with headphones and the audio is only coming through one ear, you should enable mono sound.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Note: I should mention that this won't work if one of your headphone speakers
are simply just broken. The reason this happens is not a hardware issue but an
issue with how the YouTuber/content creator edited the audio files, making the
sound completely pan to either the right or left side.

Why YSK:…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/md1sz7/ysk_that_if_youre_watching_a_youtube_video_with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/md1sz7/ysk_that_if_youre_watching_a_youtube_video_with/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 18:59:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Note: I should mention that this won&amp;#39;t work if one of your headphone speakers are simply just broken. The reason this happens is not a hardware issue but an issue with how the YouTuber/content  creator edited the audio files, making the sound completely pan to either the right or left side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Mono sound means the same audio will play through both speakers rather than anything being panned to the left or right (For example majority of all music does this to give the music a more dynamic sound)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Windows literally just search &amp;quot;Mono&amp;quot; after hitting the Windows key and its the first option that comes up. With Mac go to to System Preferences &amp;gt; Accessibility &amp;gt; Audio &amp;gt;  Tick the checkbox for Play stereo &lt;strong&gt;audio&lt;/strong&gt; as &lt;strong&gt;mono&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And  after you&amp;#39;re done watching the video just remember to disable the setting and you&amp;#39;re good to go!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can even do this on mobile, if you&amp;#39;re on IOS go to Settings &amp;gt; Accessibility &amp;gt; Audio/Visual &amp;gt; Mono audio &amp;gt; toggle the switch on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#39;re on Android, its Settings &amp;gt; Accessibility &amp;gt; Hearing Enhancements &amp;gt; Toggle Mono Audio .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope this tip helps anyone out there and if anyone has anything to add (how to enable on other OS etc.) please let me know!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: If you all of a sudden start receiving non-stop subscription signups to your email, you may be a victim of credit card fraud. Computers]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK:

This happened to me this morning (and is still occurring right now). I received
an alert this morning from Chase advising me of a purchase for $2400 for two
laptops from Sams Club for pickup locally within 15 miles of my home.
Immediately afterwards I started receiving hundreds of…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mc71jy/ysk_if_you_all_of_a_sudden_start_receiving/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mc71jy/ysk_if_you_all_of_a_sudden_start_receiving/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 14:25:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This happened to me this morning (and is still occurring right now). I received an alert this morning from Chase advising me of a purchase for $2400 for two laptops from Sams Club for pickup locally within 15 miles of my home. Immediately afterwards I started receiving hundreds of subscription emails to the account associated with it that have been flooding my email box for the last hour. Not all criminals are dumb, they are relying on people not understanding how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They start by making the purchase but as soon as it is confirmed, they begin to flood the email account with subscription sign ups in hopes that you either&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A) Click select all and delete, subsequently deleting the purchase email&lt;br/&gt;
B) Manually go through and click unsubscribe from each&lt;br/&gt;
C) Report spam on everything&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the time I were to do any, they could send their runner to pick it up with the order number and be on their way, leaving me to have to fight the charge for items that were technically picked up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: most key fobs for vehicles that have "keyless" start have a physical key inside of them]]></title><description><![CDATA[WHY YSK: I'm a tow truck op / roadside assistance tech. A job today reminded me
of a not so known detail that almost every keyless start vehicle fob has a
physical key on the inside. How you access them is different for every
make/model vehicle. So if your battery dies on your vehicle and it's…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mcn3e4/ysk_most_key_fobs_for_vehicles_that_have_keyless/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mcn3e4/ysk_most_key_fobs_for_vehicles_that_have_keyless/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 07:00:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK: I&amp;#39;m a tow truck op / roadside assistance tech. A job today reminded me of a not so known detail that almost every keyless start vehicle fob has a physical key on the inside. How you access them is different for every make/model vehicle. So if your battery dies on your vehicle and it&amp;#39;s locked. Don&amp;#39;t fret. No need to call for a lockout. (Though you may need a jump start) just Google how to access your key and unlock it yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that if your Android is crashing today, uninstalling Webview or Chrome will fix it]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Android's latest update has been causing apps to crash constantly.

Simply go to Settings->apps, click the three dots and "Show system apps". Then,
open Android Webview or Chrome and uninstall updates. Hope this helps!

Source: https://www.androidauthority.com/android-apps-crashing-1210994/]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mb7y1w/ysk_that_if_your_android_is_crashing_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mb7y1w/ysk_that_if_your_android_is_crashing_today/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 03:54:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Android&amp;#39;s latest update has been causing apps to crash constantly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simply go to Settings-&amp;gt;apps, click the three dots and &amp;quot;Show system apps&amp;quot;. Then, open Android Webview or Chrome and uninstall updates. Hope this helps!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.androidauthority.com/android-apps-crashing-1210994/&quot;&gt;https://www.androidauthority.com/android-apps-crashing-1210994/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Wolfram Alpha exists. Wolfram Alpha is an advanced mathematics that shows step by step solutions.]]></title><description><![CDATA[WHY YSK:. I used it in college to double check my work in stats 1 and 2. I use
it to this day to relearn different formula solutions to help my kids with
homework. It helps refresh the long forgotten by going through how Wolfram Alpha
Calculator got the solution. It will even graph a line.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mcanaw/ysk_wolfram_alpha_exists_wolfram_alpha_is_an/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mcanaw/ysk_wolfram_alpha_exists_wolfram_alpha_is_an/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 23:32:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK:. I used it in college to double check my work in stats 1 and 2.  I use it to this day to relearn different formula solutions to help my kids with homework.  It helps refresh the long forgotten by going through how Wolfram Alpha Calculator got the solution. It will even graph a line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: a foam roller costs about the same (or less) as going out for lunch, lasts for ages, and can instantly make a huge difference in all kinds of muscle soreness, back pain, etc.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: lots of people complain about sore muscles, but many simply either do
nothing, or load up on OTC painkillers.

For a more thorough rundown of the benefits and why you should use one, here's a
list from a chiropractic / rehab center:
https://www.thorpechiropractic.com/new/index.php/blog/28…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mc9lfl/ysk_a_foam_roller_costs_about_the_same_or_less_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mc9lfl/ysk_a_foam_roller_costs_about_the_same_or_less_as/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:51:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: lots of people complain about sore muscles, but many simply either do nothing, or load up on OTC painkillers.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a more thorough rundown of the benefits and why you should use one, here&amp;#39;s a list from a chiropractic / rehab center: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thorpechiropractic.com/new/index.php/blog/28-11-benefits-of-foam-rolling&quot;&gt;https://www.thorpechiropractic.com/new/index.php/blog/28-11-benefits-of-foam-rolling&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the simple summary from my own use and anyone else I know (including a doctor and a chiropractor) is that they&amp;#39;re practically magic.  I&amp;#39;ve gone from &amp;quot;it hurts to move&amp;quot; to &amp;quot;wow, I&amp;#39;m feeling 80-90%&amp;quot; in just a few minutes more times than I&amp;#39;d like to mention.  Sometimes the actual process of using it can be uncomfortable, but more often than I feel like a new person almost immediately, and after a few sessions over a couple of days I&amp;#39;m back to normal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK you may have unclaimed property waiting for you.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Anything from gift cards to insurance claims to uncashed checks, the
state is obligated to hold on to it until it's claimed by the rightful owner.
Google unclaimed property in whatever state it's in and search your name. Some
find thousands, good luck!]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m9ibis/ysk_you_may_have_unclaimed_property_waiting_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m9ibis/ysk_you_may_have_unclaimed_property_waiting_for/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 14:31:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Anything from gift cards to insurance claims to uncashed checks, the state is obligated to hold on to it until it&amp;#39;s claimed by the rightful owner. Google unclaimed property in whatever state it&amp;#39;s in and search your name. Some find thousands, good luck!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: If your job doesn't offer overtime payment, don't work over-time]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: It should be obvious, but too many people work overtime without getting
the proper payment/paid to do it. You shouldn't be guilted into doing over-time
if you don't get paid for it.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mc0xo5/ysk_if_your_job_doesnt_offer_overtime_payment/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mc0xo5/ysk_if_your_job_doesnt_offer_overtime_payment/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 13:01:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It should be obvious, but too many people work overtime without getting the proper payment/paid to do it. You shouldn&amp;#39;t be guilted into doing over-time if you don&amp;#39;t get paid for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that if you have a hornet, wasp, or yellow jacket nest on your property, there are people who will take it away for free. They sell it to pharmaceutical companies that make wasp allergy medicine]]></title><description><![CDATA[I've posted this before, but it didn't get a lot of attention and I think it's
important. We're also coming into spring when those little assholes are more
active.

My husband is allergic to wasps and a couple years ago we found in our large
Rhododendron bush in our yard a bald-faced hornets nest.…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m7urt6/ysk_that_if_you_have_a_hornet_wasp_or_yellow/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m7urt6/ysk_that_if_you_have_a_hornet_wasp_or_yellow/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 02:43:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve posted this before, but it didn&amp;#39;t get a lot of attention and I think it&amp;#39;s important. We&amp;#39;re also coming into spring when those little assholes are more active.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My husband is allergic to wasps and a couple years ago we found in our large Rhododendron bush in our yard a bald-faced hornets nest. It was very well hidden, and was about the size of a volleyball. An in-law gave me the number and email address to a local man who will remove it for free (as long as it hasn’t been sprayed with anything yet). We contacted him immediately and within two days he came and removed the hive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He sells these wasps to companies that use the venom to create allergy shots for people like my husband.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Before you spray, pay hundreds of dollars to an exterminator to remove them, or risk getting stung or chased down the street by a particularly pissed off group of wasps, you can probably find a person in your area that will take it away for free. Your nuisance could turn into life saving medicine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 'Forever Chemicals' or chemicals that don't breakdown in your body or the environment, have been used since 1940, may be the biggest environmental disaster our generation (and the world) has to face, and are almost certainly poisoning you right now.]]></title><description><![CDATA[It's a slow motion disaster that may potentially wipe out humanity.

> The chemicals to blame for this crisis are found in everything from plastic
> containers and food wrapping, to waterproof clothes and fragrances in cleaning
> products, to soaps and shampoos, to electronics and carpeting. Some of…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mbpcl5/ysk_forever_chemicals_or_chemicals_that_dont/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mbpcl5/ysk_forever_chemicals_or_chemicals_that_dont/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 23:26:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s a slow motion disaster that may potentially wipe out humanity. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The chemicals to blame for this crisis are found in everything from plastic containers and food wrapping, to waterproof clothes and fragrances in cleaning products, to soaps and shampoos, to electronics and carpeting. Some of them, called PFAS, are known as “forever  chemicals”, because they don’t breakdown in the environment or the human body. They just accumulate and accumulate – doing more and more damage, minute by minute, hour by hour, day by day. Now, it seems, humanity is reaching a breaking point.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2021/mar/18/toxic-chemicals-health-humanity-erin-brokovich&quot;&gt;The Guardian&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Swiss researcher covered by that article hypothesizes these chemicals are responsible for worldwide declines in fertility. Shanna Swan, an environmental and reproductive epidemiologist at Icahn School of Medicine at Mount Sinai in New York authored &lt;a href=&quot;https://academic.oup.com/humupd/article/23/6/646/4035689&quot;&gt;a study&lt;/a&gt; that found that sperm counts in the west had plummeted by 59% between 1973 and 2011, and she blames forever chemicals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“In some parts of the world, the average twentysomething woman today is less fertile than her grandmother was at 35,” Swan writes. In addition to that, Swan finds that, on average, a man today will have &lt;em&gt;half&lt;/em&gt; of the sperm his grandfather had. “The current state of reproductive affairs can’t continue much longer without threatening human survival,” writes Swan, adding: “It’s a global existential crisis.” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Swan’s research finds that these chemicals aren’t just dramatically reducing semen quality, they are also &lt;a href=&quot;https://theintercept.com/2021/01/24/toxic-chemicals-human-sexuality-shanna-swan/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;shrinking penis size and volume of the testes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. This echos &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.documentcloud.org/documents/5316830-EDCs-Androgenic-Activity-Perfluoroakyl.html&quot;&gt;other research&lt;/a&gt; that found that PFAS harms sperm production, disrupts male hormones and is correlated to a &lt;strong&gt;“reduction of semen quality, testicular volume and penile length”.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another study &lt;a href=&quot;https://pediatrics.aappublications.org/content/121/2/e260&quot;&gt;found&lt;/a&gt; phthalate exposure “widespread” in infants, and that the chemicals were found in the urine of babies who came into contact with baby shampoos, lotions and powders. Still, aggressive regulation is lacking, not least  because of lobbying by chemical industry giants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.livescience.com/new-environmental-chemicals-pfas-pregnant-woment.html&quot;&gt;Further research&lt;/a&gt; has found that these chemicals pass from mother to child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Guardian article worded it best;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Swan’s research&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/feb/26/falling-sperm-counts-human-survival&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;suggests&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;sperm counts could reach zero by 2045.&lt;/strong&gt; Zero. Let that sink in. That would mean no babies. No reproduction. No more humans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This directly affects you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sources, Citations and additional reading:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2021/mar/18/toxic-chemicals-health-humanity-erin-brokovich&quot;&gt;Plummeting sperm counts, shrinking penises: toxic chemicals threaten humanity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/feb/26/falling-sperm-counts-human-survival&quot;&gt;Falling sperm counts &amp;#39;threaten human survival&amp;#39;, expert warns&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://academic.oup.com/humupd/article/23/6/646/4035689&quot;&gt;Temporal trends in sperm count: a systematic review and meta-regression analysis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.swnewsmedia.com/savage_pacer/news/mpca-forever-chemicals-leaked-into-groundwater-by-local-landfills/article_dcc450ba-79ad-5538-9d58-62299921d02b.html&quot;&gt;MPCA: &amp;#39;Forever chemicals&amp;#39; leaked into groundwater by local landfills&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ewg.org/release/epa-takes-first-step-address-industry-pollution-forever-chemicals&quot;&gt;EPA Takes First Step To Address Industrial Pollution From ‘Forever Chemicals’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/03/03/chemicals-water-denver-colorado-pfas/&quot;&gt;Elevated Levels Of ‘Forever Chemicals’ Found In Some Colorado Drinking Water Districts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mprnews.org/story/2021/03/18/forever-chemicals-found-in-groundwater-at-dozens-of-minn-landfills&quot;&gt;‘Forever chemicals’ found in groundwater at dozens of Minn. landfills&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://dcist.com/story/21/03/10/high-levels-toxic-pfas-forever-chemicals-northern-virginia-drinking-water/&quot;&gt;High Levels Of ‘Forever Chemicals’ Detected In Northern Virginia Drinking Water&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.axios.com/defense-department-afff-pfas-contamination-9e69920d-041e-4035-969a-14cfbb3e18bd.html&quot;&gt;The Pentagon&amp;#39;s multibillion-dollar &amp;quot;forever chemicals&amp;quot; problem&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ewg.org/research/nova-pfas-testing/&quot;&gt;Is Northern Virginia a D.C.-Area Hot Spot for ‘Forever Chemicals’ in Tap Water?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://scitechdaily.com/researchers-unearth-a-ticking-time-bomb-synthetic-chemicals-in-soils/&quot;&gt;Researchers Unearth a ‘Ticking Time Bomb’ – Synthetic Chemicals in Soils&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.livescience.com/new-environmental-chemicals-pfas-pregnant-woment.html&quot;&gt;More than 50 new environmental chemicals detected in people&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that if you know a kid struggling to learn to read they may have a Convergence Insufficiency. CI is treatable with vision therapy. The condition is often missed because testing for it is not included as part of a regular eye exam.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: CI is often misdiagnosed as ADD or Dyslexia.

https://www.optometrists.org/vision-therapy-for-children/convergence-insufficiency-2/]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m7d85c/ysk_that_if_you_know_a_kid_struggling_to_learn_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m7d85c/ysk_that_if_you_know_a_kid_struggling_to_learn_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 19:56:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: CI is often misdiagnosed as ADD or 
Dyslexia.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.optometrists.org/vision-therapy-for-children/convergence-insufficiency-2/&quot;&gt;https://www.optometrists.org/vision-therapy-for-children/convergence-insufficiency-2/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK there are many reasons a person's hands might shake and telling them to "just relax" is not helpful]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Hand tremors can be caused by many different things and almost none of
them are any of your business. Anxiety, a neurological disorder, drug/alcohol
withdrawals, and brain damage are a few possible causes. The only one that can
be improved by relaxing is anxiety. But calling attention to…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mbin3p/ysk_there_are_many_reasons_a_persons_hands_might/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mbin3p/ysk_there_are_many_reasons_a_persons_hands_might/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 19:56:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Hand tremors can be caused by many different things and almost none of them are any of your business. Anxiety, a neurological disorder, drug/alcohol withdrawals, and brain damage are a few possible causes. The only one that can be improved by relaxing is anxiety. But calling attention to someone&amp;#39;s anxiety will not help. It&amp;#39;s patronizing and is likely to cause more anxiety. You&amp;#39;re basically just announcing, &amp;quot;Everyone can see your hands shaking!&amp;quot; This is not an appropriate reaction to any medical symptom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Citation: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ninds.nih.gov/Disorders/Patient-Caregiver-Education/Fact-Sheets/Tremor-Fact-Sheet&quot;&gt;https://www.ninds.nih.gov/Disorders/Patient-Caregiver-Education/Fact-Sheets/Tremor-Fact-Sheet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Always get three estimates for any large construction project]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: People who come to your house and give you a free estimate are often
under pressure to win jobs that will make a big return. What most homeowners
don't realize is that many construction projects aren't profitable for the
company, and some will actually lose money.

The point of the free…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mb3jgr/ysk_always_get_three_estimates_for_any_large/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mb3jgr/ysk_always_get_three_estimates_for_any_large/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 12:43:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: People who come to your house and give you a free estimate are often under pressure to win jobs that will make a big return. What most homeowners don&amp;#39;t realize is that many construction projects aren&amp;#39;t profitable for the company, and some will actually lose money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The point of the free estimate is to size up your job, and to see if it will make money. If it seems like a bad bet, contractors will price the job higher, to account for the risk. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should see this as a polite way of refusing the job. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you get three estimates, you&amp;#39;ll notice if one is a lot higher. Don&amp;#39;t go with that one. The contractor is either inexperienced, doesn&amp;#39;t have the time, or doesn&amp;#39;t have the equipment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If all the estimates are roughly the same, congratulations. Your job is one that will be completed without issues. Pick the middle bid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If one bid is a lot lower than the rest, don&amp;#39;t go with that one. The contractor has likely missed a major line item and will be forced to bail on your project, or take a big loss. The quality of the work will likely not be as good as it needs to be. Please don&amp;#39;t see this as a way to get a good deal. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR: in most cases, if you are excellent to your contractor they will be excellent to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: I was a contractor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: You could easily estimate the charge of AA/AAA battery cells by dropping them vertically on a table from a height of around an inch. Fresh batteries will drop still, while discharged ones will bounce like a ball.]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is true for all disposable battery cells, alkaline, and salt-based. The
more depleted the battery, the higher it bounces. It doesn't applies to
rechargeable cells.

Why YSK: sometimes you have a mess in your stack of disposable batteries which
needs to be sorted out quickly, or you just need to…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/malse0/ysk_you_could_easily_estimate_the_charge_of_aaaaa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/malse0/ysk_you_could_easily_estimate_the_charge_of_aaaaa/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 04:56:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is true for all disposable battery cells, alkaline, and salt-based. The more depleted the battery, the higher it bounces. It doesn&amp;#39;t applies to rechargeable cells.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: sometimes you have a mess in your stack of disposable batteries which needs to be sorted out quickly, or you just need to check if the battery is still alive without having a multimeter at hand. This is the fast and easy way to do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK the Average Life Span is 78.54 (US)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK the average life span in the US is 78.54?

If your mother or father is current 60 plus reflect on the amount of time you
spend with them each month. I would bet most people rarely see their parents 1
time a month. Meaning most people will have less then 100 of these moments left
some less…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mauown/ysk_the_average_life_span_is_7854_us/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mauown/ysk_the_average_life_span_is_7854_us/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 01:34:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK the average life span in the US is 78.54?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your mother or father is current 60 plus reflect on the amount of time you spend with them each month. I would bet most people rarely see their parents 1 time a month. Meaning most people will have less then 100 of these moments left some less then 10. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don’t choose when they go; we do get choose how much of our own time we spend with them. Find it in yourself to make the time for them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Prepare your teenagers to be an adult better than your own parents prepared you]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: That way your child(ren) have a better idea of what is in store.

When they become teenagers, talk to them about being an adult. Bills/saving
money/different ways to get financial help, investing in money, etc.

Teenage years are the awkward years. Not quite a kid, but not quite an…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mb05az/ysk_prepare_your_teenagers_to_be_an_adult_better/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mb05az/ysk_prepare_your_teenagers_to_be_an_adult_better/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 01:34:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: That way your child(ren) have a better idea of what is in store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When they become teenagers, talk to them about being an adult. Bills/saving money/different ways to get financial help, investing in money, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Teenage years are the awkward years. Not quite a kid, but not quite an adult. That&amp;#39;s the perfect time to get them prepared for being an adult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make sure to start your kids young at chores as well so they know about responsibility. I knew way too many teenagers and even adults who never did chores because their parents did them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make sure boys and girls do the same kind of chores, so they know how to do them as an adult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://childdevelopmentinfo.com/chores/the-ultimate-list-of-age-appropriate-chores/&quot;&gt;https://childdevelopmentinfo.com/chores/the-ultimate-list-of-age-appropriate-chores/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cmc-pa.com/teens/preparing-teen-adulthood/&quot;&gt;https://www.cmc-pa.com/teens/preparing-teen-adulthood/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://washingtonparent.com/preparing-teens-for-adulthood/&quot;&gt;https://washingtonparent.com/preparing-teens-for-adulthood/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/resolution-not-conflict/201111/prepping-kids-so-theyre-ready-thrive-adults&quot;&gt;https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/resolution-not-conflict/201111/prepping-kids-so-theyre-ready-thrive-adults&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK rubbing your eyes a lot can actually make your vision worse]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: you should know so you can avoid any further damage to your eyes.

Chronically rubbing your eyes can have multiple effects on the health of the
eye. 2 consequences in particular can actually affect your vision long term.

 1. Continuous eye rubbing can lead to thinning of the corneal…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/maikv8/ysk_rubbing_your_eyes_a_lot_can_actually_make/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/maikv8/ysk_rubbing_your_eyes_a_lot_can_actually_make/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 23:26:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: you should know so you can avoid any further damage to your eyes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chronically rubbing your eyes can have multiple effects on the health of the eye. 2 consequences in particular can actually affect your vision long term. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Continuous eye rubbing can lead to thinning of the corneal tissue, which weakens the cornea and pushes it forward to become more conical. This thinning is an eye disease called keratoconus, which is a serious condition that can lead to distorted vision and may lead to needing a corneal transplant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;People with progressive myopia (near-sightedness which is VERY common) can find that rubbing worsens their eyesight&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used to work at a laser eye surgery clinic and we would do a lot of testing to determine if someone is a candidate for surgery. We could often determine if someone is a chronic eye rubber because we can see signs of it through our testing. Sure enough when we ask our patients if they do have an eye rubbing habit most will admit they do. It goes to show that chronic eye rubbing can and does change the lens of the eye since it is easily noticable when we do our testing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to clarify that this is chronic eye rubbing and not the occasional eye rub. This is for people that may rub their eyes multiple times a day, when they are sleepy, nervous, or are far to rough with certain routines like makeup removal. If you feel you have a habit of rubbing your eyes now would be a good time to become aware of it and try to change the behaviour. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you feel your eye rubbing is due to irritated eyes your best bet is to get an artificial tear drop as the majority of everyday irritation is due to dry eyes. You can also add a fish oil supplement into your diet to help increase natural lubrication to your eyes. Allergies are another reason people may rub their eyes. Visit your doctor for a diagnoses to rule out any other issues. Allergy medicines or antihistamine eye drops can help if the issue is allergy related.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reference and more info:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.visiontexas.com/general/rubbing-eyes-bad-5-reasons-will-get-stop-asap/&quot;&gt;https://www.visiontexas.com/general/rubbing-eyes-bad-5-reasons-will-get-stop-asap/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: If you have muscle pain that wont go away, get a massage!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: I just got a massage and they found the source of my chronic pain,
which were knots in my muscles from lifting weights. The masseuse said to do
stretches after exercise to prevent knots.

/u/LordCongra adds: "The literature supports stretching for 30 second to 1
minute 2-4 times daily and…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m84onz/ysk_if_you_have_muscle_pain_that_wont_go_away_get/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m84onz/ysk_if_you_have_muscle_pain_that_wont_go_away_get/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 23:26:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I just got a massage and they found the source of my chronic pain, which were knots in my muscles from lifting weights.  The masseuse said to do stretches after exercise to prevent knots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/u/LordCongra&quot;&gt;/u/LordCongra&lt;/a&gt; adds:  &amp;quot;The literature supports stretching for 30 second to 1 minute 2-4 times daily and past that it was found to not have a profound effect on tissue length.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source to more info:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.betterhealth.vic.gov.au/health/conditionsandtreatments/massage&quot;&gt;https://www.betterhealth.vic.gov.au/health/conditionsandtreatments/massage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK (almost all) fishbowls are cruel and inhumane]]></title><description><![CDATA[You should know that fishbowls are cruel and inhumane. why YSK know this is
because of many reasons.

First is the area of the bowl. For some fish like the common goldfish, this is
important because they can get up to a foot. Cramming them in a small space
means there body grows while their organs…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/macbux/ysk_almost_all_fishbowls_are_cruel_and_inhumane/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/macbux/ysk_almost_all_fishbowls_are_cruel_and_inhumane/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 18:58:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;You should know that fishbowls are cruel and inhumane. why YSK know this is because of many reasons. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First is the area of the bowl. For some fish like the common goldfish, this is important because they can get up to a foot. Cramming them in a small space means there body grows while their organs don&amp;#39;t. Also for other fish like bettas, it just doesn&amp;#39;t feel right confining them to such a small space. This mean, while a goldfish lives for 10-20 years with GOOD care, you&amp;#39;d be lucky to have one live for 2 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next is because of ammonia nitrite and nitrate and a lack of a filter. You have filters in fish tank for two main reasons. 1. is to agitate the water. 2. Is to grow beneficial bacteria. 
You may wonder, what is beneficial bacteria? It is a type of bacteria that consumes ammonia, a common toxin in a fishes poop. Then it turns it into nitrite which is just as harmful.  Then finally, it converts it to nitrate which is much less harmful. Even having a tiny filter doesn&amp;#39;t fix most stuff,  because some fish like goldfish produce a CRAP ton of waste and the bacteria can&amp;#39;t keep up. Also some fish like bettas are tropical fish and most bowls don&amp;#39;t have a filter. Most bettas that live in bowls don&amp;#39;t last more than 6 months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally bowls are bad because if the surface area. Even with a filter, the surface area doesn&amp;#39;t allow the bowl to oxygenate which is bad for the fish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I say &amp;quot;almost all&amp;quot; because if you were too keep a 10 gallon bowl with cherry shrimp that&amp;#39;s filtered and heater and has a lot of plants that would be ok. Even though the tank size for a betta is 5 Gallons, a bowl of 5 gallons just doesn&amp;#39;t have enough surface area. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could go on and on and on but I will keep this a short as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: If you make less than $72,000 a year adjusted gross income (AGI) you can file taxes completely free with the IRS Free File program]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: (US Only) The program is a partnership between the IRS and popular tax
filing software's like TurboTax, TaxSlayer, TaxAct, etc... that allows you to
file your entire return for free if you make less than the $72,000 AGI cutoff.

Here's the link to IRS Free…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mafb13/ysk_if_you_make_less_than_72000_a_year_adjusted/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mafb13/ysk_if_you_make_less_than_72000_a_year_adjusted/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 14:27:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: (US Only) The program is a partnership between the IRS and popular tax filing software&amp;#39;s like TurboTax, TaxSlayer, TaxAct, etc... that allows you to file your entire return for free if you make less than the $72,000 AGI cutoff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s the link to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.irs.gov/filing/free-file-do-your-federal-taxes-for-free&quot;&gt;IRS Free File&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if you do make more than $72,000/year the electronic forms to file are free to use and file online. Granted I would only do that if you have a pretty straightforward tax return or you really know what you&amp;#39;re doing when it comes to taxes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#39;re unsure of what steps to take, here is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/3KTyTxndOyg&quot;&gt;guide&lt;/a&gt; walking you through the free file program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: On subscription based services, you can usually get a cheaper rate, if you call and ask.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: I just had this happen to me. My wife and I both have satellite radio
enabled cars. I don't have mine active because I don't listen to music often
enough (I prefer podcasts, audibooks, etc). I still get special advertisements
all the time about restarting my service. I happened to get one…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m9dx6u/ysk_on_subscription_based_services_you_can/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m9dx6u/ysk_on_subscription_based_services_you_can/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 09:37:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I just had this happen to me. My wife and I both have satellite radio enabled cars. I don&amp;#39;t have mine active because I don&amp;#39;t listen to music often enough (I prefer podcasts, audibooks, etc). I still get special advertisements all the time about restarting my service. I happened to get one of these just after my wife&amp;#39;s subscription price automatically renewed at the &amp;quot;going rate&amp;quot; (or whatever you call that ridiculously high rate they charge if you don&amp;#39;t call and bother them). I called them up and asked for the special rate I had just been offered. 
The guy pulls up the account and offers me some other offer which is cheaper than regular, but not as good as what I had. I asked him if I couldn&amp;#39;t get the deal I called about. He responded &amp;quot;we have to get an answer on this deal first: do you want it, yes or no.&amp;quot; My response was &amp;quot;not if I can get this other offer&amp;quot;, which he then repeated his line and I realized he was following his script literally and had to offer me some low-ball offer first before proceeding to the offer I was interested in, so I told him no and I could hear him sigh with relief as he proceeded to pull up the offer I wanted and offer it to me. I was tempted to see if there was an even better offer out there by answering no again, but didn&amp;#39;t want to push my luck and end up canceling the service (and making the Mrs. upset). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moral of the story, you can (almost) always get your subscription based service cheaper if you call and ask. You may have to threaten to cancel (and don&amp;#39;t be afraid to follow through if they say no, because sometimes they think your threat is empty and won&amp;#39;t try to sell you until you are serious).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: fixed spelling (I do know how to spell, just on mobile). Also thanks for 1k upvotes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that when you write a personal check, you’re giving the payee your bank account and routing number. Instead, use your bank’s online bill pay feature - they’ll mail out a check to the payee with a different account, protecting your info]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: A lot of people don’t utilize their bank’s online bill pay feature,
myself included up until about a year ago. Not only does it save time, the bank
usually provides this service for free and will even mail your check for free to
the designated payee (so no paying for postage either). When…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m9yqva/ysk_that_when_you_write_a_personal_check_youre/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m9yqva/ysk_that_when_you_write_a_personal_check_youre/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 05:02:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: A lot of people don’t utilize their bank’s online bill pay feature, myself included up until about a year ago. Not only does it save time, the bank usually provides this service for free and will even mail your check for free to the designated payee (so no paying for postage either).
When you go this route, your bank sends a check with a different account number on it while still debiting your account, so you get all of the benefits of writing a check without any of the vulnerability that comes with sharing your account number.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: If you know someone who has a hard time bending over, like the elderly, make sure they have a table by their front door for packages.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: I deliver for a living. If I know someone is older, I put their
packages on a table/chair if they have one in front of their house. I get a lot
of compliments for thinking of that. A little patio table can be found for
$20-$40 at Walmart or similiar stores. Or even cheaper second hand. You…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ma3i8x/ysk_if_you_know_someone_who_has_a_hard_time/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ma3i8x/ysk_if_you_know_someone_who_has_a_hard_time/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 03:34:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I deliver for a living. If I know someone is older, I put their packages on a table/chair if they have one in front of their house. I get a lot of compliments for thinking of that. A little patio table can be found for $20-$40 at Walmart or similiar stores. Or even cheaper second hand. You can even get a little sign that just says, &amp;quot;Please put packages here.&amp;quot; It&amp;#39;s just a small thing that could really help people with mobility issues. Especially with more people ordering online instead of going to stores.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: It is common advice to make your password full of random characters, numbers, and symbols. However, a sentence with at least 10 words can be much more secure and will be significantly easier to remember.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: everyone has probably received the advice saying that your password
should be something like 8*^iHs89%>l7. However, not only is this hard to
remember, it is actually less secure than "The tall horses joyfully galloping
across the wide meadow quickly became thirsty".

Assuming that you only…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m5bqm0/ysk_it_is_common_advice_to_make_your_password/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m5bqm0/ysk_it_is_common_advice_to_make_your_password/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 03:34:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: everyone has probably received the advice saying that your password should be something like &lt;code&gt;8*^iHs89%&amp;gt;l7&lt;/code&gt;. However, not only is this hard to remember, it is actually less secure than &amp;quot;The tall horses joyfully galloping across the wide meadow quickly became thirsty&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Assuming that you only use the characters available on a normal keyboard, the first password format has 94&lt;sup&gt;12&lt;/sup&gt; possible combinations, or 4.75E23. Assuming you know 40,000 words, the second password format has 40000&lt;sup&gt;12,&lt;/sup&gt; or 1.67E55 combinations. That is roughly &lt;em&gt;10 septillion times&lt;/em&gt; more secure. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, that doesn&amp;#39;t even take into account that the person attempting to hack your account doesn&amp;#39;t know you&amp;#39;re using words, doesn&amp;#39;t know if you have spaces or they&amp;#39;re right next to each other, doesn&amp;#39;t know if you have numbers between, and doesn&amp;#39;t know which ones are capitalized. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL;DR: a 12 word sentence is &lt;em&gt;much&lt;/em&gt; more secure and memorable than 12 random characters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: When making your bed, 9 times out 10, the manufacturers tag will be on the bottom right corner of your quilt/sheet (when standing at the foot of the bed looking towards it)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Knowing where the tag is at and keeping it in the bottom right corner
will prevent you from having to readjust the sheet or quilt multiple times while
making the bed.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m7ezdd/ysk_when_making_your_bed_9_times_out_10_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m7ezdd/ysk_when_making_your_bed_9_times_out_10_the/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 22:56:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Knowing where the tag is at and keeping it in the bottom right corner will prevent you from having to readjust the sheet or quilt multiple times while making the bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK If you buy a house in a state with eviction moratorium, the seller is legally allowed to remain in the house even after closing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: In states with eviction moratoriums there have been a few cases of
sellers refusing to leave the house after the buyer has purchased it, and
legally no one can do anything about it until the moratorium is lifted. If
you’re a buyer this would be terrible for you. If you’re the seller maybe…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m9wbgz/ysk_if_you_buy_a_house_in_a_state_with_eviction/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m9wbgz/ysk_if_you_buy_a_house_in_a_state_with_eviction/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 20:34:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: In states with eviction moratoriums there have been a few cases of sellers refusing to leave the house after the buyer has purchased it, and legally no one can do anything about it until the moratorium is lifted. If you’re a buyer this would be terrible for you. If you’re the seller maybe this would work to your advantage!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that when asked for your address, name, phone number or other personal information by a cashier, "No thank you" is a perfectly acceptable answer. Protect your privacy.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: I'm posting this because that has always been my answer, and more often
than not they look at me like I have three heads, which tells me that it's not a
common response they get. While they may need that for you to get a 5% discount
next time you go in, the real reason they want it is to…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m9qkye/ysk_that_when_asked_for_your_address_name_phone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m9qkye/ysk_that_when_asked_for_your_address_name_phone/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 17:26:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I&amp;#39;m posting this because that has always been my answer, and more often than not they look at me like I have three heads, which tells me that it&amp;#39;s not a common response they get. While they may need that for you to get a 5% discount next time you go in, the real reason they want it is to sell your information and have you receive unsolicited phone calls. To that I say, no thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>