<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 04:36:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK in many parts of the USA (and in all parts by July 2022), to dial the national suicide prevention hotline, you just need to call 988]]></title><description><![CDATA[Source:https://www.ky3.com/2021/04/23/new-3-digit-suicide-prevention-number-will-mean-changes-for-local-call-dialing/

Why YSK: the long form suicide hotline number is something you had to look up
whether for yourself or someone else, but the USA has recently made the number
just 988. Remembering…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ob4pye/ysk_in_many_parts_of_the_usa_and_in_all_parts_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ob4pye/ysk_in_many_parts_of_the_usa_and_in_all_parts_by/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 21:36:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Source:&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ky3.com/2021/04/23/new-3-digit-suicide-prevention-number-will-mean-changes-for-local-call-dialing/&quot;&gt;https://www.ky3.com/2021/04/23/new-3-digit-suicide-prevention-number-will-mean-changes-for-local-call-dialing/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: the long form suicide hotline number is something you had to look up whether for yourself or someone else, but the USA has recently made the number just 988. Remembering this number and calling it or suggesting it to someone in need could save a life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, this has been enacted in most major cities in the US already, but will be enacted for all US area codes by July 16, 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Calling 988 is free. It&amp;#39;s like 911, but for suicidal thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Teach your kids. Tell your friends. 988.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK penis size matters... and doesn't matter, it all really depends on who it is interacting with.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: It is useful to know this to create more confidence and show that there
is no universal answer to "does size matter"

Some people will only settle for a highly uncommon 8.5 inch monster, while some
people get hurt by anything larger than 5 inches, others are just happy to have
a penis in…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ob2ob1/ysk_penis_size_matters_and_doesnt_matter_it_all/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ob2ob1/ysk_penis_size_matters_and_doesnt_matter_it_all/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 19:38:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It is useful to know this to create more confidence and show that there is no universal answer to &amp;quot;does size matter&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some people will only settle for a highly uncommon 8.5 inch monster, while some people get hurt by anything larger than 5 inches,  others are just happy to have a penis in them, and some people just don&amp;#39;t even like sex. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The average penis is between 5 and 6 inches so if you are in that range there&amp;#39;s no reason to feel sad, bevause so are the vast majority of penis packing people. And if you are outside that range there&amp;#39;s 7 billion people and the world and someone will have a preference for yours. And guess what people with average or smaller penises? Guys with huge dicks feel insecure sometimes too because they occasionally hurt people due to their size.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes it isn&amp;#39;t even about the penis, they may just want you to be able to know a variety of knots, choke them, etc. Being a part of someone&amp;#39;s fetish can be much more important than what the length of your penis is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also don&amp;#39;t forget skill and confidence. Someone  could have a general preference for larger penises but may prefer a confident 5.5 incher who is skilled over someone who is 7 inches but unconfident or unskilled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The question does size matter isn&amp;#39;t a universal yes or no, it varries from person to person and you can only find out one way, and if they are rude or humiliating about it they are immature and you should find someone else anyways (unless you&amp;#39;re into that)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that if you feel sad or lonely, you can DM me and I'll cheer you up!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: I'm trying to make the world a better place, and this not only makes my
world better, but it is a way for me to share the love and make your world a
little better too.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oaxhzq/ysk_that_if_you_feel_sad_or_lonely_you_can_dm_me/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oaxhzq/ysk_that_if_you_feel_sad_or_lonely_you_can_dm_me/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 15:28:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I&amp;#39;m trying to make the world a better place, and this not only makes my world better, but it is a way for me to share the love and make your world a little better too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that the antidote for paracetamol/acetaminophen (Tylenol) overdose is an over the counter cough medicine, acetylcysteine.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Paracetamol overdose is very common and is the leading cause of liver
failure in the UK and the US. It is commonly used as a method of suicide. It
also occurs in doses significantly lower than normal when taken with alcohol.
Combined with it being one of the most common drugs in the world…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o7tngd/ysk_that_the_antidote_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o7tngd/ysk_that_the_antidote_for/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 02:44:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Paracetamol overdose is very common and is the leading cause of liver failure in the UK and the US. It is commonly used as a method of suicide. It also occurs in doses significantly lower than normal when taken with alcohol. Combined with it being one of the most common drugs in the world it is very dangerous. If left untreated, paracetamol overdose causes a slow and painful death through liver failure in 4 to 18 days. However, it is absolutely crucial to administer its only antidote, acetylcysteine (Acetadote, Fluimucil, Mucomyst, it&amp;#39;s OTC), as early as possible, to prevent death and liver failure. Orally, it is used as 140 mg/kg for the first dose. However it is still absolutely necessary to seek medical attention. Please use this knowledge as a last resort if medical attention is unavailable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Paracetamol_poisoning&quot;&gt;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Paracetamol_poisoning&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK if you hang a wet towel outside during the heatwave, it will provide a much needed water source for thirsty bees.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK bees are our friends and pay us back in kind.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oalry6/ysk_if_you_hang_a_wet_towel_outside_during_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oalry6/ysk_if_you_hang_a_wet_towel_outside_during_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 02:13:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK bees are our friends and pay us back in kind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Low university crime statistics do not mean they have low crime.]]></title><description><![CDATA[If you are applying to a college or university and look at their reported crime
statistics, they typically do not show an accurate value of the crime that
actually occurs. This is for two reasons: 1) many crimes, especially ones like
sexual assault, go unreported. 2) Sometimes universities try to…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oaipru/ysk_low_university_crime_statistics_do_not_mean/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oaipru/ysk_low_university_crime_statistics_do_not_mean/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 01:14:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are applying to a college or university and look at their reported crime statistics, they typically do not show an accurate value of the crime that actually occurs. This is for two reasons: 1) many crimes, especially ones like sexual assault, go unreported. 2) Sometimes universities try to stop crime from being reported or being classified in a way that will show up in their record. In fact, if your university has a crime statistic of 0 for something like rape, that statistically is impossible, and can mean the university may be purposely obfuscating the truth or impeding the reporting process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Crime statistics are not very useful in selecting a university. Unless they are so low that it indicates a reporting problem or corruption.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Indeed tells the hiring manager how many times you’ve applied to jobs they’ve posted.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: This could either be good or bad for you, as it shows the dates and
positions applied for. It could show you as very eager to work with the
particular company. But also, it could give the impression you’re not “loyal” or
that you’ve been looking for a long time.

Edit: rates>dates]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oaf9n1/ysk_indeed_tells_the_hiring_manager_how_many/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oaf9n1/ysk_indeed_tells_the_hiring_manager_how_many/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 22:41:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This could either be good or bad for you, as it shows the dates and positions applied for. It could show you as very eager to work with the particular company. But also, it could give the impression you’re not “loyal” or that you’ve been looking for a long time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: rates&amp;gt;dates&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that approximately 1 in 4 dogs develop cancer, and for dogs over the age of 10, that number may reach as high as 1 in 2.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Approximately 25 per cent of dogs develop neoplasia (tumours), and that
number grows such that almost 50 per cent of dogs over the age of 10, develop
cancer. The rate of cancer in cats is not well studied, however, some cancers
are more common in cats than in dogs e.g. lymphoma. Cancer in…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o8d2zr/ysk_that_approximately_1_in_4_dogs_develop_cancer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o8d2zr/ysk_that_approximately_1_in_4_dogs_develop_cancer/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 18:32:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Approximately 25 per cent of dogs develop neoplasia (tumours), and that number grows such that almost 50 per cent of dogs over the age of 10, develop cancer. The rate of cancer in cats is not well studied, however, some cancers are more common in cats than in dogs e.g. lymphoma. Cancer in cats is the leading cause of death among cats. The symptoms are often overlooked as signs of general malaise and it is important to get your pet checked out as these are often curable in the early stages. Symptoms may range from lumps, limping, loss of appetite to non-healing wounds. Here is some suggested reading to help take care of your pet:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.avma.org/resources/pet-owners/petcare/cancer-pets&quot;&gt;https://www.avma.org/resources/pet-owners/petcare/cancer-pets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cancer_in_dogs&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cancer_in_dogs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cancer_in_cats&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cancer_in_cats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.msdvetmanual.com/special-pet-topics/cancer-and-tumors/causes-of-cancer&quot;&gt;https://www.msdvetmanual.com/special-pet-topics/cancer-and-tumors/causes-of-cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: job application systems where you submit your resumé and still have to fill out your details manually are out of date and an indication of the company being behind on tech trends.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: not only is it annoying for you as a candidate, it is actually an
indication of that company being behind and not investing in the latest trends.
This is a red flag.

It is the equivalent of a company in the early days of computers getting their
workers to do all calculations on paper…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oacchb/ysk_job_application_systems_where_you_submit_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oacchb/ysk_job_application_systems_where_you_submit_your/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 18:32:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: not only is it annoying for you as a candidate, it is actually an indication of that company being behind and not investing in the latest trends. This is a red flag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is the equivalent of a company in the early days of computers getting their workers to do all calculations on paper rather than adapt to excel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: all yous complaining nillies down in the comments are why we cant have nice things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK If invited to an activity/party on a group chat private DM the host if you can't go]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: having multiple people say that they can't make it really puts a drag
on the party and makes it look like nobody wants to. Sending a private DM to the
host politely letting them know you can't make it is the way to go.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o9u9c9/ysk_if_invited_to_an_activityparty_on_a_group/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o9u9c9/ysk_if_invited_to_an_activityparty_on_a_group/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 15:54:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: having multiple people say that they can&amp;#39;t make it really puts a drag on the party and makes it look like nobody wants to.  Sending a private DM to the host politely letting them know you can&amp;#39;t make it is the way to go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK why you look 'uglier' in photos than you do in the mirror]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Because we all experience this, and you shouldn't feel so bad about it.
Pro tip at the end.

You, well most of you, have 2 eyes. Your camera only has one. What we see in the
mirror is a 3-dimensional object, what we see on a photo is 2 dimensional. Your
eyes are not centered, because of…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o9vy26/ysk_why_you_look_uglier_in_photos_than_you_do_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o9vy26/ysk_why_you_look_uglier_in_photos_than_you_do_in/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 05:33:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Because we all experience this, and you shouldn&amp;#39;t feel so bad about it. Pro tip at the end. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You, well most of you, have 2 eyes. Your camera only has one. What we see in the mirror is a 3-dimensional object, what we see on a photo is 2 dimensional. Your eyes are not centered, because of this you slightly see around an object, which gives a more honest view of something. A camera can only see a flat surface. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What you see in the mirror is how other people see you, a photo is more like an approximation of your appearance. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, we are not used to seeing ourselves flipped horizontally like on a photo. Your face is not perfectly symmetrical, so when you see a photo of yourself, all the asymmetrical features of your face immediately catch your attention, because you&amp;#39;re not used to seeing them in that place. Pro tip: Try flipping your pictures horizontally, you&amp;#39;ll be way more comfortable with what you see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK Sometimes people don’t want a pet not because they don’t love animals but rather they end up loving them too much]]></title><description><![CDATA[When someone says “I don’t want a pet” take a moment and ask them, ideally in
private, “Why?” There are many reasons people either can’t have or don’t want a
pet: some have a fear of the animal, others may have an allergy while still
others may feel they cannot properly care for a pet. There is also…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o9vuu7/ysk_sometimes_people_dont_want_a_pet_not_because/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o9vuu7/ysk_sometimes_people_dont_want_a_pet_not_because/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 02:37:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When someone says “I don’t want a pet” take a moment and ask them, ideally in private, “Why?” There are many reasons people either can’t have or don’t want a pet: some have a fear of the animal, others may have an allergy while still others may feel they cannot properly care for a pet. There is also a reason that is less likely to be revealed openly however, particularly by a man. These people know from past experience they can end up loving their animals &lt;em&gt;too&lt;/em&gt; much and have trouble dealing with the pain of losing a beloved pet; they choose not to endure that loss again. Mom or Dad may fall into this category… Dad may not want a pet, not because he doesn’t love animals but rather because he knows he ends up loving them too much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Inquiring WHY someone doesn’t want a pet may save a lot of heartbreak down the road&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK about Ticketmaster’s “dynamic pricing”]]></title><description><![CDATA[WHY YSK

Ticketmaster has been doing this for a few years now, but with musicians finally
getting back to work, and many struggling to do so, it’s super scummy that
Ticketmaster can exponentially increase cost of tickets based upon demand.
Neither the bands nor the venues see any of that money. If…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o9mp3a/ysk_about_ticketmasters_dynamic_pricing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o9mp3a/ysk_about_ticketmasters_dynamic_pricing/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 17:22:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ticketmaster has been doing this for a few years now, but with musicians finally getting back to work, and many struggling to do so, it’s super scummy that Ticketmaster can exponentially increase cost of tickets based upon demand. Neither the bands nor the venues see any of that money. If there’s another way to get the tickets, give it a shot. After all, we love the bands and venues, not Ticketmaster&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK to look at the overall compensation package when looking for a new job]]></title><description><![CDATA[YSK when accepting a new job offer look at the overall benefits including health
Insurance. Remember that the pay that your employer gives you isn’t the amount
you will take home. Take into account insurance, retirement and taxes.

Why YSK

Sometimes people think they are getting a pay raise but…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o8o8zn/ysk_to_look_at_the_overall_compensation_package/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o8o8zn/ysk_to_look_at_the_overall_compensation_package/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 10:45:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;YSK when accepting a new job offer look at the overall benefits including health Insurance. Remember that the pay that your employer gives you isn’t the amount you will take home. Take into account insurance, retirement and taxes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes people think they are getting a pay raise but they don’t take into account the cost of health insurance, etc. Your pay raise May not actually be a raise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Coffee and cocoa drinks are made using a 6oz "cup", versus a standard 8oz cup.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: making coffee with a standard cup means your drinks will be weaker than
expected. Adjust water down or coffee/cocoa up to make sure you are getting a
proper brew.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o8x7vf/ysk_coffee_and_cocoa_drinks_are_made_using_a_6oz/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o8x7vf/ysk_coffee_and_cocoa_drinks_are_made_using_a_6oz/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 03:23:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: making coffee with a standard cup means your drinks will be weaker than expected. Adjust water down or coffee/cocoa up to make sure you are getting a proper brew.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: it's very possible to obtain consent in a "sexy" and natural way.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: consent is everything and should be obtained before and during every
sexual encounter. The consent should be enthusiastic and clear.

Alot of people seem to think that asking for consent can dampen the mood or make
the encounter seem transactional. Instead they take the "go with the flow"…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o99dji/ysk_its_very_possible_to_obtain_consent_in_a_sexy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o99dji/ysk_its_very_possible_to_obtain_consent_in_a_sexy/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 02:42:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: consent is everything and should be obtained before and during every sexual encounter. The consent should be enthusiastic and clear. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alot of people seem to think that asking for consent can dampen the mood or make the encounter seem transactional. Instead they take the &amp;quot;go with the flow&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;just read body language* route. I&amp;#39;m not judging anybody that has good intentions, it&amp;#39;s legitimate to think that flat out asking&amp;quot; do you want to have sex now&amp;quot; can be weird or off putting, but it really doesn&amp;#39;t have to be. Asking for consent can be just as sexy and natural as any other sexy talk. Here&amp;#39;s a few examples of me personally obtaining consent:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(during a hot &amp;amp; heavy make out session) &lt;em&gt;I want make love to you&lt;/em&gt;........ &lt;em&gt;would you like that&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;her response : a lustful look and a yea&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(sitting in the car having a great conversation) I touch her hand and playfully ask &lt;em&gt;can I kiss you&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;her response: she smiles and says go ahead&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(after a bit of intercourse) I look at her and say &lt;em&gt;I want to taste you&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;her response: an enthusiastic head nod and &amp;quot;please do&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know it sounds kinda cheesy just reading the words on a screen but I promise if you let the words come out in a way that fits the mood not only will it sound natural but it can actually be incredibly sexy, try it next time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last thing, this advice is genderless&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that in “essential oils,” the word “essential” is not synonymous with “important” or “necessary”]]></title><description><![CDATA[In the case of essential oils, the word essential just means that the oil
contains the essence (i.e., smell) of whatever substance from which it was
derived.

Why YSK: if you think these oils are “essential” to your health you might be
more inclined to waste your money thinking you’ll receive a…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o8n30t/ysk_that_in_essential_oils_the_word_essential_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o8n30t/ysk_that_in_essential_oils_the_word_essential_is/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 02:43:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the case of essential oils, the word essential just means that the oil contains the essence (i.e., smell) of whatever substance from which it was derived. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: if you think these oils are “essential” to your health you might be more inclined to waste your money thinking you’ll receive a medical health benefit. Not to say there aren’t benefits, but when one hears “essential!” they might think they’re necessary or important.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that if you live in the U.S. and have medical insurance, it is your responsibility to confirm your providers are in-network before seeking care.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Medical biller, here! I can't tell you how many times we've had
patients show up at our clinic, only to be told we are not in-network with their
insurance. This is usually due to a few senarios:

 1. The patient flat out did not tell us what insurance plan they had before
    arriving.
 2.…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o8cjms/ysk_that_if_you_live_in_the_us_and_have_medical/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o8cjms/ysk_that_if_you_live_in_the_us_and_have_medical/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 01:09:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Medical biller, here! I can&amp;#39;t tell you how many times we&amp;#39;ve had patients show up at our clinic, only to be told we are not in-network with their insurance. This is usually due to a few senarios:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The patient flat out did not tell us what insurance plan they had before arriving.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The patient told us they had &amp;quot;Medicare&amp;quot; but did not inform us/did not know that they had opted into a certain Medicare Advantage plan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The patient did not realize that their &lt;em&gt;insert provider specialty here&lt;/em&gt; coverage is through a &amp;quot;carve out&amp;quot; plan that is different that their primary medical insurance (e.g., they have BlueCross BlueShield insurance but the mental health benefits are through a &amp;quot;carve out&amp;quot; plan with United Healthcare).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The patient called their insurance company and they told the patient our clinic was in-network, but the insurance company had the wrong information. &lt;em&gt;Always call the provider&amp;#39;s office and confirm they are in-network with your insurance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; The patient has two insurances but only gave the provider&amp;#39;s office one of them. THIS ONE IS ESPECIALLY BAD BECAUSE WE USUALLY DO NOT FIND OUT UNTIL AFTER SERVICES HAVE BEEN RENDERED, MEANING YOU ARE STUCK WITH THE FEES!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After most of these scenarios (except #5), patients have only two options: pay a high self pay rate or don&amp;#39;t be seen and seek care elsewhere. Yes, it&amp;#39;s a broken healthcare system and often the rules are unfair/don&amp;#39;t make sense, but that&amp;#39;s why I always encourage patients to be informed and self-reliant when it comes to their medical insurance. In my experience that is the best way to avoid unnecessary out of pocket fees. Definitely don&amp;#39;t expect your insurance company or medical care providers to go out of their way to inform you, because in my experience, they will not, and you will be stuck with an unnecessary bill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy to address questions and concerns in the comments section!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: Medical billing is extremely complicated and tedious, so even after 3 years as a medical biller, my knowledge is still imperfect.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that raincoats expire.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: I debated whether to post this in TIFU, TIL, or YSK. I decided to go
the community service route. People of Reddit: raincoats expire. Or rather, the
water repellant material that keeps you dry degrades over time. I learned this
the hard way today when I stepped into a full on rainstorm with…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o8f7ir/ysk_that_raincoats_expire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o8f7ir/ysk_that_raincoats_expire/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 21:07:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; I debated whether to post this in TIFU, TIL, or YSK. I decided to go the community service route. People of Reddit: raincoats expire. Or rather, the water repellant material that keeps you dry degrades over time. I learned this the hard way today when I stepped into a full on rainstorm with my &amp;quot;trusty,&amp;quot; expensive, fancy brand raincoat and was soaked to the bone within seconds. I got it as a gift 7 years ago and have been too poor to replace it. I guess in the year of closet time since last rainy season, it gave up the ghost: when I took it off, I was covered with flakes from the dissolved inner layer. Apparently you can delay this from happening by treating your coats now and then, but you&amp;#39;ll only delay the inevitable. Thankfully, I&amp;#39;m no longer poor, so I can buy myself a new one plus one to donate. Go forth and be dry!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL;DR: The water repellant material degrades over time; you&amp;#39;ll need to re-treat your coat and, eventually, replace it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: People who complain about noise often have very good reasons.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am not saying to stop doing things you need to do if you are being noisy.
However people often complain about how neighbors or roommates are easily upset
by noise. There are a lot of good reasons however for them to get upset. They
may work nights and are trying to sleep. Or they may have…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o8aamm/ysk_people_who_complain_about_noise_often_have/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o8aamm/ysk_people_who_complain_about_noise_often_have/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:20:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am not saying to stop doing things you need to do if you are being noisy. However people often complain about how neighbors or roommates are easily upset by noise. There are a lot of good reasons however for them to get upset. They may work nights and are trying to sleep. Or they may have insomnia. Or they may be recovering from something or have a concussion or other medical condition that makes them sensitive to noise. Even if they are just a teenager; teenagers are biologically wired not to be able to go to bed early &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.neurologylive.com/view/teenage-circadian-rhythm&quot;&gt;https://www.neurologylive.com/view/teenage-circadian-rhythm&lt;/a&gt;). Or they may work from home and have difficulty focusing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: People who complain about noise aren&amp;#39;t just assholes. They usually have good reason. So please be polite and obey your city ordinance laws.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: But also, if you have a noise complaint, calling the police is not always necessary if you haven&amp;#39;t already talked to the people making the noise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: You should always thank the home-chef for a home-cooked meal, and remember to overlook the small stuff]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Cooking at home can be distracting and the recipes may not turn out
perfect all the time. This is not because of the lack of effort or care but
could be a million other factors.

Your partner or significant other may be spending hours preparing a home-cooked
meal. The least you can do is…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o88y94/ysk_you_should_always_thank_the_homechef_for_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o88y94/ysk_you_should_always_thank_the_homechef_for_a/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 13:41:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Cooking at home can be distracting and the recipes may not turn out perfect all the time. This is not because of the lack of effort or care but could be a million other factors. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your partner or significant other may be spending hours preparing a home-cooked meal. The least you can do is the appreciate the effort. And remember to overlook the small stuff - even if the dish is a bit salty or over done&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK if you’re still using an old version of Windows, that you can STILL upgrade to Windows 10 for free, legitimately, through Microsoft, and probably should do so before 11 is released.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Here is a write-up on ZD-Net
[https://www.zdnet.com/article/heres-how-you-can-still-get-a-free-windows-10-upgrade/].

> Microsoft's much-hyped free upgrade offer for Windows 10 ended years ago,
> right? Not exactly. We've made it to 2021 and my readers report that you can
> still use Microsoft's…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o7qq3w/ysk_if_youre_still_using_an_old_version_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o7qq3w/ysk_if_youre_still_using_an_old_version_of/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 07:55:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zdnet.com/article/heres-how-you-can-still-get-a-free-windows-10-upgrade/&quot;&gt;Here is a write-up on ZD-Net&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft&amp;#39;s much-hyped free upgrade offer for Windows 10 ended years ago, right? Not exactly. We&amp;#39;ve made it to 2021 and my readers report that you can still use Microsoft&amp;#39;s free upgrade tools to install Windows 10 on an old PC running Windows 7 or Windows 8.1. No product key is required, and the digital license says you&amp;#39;re activated and ready to go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.microsoft.com/software-download/windows10&quot;&gt;Here is the direct link to the Microsoft upgrade page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can confirm it still works, having upgraded an old computer with 7 mere days ago, without a hitch. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you visit the link on a non-Windows device, you will be directed to Microsoft’s page for creating a Windows-10 ISO disc, which will still be an option of you visit using a Windows machine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Once Windows 11 is released, this totally free and licensed upgrade will likely cease working. It was originally stated that the offer was time-limited and would end years ago, but for whatever reason they have left it active and operational. Now is the time to jump on board if you haven’t done so yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that if you are traveling westbound on even numbered highways or southbound on odd numbered highways, the exit numbers usually match with the miles left to the next state border.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK because it can help you plan your trip and keep track of time, mileage
and gas in you car.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o6px1e/ysk_that_if_you_are_traveling_westbound_on_even/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o6px1e/ysk_that_if_you_are_traveling_westbound_on_even/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 05:19:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK because it can help you plan your trip and keep track of time, mileage and gas in you car.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that there are some very simple steps one can take to improve the odds of finding a significant other.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Interpersonal relationships are an important aspect of humanity, and
greatly improve quality of life.

I was a borderline incel in high school and college. Girls didn't want to date
me even though I was a really really nice guy and even tall (I'm 6'5" but built
like Baby Huey)! Obviously, I…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o7v9fx/ysk_that_there_are_some_very_simple_steps_one_can/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o7v9fx/ysk_that_there_are_some_very_simple_steps_one_can/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 22:00:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Interpersonal relationships are an important aspect of humanity, and greatly improve quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was a borderline incel in high school and college. Girls didn&amp;#39;t want to date me even though I was a really really nice guy and even tall (I&amp;#39;m 6&amp;#39;5&amp;quot; but built like Baby Huey)! Obviously, I was a perfect specimen (I was even one of those jags who bragged about my IQ), and it was the women who just hated nice dudes blah blah blah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was lucky enough to have a friend who gave me a few pieces of sage advice that I&amp;#39;d like to pass on, to help prevent teens and young adults like me from wasting the prime years of their lives. I&amp;#39;d like to say that, for me personally, this list was fucking gangbusters. In less than a year of shifting my perspectives on relationships and making some easy, relatively inexpensive changes, I had a girlfriend. We&amp;#39;re still together and will be celebrating our fifth anniversary in September:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- The most important advice I was given was this (you&amp;#39;ve probably heard it a hundred times just this month on Reddit, but it bears repeating): Nice isn&amp;#39;t a personality. Nice is the bare fucking minimum to being human. A person advertising how nice they are would be like a car commercial that only focuses on the fact that the car has four wheels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- It doesn&amp;#39;t matter if you saved a person&amp;#39;s entire extended family and pets from falling into a giant woodchipper, that person owes you nothing, and much more importantly, that person owes you NOTHING sexual. This goes quadruple for being &amp;quot;nice.&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- You have to put in some effort. I used to get my hair cut about every 8 months. It would sit in a mop on my head, getting longer and grosser as the months went on. I wore ratty clothes and didn&amp;#39;t shave or shower often enough. If you&amp;#39;re looking for a significant other, you&amp;#39;re going to fail the (literal) smell test, even if you&amp;#39;re genuinely a good person.  Get somewhat regular haircuts, trim your bead (or if you&amp;#39;re like me and can&amp;#39;t grow one, accept that fact and start shaving), and shower before you go out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Related to the above, fashion is also important. I&amp;#39;m not saying you should go out and buy an Armani suit, but you should have at least one set of (clean!) &amp;quot;going out&amp;quot; clothes. Personally, I went to Marshalls and got a decent pair of darkish jeans, a nice pair of brown leather boots, and a nice button up shirt. Bought it all on clearance for less than $50, and nothing in this world gave me more confidence than a friend&amp;#39;s long time girlfriend saying &amp;quot;Steven, you look really nice tonight.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Second only to the first bullet point, it&amp;#39;s important that you know this: You can do everything right. You can get the look, you can change your perceptions,  you can be as clean as a whistle, you can smell like an $800 bottle of cologne, and you can have the perfect witty response to every single thing a person says, but that doesn&amp;#39;t mean that someone will like you romantically. It&amp;#39;s not up to you if someone is attracted to you, and you putting forth the effort doesn&amp;#39;t mean you&amp;#39;re owed anything. Be an adult, thank the person for their candor (or just don&amp;#39;t respond if they&amp;#39;re dicks about it), and move on. Two things that can easily derail someone&amp;#39;s positive perception of you are sudden anger and desperation. The only thing worse than those is yo-yoing violently between them (Like in all the &lt;a href=&quot;/r/niceguys&quot;&gt;r/niceguys&lt;/a&gt; screenshots you see). A big part of maturity is licking your wounds and realizing that you&amp;#39;re not everyone&amp;#39;s cup of tea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- To build on the above, don&amp;#39;t burn your bridges. Maybe that girl wasn&amp;#39;t interested in you, but has a friend who would LOVE the fact that you use the word &amp;quot;grok&amp;quot; in casual conversation and can recite the Holy Hand Grenade speech from memory (Five is right out!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This list obviously isn&amp;#39;t perfect, nor is it all encompassing, but these pieces of advice legitimately changed my life for the better, and my biggest regret is that I didn&amp;#39;t listen to my friends earlier in life. I hope they work for those who need them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL;DR: Don&amp;#39;t be a dick and take some modicum of care of yourself&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that putting your napkin/trasg inside your cup at the end of a meal at a restaurant is not helpful or polite to the staff.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK:

Although consolidating your trash and dishes after your meal is generally a
polite, helpful thing to do, you should not put your dirty napkin inside your
cup. You can leave it on a plate or tuck it underneath if you are outside and
worried about it blowing away, but you should not stuff it…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o7ss6a/ysk_that_putting_your_napkintrasg_inside_your_cup/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o7ss6a/ysk_that_putting_your_napkintrasg_inside_your_cup/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 19:49:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although consolidating your trash and dishes after your meal is generally a polite, helpful thing to do, you should not put your dirty napkin inside your cup. You can leave it on a plate or tuck it underneath if you are outside and worried about it blowing away, but you should not stuff it into your cup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you put it inside your cup, whoever is washing your dishes will inevitably have to reach inside your dirty cup and pull out the soggy napkin to throw it away. This of course makes restaurant staff&amp;#39;s job harder and grosser, not easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: &lt;em&gt;trash&lt;/em&gt; in the title&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: You NEED (not should) to consider your financial well being before adopting an animal.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Animals are very expensive (and time consuming) to have if you want to
PROPERLY take care of them. Of course, there are some outliers when it comes to
this.

Veterinary care is expensive and can break you if you’re wallet isn’t ready for
it. Look into insurance costs, what they cover,…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o7q1vh/ysk_you_need_not_should_to_consider_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o7q1vh/ysk_you_need_not_should_to_consider_your/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 16:59:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Animals are very expensive (and time consuming) to have if you want to PROPERLY take care of them. Of course, there are some outliers when it comes to this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Veterinary care is expensive and can break you if you’re wallet isn’t ready for it. Look into insurance costs, what they cover, deductible and any other hoops they may have you jump through to get an animal insured. That small monthly cost may save you a few thousand and the stress of trying to come up with it if you don’t already have it. Also, check with vet offices in your area to see what insurance they will approve (and their reviews if you’re wanting quality care). Some vet offices even have financial assistance programs for animals to get the care they need while also relieving financial burden from the owner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that George Orwell, the author of Animal Farm and 1984, was a pen name. His real name is Eric Arthur Blair.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK.. he created four pseudonyms P. S. Burton (a name he used when
tramping), Kenneth Miles, George Orwell, and H. Lewis Allways. He finally
adopted the nom de plume George Orwell because "It is a good round English
name."]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o7n5vf/ysk_that_george_orwell_the_author_of_animal_farm/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o7n5vf/ysk_that_george_orwell_the_author_of_animal_farm/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 14:33:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK.. he created four pseudonyms P. S. Burton (a name he used when tramping), Kenneth Miles, George Orwell, and H. Lewis Allways. He finally adopted the nom de plume George Orwell because &amp;quot;It is a good round English name.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that "light" "diet" and "kids" versions of juice are a major ripoff]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why ysk: the low sugar versions of juice are just watered down with vitamin c
and sweetener added for flavor. You can just add water to a glass of juice,
achieve the same effect, and even extend your value from regular juice.

Though watered down OJ tastes bad, the rest are about the same as long as…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o7fs9v/ysk_that_light_diet_and_kids_versions_of_juice/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o7fs9v/ysk_that_light_diet_and_kids_versions_of_juice/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 07:39:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why ysk: the low sugar versions of juice are just watered down with vitamin c and sweetener added for flavor. You can just add water to a glass of juice, achieve the same effect, and even extend your value from regular juice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though watered down OJ tastes bad, the rest are about the same as long as you don&amp;#39;t water it down too much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK That if you have a vehicle lease ending soon, there's a VERY good chance you have equity and you should trade or sell it to the dealer as instead of just a lease return.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: It usually is very rare that a leased vehicle will have equity (unless
driven very little). But with the current used car and new car inventory
shortages due to the pandemic and microchip shortages, it is now very common to
have equity in your leased vehicle. A typical dealer won't even…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o30j84/ysk_that_if_you_have_a_vehicle_lease_ending_soon/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o30j84/ysk_that_if_you_have_a_vehicle_lease_ending_soon/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 07:11:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  It usually is very rare that a leased vehicle will have equity (unless driven very little).  But with the current used car and new car inventory shortages due to the pandemic and microchip shortages, it is now very common to have equity in your leased vehicle.  A typical dealer won&amp;#39;t even suggest this option because they will offer to &amp;quot;take it off your hands&amp;quot;  and pocket the profit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK in the US foods can be listed as TRANS FAT FREE and containing 0g trans fat and STILL CONTAIN TRANS FAT. If you see the word hydrogenated or partially hydroganted oils under ingredients, it contains trans fat.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Trans fat raises bad cholesterol levels and lowers good cholesterol
levels. It may also increase risk of type 2 diabetes and inflammation.

Foods containing fewer than 0.5g trans fat per serving may be labeled as trans
fat free, but people often consume more than one serving. Frequent…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o77i16/ysk_in_the_us_foods_can_be_listed_as_trans_fat/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o77i16/ysk_in_the_us_foods_can_be_listed_as_trans_fat/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 21:49:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Trans fat raises bad cholesterol levels and lowers good cholesterol levels. It may also increase risk of type 2 diabetes and inflammation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Foods containing fewer than 0.5g trans fat per serving may be labeled as trans fat free, but people often consume more than one serving. Frequent consumption of multiple foods containing trans fat can also add up. Any amount of trans fat can potentially have negative impacts, so it&amp;#39;s important to check! There often alternatives available of the same food, so foregoing trans fat doesn&amp;#39;t necessarily mean you can&amp;#39;t have the foods you enjoy! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/healthy-eating/eat-smart/fats/trans-fat&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: not everything can go down your garbage disposal.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I think a lot of people don't know not everything can go in a garbage disposal.
Things like lettuce, pasta, rice, animal bones, egg shells, onion layers, coffee
grounds, nuts and so much more. Don't be shocked if it stops working after you
have emptied all dinner plate leftovers down there.

Why YSK…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o6u65t/ysk_not_everything_can_go_down_your_garbage/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o6u65t/ysk_not_everything_can_go_down_your_garbage/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 20:35:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think a lot of people don&amp;#39;t know not everything can go in a garbage disposal.  Things like lettuce, pasta, rice, animal bones, egg shells, onion layers, coffee grounds, nuts and so much more. Don&amp;#39;t be shocked if it stops working after you have emptied all dinner plate leftovers down there. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK it&amp;#39;s just not good for the disposal&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK if you are vegan or vegetarian and you go to dine at a fixed-menu restaurant you should notify them about your diet in advance or meat could be wasted.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: restaurants that serve a fixed menu usually start prepping their meals
long before the customers sit down to eat. This is why you should always make
sure the restaurant knows about your dietary limitations in advance, especially
if you are vegan or vegetarian. If you wait to notify the…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o4bxtj/ysk_if_you_are_vegan_or_vegetarian_and_you_go_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o4bxtj/ysk_if_you_are_vegan_or_vegetarian_and_you_go_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 18:52:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: restaurants that serve a fixed menu usually start prepping their meals long before the customers sit down to eat. This is why you should always make sure the restaurant knows about your dietary limitations in advance, especially if you are vegan or vegetarian. If you wait to notify the restaurant you are vegan/vegetarian untill you sit down to eat, chances are the meat that would be served to you has already been prepped and can&amp;#39;t be saved for another customer another day. A great habit that will prevent any meat from being wasted, undermining your commitment to a meat free diet, is to always make sure the restaurant knows in advance. Most online reservation tools will ask about dietary limitations automatically. A vegetarian diet should be mentioned there. When making reservations through the phone most restaurants will have the habit to ask about diets but they can forget, especially during  busy hours. A little effort could save literally the entire staff of the restaurant from a headache and, of course, save food from being wasted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL;DR if you wait to tell a restaurant you don&amp;#39;t eat meat untill you sit down to eat you&amp;#39;re probably too late and food that had already been prepped will be wasted. Make sure to notify them ahead of time even if they forget to ask.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that your paper coffee cup may leak if the cup's seam is aligned with the hole for your mouth in the cup's lid]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: certain placements of a coffee cup lid can result in drips, staining
your clothes.

After having coffee stain my pants too many times, I found that most of the time
drips occurred when the seam in the cup lined up with the hole in the lid. Since
then, I make it a point to make sure the two…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o5m023/ysk_that_your_paper_coffee_cup_may_leak_if_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o5m023/ysk_that_your_paper_coffee_cup_may_leak_if_the/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 03:32:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: certain placements of a coffee cup lid can result in drips, staining your clothes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After having coffee stain my pants too many times, I found that most of the time drips occurred when the seam in the cup lined up with the hole in the lid.  Since then, I make it a point to make sure the two are opposite each other, or at least aren&amp;#39;t aligned with each other.  No drips.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Every Car Built from 2018 Onwards is REQUIRED to Have a Backup Camera -- It is not an extra feature]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Since May 2018, all newly-built cars sold in the United States are
required to have a backup camera and video display for the camera. Many car
dealers, both used and new, will advertise the backup camera as some kind of
added luxury or special option and try to charge you more for it. Don't…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o6lscq/ysk_every_car_built_from_2018_onwards_is_required/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o6lscq/ysk_every_car_built_from_2018_onwards_is_required/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 02:08:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Since May 2018, all newly-built cars sold in the United States are required to have a backup camera and video display for the camera. Many car dealers, both used and new, will advertise the backup camera as some kind of added luxury or special option and try to charge you more for it. Don&amp;#39;t bite the bait and understand that it is 100% a legal mandate to have it, like seat belts or air bags.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK what your interest rate/APR and positive/negative equity means when buying a car.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: You could save thousands of dollars and prevent yourself from having a
lot of negative equity in the future if you wanted to sell or trade the vehicle.
See my post here
[https://reddit.com/r/whatcarshouldIbuy/comments/o5453w/sorry_this_isnt_a_typical_post_but_if_youre_going/]

Edit: The…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o6ecat/ysk_what_your_interest_rateapr_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o6ecat/ysk_what_your_interest_rateapr_and/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 01:26:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: You could save thousands of dollars and prevent yourself from having a lot of negative equity in the future if you wanted to sell or trade the vehicle. See my post &lt;a href=&quot;https://reddit.com/r/whatcarshouldIbuy/comments/o5453w/sorry_this_isnt_a_typical_post_but_if_youre_going/&quot;&gt;here &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: The reason I didn’t copy/paste from the post I have linked above is because there are a lot of good comments that have good info - not just what I had to say. Read those comments too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: your body is still changing in your 20s]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: This is something I had never learned until the past year. None of my
friends had heard of this either. I noticed my body composition and where fat
went was changing. I previously struggled with an eating disorder for several
years, so this was hard for me to accept. Your body is still…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o62cre/ysk_your_body_is_still_changing_in_your_20s/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o62cre/ysk_your_body_is_still_changing_in_your_20s/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 06:29:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This is something I had never learned until the past year. None of my friends had heard of this either. I noticed my body composition and where fat went was changing. I previously struggled with an eating disorder for several years, so this was hard for me to accept. Your body is still maturing and changing as you age, not just in your 20s but throughout your life. It&amp;#39;s normal and healthy. You may try to get back to a weight or shape you were when you were a teenager and it may be impossible/unhealthy because your hormones have shifted. I wish I had known this sooner myself so I figured I would make a post about it to let other people know that gaining some weight or your body changing shape still in your 20s is a normal part of life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/health/second-puberty&quot;&gt;https://www.healthline.com/health/second-puberty&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: "Money is the root of all evil" is not the full quote and can be misleading.]]></title><description><![CDATA[The full quote is, according to one of many Bible translations, "For the love of
money is the root of all kinds of evil" (1 Timothy 6:10).

Why YSK: When saying money is the root of evil, it suggests that physical money
is the source of evil. When using the full quote, it is the emotional…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o612ny/ysk_money_is_the_root_of_all_evil_is_not_the_full/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o612ny/ysk_money_is_the_root_of_all_evil_is_not_the_full/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 03:47:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The full quote is, according to one of many Bible translations, &amp;quot;&lt;em&gt;For the love of money is the root of all kinds of evil&lt;/em&gt;&amp;quot; (1 Timothy 6:10).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: When saying money is the root of evil, it suggests that physical money is the source of evil. When using the full quote, it is the emotional connection to money and wealth that is the source of evil and evildoings, and changes the intended meaning entirely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK if you're buying or selling a house, what is considered a "fixture" and stays with the house.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Many people end up disappointed when buying a house to discover that
items or appliances they thought should be included with the home were not left
behind; or when selling a home take items that should have been left behind and
have to pay the buyer to replace them.



Legally, (in the US…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o5uddm/ysk_if_youre_buying_or_selling_a_house_what_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o5uddm/ysk_if_youre_buying_or_selling_a_house_what_is/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 23:33:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Many people end up disappointed when buying a house to discover that items or appliances they thought should be included with the home were not left behind; or when selling a home take items that should have been left behind and have to pay the buyer to replace them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Legally, (in the US at least), a Fixture is anything that is &amp;quot;physically and permanently&amp;quot; attached to the home or property, and must be included in the sale of the home.  Common items that are considered fixtures include: window blinds and curtain rods, built in shelves, chandeliers and ceiling fans, appliances that are built into cabinets like dishwashers, out buildings like sheds, and trees or plants in the ground.  Common items that are NOT considered fixtures include: drapes, shower curtains, refrigerators that are not built into a cabinet, countertop appliances, and plants in pots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A common point of contention is attachments for hanging flat screen TVs on walls. They are &amp;quot;physically and permanently&amp;quot; attached to the wall, and normally should be included. But many times they are only good with the brand/size of TV they are made for, and probably useless to the buyer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are buying a house and want to make sure something is included, its always a good idea to ask. Sellers may be willing to include things that are not normally considered fixtures that they may not be able to use again, or just to avoid moving it to the next house, like custom sized drapes or an extra refrigerator in the basement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are selling a house and want to take something that normally would be considered a fixture, you can put this in the contract as an exclusion. For example, some people may be very attached to a tree or plants they put in, and want to take them along to their next house. If you don&amp;#39;t put this in the contract, the buyer could sue and force you to pay to replace them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edited to add: I see there is some discussion over the definition of what &amp;quot;permanently&amp;quot; attached means. In the case of real estate law, it is generally defined as &amp;quot;affixed to the property through the application of plaster, cement, bolts, screws, nuts, or nails.&amp;quot; i.e. if you need tools to remove it, its usually considered &amp;quot;permanently&amp;quot; attached.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK local police or Fire/EMS will do a health and safety check on a loved one if you’re worried that they may have died.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: recently read a post detailing how devastated a family was after
checking on a loved one they hadn’t heard from for several days, these traumatic
experiences can do decades of damage to families. Utilizing local emergency
services to do the check can save families from the extensive trauma…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o5q5od/ysk_local_police_or_fireems_will_do_a_health_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o5q5od/ysk_local_police_or_fireems_will_do_a_health_and/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 21:37:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: recently read a post detailing how devastated a family was after checking on a loved one they hadn’t heard from for several days, these traumatic experiences can do decades of damage to families. Utilizing local emergency services to do the check can save families from the extensive trauma of seeing someone after they’ve passed. This of course also applies to suicides and OD’s, as those scenes can also be very traumatic. Please do not let guilt or concern cause you decades of mental anguish, or ruin your last good memories of a loved one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Cigarette butts are the most common form of marine litter and if you smoke, the best you can do is to purchase a pocket ashtray if you are worried about the smell from cigarettes in your pocket.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Cigarette butts continue to rank among the most common types of marine
debris found. You can have a look at the The Ocean Conservancy’s International
Coastal Cleanup Report
[https://oceanconservancy.org/trash-free-seas/international-coastal-cleanup/annual-data-release/]

And as a…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o5jgpa/ysk_cigarette_butts_are_the_most_common_form_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o5jgpa/ysk_cigarette_butts_are_the_most_common_form_of/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 19:39:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Cigarette butts continue to rank among the most common types of marine debris found. You can have a look at the &lt;a href=&quot;https://oceanconservancy.org/trash-free-seas/international-coastal-cleanup/annual-data-release/&quot;&gt;The Ocean Conservancy’s International Coastal Cleanup Report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And as a responsible person, we can do some simple things to stop adding more to the mess.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As per this &lt;a href=&quot;https://oceanservice.noaa.gov/facts/most-common-ocean-litter.html&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;:
- If you smoke, don’t flick your butt!
- Purchase a pocket ashtray! These trays can come in the form of metal boxes or vinyl pouches, fit in your pocket, purse, or backpack, and extinguish cigarettes until they can be properly disposed of in the trash.
- Check to see if there any programs in your area who recycle cigarette butts. 
 - There are a few places, like the City of Vancouver, and organizations, like TerraCycle, that will actually recycle your filters for you.
- You can spread awareness among your friends, family members or people you know so that they can follow the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: The most overlooked defense to avoid respiratory illnesses is proper ventilation.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: You can dramatically reduce the chance you catch a communicable
respiratory illness.

For example, offices and public restrooms are very common transmission origins.
This is because commercial buildings are constructed with most of the HVAC in
the common areas, so the smaller spaces and…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o5mhhc/ysk_the_most_overlooked_defense_to_avoid/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o5mhhc/ysk_the_most_overlooked_defense_to_avoid/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 19:39:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: You can dramatically reduce the chance you catch a communicable respiratory illness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, offices and public restrooms are very common transmission origins. This is because commercial buildings are constructed with most of the HVAC in the common areas, so the smaller spaces and individual offices have minimal ductwork. This means almost all of the fresh air is circulating in the main areas, rather than in smaller spaces like offices, which often have meetings (or are shared), with everyone breathing the same air over and over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note when I say circulation, that’s only part of it. &lt;strong&gt;The air &lt;em&gt;exchange&lt;/em&gt; rate is very important.&lt;/strong&gt; This is why relatively few respiratory illnesses get traced back to airplanes… You sit elbow to elbow, jam-packed like sardines, for hours, and almost no one gets sick. This is because the entire volume of air on a flight is completely changed every few minutes. That’s air circulation and exchange. Look at this way: If I put a grain of salt in a bowl of soup you won’t know it. If I add 5 more grains in you probably won’t know it. But If I put 50 grains in you’re almost sure to taste it. The same principle applies to particles in the air. Breathe too many from someone in the transmissible stage and you may be soon share it. This is why it matters if the air is still versus if there’s a slight breeze, because the odds of you catching something become much slimmer. This is like how you might gag on cigarette smoke coming from a restaurant table next to you, versus barely noticing someone smoking outside at the same distance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for public restrooms, here is where millions of people have been unknowingly infected. Like offices, most are constructed with little duct work, so the air is not exchanging/transferring. But now it’s even worse because every time someone flushes it launches millions of microscopic particles into the room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So act accordingly... Office meetings should be held with a door open and a fan blowing in or out of the doorway. Public restrooms? Ceiling vent fans should run non-stop during the work day and they should have a high capacity blower, too. Occupancy should be limited and break times should be staggered. And leave the doors open when not in use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve included a link about ventilation importance, too. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-jmzEQtGRXQ&amp;amp;t=64s&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-jmzEQtGRXQ&amp;amp;t=64s&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: that you should clean glasses (e.g. for honey) before throwing them in recycling containers.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: when the glass breaks, bees are tempted to fly in the containers.
Especially if you live in a city, where there are not that many sources of food
for bees. From trash and recycling containers, bees will carry bacteria back to
their hives. This can be tragic for the entire bee hive. You…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o5fakl/ysk_that_you_should_clean_glasses_eg_for_honey/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o5fakl/ysk_that_you_should_clean_glasses_eg_for_honey/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 17:59:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: when the glass breaks, bees are tempted to fly in the containers. Especially if you live in a city, where there are not that many sources of food for bees. From trash and recycling containers, bees will carry bacteria back to their hives. This can be tragic for the entire bee hive. You could also bring used honey glasses to your local beekeeper, to be reused.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that if your pet develops a limp or reluctance to use one of its legs that gets worse or does not improve over time, and there is no obvious cause, go to the vet sooner than later because it may be cancer.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: a lot of critters develop limps because of an injured tendon, sprain or
problem with their paws. But if your pet starts limping without any reason you
can identify, go to the vet for x-rays sooner than later. Osteosarcoma (bone
cancer) is more common than people recognize and causes…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o5exqy/ysk_that_if_your_pet_develops_a_limp_or/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o5exqy/ysk_that_if_your_pet_develops_a_limp_or/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 09:41:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: a lot of critters develop limps because of an injured tendon, sprain or problem with their paws. But if your pet starts limping without any reason you can identify, go to the vet for x-rays sooner than later. Osteosarcoma (bone cancer) is more common than people recognize and causes significant pain. If it is in the extremities, that can cause a limp or refusal of your pet to use that leg at all, and lead to muscle mass. Unfortunately it is fast spreading. If you can identify it before it spreads, amputation may save your critter&amp;#39;s life and eliminate the pain. Don&amp;#39;t wait to get it checked out if your buddy is not improving. Life on 3 legs beats the heck out of the alternative.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK There is an app that is easy to use to help scientists identify wildlife with just a picture when you’re out.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why ysk: there are many endangered animals, insects, and plants in the world.
Something as simple as sharing photos of the pretty flowers or butterfly you saw
camping this summer can help scientists study them. This in turn can help us
understand the patterns better and in endangered cases help…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o5dslz/ysk_there_is_an_app_that_is_easy_to_use_to_help/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o5dslz/ysk_there_is_an_app_that_is_easy_to_use_to_help/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 08:27:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why ysk: there are many endangered animals, insects, and plants in the world. Something as simple as sharing photos of the pretty flowers or butterfly you saw camping this summer can help scientists study them. This in turn can help us understand the patterns better and in endangered cases help preserve the sites they are found. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s all save the earth together. Snap pics of everything you enjoy in your time outside even if it’s a walk in the park and post them to places like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.inaturalist.org/&quot;&gt;iNaturalist &lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://plantnet.org/&quot;&gt;Plantnet&lt;/a&gt; for free. You don’t need to know what it is exactly just post the pic and your location and it helps the scientists out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK the difference between irony and sarcasm]]></title><description><![CDATA[Taken from dictionary.com:

Irony: The use of words to convey a meaning that is the opposite of its literal
meaning

Sarcasm: Harsh or bitter derision or irony

Sarcasm is when you use irony to put up with a bad situation you are in,
possibly sneering at the person you are talking with.

Why YSK:…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o59e7e/ysk_the_difference_between_irony_and_sarcasm/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o59e7e/ysk_the_difference_between_irony_and_sarcasm/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 02:08:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taken from dictionary.com:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Irony:&lt;/strong&gt; The use of words to convey a meaning that is the opposite of its literal meaning&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sarcasm:&lt;/strong&gt; Harsh or bitter derision or irony&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sarcasm is when you use irony to put up with a bad situation you are in, possibly sneering at the person you are talking with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It&amp;#39;s not the same. If you call your irony sarcasm, you might imply that you took offense in something or have other accusations. You might make an uneducated impression. You could also imply that something you said was meant to offend when it was not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A side note: Yes, the /s flag on reddit is used wrong 90% of the time. Most times, it&amp;#39;s actally irony and not sarcasm when people use it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: that you can YouTube videos without being intrurpted by adverts. If you skip the video to the end, hit the replay button that should restart the video without any adverts.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: you won't be intrurpted when watching YouTube video. By skipping all
the way to the end and replaying the video, it should get rid of all adverts
during that video. Make sure you have slid the video length bar all the way
across to the end and not a few seconds before.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o4m95p/ysk_that_you_can_youtube_videos_without_being/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o4m95p/ysk_that_you_can_youtube_videos_without_being/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 20:11:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: you won&amp;#39;t be intrurpted when watching YouTube video. By skipping all the way to the end and replaying the video, it should get rid of all adverts during that video. Make sure you have slid the video length bar all the way across to the end and not a few seconds before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that if your face flushes soon after you drink even a little alcohol, you might have alcohol intolerance.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK:

Alcohol intolerance, or acute alcohol sensitivity, is a pretty common condition.
It's especially common among those of East Asian descent, but is also present in
other populations. It's associated with symptoms like face flushing (sometimes
known as "Asian glow"), feeling warm, nausea, and…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o3wecb/ysk_that_if_your_face_flushes_soon_after_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o3wecb/ysk_that_if_your_face_flushes_soon_after_you/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 07:53:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alcohol intolerance, or acute alcohol sensitivity, is a pretty common condition.  It&amp;#39;s especially common among those of East Asian descent, but is also present in other populations. It&amp;#39;s associated with symptoms like face flushing (sometimes known as &amp;quot;Asian glow&amp;quot;), feeling warm, nausea, and a stuffy nose, among others.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the most part, it&amp;#39;s just uncomfortable, but there are some associated risk elevations.  According to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/17659-alcohol-intolerance&quot;&gt;Cleveland Clinic website&lt;/a&gt;, people with alcohol intolerance who drink alcohol regularly are at higher risk for throat and mouth cancer, liver disease, and Alzheimer&amp;#39;s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn&amp;#39;t realize this was a thing until I was maybe 23, and until then I wondered why I felt so uncomfortable after drinking even a small amount of alcohol.  Learning why I had such negative experiences with alcohol has helped me say no to drinks, because I know now that it&amp;#39;s an immediate ticket to discomfort.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;YSK that alcohol intolerance exists because it might be something you also experience, and if not, it might also help you understand why some people around you don&amp;#39;t want to drink.  While people shouldn&amp;#39;t need an excuse not to drink alcohol, it&amp;#39;s helpful to understand some of the reasons why people may make that choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that some restaurants on DoorDash and Grubhub are fake restaurants that chains put up to get more business]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: If you're trying to order food from local places it's best to look the
place up before ordering. There are several restaurants on DoorDash and GrubHub
that have names like "Just Wings", "Just Sliders and Pies", and "The Meltdown"
that are actually just Wingstop, Chilies, and Denny's…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o49d7o/ysk_that_some_restaurants_on_doordash_and_grubhub/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o49d7o/ysk_that_some_restaurants_on_doordash_and_grubhub/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 20:32:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If you&amp;#39;re trying to order food from local places it&amp;#39;s best to look the place up before ordering. There are several restaurants on DoorDash and GrubHub that have names like &amp;quot;Just Wings&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Just Sliders and Pies&amp;quot;, and &amp;quot;The Meltdown&amp;quot; that are actually just Wingstop, Chilies, and Denny&amp;#39;s masquerading as other restaurants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Links and sources: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.today.com/food/chuck-e-cheese-applebee-s-are-delivering-food-under-different-t181814&quot;&gt;https://www.today.com/food/chuck-e-cheese-applebee-s-are-delivering-food-under-different-t181814&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s Just Sliders &amp;amp; Pies
&lt;a href=&quot;https://yelp.to/Ghr3SKenfhb&quot;&gt;https://yelp.to/Ghr3SKenfhb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://foodondemandnews.com/03102021/qa-with-dennys-virtual-brand-leader-dave-coltrin/&quot;&gt;https://foodondemandnews.com/03102021/qa-with-dennys-virtual-brand-leader-dave-coltrin/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK about RunPee, the app that lets you know when you should run pee during movies]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: if you often need to pee during movies and don't want to miss out on
any important parts this is a great free solution. The app is up to date with
the latest movies and lets you know when is the right time to get out, it uses
subtle vibration to notify you and the UI is dark so it won't…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o44q9u/ysk_about_runpee_the_app_that_lets_you_know_when/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o44q9u/ysk_about_runpee_the_app_that_lets_you_know_when/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 18:55:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: if you often need to pee during movies and don&amp;#39;t want to miss out on any important parts this is a great free solution. The app is up to date with the latest movies and lets you know when is the right time to get out, it uses subtle vibration to notify you and the UI is dark so it won&amp;#39;t interupt anyone else&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: You can get rid of many allergies permanently]]></title><description><![CDATA[Immunotherapy for food and environmental allergies has existed for a number of
years now. Basically you're desensitizing your immune system using micro doses
of the allergen. There are two types of immunotherapy. One is an injection that
you do three times a week, and the other is drops you put…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o3su1j/ysk_you_can_get_rid_of_many_allergies_permanently/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o3su1j/ysk_you_can_get_rid_of_many_allergies_permanently/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 07:39:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Immunotherapy for food and environmental allergies has existed for a number of years now. Basically you&amp;#39;re desensitizing your immune system using micro doses of the allergen. There are two types of immunotherapy. One is an injection that you do three times a week, and the other is drops you put under the tongue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If your allergies really bother you, you could get them cured potentially.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personal story: It is worth pointing out that the FDA has not approved all types of the drops being used for allergies yet, despite Europe and the UK having used them for a decade. What this means is that if you are in the US, your insurance will not necessarily pay for the drops depending on your allergies. I mistakenly thought that this meant the shots would be easier. However you have to go in and pay the doctor to give you the shots, in person, since with them there is a risk of anaphylaxis. This in the long term made it more expensive than paying $100 for a 3-month supply of drops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mayoclinic.org/tests-procedures/allergy-shots/about/pac-20392876&quot;&gt;https://www.mayoclinic.org/tests-procedures/allergy-shots/about/pac-20392876&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/otolaryngology/specialty_areas/sinus_center/sublingual_immunotherapy.html&quot;&gt;https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/otolaryngology/specialty_areas/sinus_center/sublingual_immunotherapy.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/health/allergy-drops&quot;&gt;https://www.healthline.com/health/allergy-drops&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>