<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 04:40:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK if you're ever in a plane that crashes into water, DO NOT inflate your lifevest until you are outside the aircraft. Inflating your lifevest inside a sinking aircraft will cause you to float and become trapped.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: During the safety demonstrations on aircraft equipped for overwater
operations flight attendants will tell you to not inflate your lifevest until
outside the aircraft. This is not only because doing so in the aircraft will
take up space for other evacuees, but because in a rapidly filling…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pyqcze/ysk_if_youre_ever_in_a_plane_that_crashes_into/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pyqcze/ysk_if_youre_ever_in_a_plane_that_crashes_into/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 21:35:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; During the safety demonstrations on aircraft equipped for overwater operations flight attendants will tell you to not inflate your lifevest until outside the aircraft.  This is not only because doing so in the aircraft will take up space for other evacuees, but because in a rapidly filling aircraft your lifevest can cause you to become pinned to the ceiling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that if you struggle with extremely cold hands in the winter, your doctor may be able to help]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: I've struggled with numb/cold hands in quite literally any ambient
temperature less than 10C (50F) for most of my adult life. I had to use a
combination of mittens and chemical hand warmers for winter, because my hands
still wouldn't stay warm in regular gloves. I thought this was just a…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pym44m/ysk_that_if_you_struggle_with_extremely_cold/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pym44m/ysk_that_if_you_struggle_with_extremely_cold/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 17:44:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I&amp;#39;ve struggled with numb/cold hands in quite literally any ambient temperature less than 10C (50F) for most of my adult life. I had to use a combination of mittens and chemical hand warmers for winter, because my hands still wouldn&amp;#39;t stay warm in regular gloves. I thought this was just a miserable quirk that I couldn&amp;#39;t change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it came up at a doctor&amp;#39;s appointment randomly, the doc said that this is classic Raynaud&amp;#39;s Phenomenon (previously I thought that just meant purple hands, and mine were never as purple as the pictures), and that the issue with cold is absolutely treatable! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was put on an extremely low dose of a calcium channel blocker (hopefully &lt;a href=&quot;https://emedicine.medscape.com/article/331197-treatment&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; is an okay citation) to open my blood vessels a bit, and the doc said that alternatives are available if that isn&amp;#39;t enough. So far, though, I&amp;#39;ve have huge improvements in numbness and have been able to go without gloves in fall weather, which I could not do before!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, the bottom line - if you struggle with something like this, YOU ARE NOT DOOMED TO BE MISERABLE. It&amp;#39;s worth bringing up to a medical professional!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK Your employer can see everything you do on your work computer]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: The bigger your employer, the bigger their security budget and
regulatory compliance requirements AKA they have to keep more records, which
includes everything you do on your computer. I work in Cybersecurity &
Compliance, and the number of people who simply don't realize the…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pykc5x/ysk_your_employer_can_see_everything_you_do_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pykc5x/ysk_your_employer_can_see_everything_you_do_on/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 16:34:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: The bigger your employer, the bigger their security budget and regulatory compliance requirements AKA they have to keep more records, which includes everything you do on your computer. I work in Cybersecurity &amp;amp; Compliance, and the number of people who simply don&amp;#39;t realize the extensive tooling and visibility that is maintained on &amp;quot;company-issued&amp;quot; devices is too damn high. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This might sound like common-sense, and i used to think it was, but people use &amp;quot;incognito&amp;quot; or whatever and think its private - nothing is private on a managed device. 95% of my investigations always turn up something stupid someone did on their device, and yes, thats ammo in court if you&amp;#39;re ever in litigation. nuff said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that silent pauses are normal in a conversation; they don't always mean something is wrong. It's fairly typical for most of us to rush to fill in the silences, but learning how to be comfortable with silence will keep your foot out of your mouth and give you time to think.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Silence is considered to be negative by some people, but we need to
think of silence more as a way to slow down and think about our responses. It
helps if we can accept other people's silences as "time to think" instead of
"judgement" or "disagreement." Some of us tend to chatter when we're…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pybhf0/ysk_that_silent_pauses_are_normal_in_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pybhf0/ysk_that_silent_pauses_are_normal_in_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 05:43:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Silence is considered to be negative by some people, but we need to think of silence more as a way to slow down and think about our responses. It helps if we can accept other people&amp;#39;s silences as &amp;quot;time to think&amp;quot; instead of &amp;quot;judgement&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;disagreement.&amp;quot; Some of us tend to chatter when we&amp;#39;re nervous or whenever there&amp;#39;s a lull in the conversation, but filling the silence just clutters the conversation and interrupts whatever thoughts the speaker is putting together internally.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should also know that staying silent yourself from time to time during a conversation can give you a micro-dose of social power -- use it wisely, though, or it could be mistaken for arrogance or manipulation (because &amp;quot;the silent treatment&amp;quot; is juvenile and unproductive). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;tbc, I&amp;#39;m not suggesting long, uncomfortable, squirm-in-your-chair silences -- but pauses that are long enough to give you and others time to think before replying (something we don&amp;#39;t do enough). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many appropriate times to take a silent pause during a conversation. For example, &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Silence is quite effective when you&amp;#39;ve made a statement but someone wants to argue with you about it, especially if you didn&amp;#39;t say it to start a debate, such as a decision you&amp;#39;ve made or an opinion you hold. Your silence holds firm and solidifies your statement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Silence is also appropriate after asking someone a question, to give them time to think &amp;amp; process their answer. Consider, they may be going over several possible answers in their minds and need time to think, although we might feel impatient because we were already prepared with our question. Also, it&amp;#39;s not necessary to chatter on about the question while they&amp;#39;re thinking about it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Another useful time for silence is while listening to someone talk, which includes silencing your thoughts and mindfully listening instead of planning the next thing you want to say.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; It&amp;#39;s also respectful to be quiet for a few moments after someone has finished what they want to say about a topic, making sure they&amp;#39;re finished and that you&amp;#39;re digesting what they&amp;#39;ve said. Taking time before speaking shows that you were listening rather than waiting impatiently for your turn to speak.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Bags are like lottery tickets for thieves, and you should not leave them in your car.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Leaving backpacks, purses, briefcases, or other bags in your car is an
open invitation for window-smashing thieves. You can avoid having to replace
your windows, bags, and other stolen valuables by taking your bag with you or
putting it in your trunk instead – the few seconds it takes to do…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/py6pi7/ysk_bags_are_like_lottery_tickets_for_thieves_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/py6pi7/ysk_bags_are_like_lottery_tickets_for_thieves_and/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 03:36:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Leaving backpacks, purses, briefcases, or other bags in your car is an open invitation for window-smashing thieves. You can avoid having to replace your windows, bags, and other stolen valuables by taking your bag with you or putting it in your trunk instead – the few seconds it takes to do so is worth as much as what you paid for it, if not more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To a thief, a bag in a car is full of valuable stuff at best, and a new bag to cram other stolen stuff into at worst. Even if it looks empty, it could still have a laptop, a gun, a camera, a Nintendo Switch, or any number of other expensive, pawnable things in it. If it&amp;#39;s a designer bag, the bag itself may be worth selling. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t assume it won&amp;#39;t happen to you, especially if you live in a big city.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that in most jurisdictions the crime of assault means you threatened someone, not actually attacked them.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Every time there is a video of an idiot punching someone for no good reason or
spitting on them or otherwise making unlawful contact, all the comments yell
out: "That's assault!"

I know it's incredibly pedantic of me to be bothered by this, but that is a
battery. Yes, some jurisdictions have…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/py0sv5/ysk_that_in_most_jurisdictions_the_crime_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/py0sv5/ysk_that_in_most_jurisdictions_the_crime_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 02:14:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every time there is a video of an idiot punching someone for no good reason or spitting on them or otherwise making unlawful contact, all the comments yell out: &amp;quot;That&amp;#39;s assault!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know it&amp;#39;s incredibly pedantic of me to be bothered by this, but that is a battery. Yes, some jurisdictions have different definitions, but in most places and under common law, assault means a credible threat to commit a battery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: so that you use the correct legal term when describing the behavior of the lunatics in viral videos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK if I don't have the right of way, DON'T yield to me!]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know you are trying to be nice but your unpredictable driving can put other
people at risk.

Why YSK: While people not yielding when they should yield is much more common,
several times now since moving out to California when I've been waiting to pull
out from a parking lot I've had people hard…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/py6zmk/ysk_if_i_dont_have_the_right_of_way_dont_yield_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/py6zmk/ysk_if_i_dont_have_the_right_of_way_dont_yield_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 01:16:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know you are trying to be nice but your unpredictable driving can put other people at risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: While people not yielding when they should yield is much more common, several times now since moving out to California when I&amp;#39;ve been waiting to pull out from a parking lot I&amp;#39;ve had people hard brake on busy roads in order to let me &amp;quot;safely&amp;quot; make a left hand turn. The first time it happened I was taken off guard, but no one was behind the car that randomly decided to yield so it was ultimately fine. The second time on the other hand, multiple cars had to slam on their brakes to accommodate for the driver who randomly decided to stop in the middle of the road to let me turn. Now if I was edging out into the road, looking like I was going to dart in front of the incoming traffic, I could understand why people might slow down or even yield just to be safe, but on both occasions I was at a full stop and not in the main road at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once again, I know you&amp;#39;re trying to be polite but you&amp;#39;re just making the road more dangerous for other drivers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that men very rarely are on the receiving end of compliments (from men or women) and giving them one can absolutely change their entire day]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: as a woman, I love lifting other women up. I make it a personal goal to
give 10 compliments per day either in person or online BUT I very very rarely
compliment men due to past trauma from the hands of a man and now I have a
general fear of them. I am in therapy and working on it. Anyway,…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/py0fbz/ysk_that_men_very_rarely_are_on_the_receiving_end/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/py0fbz/ysk_that_men_very_rarely_are_on_the_receiving_end/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 19:43:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: as a woman, I love lifting other women up. I make it a personal goal to give 10 compliments per day either in person or online BUT I very very rarely compliment men due to past trauma from the hands of a man and now I have a general fear of them. I am in therapy and working on it. Anyway, today at the gym, a gentleman had a really cool shirt on that said “train everything” and it caught my eye. I didn’t say anything because I was scared I’d be seen as flirting or he’d see it as an excuse to flirt with ME and I didn’t want that. So I stayed silent. But, when I ran into him again at the water fountain I shoved my fears down and said &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Hey I really like your shirt!!! And it fits you so well!” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AND MY GOD YALL!!! The SMILE I got from this man! He was absolutely BEAMING. He just said “wow thank you so much!” And that was it. I couldn’t believe how incredibly happy he looked. I’ve seen that look from women before but not nearly as drastic. He looked like a starving man who was just offered a steak dinner. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It made me realize that while I am still very scared of men from my past trauma, 99% of them are just humans who deserve compliments just like women BUT… they don’t get them very often. Like it’s difficult for a cis man to compliment another man, especially on his body or attire, because it might be seen as &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;GASP&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; “gay”. And while that is an issue that also needs addressed, I think we, as women, can do our part too. Of course always stay safe and trust your gut, but let’s compliment some men together!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that most helmets (for biking, skateboarding, snowboarding, etc) have a stiff foam inside that crumples to absorb impact, but once it's crumpled, it doesn't bounce back. Your helmet will eventually stop protecting you after a few big falls.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: so you and your kids don't die.

Helmets are filled with what's called EPS foam (expanded polystyrene). EPS is a
very light but stiff foam similar to styrofoam. Once you deform or crush it, it
stays that way.

From epsindustry.org:

> Unlike other types of padding, EPS foam does not bounce…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pxqvzd/ysk_that_most_helmets_for_biking_skateboarding/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pxqvzd/ysk_that_most_helmets_for_biking_skateboarding/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 13:42:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: so you and your kids don&amp;#39;t die.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Helmets are filled with what&amp;#39;s called EPS foam (expanded polystyrene). EPS is a very light but stiff foam similar to styrofoam. Once you deform or crush it, it stays that way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From epsindustry.org:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike other types of padding, EPS foam does not bounce back after a compressing impact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This means it&amp;#39;s better at absorbing impact than a softer foam, which is good for protecting your head. But after an impact, that foam is crushed at that spot and no longer able to absorb any impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From off.road.cc:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to tiny impact after tiny impact over time, the EPS will gradually lose its volume making it less able to deal with the energy in the unfortunate event of an impact. Of course the more the helmet is used the more it will deteriorate, so one rule for all does not work here, but three years is a good guide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Replace your bike helmets after every big fall.
Replace your skateboard/ski/snowboard helmet after a few big falls.
Someone let me know about motorcycle helmets, I assume you wanna replace that after 1 fall.
Replace your helmets every 3 years even if you have no falls or minor falls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: Some great extra notes from the comments:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bike helmets are designs for 1 fall.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sturdier helmets like for skating or snowboarding can take a few more falls.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dropping your helmet is the same as falling on it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sources:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://epsindustry.org/other-applications/safety-devices&quot;&gt;http://epsindustry.org/other-applications/safety-devices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://off.road.cc/content/feature/when-should-you-replace-your-bicycle-helmet-1280&quot;&gt;https://off.road.cc/content/feature/when-should-you-replace-your-bicycle-helmet-1280&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Assume that the company you work for can see (and hear!) everything you do when you WFH.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: This information can be used to fire you, and to deny your
raise/promotion. Shortsighted HR departments are increasingly using this
software as the leading indicator of your value to the company above all else.

See the bottom of this post for things you can do to protect yourself from…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pxtjse/ysk_assume_that_the_company_you_work_for_can_see/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pxtjse/ysk_assume_that_the_company_you_work_for_can_see/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 13:42:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; This information can be used to fire you, and to deny your raise/promotion.  Shortsighted HR departments are increasingly using this software as the leading indicator of your value to the company &lt;em&gt;above all else.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See the bottom of this post for things you can do to protect yourself from this idiocy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why I wrote this:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was shocked at the response when I mentioned this concept in a prior comment.  Many people this affects are wholly unaware.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently, someone I know was fired FOR CAUSE due to their &amp;quot;lack of engagement, and unprofessional conduct.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a little insight into what that means by way of some work buddies, and personal review of the software that was used because her boss is a narcissistic assclown who was so proud of himself that he showed me the tools that were used.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This all began because the software on her computer flagged a word in a &amp;quot;private&amp;quot; Teams chat with a colleague which started the boss down a vindictive road of parallel construction - eventually lead to her termination.  That word was &amp;quot;ass.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A quick summary:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Bossware&amp;quot; has been something companies could use for over a decade, but the bastards have integrated other Orwellian stuff like facial recognition to monitor your mood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2020/06/inside-invasive-secretive-bossware-tracking-workers&quot;&gt;Here is an in-depth article about it from EFF.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theladders.com/wp-content/uploads/02-How-Employers-Monitor-Employees.png&quot;&gt;This is a one-pager about it.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/5JiyAfT.png&quot;&gt;This is a comparison of a handful of bossware&amp;#39;s features.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theladders.com/career-advice/bossware-report-when-wfh-means-the-boss-is-watching-what-bosses-see-how-to-prevent-it&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12% of all firms have already installed it (16% at larger firms), and 8% already plan to implement it (11% at larger firms). Tracking software like this has an ominously William Gibson-esque nickname: bossware.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, bosses may use unpublicized features of their corporate email package to look out for trigger words in your emails. Or they may use dedicated bossware to check that you’re actually at your computer when you say you are.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Employers can install hidden software on your device that tracks your movements via GPS, all SMS messages and other messaging app usage, and can even record calls and Skype interactions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There is a nonzero chance that:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your webcam is taking periodic screenshots, or even video of you and your surroundings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your mic is &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; &amp;quot;hot.&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your calls are &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; recorded.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your chats and emails are &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; scraped for keywords.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your keystrokes, and mouse movements are &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; tracked.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your &amp;quot;engagement&amp;quot; is &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; monitored to the millisecond.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I emphasize the word always because software doesn&amp;#39;t sleep.  Humans don&amp;#39;t see everything at all times.  The key here is that a human is flagged for nonsensical things by the software, and that human can really pick you apart from there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Some basic stuff you can do to protec&amp;#39; ya&amp;#39; neck:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shut your computer down after work.  A device that&amp;#39;s off has very low risk of snooping during time you don&amp;#39;t even get paid for &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reconsider having personal sidechats with your coworkers on company hardware.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cover your webcam when not in use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get your own headset with a hardware mute button and leave it muted until you need to speak.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Move your mouse if you are idle during a listening task like an all hands call.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Type things frequently.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;#39;t browse anything that isn&amp;#39;t 100% work related on company hardware.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All else fails - get another job, and let your boss know why after the new contract is signed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**Edited to add something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that staring straight and far ahead can combat car sickness.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Growing up I got super car sick all the time. Any drive over 10mins I would feel
nauseous and anything over 30 I would usually throw up. But a super helpful tip
I learned to combat it is looking straight ahead, this helps balance the fluids
in your ear that otherwise would cause car sickness. It…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pxqiuy/ysk_that_staring_straight_and_far_ahead_can/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pxqiuy/ysk_that_staring_straight_and_far_ahead_can/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 10:43:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Growing up I got super car sick all the time. Any drive over 10mins I would feel nauseous and anything over 30 I would usually throw up. But a super helpful tip I learned to combat it is looking straight ahead, this helps balance the fluids in your ear that otherwise would cause car sickness. It also helps to stare at something far ahead. Since it is far it seems to move less and is less visually nauseating. However car sickness medication can do wonders as-well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: sometimes you get carsick when you normally don’t and need to not throw up. Or you get carsick often and need help. Or you forgot the medicine you normally take. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also would love to hear more tips in the comments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK if you're looking to buy a smart thermostat, led light bulbs, or other energy saving products to check your electricity provider's website. They might have rebates on products that could save you a lot of money.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Here in Illinois we have ComEd that supplies our electricity. On their
website [https://secure.comed.com/marketplace/category/comed_smart_thermostats]
they also have a marketplace with a bunch of products that have instant rebates.
Right now you can get a Nest thermostat for $1 and most…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/px6pwi/ysk_if_youre_looking_to_buy_a_smart_thermostat/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/px6pwi/ysk_if_youre_looking_to_buy_a_smart_thermostat/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 09:17:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Here in Illinois we have ComEd that supplies our electricity. On their &lt;a href=&quot;https://secure.comed.com/marketplace/category/comed_smart_thermostats&quot;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; they also have a marketplace with a bunch of products that have instant rebates. Right now you can get a Nest thermostat for $1 and most other thermostats are $100 off. You can also save quite a bit of cash if you&amp;#39;re looking to replace your light bulbs with LEDs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK the rules for driving with semi trucks]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: The semi truck is an unforgiving and deadly beast, and failing to pay
respect to it may be the last thing you ever do. If something goes wrong (which
it does), and you are caught in the crossfire, you will die.

Rule #1: The semi always wins. Always.

Rule #2: When on the freeway, keep your…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pxfpha/ysk_the_rules_for_driving_with_semi_trucks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pxfpha/ysk_the_rules_for_driving_with_semi_trucks/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 02:39:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: The semi truck is an unforgiving and deadly beast, and failing to pay respect to it may be the last thing you ever do. If something goes wrong (which it does), and you are caught in the crossfire, you will die. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rule #1: &lt;strong&gt;The semi always wins. Always.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rule #2: When on the freeway, keep your distance from the semi. As a rule of thumb, if you can read the license plate, you&amp;#39;re too close. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rule #3: When passing, do so as quickly as possible. If they are passing you, slow down. If you are passing them, speed up. Driving next to a semi is one of the most dangerous places you can be for multiple reasons, and therefore is a place you don&amp;#39;t want to be. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rule #4: When lane-shifting in front of the semi, make sure that you do so at a safe distance. If you shift too close, you may scare the driver, and they may swerve to avoid you. In general, if you can see both of the semi&amp;#39;s headlights in your side mirror, you&amp;#39;re at a safe distance to move. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rule #5: The semi has very large blind spots. Don&amp;#39;t be in them. They can&amp;#39;t check their blind spots very well, so a lane shift may very well shove you off the road. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rule #6: Sometimes, semis will need to take &amp;quot;Wide turns&amp;quot;, which essentially means that they can&amp;#39;t use the rightmost lane to take a right turn-they need to move one over. If you are at an intersection and have a semi next to you, don&amp;#39;t start moving as soon as the light changes-wait to see if the semi makes the first move, and confirm where they are going before making yours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK Uber Eats no longer refunds cash for missing food. They only give “Uber cash” credits to your account.]]></title><description><![CDATA[WHY YSK: Normally restaurants will correct their mistake by giving you the right
food, taking something off the bill, or refunding a portion of your money. Real
cash is of course far more useful and less restrictive.

But Uber eats now only gives small Uber cash credits that can only be used…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/px9hfr/ysk_uber_eats_no_longer_refunds_cash_for_missing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/px9hfr/ysk_uber_eats_no_longer_refunds_cash_for_missing/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 18:49:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Normally restaurants will correct their mistake by giving you the right food, taking something off the bill, or refunding a portion of your money. Real cash is of course far more useful and less restrictive. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Uber eats now only gives small Uber cash credits that can only be used on their platform. They say they can no longer refund actual cash. Be careful when ordering for groups, as you have little recourse for restaurant mistakes now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: E-mails received that look like they are from legitimate companies like Amazon or PayPal that claim you have a problem with you account and ask you to log-in again, are scams.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why ysk: Scammers are plentiful on the Internet. I have recently been receiving
e-mails claiming that my account has been compromised or that they have noticed
some suspicious activity on my account or whatever else these scammers come up
with. If you open their e-mail it looks legitimate, but it's…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/px2aze/ysk_emails_received_that_look_like_they_are_from/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/px2aze/ysk_emails_received_that_look_like_they_are_from/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 14:42:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why ysk: Scammers are plentiful on the Internet. I have recently been receiving e-mails claiming that my account has been compromised or that they have noticed some suspicious activity on my account  or whatever else these scammers come up with. If you open their e-mail it looks legitimate, but it&amp;#39;s not. There are a lot of ways you can tell that an e-mail is a scam and if you want you can click &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/how-recognize-and-avoid-phishing-scams&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to find out more about how there phishing attacks work and recognize them so that you don&amp;#39;t fall victim to these scams.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What they usually want is for you to log-in so this way they can steal your information and then they can do whatever they want with it. If they steal, for example, your log-in information for your Amazon account, they will try and see if you have a credit card attached to your account and they end up stealing it. If you want to see more on how these scammers operate, there are a lot of YouTube videos that expose these scammers, I&amp;#39;d recommend &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FO9mWvJAugQ&quot;&gt;this person&lt;/a&gt; because he explains in-depth how they operate and he even manages to hack the scammers and scare them by showing their webcam or calling them by their real name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In summary, be careful on the internet, don&amp;#39;t trust unfamiliar sources and don&amp;#39;t open suspicious e-mails. Other ways you can protect yourself online is the use of better passwords and using different passwords for every website. You can read more about how to create better passwords &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcafee.com/blogs/enterprise/cloud-security/how-to-create-a-strong-password-you-actually-remember/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be careful out there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: There is a breathing technique that some literature suggests activates your parasympathetic nervous system, which is tied to your instinct to sleep after eating. It can be used to reduce anxiety, trigger relaxation, and fall asleep at will. It's called 4-7-8.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: While being able to sleep at will might come easy to some people, to
others (such as myself) it's very difficult. It's my hope that people who suffer
from chronic insomnia or issues falling asleep might be able to use this
technique to sleep more consistently. I also think it may prove a…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwypd6/ysk_there_is_a_breathing_technique_that_some/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwypd6/ysk_there_is_a_breathing_technique_that_some/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 06:36:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: While being able to sleep at will might come easy to some people, to others (such as myself) it&amp;#39;s very difficult. It&amp;#39;s my hope that people who suffer from chronic insomnia or issues falling asleep might be able to use this technique to sleep more consistently. I also think it may prove a useful tool for people who suffer constantly from issues like anxiety, stress, and panic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To perform the technique, first expel all air from your lungs, then do a deep inhale that lasts 4 seconds. With your lungs full of air, hold your breath for 7 seconds. Finally, exhale through your mouth (through your lips, making a whooshing sound) for 8 seconds. The ratio between the time of each step is more important than counting seconds accurately, so if you have trouble holding your breath, timing like 2, 3.5, and 4 might work too, although 4-7-8 is the most common recommendation and seems to elicit the most success. If you repeat the steps 2 or 3 times, your body should enter &amp;quot;rest and digest&amp;quot; mode, which may help you fall asleep quickly if you&amp;#39;re already in good sleeping conditions (comfortable, laying down, dark and quiet) or promote relaxation if you&amp;#39;re stressed or anxious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: The rule of 3’s for survival]]></title><description><![CDATA[As a general rule of thumb you can survive…

3 minutes without oxygen

3 hours without shelter in harsh environments

3 days without water

3 weeks without food

3 months without rescue

3 years without hope

Why YSK: This rule of 3s helps you remember what are priorities in times of
survival and…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwwc6b/ysk_the_rule_of_3s_for_survival/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwwc6b/ysk_the_rule_of_3s_for_survival/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 04:49:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a general rule of thumb you can survive…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 minutes without oxygen&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 hours without shelter in harsh environments &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 days without water&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 weeks without food&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 months without rescue&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 years without hope&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This rule of 3s helps you remember what are priorities in times of survival and which priorities are more important than others for a certain given time, this clearly isn’t 100% accurate but it’s a great general guide to go by and has saved many people and remembering it could save your life one day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that the Chrome browser now tracks if you're idle, and how to disable it.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: This is a setting that is enabled by default with the latest release.
The concern here is that knowing you're not looking at a particular screen is a
signal that sites can use on you, for good (pausing a video when you're not
watching), or bad (your job using it to track your activity).

If…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwuvxl/ysk_that_the_chrome_browser_now_tracks_if_youre/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwuvxl/ysk_that_the_chrome_browser_now_tracks_if_youre/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 02:37:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: 
This is a setting that is enabled by default with the latest release. The concern here is that knowing you&amp;#39;re not looking at a particular screen is a signal that sites can use on you, for good (pausing a video when you&amp;#39;re not watching), or bad (your job using it to track your activity).  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you use Chrome or Brave, here&amp;#39;s how to disable it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;chrome://settings/content/idleDetection&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look for &amp;quot;Don’t allow sites to know when you’re actively using your device&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK you should avoid using dryer sheets or fabric softener in the laundry when cleaning any moisture-wicking athletic wear, towels, athletic wear, flame-resistant or water-repellant clothes. These products block the “pores” of the fabric, reducing the moisture wicking capabilities.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Many people use fabric softener and/or dryer sheets with every load of
laundry. This is not advisable when cleaning athletic wear in order to keep the
athletic wear in optimal working condition.

https://www.latimes.com/bestcovery/best-dryer-sheets]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwkw2g/ysk_you_should_avoid_using_dryer_sheets_or_fabric/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwkw2g/ysk_you_should_avoid_using_dryer_sheets_or_fabric/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 23:28:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  Many people use fabric softener and/or dryer sheets with every load of laundry.  This is not advisable when cleaning athletic wear in order to keep the athletic wear in optimal working condition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.latimes.com/bestcovery/best-dryer-sheets&quot;&gt;https://www.latimes.com/bestcovery/best-dryer-sheets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK - Reddit is not a substitute for a therapist]]></title><description><![CDATA[Wish someone had told me this earlier. Why YSK: If you’re having issues, go talk
to someone who has the proper training to deal with whatever issue you’re
having, not some random person on the internet. More often than not you will get
unhelpful or wrong advice (or none at all, which only makes the…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwj4k1/ysk_reddit_is_not_a_substitute_for_a_therapist/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwj4k1/ysk_reddit_is_not_a_substitute_for_a_therapist/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 17:44:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wish someone had told me this earlier. Why YSK: If you’re having issues, go talk to someone who has the proper training to deal with whatever issue you’re having, not some random person on the internet. More often than not you will get unhelpful or wrong advice (or none at all, which only makes the problem worse)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: You shouldn’t hold too rigid opinions of the world and what is true or is not true]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK:

Interacting with a closed and supposedly static population results in very rigid
world views and misconceptions that make you close minded even though the new
information may actually be in your favour.

——

Societies pass on information to younger generations through education…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwf508/ysk_you_shouldnt_hold_too_rigid_opinions_of_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwf508/ysk_you_shouldnt_hold_too_rigid_opinions_of_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 15:39:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interacting with a closed and supposedly static population results in very rigid world views and misconceptions that make you close minded even though the new information may actually be in your favour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;——&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Societies pass on information to younger generations through education and interactions with them. This creates a thesaurus of “common knowledge”. The problem with “common knowledge” passed down from generations is that it is often filled with misconceptions and misunderstandings. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the outcome of multiple people with varying degrees of understanding and experiences providing a take, and you as a receiver only have a partial point of view of that information, and of the person disseminating it, so it is difficult for you to understand that person’s biases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, people tend to coalesce to communities of similar thoughts and behaviour. This is called “intellectual inbreeding”, where ideas are rehashed amongst a community and over time get perverted because the community doesn’t get exposed to new information or someone willing to provide counter arguments. This is such a major problem in science that top universities often don’t accept their own graduates (PhD or not) in positions and look for candidates from other universities, though exceptions exist. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, due to the brain’s plasticity, disseminating the same ideas as our group reinforces those ideas and causes them to become very rigid and fundamental parts of our world model.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we have a very rigid world view and we encounter a person who subscribes to fundamentally different ideas, our world view gets shaken exactly because it is very rigid, and we become unable to accept the new ideas regardless of correctness because our brain interprets the new information as an attack to itself and reality. This “attach”  physically manifests as narrow-mindedness in the brain and prevents us from accepting them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What can you do about it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cultivate a process in your brain that keeps challenging the status quo and actively and honestly tries to find mistakes in it. Read books/listen to podcasts, and have discussions with people of opposing views.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keep asking, what if I am wrong, why do I have this belief, and suppose a malevolent person disseminated this idea, what could they gain from it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Just because you are not a kid doesn’t mean that you can pick up new skills. Adults (and teens) can learn much faster than they believe if they understand how the brain learns new things]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: adults can learn things faster than what they believe, and learning new
things and skills can be a very satisfying process on its own, but many people
wished they had learned to play an instrument or some other skill but never do
something about it because they feel that “it is too late”.…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwfb0m/ysk_just_because_you_are_not_a_kid_doesnt_mean/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwfb0m/ysk_just_because_you_are_not_a_kid_doesnt_mean/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 14:46:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: adults can learn things faster than what they believe, and learning new things and skills can be a very satisfying process on its own, but many people wished they had learned to play an instrument or some other skill but never do something about it because they feel that “it is too late”. It isn’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, how do I do that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is this common misconception that just because you are older and the brain doesn’t “learn as fast”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this is true by some regards, kids don’t learn in the same way as adults do. Kids learn by imitating actions from their environment, they can do that because their brain has significantly more synapses(=connections between brain cells) than adults, so it’s easier for the brain to find the right pathway and reinforce it while pruning “wrong” synapses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In contrast, adults have preexisting synapses that have been reinforced for a long time and so it’s significantly harder to learn by imitation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But adults also have a significantly better world model (=understanding of the world), and significantly more developed frontal cortex (=rational thinking and control of functions and behaviour). This means that by employing pre existing knowledge and understanding you can attain a much better understanding of the skill you are trying to learn than kids. This, then means that you can explore and generate new “actions” and behaviour much better than kids because you have better understanding of what is going on under it. By doing that consciously you will be able to turn the actually “correct” and “high quality” conscious actions into subconscious actions that are second nature. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, even learning itself and creativity are skills that can be trained for (as a grad student with publications from undergrad, and a lot of original work, who has ventured into other fields in her own time because she found it interesting, I recommend the Feynman method with flashcards and extensive notes).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The brain is a very strong pattern matching and creative computer. It’s a shame that many people live with regrets of not learning to play instruments or some other skill. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some authors that I can recommend:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Kahneman (eg. “Thinking fast and slow”)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  David Eagleman (eg. “Livewired”, ”the brain”)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Robert Sapolsky (eg “Behave”, “why zebras don’t get ulcers”)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Elizier Yudkowsky (eg “Inadequate equilibria”)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Lieberman and Long (The molecule of more)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Oliver Sacks (eg “The man who mistook his wife for a hat”, “Hallucinations”, “On the river of consciousness”)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry for reposting, the title had a typo…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit:
This one has a typo as well. Jesus Christ today. Sorry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK if you're given a school or county-based Chromebook, how to bypass website admin blocks.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Us students know schools go absolutely overboard on website
restrictions. Completely locked down with browser management extensions and
admin blocks. For gosh-sake sometimes I just wanna scroll Reddit or watch Twitch
when there's nothing else going on. And for those of you who a school…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pusbj0/ysk_if_youre_given_a_school_or_countybased/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pusbj0/ysk_if_youre_given_a_school_or_countybased/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 13:31:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Us students know schools go absolutely overboard on website restrictions. Completely locked down with browser management extensions and admin blocks. For gosh-sake sometimes I just wanna scroll Reddit or watch Twitch when there&amp;#39;s nothing else going on. And for those of you who a school Chromebook is the only access you have to internet, you&amp;#39;re going to want to take a break and relax sometimes. Without further delay, here&amp;#39;s how to bypass website blocks on school Chromebooks on which website &amp;quot;security&amp;quot; is managed by extensions&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1: Google search the website you want to visit. Don&amp;#39;t click the link yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2: In the top right corner you should see three vertical dots. Click that&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3: Head over to more tools and click task manager&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4: End the processes associated with your Chromebook&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;security&amp;quot; (e.g. cisco umbrella extension) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5: After that, quickly click the website you want to visit. Do this fast as the &amp;quot;security&amp;quot; processes reinstate themselves and you may have to spam &amp;#39;end process&amp;#39; multiple times for the request to go through. Refresh the page and end &amp;quot;security&amp;quot; extensions as needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once the website loads in, you should not have to spam close the &amp;quot;security&amp;quot; extensions, and most of the website features should run as normal. You should also be able to visit those websites in the future without having to complete the process above. The only exception Ive seen where consistent buffering occurs is crunchyroll and the Reddit media player.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope this helps some people :D&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: This solution only works if your school didn&amp;#39;t block task manager. If they did, you gotta resort to a dual boot process off an external drive if your processor supports windows/linux&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t exactly know the process, but I&amp;#39;m sure you could find a youtube video that shows you how to do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AMD and Intel processors support both Windows 10 and some versions of Linux.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you to &lt;a href=&quot;/u/enderwiggin42&quot;&gt;u/enderwiggin42&lt;/a&gt; for the info!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: If you want to make sure your egg is hard boiled before you crack it open you can spin it on a flat surface.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: If it spins quickly it means that the inside is now solid and your egg
is done. If it spins slowly and/or wobbles that means part of it is still liquid
and you should boil it for longer.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwejx8/ysk_if_you_want_to_make_sure_your_egg_is_hard/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwejx8/ysk_if_you_want_to_make_sure_your_egg_is_hard/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 13:31:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If it spins quickly it means that the inside is now solid and your egg is done. If it spins slowly and/or wobbles that means part of it is still liquid and you should boil it for longer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: before you decide you don’t like a fruit/vegetable, try heirloom or locally grown]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: most fruits and vegetables sold in supermarkets are mass farmed
varieties and are picked well before they’re ripe, then shipped across the
country, or world.

Commonly sold fruits and vegetables, such as red delicious apples and carrots,
are devoid of flavor and turn lots of people off of…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pw3dqc/ysk_before_you_decide_you_dont_like_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pw3dqc/ysk_before_you_decide_you_dont_like_a/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 10:58:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: most fruits and vegetables sold in supermarkets are mass farmed varieties and are picked well before they’re ripe, then shipped across the country, or world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Commonly sold fruits and vegetables, such as red delicious apples and carrots, are devoid of flavor and turn lots of people off of them forever. Locally sourced varieties, which are in season, are so much better that they scarcely qualify as the same thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK if your tooth gets knocked out you can save it following these important steps. (Important first aid information)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: I’m a dentistry student and it came to my attention that not a lot of
people know you can save your tooth if it gets knocked out and it can grow back
alive. For example in a fight or (sport)accident. If you don’t follow these
steps it reduces the chance of survival of your tooth…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pw3m1h/ysk_if_your_tooth_gets_knocked_out_you_can_save/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pw3m1h/ysk_if_your_tooth_gets_knocked_out_you_can_save/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 23:31:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I’m a dentistry student and it came to my attention that not a lot of people know you can save your tooth if it gets knocked out and it can grow back alive. For example in a fight or (sport)accident. If you don’t follow these steps it reduces the chance of survival of your tooth drastically. When it dies it becomes brown-ish and it has a short life span.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A tooth is a living part of your body. The inner part of the tooth is called the pulpa. The pulpa consists of nerves, bloodvessels, stemcells and this can die. When this happens the lifespan of the tooth is short (around &amp;lt;10 years) and will eventually require an implant or a bridge because it will fall out. When your tooth gets knocked out (or you see one getting knocked out) it is important to follow these steps:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;pick the tooth up by the crown (chewing surface). Never touch the root! These are surrounded by specialised cells which can be destroyed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inspect the tooth: is it covered in dirt? 
—&amp;gt; yes: rinse with milk or your own(!) saliva. By pouring the milk on it or spitting your saliva on it. (Clean drinkable (not tap water)) water works too. Still don’t touch or wipe the root and don’t use chemicals like soap!
If not this step can be skipped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preserve the tooth in a save environment.
There are several ways to do this:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a. (Best option) - look at the tooth. What is the front and what is the back? Place it back correctly and hold it in place with a rag (or something  soft which is similar, like toilet paper or a piece of clothing). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;b. When this is not possible because the person is either a child (because they can swallow it) unconcious, jaw is broken, or you don’t know where it belongs because several teeth are out: collect saliva of the person it belongs to (!) in a clean cup (or something similar which is clean like a cap of a waterbottle) and put it gently in there. It should be completely covered in saliva (blood doesn’t matter). Milk works too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;c. Put it in your mouth between the cheek and your teeth with your mouth closed. Don’t touch it with your tongue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contact a dentist. He needs to prepare an emergency. You need to go there asap. The dentist will clean the tooth, put it back and spalk it temporarily. This is not expensive (ask if this concerns you). After a few weeks you need to go back to see if the tooth survived. Often more than not it will survive when the above steps are done correctly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Important:
Never put back baby teeth. This might damage the gums. Not sure? Follow 3b or 3c.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only the person where the knocked out  belongs to can use his own saliva to rinse or clean it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You need to go to the dentist as soon as possible (within an hour)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Putting soap into a public water fountain to make a bunch of foam is not a harmless prank, it damages most fountain pumps and costs a ton to repair]]></title><description><![CDATA[Every year we see posts with some kids or drunks deciding it would be fun to
throw a little soap into a public fountain, and watch the chaos ensue. Sounds
silly and fun, and an impromptu suds dance party will just take a little extra
water to clean up so no harm, right?

Fountains use specialized…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pw27nj/ysk_putting_soap_into_a_public_water_fountain_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pw27nj/ysk_putting_soap_into_a_public_water_fountain_to/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 22:40:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every year we see posts with some kids or drunks deciding it would be fun to throw a little soap into a public fountain, and watch the chaos ensue. Sounds silly and fun, and an impromptu suds dance party will just take a little extra water to clean up so no harm, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fountains use specialized water pumps which are designed to keep lubricated even when in constant use with plain water. Unfortunately, the soap works to destroy the seals and strip the pump motors of their protective lubrication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is one major reason there are very few public water fountains anymore. One or two attacks, and most cash-strapped facilities opt to drain the fountain and let the thing rot until they can afford to dismantle it altogether.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fountains on the Lee Clarion University campus in Cleveland, Tennessee are historically prone to vandalism. One particular event in August 2010 cost the university $1,000 in materials alone to drain the fountain, clean all surfaces, chemically remove the suds and flush the pipes, not to mention add important chemicals back in to prevent algae growth and keep the water crystal clear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More recently in July 2014, a soaped fountain in Eau Claire, Wisconsin kept city workers busy for days cleaning up the mess. Crews had to clean out the whole fountain, backwash the filters, rinse, wash and repeat multiple times before all the soap was cleared out of the system. It took hours of manpower and several days before the fountain was back up and running.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.groundsguys.com/blog/2015/august/you-ve-been-soaped-now-what-/&quot;&gt;the Grounds Guys&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obligatory Why YSK: if your friends suggest damaging communal property just because they think it&amp;#39;s harmless, you may convince them to find something else is a better outlet for their energy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 3000 mile oil changes that are still so popular in the USA are a myth and a waste of money.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK. I'm a British expat who moved to the USA 5 years ago. On every street
corner is a quick oil change place and I found out almost everyone changes their
oil at 3000 miles.

Why is this a waste?

 1. This is a myth purported from the 60s and 70s, car engine technology and oil
    technology…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pvrtfo/ysk_3000_mile_oil_changes_that_are_still_so/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pvrtfo/ysk_3000_mile_oil_changes_that_are_still_so/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 12:50:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK. I&amp;#39;m a British expat who moved to the USA 5 years ago. On every street corner is a quick oil change place and I found out almost everyone changes their oil at 3000 miles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why is this a waste?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a myth purported from the 60s and 70s, car engine technology and oil technology has evolved greatly since then and engines go longer between oil changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most cars in the US have engines that are used worldwide. For example, Ford engines used in cars in American are manufactured and used worldwide. Oil change intervals for these same engines are 10,000 miles +&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most cars since about 2010 will notify you when an oil change is due, based on environmental and driving conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source? I&amp;#39;m an ex Automotive filter development engineer and ex Ford development engineer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK not liking something doesn’t mean disliking it]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: often people ask questions like “Do you like X?” and many people will
automatically assume you dislike X when you say no. Sometimes it just means you
are neutral, don’t care or don’t know enough to either like or dislike something
or someone.

I think people should know because we live in a…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pvbrsh/ysk_not_liking_something_doesnt_mean_disliking_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pvbrsh/ysk_not_liking_something_doesnt_mean_disliking_it/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 04:22:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: often people ask questions like “Do you like X?” and many people will automatically assume you dislike X when you say no. Sometimes it just means you are neutral, don’t care or don’t know enough to either like or dislike something or someone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think people should know because we live in a more and more polarized society and people more often fail to nuance that things aren’t always either this OR that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK, while trying on clothes in a store, make sure to sit down to confirm fit and comfort]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK, it's easy to see and feel whether clothes fit while standing... so I
used to think when I was younger. But to make sure that clothes fit and are
comfortable, make sure to sit down while you are trying them on]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pviwo5/ysk_while_trying_on_clothes_in_a_store_make_sure/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pviwo5/ysk_while_trying_on_clothes_in_a_store_make_sure/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 01:56:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK, it&amp;#39;s easy to see and feel whether clothes fit while standing... so I used to think when I was younger. But to make sure that clothes fit and are comfortable, make sure to sit down while you are trying them on&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: You can bring a tab in your browser back if you accidentally closed it]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: I have accidentaylly closed so many tabs in my lifetime and it seems
quite common for people to not know that you can just hit:

Shift control T

If you're on Mac it's

Shift command T

Too many people seem to accept it's gone forever and spend a lot of time getting
back to the website they…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pvee8e/ysk_you_can_bring_a_tab_in_your_browser_back_if/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pvee8e/ysk_you_can_bring_a_tab_in_your_browser_back_if/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 01:56:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I have accidentaylly closed so many tabs in my lifetime and it seems quite common for people to not know that you can just hit:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shift control T&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#39;re on Mac it&amp;#39;s&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shift command T&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Too many people seem to accept it&amp;#39;s gone forever and spend a lot of time getting back to the website they were once on so hopefully this saves some people some time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK These websites to get FREE textbooks and solution manuals]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: I regret paying hard copies of all my books, especially after an online
year. Here is where you can usually find them without paying a cent.


LIBRARY GENESIS

This is the go-to site for most ebooks. Some of the engineering textbooks comes
with the solution manual as well. Searching for the…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pvaqms/ysk_these_websites_to_get_free_textbooks_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pvaqms/ysk_these_websites_to_get_free_textbooks_and/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 21:01:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I regret paying hard copies of all my books, especially after an online year. Here is where you can usually find them without paying a cent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Library Genesis&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the go-to site for most ebooks. Some of the engineering textbooks comes with the solution manual as well. Searching for the title + &amp;quot;solution manual&amp;quot; will give you some results. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Ch36650lut10n5 (cheggsolutions)&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A website which has textbook solutions ripped from chegg. It has quite a lot of books and free, no need to sign up or give any credentials. You can find many textbook solutions that are not on libgen or zlibrary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Zlibrary&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is another site where you can try if you can&amp;#39;t find it in Library Genesis.
You may need an account if you exceed the download limit. If you do not like to use your personal email, you can opt to use a temporary mail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Slader&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for textbook solutions for free, check Slader. You have to sign up to access materials, after that you can access many solution manuals written by teachers and professors. 
They recently installed a limit, trying to make access to answers a paid service unfortunately. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Studylib&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the name itself says it’s like a library, where you can have a large number of assignments and solutions. You can also share your notes with your friends which would help them to solve the problems. It will provide you with a solution for all the subjects. You can also upload your documents and find the solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Pdfdrive&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An online PDF search engine that lets you search, preview and download PDFs. According to the site as of right now, there are over 75 million eBooks, magazines, articles, and more that are indexed and discoverable directly on PDF Drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Sci-Hub&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great place for finding published journal/conference papers that are (usually) paywalled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;AudioBookBay&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If what you want is audiobooks then audiobookbay is the go-to place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good luck on your new semester everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Human Resources is not "Resources for Humans"]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Your company views you as a commodity and has an HR team to ensure that
the company stays in compliance with all laws and they do not get sued by their
possessions. If you're bringing a complaint to HR they will immediately look to
protect themselves legally. They will NOT instinctively…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pvciam/ysk_human_resources_is_not_resources_for_humans/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pvciam/ysk_human_resources_is_not_resources_for_humans/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 19:56:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Your company views you as a commodity and has an HR team to ensure  that the company stays in compliance with all laws and they do not get  sued by their possessions. If you&amp;#39;re bringing a complaint to HR they will immediately look to protect themselves legally. They will NOT instinctively look to protect you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your HR rep is on your company&amp;#39;s side. Not yours. Not ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: If a company makes a mistake in charging you and tries to reimburse you in coupons, you should probably not accept it]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Coupons are designed in the interest of the company not you. You're
probably getting a bad deal from it.

Some restaurant tried to reimburse the "mistake" in overcharging us with
coupons.

Might look nice on the surface but its not. Aside from expiry date, there are
many huge limitations…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pv857p/ysk_if_a_company_makes_a_mistake_in_charging_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pv857p/ysk_if_a_company_makes_a_mistake_in_charging_you/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 18:05:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Coupons are designed in the interest of the company not you. You&amp;#39;re probably getting a bad deal from it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some restaurant tried to reimburse the &amp;quot;mistake&amp;quot; in overcharging us with coupons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Might look nice on the surface but its not. Aside from expiry date, there are many huge limitations such as only being able to use one coupon each time (small amount) AFTER spending a certain amount. So basically I need to spend more at your place for your mistake? Who the hell do you think you are here?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s always a lot of &amp;quot;fine print&amp;quot; when it comes to coupons. Think of it on the lines of &amp;quot;Itchy and Scratchy money&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Get the transactions cancelled or ask them to pay in cash. Or something else! Don&amp;#39;t just lie down and let them get away with it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK That “calling out” someone as having a logical fallacy can be as much of a problem as what you are trying to identify. Recognising fallacies should be used to improve your communication, not as a tool to shut down conversations you don’t like]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK I have had a few attempts recently to talk to groups about controversial
topics, and instead of discussion just got a lot of accusations about being a
troll and had everything I said labeled as a logical fallacy, effectively
shutting down the conversation.

Try not to use these terms and…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pv537y/ysk_that_calling_out_someone_as_having_a_logical/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pv537y/ysk_that_calling_out_someone_as_having_a_logical/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 13:33:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK    I have had a few attempts recently to talk to groups about controversial topics, and instead of discussion just got a lot of accusations about being a troll and had everything I said labeled as a logical fallacy, effectively shutting down the conversation.    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Try not to use these terms and explain what you mean in plain language.   Posting “that is a Strawman argument” adds nothing.  Posting “people don’t believe X like you said, they believe various things from Y to Z, which makes your argument wrong” says what you actually mean and allows for ongoing discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have no term to describe it, but the practice of labelling every view you disagree with as a logical fallacy is definitely a rhetorical fallacy that should be avoided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK how to measure with an accuracy of a sixteenth of an inch using a ruler or measuring tape]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Many things that you will need to cut with scissors, a knife, or a saw
will need to be precisely measured first. In many trades and professions in the
United States, a sixteenth of an inch is accurate enough to be considered exact.

It's extremely difficult to explain in text how to read a…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/puvoxb/ysk_how_to_measure_with_an_accuracy_of_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/puvoxb/ysk_how_to_measure_with_an_accuracy_of_a/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 12:53:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Many things that you will need to cut with scissors, a knife, or a saw will need to be precisely measured first. In many trades and professions in the United States, a sixteenth of an inch is accurate enough to be considered exact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s extremely difficult to explain in text how to read a ruler or measuring tape down to the sixteenth of an inch, but &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l3Nv1mjof-I&quot;&gt;this video does an accurate job&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: If someone offers you a breath mint/gum, you should always accept it.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: They may be hinting that your breath is offensive and needs to be
addressed. The worst that happens is you get a few extra calories (or they
poison you idk).]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/puq9gv/ysk_if_someone_offers_you_a_breath_mintgum_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/puq9gv/ysk_if_someone_offers_you_a_breath_mintgum_you/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 19:56:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: They may be hinting that your breath is offensive and needs to be addressed. The worst that happens is you get a few extra calories (or they poison you idk).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that Apple's new Mail Privacy Protection feature will flag your email address as valid to any marketer (or scammer).]]></title><description><![CDATA[If you use the Apple Mail App and enable MPP, here’s what happens: Apple first
routes emails through a proxy server to pre-load message content—including
tracking pixels—before serving it to you. This happens even if you don’t
actually open those emails.

This means that when you open an email, you…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pu7y8k/ysk_that_apples_new_mail_privacy_protection/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pu7y8k/ysk_that_apples_new_mail_privacy_protection/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 17:13:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you use the Apple Mail App and enable MPP, here’s what happens: Apple first routes emails through a proxy server to pre-load message content—including tracking pixels—before serving it to you. This happens even if you don’t actually open those emails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This means that when you open an email, you essentially access Apple&amp;#39;s version instead of the sender&amp;#39;s, disguising your IP address and time of opening to the sender.  However, when Apple initially downloads the images, it sends a signal to the sender that their email has reached a valid and active address. This has the potential to actually &lt;em&gt;increase&lt;/em&gt; the amount of unwanted emails you receive, as a scammer will know they&amp;#39;ve hit a live address and will undoubtedly make use of it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; To help you make an informed decision about your privacy. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; This is my understanding of the following article by Magan Le at Litmus &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.litmus.com/blog/apple-mail-privacy-protection-for-marketers/&quot;&gt;https://www.litmus.com/blog/apple-mail-privacy-protection-for-marketers/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that you should not rinse your mouth out after you brush your teeth.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: in movies and tv people always rinse their mouth out after brushing
their teeth. But rinsing your mouth after you brush rinses away all the good
stuff that protects them like fluoride. If you must rinse, take a small sip of
water and swish it around your teeth like mouthwash and…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/puaq66/ysk_that_you_should_not_rinse_your_mouth_out/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/puaq66/ysk_that_you_should_not_rinse_your_mouth_out/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 15:37:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: in movies and tv people always rinse their mouth out after brushing their teeth. But rinsing your mouth after you brush rinses away all the good stuff that protects them like fluoride. If you must rinse, take a small sip of water and swish it around your teeth like mouthwash and spit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.oralanswers.com/rinse-after-brushing/&quot;&gt;https://www.oralanswers.com/rinse-after-brushing/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK how to avoid killing animals with your car.]]></title><description><![CDATA[why YSK: avoid death, suffering, guilt, a potential car accident, and potential
vehicle damage.



the first thing you need to know about how to avoid hitting an animal is to
expect the animal to be on the road before it's on the road. complacency is the
thing that kills most animals that wander…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/puhs4j/ysk_how_to_avoid_killing_animals_with_your_car/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/puhs4j/ysk_how_to_avoid_killing_animals_with_your_car/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 12:59:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;why YSK: avoid death, suffering, guilt, a potential car accident, and potential vehicle damage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the first thing you need to know about how to avoid hitting an animal is to expect the animal to be on the road before it&amp;#39;s on the road. complacency is the thing that kills most animals that wander onto a road. COMPLACENCY is also the thing that kills most HUMANS on the road. imagine you&amp;#39;re just driving, chilling, listening to music, and suddenly there&amp;#39;s some random animal in your way and because this is such an oddity in your life your brain does not come up with a solution quickly enough. if you simulate the scenario in your mind before it happens you will be able to react accordingly, minimizing potential losses without risk to yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-if you drive at night this is relatively simple. most animal and vehicle crashes occur between the hours of 5PM and midnight. be on the lookout for animals if you drive during these times, but &lt;em&gt;especially&lt;/em&gt; if you&amp;#39;re driving while it&amp;#39;s dark out. and remember not to limit your view to what&amp;#39;s immediately in front of you. you should be aiming to look down the road 10 to 15 seconds ahead of your vehicle in order to avoid any last minute moves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;this is the thing you need to know about animals on the road: 99% of the time you encounter an animal on the road, the animal will stop in the middle of the road and/or turn around after noticing your car. the headlights confuse their dark-adjusted eyes and signal that there is imminent danger, and their brain tells them to retreat. you must anticipate this. to see this for yourself, if you look up &amp;quot;russ lepage deer&amp;quot; on google you&amp;#39;ll be directed to a video that shows a close call with an automated tesla driver and a deer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;(I would like to mention that the vehicle in this video made a lane change that I would consider too sharp for comfort, and making a split second decision to switch lanes like that is not ideal. this is not a demonstration, but it is some footage for you to get yourself acquainted with the idea of having an animal stuck in your headlights because it is a textbook encounter and should better prepare you for the situation. do not try to replicate the technique shown here. instead, read on.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;so, animals don&amp;#39;t know what&amp;#39;s on the other side of the road. they only know the area they came from. when they see your scary car, their instinct is to go back to safety. which means they&amp;#39;ll literally spin around and go back, and this will even happen if they&amp;#39;ve already safely made it to the other side of the road. all animals are guilty of this. raccoons, foxes, deer, cats, squirrels, it doesn&amp;#39;t matter. in a pinch, they will always go back to the side of the road they entered from. they will not move forward into an unknown area after realizing they&amp;#39;re in danger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&amp;#39;the maneuver&amp;#39;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;identify animal in your field of vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;take your foot off of the accelerator pedal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;switch lanes if possible in a controlled manner. do not act with haste. you must not make any sudden or sharp movements. if you are close to the animal, you want to switch to the lane that they came from. if you are far away or very close, do not switch lanes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;always slow down. if you are switching lanes, begin to slow down halfway into your transition from one side of the road to the other. do not brake and switch lanes at the same time. do not slam the brakes. do not brake in a way that would cause your vehicle to skid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;on switching lanes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;~8&lt;/strong&gt; seconds seconds of time to react: in the video I referenced, it is a close call. but if this was in reality, you can clearly see the deer coming a mile away. the correct choice in that instance would be to simply slow down upon spotting the deer and alerting the animal and drivers behind you that something is up by hitting your car horn. no need to switch lanes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;~&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; seconds of time to react: in an instance where you have less time to react to the animal where it is directly in front of you, you are looking to switch lanes so that you pass the animal before it is making the active decision to turn around. the animal is also more likely to make a better decision if it can see the trajectory of your vehicle. it cannot properly see your trajectory if you are heading straight towards it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;~&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; seconds of time to react: if you ever have a very short amount of time to react to an animal on the road unfortunately the best course of action is to slow down as much as possible without losing control of your vehicle, drive straight, and brace yourself for impact. do not attempt to change the trajectory of your vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(note that these numbers are just approximations. I&amp;#39;m not a driving expert. I am only trying to help you make the decision to switch lanes for yourself)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;tips:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;constantly check your blind spot and your left/right mirrors&lt;/strong&gt; as you are driving so you can prematurely know if you&amp;#39;re able to switch lanes on the fly if necessary. this is a helpful driving tip in general and you can avoid vehicle collisions this way as well. you may need to react quickly and not have time to check for cars on the other lane. this does not mean recklessly switch lanes without looking. it means that if you know for certain there are no cars in your way, you will be able to use the other lane to your advantage if the need arises.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;always slow down&lt;/strong&gt; if you identify an obstacle in your path (such as an animal, or another car, or a human being) there is no reason to ever not slow down. do not slam the breaks. just slow down like you normally would in a timely manner. the slower you are going, the more control you have over your vehicle. if you crash into a massive animal such as a moose or a large buck, the faster you are going the more likely you are to suffer a fatal collision. with moose, it is not much different than crashing into another vehicle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;combine tip #1 and #2.&lt;/strong&gt; just make sure that this is not done in a panic. it must be a calculated maneuver. if you make too sharp of a turn and your brakes are engaged too aggressively you could flip your car or lose control of your vehicle and spiral out of control, and kill or injure yourself and other drivers around you. and just to reiterate what I&amp;#39;ve said before, don&amp;#39;t begin to brake until you are at least halfway into your lane change. just make sure you take your foot off the accelerator before doing anything.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;do not swerve&lt;/strong&gt;. swerving is a last ditch effort and extremely dangerous. if you are going to change your trajectory to avoid an incoming collision, you must do it in a similar manner as if you were turning to switch lanes. any abrupt changes to the steering wheel at high speeds will severely and negatively impact the stability of your vehicle. this is why the previously mentioned tips are so useful. if you practice them you should not ever feel the need to swerve. animals do not usually run onto the road so spontaneously that you would need to swerve, rather we react so slowly to these situations that we may impulsively feel like swerving because we ran out of time, failed to make a decision, and panicked. on the other hand people may panic and decide to crash into an animal that they could have avoided if they were better prepared. you should expect to have around 5 seconds of time to react to an animal that has suddenly tried to cross the road, on average. 5 seconds is enough time to make a decision and execute it while on the road, provided that you were paying attention and not drifting off while manning a vehicle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;stay the speed limit while driving at night&lt;/strong&gt;. animals will not be able to react properly to anything that is going significantly faster than your average wildlife predator. if you&amp;#39;re driving in a 65mph zone, drive 65mph. it&amp;#39;s night time. you are in no rush to get home. don&amp;#39;t put animal lives in jeopardy in order to save yourself a meaningless amount of time. speed inhibits control of the vehicle. the faster you&amp;#39;re going, the longer it takes to slow down and the more vulnerable your vehicle&amp;#39;s stability is to sudden movements, and the more likely you are to get in an accident and/or run over an animal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;every time you get out of the driveway always go and personally seek out your surroundings&lt;/strong&gt; to check for animals or people around you before you get in the car, even if you live in a populated neighborhood. it is not uncommon to run over a baby duck, baby rabbit, kitten, or frog while backing out of a driveway, and they are too small for you to notice them in your mirrors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would like everyone to remind everyone to never forget how powerful a vehicle is and how weak living things are in comparison. as the years go by you get used to these machines. complacency is a killer. do not ever get used to driving a vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: About the site https://www.doesthedogdie.com/]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: On this site you can search for a movie or series and look if there is
any content that might be hard for you to watch. As the name suggests you can
look if a dog dies in a movie/serie but it also covers other topics like
spiders, vomit, torture, rape or cancer. The site collects…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pu41p9/ysk_about_the_site_httpswwwdoesthedogdiecom/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pu41p9/ysk_about_the_site_httpswwwdoesthedogdiecom/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 03:45:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: On this site you can search for a movie or series and look if there is any content that might be hard for you to watch. As the name suggests you can look if a dog dies in a movie/serie but it also covers other topics like spiders, vomit, torture, rape or cancer. The site collects information about more than 80 topics and if there is anything you dont want to see, you should know about this site to see if you can watch a movie or series.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK about Fundamental Attribution Error, and how it can affect how you see the world and people around you.]]></title><description><![CDATA[YSK about Fundamental Attribution Error which is the tendency for humans to
justify our own behaviour or situation because we know the environmental factors
that have caused them, but to assume another person’s behaviour or situation is
indicative of who they are as a person without consideration to…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pu4srn/ysk_about_fundamental_attribution_error_and_how/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pu4srn/ysk_about_fundamental_attribution_error_and_how/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 03:10:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;YSK about Fundamental Attribution Error which is the tendency for humans to justify our own behaviour or situation because we know the environmental factors that have caused them, but to assume another person’s behaviour or situation is indicative of who they are as a person without consideration to environmental factors. One of the worst instances of this is victim blaming. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another example might be: Someone else who runs a red light must be reckless and stupid. If you were to run a red light, you justify the behaviour because you know your family member is having a medical emergency and you are rushing to the hospital. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: YSK about Fundamental Attribution Error because being mindful of it can give you a more positive outlook on life. We shouldn’t always assume the worst of others and should instead wonder what factors have put them in that situation or what else is contributing them to behave that way. Most people aren’t intentionally being malicious. People aren’t always as bad as we make them out to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fundamental_attribution_error&quot;&gt;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fundamental_attribution_error&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.simplypsychology.org/fundamental-attribution.html&quot;&gt;https://www.simplypsychology.org/fundamental-attribution.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK in the eyes of a delivery driver your dog is not "friendly"]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Dog bites are a very big problem when it comes to delivery drivers, And
simply saying your dog is friendly means nothing because essentially it's a
stranger walking on your property that your dog does not know and it's behavior
is not predictable in that situation.

It experienced driver…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptyi0a/ysk_in_the_eyes_of_a_delivery_driver_your_dog_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptyi0a/ysk_in_the_eyes_of_a_delivery_driver_your_dog_is/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 17:35:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Dog bites are a very big problem when it comes to delivery drivers, And simply saying your dog is friendly means nothing because essentially it&amp;#39;s a stranger walking on your property that your dog does not know and it&amp;#39;s behavior is not predictable in that situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It experienced driver knows how to handle a dog aggressive or not and you&amp;#39;re insistence that they are friendly and won&amp;#39;t do anything typically is what leads to drivers being bitten and we are required to report when we are bitten which could mean your dog can get put on a vicious dog list and/or put down which is something we all want to avoid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So unless you were there to hold back your dog and introduce them to a delivery driver either keep them inside or chained up to avoid any incidents so that you can get your package because it is well within the driver&amp;#39;s right to refuse the delivery if they believe a dog is dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make sure everyone&amp;#39;s safe, no one&amp;#39;s going to get hurt, and do what you can to introduce your dogs to the drivers if they&amp;#39;re going to be your regular.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Your dishwasher is far more energy / water efficient than you are at washing dishes. Running a dishwasher that is only 25% full will still use less water, on average, than hand washing those dishes. Save water, energy, and time by using your dishwasher instead of washing by hand.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: This tip will save you time and money while helping the environment.
Depending on the detergent you use, you don't even have to rinse the dishes
before loading them, which saves you even more (just make sure to clean your
filter often).

Bonus: if you have an Energy Star dishwasher, it is…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptwcm2/ysk_your_dishwasher_is_far_more_energy_water/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptwcm2/ysk_your_dishwasher_is_far_more_energy_water/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 15:37:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This tip will save you time and money while helping the environment. Depending on the detergent you use, you don&amp;#39;t even have to rinse the dishes before loading them, which saves you even more (just make sure to clean your filter often). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bonus: if you have an Energy Star dishwasher, it is required that they use no more than 3.5 gallons per cycle (compared to the standard 5 gallons), so your water/energy savings will be even greater.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: People will respond much better to your small talk attempts if you mention a time constraint.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Many people feel awkward when initiating small talk. It's also often
awkward to have someone initiate small talk with you, at least initially.
Mentioning a time constraint gives both of you an out, reducing the pressure and
relaxing both of you into an easier conversation. If it goes well,…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptuulu/ysk_people_will_respond_much_better_to_your_small/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptuulu/ysk_people_will_respond_much_better_to_your_small/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 14:41:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Many people feel awkward when initiating small talk. It&amp;#39;s also often awkward to have someone initiate small talk with you, at least initially. Mentioning a time constraint gives both of you an out, reducing the pressure and relaxing both of you into an easier conversation. If it goes well, you can mention re-engaging later rather than running out of things to say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Example added for clarity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Hi, I&amp;#39;m on my way to work and in a bit of a hurry, but I wanted to let you know those shoes are awesome! Where did you get them?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Hey bro, I only have a minute before my next set (at the gym), but I gotta ask. What&amp;#39;s your tattoo mean?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK That it’s about to be Raptor Season!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Raptor Season is when adult hawks, owls, and eagles push this years babies from
their territory.

Why YSK: young hawks, eagles, or owls may become more desperate and go after
barn kittens, chickens, or end up in your yard stranded

Each year raptors have babies. But each raptor, or breeding pair,…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptfyoz/ysk_that_its_about_to_be_raptor_season/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptfyoz/ysk_that_its_about_to_be_raptor_season/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 14:12:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Raptor Season is when adult hawks, owls, and eagles push this years babies from their territory. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: young hawks, eagles, or owls may become more desperate and go after barn kittens, chickens, or end up in your yard stranded&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each year raptors have babies. But each raptor, or breeding pair, prefer to have their own territory to hunt in. Especially as food becomes more scarce in the winter. Beginning now, and extending throughout the winter is what a lot of wildlife biologists refer to as “Raptor Season”. This is the final test basically for these babies, seeing if they can survive throughout the winter. They may be more desperate. Usually they won’t go after anything near humans (even chickens despite how many hawks have taken your chickens, only large ones can and even then they would prefer squirrel) however during this time they are more focused on not starving than safety. They may dive into cars, try to go after barn cats, try to go after chickens, or you may even find them in your yard. Raptors that become too weak to fly will quickly get parasites from prolonged time on the ground, keeping them grounded until they find help or die. Keep an extra eye out and extra caution for our winged friends as we progress more into winter!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tl;dr Raptor starvation during the winter can lead to increased exposure&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that if you are indoors and an earthquake hits, you should NOT attempt to change locations or leave the building. The danger of falling objects is far greater than the danger of building collapse.]]></title><description><![CDATA[It is a common misconception that, due the risk of building collapse, you should
attempt to leave the building when you feel shaking. This is EXACTLY WHAT YOU
SHOULD NOT DO.

The official guidance is unanimous. In the event of an earthquake, do one thing
and one thing ONLY:

 1. DUCK beneath a…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptdv0u/ysk_that_if_you_are_indoors_and_an_earthquake/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptdv0u/ysk_that_if_you_are_indoors_and_an_earthquake/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:53:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a common misconception that, due the risk of building collapse, you should attempt to leave the building when you feel shaking. This is EXACTLY WHAT YOU SHOULD NOT DO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The official guidance is unanimous. In the event of an earthquake, do one thing and one thing ONLY:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DUCK&lt;/strong&gt; beneath a nearby sturdy object. If no sturdy desk, table, or countertop is available, duck next to an interior wall away form windows, heavy frames, shelves, and fixtures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COVER&lt;/strong&gt; your neck and head with your arms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOLD&lt;/strong&gt; on to the object you&amp;#39;re covering under until the shaking stops.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: In a major earthquake, it will be &lt;em&gt;extremely&lt;/em&gt; difficult to move around inside a building. The ground is literally sweeping violently side to side beneath your feet. It would be like trying to run on the bed of a flatbed truck while it drives over a series of speed bumps. The danger of tripping and falling is serious, and winding up on the floor with your head and neck exposed while objects may be falling down all around you is a VERY DANGEROUS situation to be in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, even if you manage to get out of the building, you will have to pass through the area immediately beneath the facade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Glass, masonry, concrete, etc...can very likely be separating from the facade of the building and falling to the street below, even if the building itself remains standing. You do NOT want to be in the area beneath the exterior of a building while the shaking is taking place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only AFTER the shaking stops should you check for injuries, put on sturdy shoes, and calmly leave the building until it can be inspected for structural damage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The USGS web page on what to do during an earthquake reads:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are INDOORS -- STAY THERE! Get under a desk or table and hang on to it (Drop, Cover, and Hold on!) or move into a hallway or against an inside wall. STAY CLEAR of windows, fireplaces, and heavy furniture or appliances. GET OUT of the kitchen, which is a dangerous place (things can fall on you). DON&amp;#39;T run downstairs or rush outside while the building is shaking or while there is danger of falling and hurting yourself or being hit by falling glass or debris.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The University of Washington advises:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DO NOT run outside or to other rooms during shaking: The area near the exterior walls of a building is the most dangerous place to be. Windows, facades and architectural details are often the first parts of the building to collapse. To stay away from this danger zone, stay inside if you are inside and outside if you are outside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: "Mortified" means "embarrassed," not "terrified"]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Cuz I've seen the two confused a mortifying amount of times.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pte645/ysk_mortified_means_embarrassed_not_terrified/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pte645/ysk_mortified_means_embarrassed_not_terrified/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 22:32:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Cuz I&amp;#39;ve seen the two confused a &lt;em&gt;mortifying&lt;/em&gt; amount of times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that if you ever have a disagreement with someone, you should ask them, "Is there any proof/evidence that would change your mind?"]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: If they say no, then nothing you can say or do will change their mind
so there's no point in trying. You'll just be spinning your wheels so to speak.

If they say, "I'm not sure, but I'm open to looking at whatever proof/evidence
you have." that's a completely valid response. Some people…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pt90q2/ysk_that_if_you_ever_have_a_disagreement_with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pt90q2/ysk_that_if_you_ever_have_a_disagreement_with/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 19:58:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If they say no, then nothing you can say or do will change their mind so there&amp;#39;s no point in trying. You&amp;#39;ll just be spinning your wheels so to speak. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If they say, &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m not sure, but I&amp;#39;m open to looking at whatever proof/evidence you have.&amp;quot; that&amp;#39;s a completely valid response. Some people don&amp;#39;t know what it would take to change their opinion, but if they&amp;#39;re open to the idea of seeing evidence that goes against their beliefs, then it could warrant dialogue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK if you are in the U.S. and have health insurance through your employer, there's a 2/3 chance that your employer dictates what's covered and not covered - not the health insurance company.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: If one of your procedures has been denied, it might be worth talking to
whoever is in charge of benefits in HR to change it in the future.

In 2020, 67% of covered workers in the U.S. were receiving coverage through a
self-funded plan. (Linked source)
[https://www.kff.org/report…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptb8dr/ysk_if_you_are_in_the_us_and_have_health/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptb8dr/ysk_if_you_are_in_the_us_and_have_health/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 18:59:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:   If one of your procedures has been denied, it might be worth talking to whoever is in charge of benefits in HR to change it in the future.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2020, 67% of covered workers in the U.S. were receiving coverage through a self-funded plan. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kff.org/report-section/ehbs-2020-section-10-plan-funding/&quot;&gt;(Linked source)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Self-funded&amp;quot; means that any health premiums collected only come from that employer AND are only used on healthcare expenses for that employer. In many cases, this also allows the employer to customize elements of what they will allow to be covered and not covered. Self-funded plans can also circumvent most state-level insurance mandates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If your insurance doesn&amp;#39;t cover something like &amp;quot;transgender services&amp;quot;, that decision could be on your employer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;#39;t like the payments for your mental/behavioral health provider?  That might be something that&amp;#39;s controllable by your employer - not the insurer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your buddy went in for XYZ procedure and his was fully paid for by ABC Insurance?  If you also have an ABC Insurance card, even if you had the same procedure done on the exact same day from the exact same provider, yours might NOT be paid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And we all wonder why the U.S. Healthcare system needs an overhaul...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>