<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 19:20:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: how to clutch your assignments last min. professional procrastinator guide]]></title><description><![CDATA[why YSK: you have an assignment due very soon this will help you finish them on
time or get the grade.

this isn't about long-term procrastination. if you can stop, stop asap. these
tips only work in a hinge and overusing them will get you in trouble as they get
less effective every time.

3 tips +…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/np5qt5/ysk_how_to_clutch_your_assignments_last_min/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/np5qt5/ysk_how_to_clutch_your_assignments_last_min/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 20:10:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;why YSK: you have an assignment due very soon this will help you finish them on time or get the grade. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;this isn&amp;#39;t about long-term procrastination. if you can stop, stop asap. these tips only work in a hinge and overusing them will get you in trouble as they get less effective every time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 tips + consumables&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;don&amp;#39;t panic. you panic, you cant work. you think of the large pile of homework ahead of you, the three essays and exams. I don&amp;#39;t care if you have it due in 5 mins. if you panic you won&amp;#39;t start working until much later. also, most emotions can lead to panic, so try and suppress them. this isn&amp;#39;t about finishing your homework in a healthy way, but about not handing it in late.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;decide the compromise right now. if it&amp;#39;s a test, the content you studied the most before is gonna have to go. if it&amp;#39;s a project, skip on the least marked criteria. have an action plan that gets you somewhere on the deadline then fix the compromises. fixing something, even if it&amp;#39;s trash is a lot easier than working on a blank slate because it gives you the illusion that you&amp;#39;re almost there. but understand you can also make a compromise in time. if you put this in mind, however, it leads to more procrastination. you make the compromise at the end. maybe skip the class before it&amp;#39;s due. pull an allnighter. make an excuse for why it&amp;#39;s late, its gonna get scummy and degrading but gain, this about clutching the grade.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;don&amp;#39;t compromise sleep. you lose sleep and you lose your sanity. don&amp;#39;t get me wrong, all-nighters are okay in the case of a single project which you can rest afterward, but an all-nighter takes time to regenerate from, ruining your sleep schedule. this doesn&amp;#39;t work in the areas of stress where you need to procrastinate such as finals. you will trick yourself into thinking it&amp;#39;s an easy compromise, it&amp;#39;s not. in long periods of time, it will destroy your sanity, you will panic, and everything will fall apart. unless you have the next 2 days to regenerate, make sure you get 5 hours minimum every day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;last but not least and most importantly, use consumables wisely. I&amp;#39;m referring to coffee, that music that gets you hyped, alarms, maybe a drink or food that you associate with a clutch night. they are very powerful. the first time you drink coffee, its effect is insane. when I first listened to a hype song, I felt like on my way to Valhalla finishing the homework. they&amp;#39;re incredibly useful and are your secret weapons. if you over procrastinate and use them all the time, they start to feel normal. associate them with clutch situations and only use them then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;now go finish the assignment NOW you&amp;#39;ve wasted too much time reading&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Your mental imagery of drownings is probably wrong.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi, r/YouShouldKnow [/r/YouShouldKnow]! I was a lifeguard for 5 years,
eventually working my way up to running my city’s biggest aquatic facility with
20+ lifeguards on staff working under me at any given time. With Memorial Day
coming up (the start of the summer season for my organization) and…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nnj14f/ysk_your_mental_imagery_of_drownings_is_probably/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nnj14f/ysk_your_mental_imagery_of_drownings_is_probably/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 12:07:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi, &lt;a href=&quot;/r/YouShouldKnow&quot;&gt;r/YouShouldKnow&lt;/a&gt;! I was a lifeguard for 5 years, eventually working my way up to running my city’s biggest aquatic facility with 20+ lifeguards on staff working under me at any given time. With Memorial Day coming up (the start of the summer season for my organization) and plenty of people looking to hit the beach or pool after missing out last year, there’s going to be lots of inexperienced swimmers back in the water… many of whom haven’t swam for at least two years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I ask people what they think a drowning victim looks like, they usually describe to me &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HWgONcX5VhQ&quot;&gt;something that looks like this&lt;/a&gt; - someone shouting for help, raising their arms high, and making a lot of noise as they splash in the water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a dramatic and somewhat inaccurate representation invented by Hollywood. Real active drownings tend to be much, much quieter events. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a video with sound of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=beNheoRRdKk&amp;amp;t=10s&quot;&gt;a girl who is actively drowning&lt;/a&gt; before a lifeguard rescues her - notice how little sound she makes, and how little time it takes for her head to sink underwater. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Active drowning is a state of panic in which someone is struggling to keep their head above water. A person who is actively drowning will instinctively do whatever they can to keep their head above water and will try to take in as much air as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: An actively drowning person won’t have the time nor breath to call for air, because every fiber of their being is focused on trying to keep their lungs full. I have seen many parents think their kids were completely fine when in reality, their kids were distressed or actively drowning less than five feet behind them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than trying to listen for sounds of drowning, keep on the lookout for people who are: struggling to keep their head above water and/or making big sweeping motions in an attempt to move water under them. If there is little to no pattern for how long their head is above water vs below water, there’s a good chance they’re actively drowning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s another video (also with sound) of &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/nANNAtq8Bpw?t=5&quot;&gt;a child actively drowning&lt;/a&gt; - again, I want to point your attention to how little sound the victim makes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What if I see someone who is drowning?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So say you’re a drowning-spotting expert now. You’re hanging out at the beach/pool, you&amp;#39;re soaking some sun, and you successfully spot someone drowning - what do you do now?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For many people their first instinct is to dash into the water and help the victim - particularly if they are a child and/or relative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is this the part where I tell you that it’s a bad idea? Well… maybe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In shallow water, it’s totally fine to mosey on over and pick up a child that’s struggling. If it’s deep water, then it’s a different story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please listen to what I’m about to say, because I cannot stress this enough - if you spot someone actively drowning in deep water, do not just jump in to try to save them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A person who is actively drowning is literally not thinking. They are acting out of pure instinct to push whatever objects they can underneath their body to stay above water, whether it be driftwood, floaties, or another human being.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have seen parents jump into 12-feet deep water trying to save their struggling child, only to become a victim themselves when their child inevitably push the parent’s head underwater to try to stay afloat. PEOPLE WHO ARE ACTIVELY DROWNING WILL ALSO DROWN YOU.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me say that again - PEOPLE WHO ARE ACTIVELY DROWNING WILL ALSO DROWN YOU.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me let you in on a secret - you know the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.americanlifeguard.net/Images/40ComfortGuard.jpg&quot;&gt;ring buoys&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://marydonahue.org/facultyfiles.deanza.edu/images/donahuemary//sheperdscrookonwall.jpg&quot;&gt;shepherds hook&lt;/a&gt; you see hanging on the pool fence? Those are there for you. Many lifeguards aren’t even trained to use them, because it’s far quicker and easier for us to use ourselves and our rescue tubes to do rescues. Health codes in basically every US state, however, require pools to have them, because basically anyone can use them to help someone who is actively drowning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So to get back to the question - what should you do if someone in front of you is actively drowning in deep water?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First off, if any lifeguards are nearby, direct their attention to the drowning person. Waving one arm over your head and pointing to the victim with your other arm while looking straight at a lifeguard is usually sufficient, and shouting “active drowning” will definitely grab the attention of any competent lifeguards on duty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But what if there are no lifeguards? Maybe I’m at a river, or a private beach, or it’s a “swim at my own risk” area.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The answer is that you should first make sure that you’re safely anchored to the shore - usually by holding onto a pole/tree with a hand, or by lying flat on the ground. Failing to anchor yourself could result in the victim pulling you into the water! Once safely anchored, you should extend anything you can to them for them to pull themselves to shore. Either the ring buoy or the shepherds hook that I mentioned above, a beach towel, your shirt, a tree branch - anything that the victim can grab onto and pull themselves on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What if they’re too far away, or I don’t have anything I can use to safely pull them in?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re unable to locate a rope or long object that you can extend to the victim, then you’ll need to do two things - a.) try to throw buoyant objects for them to make use of (like beach balls, life jackets, or floaties), and b.) call 911 (or your local emergency number). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll say it again - it is not safe for you to attempt to help someone who is actively drowning in deep water if you don’t have any available tools to assist you. If you are unable to help someone who is actively drowning, then you should call your local emergency services as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a brief period of time, active drowning victims will tire themselves out. At this point in time, they will likely lose consciousness and go limp. If someone in front of you is actively drowning in deep water, and you don’t have any tools you can use to bring them to shore safely, it is much safer for you to wait for them to “go passive” before bringing them in than it is for you to assist them while they’re still conscious. You can help someone who is unconscious, but you can’t help someone if you’re unconscious yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s cold, it’s heartbreaking, and it’s painful to type these words, but it’s also how you can guarantee that one drowning person doesn’t turn into two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But don’t let me end this on a downer - here are some tips to help keep you and your loved ones safe!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stay within arm’s reach of your group, and especially keep track of beginner/poor/non-swimmers. If you’re a parent, it is your duty to keep watch of your children. Lifeguards are not there to babysit - they’re there to enforce rules and respond to emergencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Take a break at least once an hour to rest and rehydrate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whenever you enter a waterfront, pool, or aquatic facility, try to spot any ring buoys, shepherd hooks, or other safety equipment that you can run to if an emergency occurs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Take it slow - stay in shallow areas until you’re confident that you’re able to tackle deeper areas safely. Do not pressure friends or family to enter areas they feel uncomfortable to enter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please listen to your lifeguards, if present - I promise you, we make our patrons’ safety our utmost priority… even if it means we have to be killjoys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please do whatever you can to have a fun and safe time out in the water!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer - I am not a medical professional nor am I liable for any injuries that may occur as a result of you following this advice. Please exercise your best judgement when in an emergency. When in doubt, call 911.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Apple has much nicer alarm ringtones in the health app]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Most of us use the clock app for our morning alarms, with crappy
ringtone options that only scare us awake and make us hate the sound, but I
recently found that in the health app (which comes with the iPhone) there is a
sleep section where you can set your sleeping schedule, and choose from…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nm0vaz/ysk_apple_has_much_nicer_alarm_ringtones_in_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nm0vaz/ysk_apple_has_much_nicer_alarm_ringtones_in_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 09:34:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Most of us use the clock app for our morning alarms, with crappy ringtone options that only scare us awake and make us hate the sound, but I recently found that in the health app (which comes with the iPhone) there is a sleep section where you can set your sleeping schedule, and choose from some amazing alarm sounds like Helios and first light, that are meant for waking up to. They start slow and have some really calming tunes that could be from a video game soundtrack. I 100% recommend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK your VHS tapes and home movies have a short lifespan and need to be transferred to save them]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK : VHS tapes were not meant to last forever and every day that goes by is
one day closer to your precious memories being lost forever. Old VHS tapes and
home movies are in danger of being destroyed by mold, age and ribbon
deterioration. There are companies all over the world that will…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nn75g5/ysk_your_vhs_tapes_and_home_movies_have_a_short/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nn75g5/ysk_your_vhs_tapes_and_home_movies_have_a_short/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 22:55:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK :  VHS tapes were not meant to last forever and every day that goes by is one day closer to your precious memories being lost forever. Old VHS tapes and home movies are in danger of being destroyed by mold, age and ribbon deterioration. There are companies all over the world that will transfer your VHS tapes to a more long term options. Even if you find the ribbons have mold or damage there are companies that can repair and transfer your movies. It&amp;#39;s much cheaper transferring tapes in good condition than it is to transfer moldy or damaged tapes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Seizure Treatment]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Whenever you see someone having a seizure whilst there are people
around them panicking, you have to tell them all to stay clear as crowding will
make the person panic and make it hard to breathe. Next, you lay them on their
side so they can breathe and get rid of foam because that can…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nmr2h5/ysk_seizure_treatment/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nmr2h5/ysk_seizure_treatment/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 18:20:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Whenever you see someone having a seizure whilst there are people around them panicking, you have to tell them all to stay clear as crowding will make the person panic and make it hard to breathe. Next, you lay them on their side so they can breathe and get rid of foam because that can obstruct breathing. Finally, calmly comfort them and help them breathe whilst the seizure runs its course. On average a seizure lasts between 30-2:30 seconds but if the seizure persists for over 5 minutes seek immediate medical attention as this circumstance can be a serious problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Captcha requests linked to feeding data to build AI systems do not necessarily know all the correct answers. You can feed it incorrect answers and, while you will fail a few times, it will eventually let you through because it does not know all of the images which are mountains/bikes/cars/etc.]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is in response to a recent YSK discussing CAPTCHA requests that are used to
help build out AI systems.

Why YSK: Because, if you do not want to participate in giving free labor to some
service to build an AI to be used for who knows what purpose, I imagine it is
your right to refuse.

This may…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nmsc8c/ysk_captcha_requests_linked_to_feeding_data_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nmsc8c/ysk_captcha_requests_linked_to_feeding_data_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 14:50:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is in response to a recent YSK discussing CAPTCHA requests that are used to help build out AI systems.      &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Because, if you do not want to participate in giving free labor to some service to build an AI to be used for who knows what purpose, I imagine it is your right to refuse.      &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This may sound like extra work, because it is, but you can get rather quick at it after doing it a few times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: that the average residential oven is rarely accurate. An aftermarket in oven thermometer is necessary.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: your oven face plate temperature scale is printed on a piece of metal
in a production line that's not really accurate. Baking and cooking have core
temps for a reason. Your flopped Japanese cheesecake or overcooked muffins but
undercooked in the middle may not be entirely your fault.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nmqvkj/ysk_that_the_average_residential_oven_is_rarely/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nmqvkj/ysk_that_the_average_residential_oven_is_rarely/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 12:03:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: your oven face plate temperature scale is printed on a piece of metal in a production line that&amp;#39;s not really accurate. Baking and cooking have core temps for a reason. Your flopped Japanese cheesecake or overcooked muffins but undercooked in the middle may not be entirely your fault.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK To avoid feeling victimized by problems, you should adopt the hero mindset. Games teach it really well and it’s backed by research.]]></title><description><![CDATA[At the recent global conference on human-computer interaction (CHI), an AI
researcher presented a new free app [http://betwixt.life/] as the next wave in
mental health innovation and it was described as a cross between the game
Lifeline and Lord of the Rings.

The idea behind it apparently came from…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nm85br/ysk_to_avoid_feeling_victimized_by_problems_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nm85br/ysk_to_avoid_feeling_victimized_by_problems_you/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 15:56:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the recent global conference on human-computer interaction (CHI), an AI researcher presented &lt;a href=&quot;http://betwixt.life/&quot;&gt;a new free app&lt;/a&gt; as the next wave in mental health innovation and it was described as a cross between the game Lifeline and Lord of the Rings. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea behind it apparently came from research in narrative identity, which found that the people who improved most from therapy and achieved sustained better health, were able to adopt a hero mindset. Basically, they managed to see themselves as characters in an epic story overcoming obstacles along their journey. This subtle mind shift allowed them to reframe their problems as challenges that are part and parcel of the hero’s journey, that can be figured out and that provide opportunities for growth. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adopting a hero mindset increases your sense of agency in the face of struggle, allowing you to change your perspective and feel empowered to tackle the problems life throws at you. If you manage to see yourself as the hero of an epic story (even a little bit), you won’t feel victimised by the setbacks along the way, because your willingness to confront obstacles is precisely what defines you as a hero in the first place. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously I’m not saying you should engage in wishful thinking. This is just a subtle, simple mental shift to think about your life that’s been shown to link with bigger and more lasting improvements in therapy. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SOURCES:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AI researcher’s paper on the future of mental health chatbots: &lt;a href=&quot;http://francisconunes.me/RealizingAIinHealthcareWS/papers/Harmon2021.pdf&quot;&gt;http://francisconunes.me/RealizingAIinHealthcareWS/papers/Harmon2021.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The app (it’s free) based on this research: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.betwixt.life/&quot;&gt;https://www.betwixt.life/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Narrative identity research mentioned in the post: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/269603657_Narrative_Identity&quot;&gt;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/269603657_Narrative_Identity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that there is an animal Poison Control number you can contact incase your pet ingests something potentially dangerous]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Time can be very critical when it comes to an accidental poisoning. You
are connected to a member of the ASPCA Poison Control who can walk you through
any necessary things you can do or if you need to take your pet to the vet. I
unfortunately had to utilize this yesterday after my dog got…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nl0bar/ysk_that_there_is_an_animal_poison_control_number/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nl0bar/ysk_that_there_is_an_animal_poison_control_number/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 21:24:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Time can be very critical when it comes to an accidental poisoning. You are connected to a member of the ASPCA Poison Control who can walk you through any necessary things you can do or if you need to take your pet to the vet. I unfortunately had to utilize this yesterday after my dog got into  a slow release fertilizer (it smells sweet by comparison to normal fertilizer) and as I was taking him to the vet, I was able to call them and they were able to see if there were any specific reactions that could happen as well as assuring me that the active chemicals were not life threatening&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aspca.org/pet-care/animal-poison-control&quot;&gt;The number is  (888) 426-4435.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Your library has more than books]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: This recent comment
[https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/nkwaqy/whats_a_free_resource_available_to_everyone_that/gzf3x0l?utm_source=share&utm_medium=web2x&context=3]
inspired me to go to my library. Besides "books" (and one hottie librarian), my
main library has classes such as art…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nlep8l/ysk_your_library_has_more_than_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nlep8l/ysk_your_library_has_more_than_books/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 15:42:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/nkwaqy/whats_a_free_resource_available_to_everyone_that/gzf3x0l?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web2x&amp;amp;context=3&quot;&gt;This recent comment&lt;/a&gt; inspired me to go to my library.  Besides &amp;quot;books&amp;quot; (and one hottie librarian), my main library has classes such as art classes, laser cutting and computer courses; you can check out (location-dependent) sports equipment like tennis rackets and kayaks, kitchen appliances, CDs/DVDs, use 3-D printers, even telescopes.  If there&amp;#39;s something you can&amp;#39;t find, they might be able to order it for you.  [this is in the US and very location-dependent]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: On food labels, the first ingredient listed is present in the largest amount by weight and the last ingredient listed is present in the least amount by weight.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK:

For example, here's the ingredients list for Danone's Dannon Fruit on the Bottom
Yogurt
[https://www.danoneawayfromhome.com/food-service-products/brand-dannon-fruit-on-the-bottom-strawberry-5-3oz/]:

> Milk, Sugar, Raspberry Puree, Water, Modified Food Starch, Contains Less Than
> 1% Of…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nkpsr7/ysk_on_food_labels_the_first_ingredient_listed_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nkpsr7/ysk_on_food_labels_the_first_ingredient_listed_is/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 04:29:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, here&amp;#39;s the ingredients list for Danone&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.danoneawayfromhome.com/food-service-products/brand-dannon-fruit-on-the-bottom-strawberry-5-3oz/&quot;&gt;Dannon Fruit on the Bottom Yogurt&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Milk,  Sugar, Raspberry Puree, Water, Modified Food Starch, Contains Less Than  1% Of Kosher Gelatin, Pectin, Vegetable Juice Concentrate (For Color),  Natural Flavor, Calcium Citrate, Vitamin D3, Sodium Citrate, Malic Acid&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As  you can see, &amp;quot;Sugar&amp;quot; comes before &amp;quot;Raspberry Puree&amp;quot;. This means that  there&amp;#39;s more sugar than fruit, and there&amp;#39;s more fruit than natural flavors, and so on...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is especially useful when you want to know how much of an unhealthy ingredient is present in the product. So even when you think  something (like yogurt) might be healthy enough (because you might think that it&amp;#39;s basically &amp;quot;just milk with fruits&amp;quot;), you can just check the food label to see if the product actually is healthy enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bonus tip: When it comes to processed/packaged/canned foods, the less ingredients are on the food label, the healthier the product!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that when using websites that limit you to a few free articles a month, you can copy paste the article into an incognito tab to bypass the paywall.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Certain sites like the NYTimes limit users to 3-5 free articles a
month, and require a subscription to read more. By copying and pasting the link
into an incognito tab, you bypass this and can read an unlimited amount of
articles. Still, if you can, it's better to subscribe to support the…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nl0k35/ysk_that_when_using_websites_that_limit_you_to_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nl0k35/ysk_that_when_using_websites_that_limit_you_to_a/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 23:34:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Certain sites like the NYTimes limit users to 3-5 free articles a month, and require a subscription to read more. By copying and pasting the link into an incognito tab, you bypass this and can read an unlimited amount of articles. Still, if you can, it&amp;#39;s better to subscribe to support the journalism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that the phrase Reduce, Reuse, Recycle is in that order for a reason. Not buying things that would be recycled or reusing them is more important than recycling.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Recycling is expensive, and sometimes the product ends up in a landfill
anyway
[https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/jun/21/us-plastic-recycling-landfills].
Buying less junk or reusing things yourself are better for the environment than
recycling.

Reusing a product is also better than…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nkxmsk/ysk_that_the_phrase_reduce_reuse_recycle_is_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nkxmsk/ysk_that_the_phrase_reduce_reuse_recycle_is_in/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 21:43:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Recycling is expensive, and sometimes the product &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/jun/21/us-plastic-recycling-landfills&quot;&gt;ends up in a landfill anyway&lt;/a&gt;. Buying less junk or reusing things yourself are better for the environment than recycling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reusing a product is also better than recycling. Sell or give away old furniture. Use old jelly jars to store leftovers. Refill soap dispensers. Reusing products means buying new stuff less often.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK if you give two weeks notice at work, they often have to pay you even if they ask you to leave before those two weeks are up.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: if you get sent away on the same day as giving notice, your boss might
be hoping you don’t realize you are owed this pay.

If an employer includes a requirement for notice in their contract or employee
handbook then the law in most states (US) require they pay out for those two
weeks even…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nj76du/ysk_if_you_give_two_weeks_notice_at_work_they/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nj76du/ysk_if_you_give_two_weeks_notice_at_work_they/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 19:06:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: if you get sent away on the same day as giving notice, your boss might be hoping you don’t realize you are owed this pay. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If an employer includes a requirement for notice in their contract or employee handbook then the law in most states (US) require they pay out for those two weeks even if they tell you not to come in to work. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An angry manager, or a job that considers a resigning employee a security risk, does not have to allow the employee to work for two weeks, but must pay them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK You shouldn’t feel guilty about playing games or reading fantasy. They can teach you a valuable mindset shift that’s backed by research and used in new tools to improve mental health]]></title><description><![CDATA[At the recent global conference on human-computer interaction (CHI), an AI
researcher presented a new free app [http://betwixt.life/] as the next wave in
mental health innovation and it was described as a cross between the game
Lifeline and Lord of the Rings.

The idea behind it apparently came from…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nkrlgq/ysk_you_shouldnt_feel_guilty_about_playing_games/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nkrlgq/ysk_you_shouldnt_feel_guilty_about_playing_games/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 18:20:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the recent global conference on human-computer interaction (CHI), an AI researcher presented &lt;a href=&quot;http://betwixt.life/&quot;&gt;a new free app&lt;/a&gt; as the next wave in mental health innovation and it was described as a cross between the game Lifeline and Lord of the Rings. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea behind it apparently came from research in narrative identity, which found that the people who improved most from therapy and achieved sustained better health, were able to adopt a heroic mindset. Basically, they saw themselves more like the heroes of an epic story, overcoming obstacles along the way, and this allowed them to reframe problems as challenges and growth opportunities. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s easy to (be made to) feel guilty for “escaping” your real life through fantasy and video games, but these escapes can also teach you a valuable mindset and help you cope better when you come back to the real world. Game mindset = Growth mindset &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SOURCES:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AI researcher’s paper on the future of mental health chatbots: &lt;a href=&quot;http://francisconunes.me/RealizingAIinHealthcareWS/papers/Harmon2021.pdf&quot;&gt;http://francisconunes.me/RealizingAIinHealthcareWS/papers/Harmon2021.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The app (it’s free) presented at the conference: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.betwixt.life/&quot;&gt;https://www.betwixt.life/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Narrative identity research mentioned in the post: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/269603657_Narrative_Identity&quot;&gt;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/269603657_Narrative_Identity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Cicadas can't bite you; they don't even have mouths.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Cicadas don't eat; they only consume food in their larval stage. When they grow
up into what we call cicadas, their body does not even have a "mouth". When they
run out of energy, they do some final death cries and drop dead. So don't be
afraid, they literally can't bite you! They do have a…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nkm3s5/ysk_cicadas_cant_bite_you_they_dont_even_have/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nkm3s5/ysk_cicadas_cant_bite_you_they_dont_even_have/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 12:47:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cicadas don&amp;#39;t eat; they only consume food in their larval stage. When they grow up into what we call &lt;em&gt;cicadas&lt;/em&gt;, their body does not even have a &amp;quot;mouth&amp;quot;. When they run out of energy, they do some final death cries and drop dead. So don&amp;#39;t be afraid, they literally &lt;em&gt;can&amp;#39;t&lt;/em&gt; bite you! They do have a proboscis for drinking, though. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I heard there is a mass emergence of cicadas in the United States right now and it&amp;#39;s freaking people out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: That if you drive for Doordash, Uber Eats, Grubhub, you should modify your insurance policy.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: A lot of people don't know that if you deliver for these apps, your
insurance company will not cover you if an accident occurs while your app is
running.

Moreover, while companies like Doordash or Grubhub have their own liability
insurance, what many drivers don't realize, is that this…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nk163d/ysk_that_if_you_drive_for_doordash_uber_eats/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nk163d/ysk_that_if_you_drive_for_doordash_uber_eats/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 06:50:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  A lot of people don&amp;#39;t know that if you deliver for these apps, your insurance company will not cover you if an accident occurs while your app is running.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, while companies like Doordash or Grubhub have their own liability insurance, what many drivers don&amp;#39;t realize, is that this does not benefit YOU in any way. This only covers damage you cause to another party - bodily injury, property damage, etc.   Whatever damage you incur on the job - even if it was 100% the other guy&amp;#39;s fault - has to come out of your own pocket.  As far as you are concerned, you are uninsured in that moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;((Just came back to make an edit.  The liability insurance policy is going to vary between what company you use - Postmates is going to differ from Grubhub which will differ from Doordash))&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So even though you have to provide some proof of insurance in order to sign up for these apps, that is not because they want to see that you have coverage while you&amp;#39;re driving FOR them.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some insurance companies have what&amp;#39;s called &amp;quot;Rideshare gap.&amp;quot; What this means is that you have coverage for when you are waiting for an order.  Once you have an order, and have the delivery items in your possession, the app&amp;#39;s insurance kicks in (again, this only covers other people).  This means you have insurance coverage during the &amp;quot;gap&amp;quot; between orders, but you, personally, have ZERO coverage during an active delivery.  If you choose Rideshare Gap as an add-on to your policy, it&amp;#39;s another $5-15 a month, which is basically a &amp;quot;better than nothing&amp;quot; option, but not the best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some people have found that their insurance company didn&amp;#39;t provide any kind of coverage, and as a result they had to change insurance providers.  In some cases, they have been involved in an accident and decided to omit the fact that their app was on.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this omission is insurance fraud.   Many car insurance companies will actually contact these  delivery apps, and if they find out that you were signed in to the app during the accident - even if it was a straight up hit and run that you caught on camera - they will not cover you.  Moreover, you may be hit with a felony insurance fraud charge, as you did not disclose that you were working during the accident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thing is, both your insurance company, AND the delivery app you work for, have your social security number, they have your license plate, they have a lot of the some personal information about you.  You might as well not lie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moral of the story&lt;/strong&gt;:  if you use any rideshare or delivery apps, make sure you are covered with some sort of Rideshare policy.  If you are not covered, DON&amp;#39;T LIE if you are in an accident.  Just eat the cost and learn whatever lesson you need to learn.  At that point, you&amp;#39;re better off learning the lesson of a totaled car, than learning the lesson of felony insurance fraud charges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Most Fridges/Freezers Are Safe To Transport On Their Side]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: I know a lot of people who have complained about how they broke their
fridge after they did this, and know even more people who choose to just leave
behind/sell their fridge when they move because of what a hassle it is to
transport. Knowing how a fridge/freezer works will save you money…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/njsj9t/ysk_most_fridgesfreezers_are_safe_to_transport_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/njsj9t/ysk_most_fridgesfreezers_are_safe_to_transport_on/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 12:46:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I know a lot of people who have complained about how they broke their fridge after they did this, and know even more people who choose to just leave behind/sell their fridge when they move because of what a hassle it is to transport. Knowing how a fridge/freezer works will save you money and time, and prevent you from breaking it yourself on accident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The concern comes from an issue that was common in older fridges/freezers. When tilted past a 45 degree angle, the oil in the compressor had a tendency to spill out into the cooling tubes and clog them, preventing coolant from filling the fridge completely. This used to be the end of a fridge&amp;#39;s life and meant a hefty bill for a new one. Over time though, oils were treated so they wouldn&amp;#39;t congeal around foreign particles, which prevented blocking. Additionally, more stringent, coiled cooling tubes were made with better materials like fiberglass and unique polymers that became an industry standard because they would give and compress to push things through the pipe. These two features have worked in tandem to prevent blockage, but their efforts won&amp;#39;t stop people who ruin their fridges on accident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because coolant tubes are usually quite small and oil is fairly viscous, it takes some time for the oil to move through the tubes. What usually kills a fridge/freezer after transport is turning it on before the oil has had a chance to settle in the compressor. If you run it without oil, the machine simply won&amp;#39;t function outside of forcing pressure into the oil-filled coolant tubes, which only pushes the oil further up the pipe and compresses it into an actual blockage. It&amp;#39;s a waste of a good fridge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The solution, of course, is to let the oil settle. In most fridges/freezers, the oil will settle back into the compressor after sitting upright for 24-48 hours regardless of how long it was on it&amp;#39;s side. At bare minimum, give it the same amount of time upright as it was in transport. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope this helped!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: Grammar&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Smoking (and vaping) significantly increases mens' risk of erectile dysfunction]]></title><description><![CDATA[The chemicals in cigarettes cause poor circulation, doubling a man's chances of
getting erectile dysfunction. Because nicotine constricts blood vessels, vaping
it can also cause erectile dysfunction.

Why YSK: Many people talk about the future risks of cancer with smoking. But
there are a ton of…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/njlxej/ysk_smoking_and_vaping_significantly_increases/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/njlxej/ysk_smoking_and_vaping_significantly_increases/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 05:00:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The chemicals in cigarettes cause poor circulation, doubling a man&amp;#39;s chances of getting erectile dysfunction. Because nicotine constricts blood vessels, vaping it can also cause erectile dysfunction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Many people talk about the future risks of cancer with smoking. But there are a ton of other, often more immediate, risks including erectile dysfunction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/health/erectile-dysfunction/impotence-and-smoking&quot;&gt;https://www.healthline.com/health/erectile-dysfunction/impotence-and-smoking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.manual.co/health-centre/erectile-dysfunction/smoking&quot;&gt;https://www.manual.co/health-centre/erectile-dysfunction/smoking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I want to add that many states and countries have FREE smoking cessation programs. So it isn&amp;#39;t something that needs to be done alone, even if you can&amp;#39;t pay for help (although paid help can often be covered by insurance as well).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK Documentaries can be extremely misleading.]]></title><description><![CDATA[There's an "interestingasf*ck" post stating a Monk had to be "retested" in 3
years if he failed his "test" regarding a particular stance/moves.



It's an extreme exaggeration. A lot of the information in the documentary
relating to it was greatly exaggerated or just plain wrong.



Why YSK: Taking…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/njdb5l/ysk_documentaries_can_be_extremely_misleading/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/njdb5l/ysk_documentaries_can_be_extremely_misleading/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 21:48:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s an &amp;quot;interestingasf*ck&amp;quot; post stating a Monk had to be &amp;quot;retested&amp;quot; in 3 years if he failed his &amp;quot;test&amp;quot; regarding a particular stance/moves. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s an extreme exaggeration. A lot of the information in the documentary relating to it was greatly exaggerated or just plain wrong. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Taking documentaries as the end all will leave you with a much poorer understanding of the reality of the world. This could be your health or being insulting incorrect about someone&amp;#39;s culture. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to see why the Shaolin Monk documentary is extremely exaggerated, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jHUewEWi9SE&amp;amp;t=38s&quot;&gt;watch this YouTuber who has video/picture evidence of his time being there who reviews the documentary himself&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK crying actually makes you happier!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: crying releases pheromones which serves as an auto mood-lifter! Never
be afraid to cry!]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nj2o5z/ysk_crying_actually_makes_you_happier/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nj2o5z/ysk_crying_actually_makes_you_happier/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 10:58:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: crying releases pheromones which serves as an auto mood-lifter! Never be afraid to cry!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that Stevia and Ragweed are from the same family]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Stevia can give people with Ragweed allergies the same type of (or
worse) allergic reaction as Ragweed.
https://www.marconews.com/story/life/2018/10/08/ask-pharmacist-allergic-connection-between-stevia-and-ragweed/1525152002/]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/niynqn/ysk_that_stevia_and_ragweed_are_from_the_same/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/niynqn/ysk_that_stevia_and_ragweed_are_from_the_same/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 08:57:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Stevia can give people with Ragweed allergies the same type of (or worse) allergic reaction as Ragweed.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marconews.com/story/life/2018/10/08/ask-pharmacist-allergic-connection-between-stevia-and-ragweed/1525152002/&quot;&gt;https://www.marconews.com/story/life/2018/10/08/ask-pharmacist-allergic-connection-between-stevia-and-ragweed/1525152002/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK The three sets numbers on the inside arm of your eyeglasses are in millimeters for: lens width, nose bridge width, and temple length. Adjust size accordingly to your face and its features.]]></title><description><![CDATA[WHY YSK:

A frame that is too narrow will make your face look wider, while a frame that is
too wide will make your face look narrower. This is one of the most important
factors in finding a pair of glasses that fits well. Find a frame that is
slightly wider than your face — no more than a finger…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/niuwil/ysk_the_three_sets_numbers_on_the_inside_arm_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/niuwil/ysk_the_three_sets_numbers_on_the_inside_arm_of/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 03:58:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;h1&gt;WHY YSK:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A frame that is too narrow will make your face look wider, while a frame that is too wide will make your face look narrower. This is one of the most important factors in finding a pair of glasses that fits well. Find a frame that is slightly wider than your face — no more than a finger width between the temple and your face. Any wider is a sign your frames are too wide. (This measurement is not printed on the temple of your glasses. To find it, take your measuring tape and measure horizontally across the front of your frames, including any hinges or design features that stick out on the sides.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The numbers, from left to right are for:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;LENS WIDTH&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To determine which lens size is right for you, know that a small lens width is 50mm or less, medium is between 51mm and 54mm and large is any lens wider than 55mm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your eyes should be centered within your lenses. Eyeglass frames that are too wide will make your eyes appear too close together, while narrow frames will give your eyes a wide-set look.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;TEMPLE LENGTH&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Temple length is the measurement in millimeters of the “arms” of the frame. This measurement does not vary as much as the others. 135mm, 140mm, 145mm, and 150mm are the most common options. The temple should fit horizontally and evenly along your face and fit comfortably along the outside of your ear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;BRIDGE WIDTH&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The distance between two lenses equals a frame&amp;#39;s bridge width. The bridge should sit comfortably flush against your nose. If you have close-set eyes or want a narrow bridge, this number should be lower. If you have wide-set eyes or want a wide bridge, this number should be higher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The location of your nose can help determine which frame style works best for you. If your nose is higher on your face, an eyeglass style where the bridge is even with the frame’s brow line will look best. If your nose is situated a bit lower on your face, a frame with a lower bridge and curved brow line will better suit your features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK Self-reflection can actually make your mental health worse if you aren't careful how you do it.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Self-reflection is considered one of the keys to self-development,
mental well-being and improvement in therapy. However, research shows
[http://selfcontrol.psych.lsa.umich.edu/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/1-s2.0-S0065260116300338-main-2.pdf]
that if you do it the wrong way, it can actually…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nikcds/ysk_selfreflection_can_actually_make_your_mental/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nikcds/ysk_selfreflection_can_actually_make_your_mental/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 00:42:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK&lt;/strong&gt;: Self-reflection is considered one of the keys to self-development, mental well-being and improvement in therapy. However, &lt;a href=&quot;http://selfcontrol.psych.lsa.umich.edu/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/1-s2.0-S0065260116300338-main-2.pdf&quot;&gt;research shows&lt;/a&gt; that if you do it the wrong way, it can actually make your problems worse. The wrong way, it turns out, is when you get too immersed in whatever is upsetting you by reflecting on it. To make self-reflection actually work, you need to learn to self-distance while doing it - i.e. take a mental step back from the problem. For example, you can imagine that you are looking at the situation from afar, or through someone else’s eyes; or you can write about it by referring to yourself in the third person (‘he’, ‘she’, ‘they’).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The studies show that this can reduce your negative emotions, and help you achieve closure and greater clarity. There’s also a free iOS app (not sure if it’s on Android, too) based on this research that uses roleplaying and guided journaling to make this type of self-reflection easier to do on the go and turn into a habit:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.apple.com/gb/app/betwixt-the-story-of-you/id1540472983&quot;&gt;https://apps.apple.com/gb/app/betwixt-the-story-of-you/id1540472983&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK If you’re using more than one tin of paint you should mix them together first]]></title><description><![CDATA[If you’re needing to cover a large surface and going to use multiple tins you
should mix them together before hand rather than using one and opening another
as you’ll be able to see the slight differences next to one another and doing
this makes the paint job look more uniform.

Why YSK: Even though…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nio494/ysk_if_youre_using_more_than_one_tin_of_paint_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nio494/ysk_if_youre_using_more_than_one_tin_of_paint_you/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 22:59:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re needing to cover a large surface and going to use multiple tins you should mix them together before hand rather than using one and opening another as you’ll be able to see the slight differences next to one another and doing this makes the paint job look more uniform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Even though you will be buying the same colour of paint there is always slight variation between every tin of paint that make it more obvious where the start of a new tin of paint has began.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that "Powerful Bass" and terms alike are just a marketing gimmick. Making the high end and bass louder is just a cheap way to produce sound that people Will think is good]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK : Your headphones should represent your music well, not alter it. Not to
mention that you could get better sound by just avoiding brands with such
marketing. Always check headphones sound signature on websites like rtings and
soundguys. Detail is also very important]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nifwwv/ysk_that_powerful_bass_and_terms_alike_are_just_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nifwwv/ysk_that_powerful_bass_and_terms_alike_are_just_a/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 12:27:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK : Your headphones should represent your music well, not alter it. Not to mention that you could get better sound by just avoiding brands with such marketing. 
Always check headphones sound signature on websites like rtings and soundguys. Detail is also very important&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: When huge companies like Amazon, banks, and etc say they support "small businesses" they mean businesses with up to 250-1500 employees (depending on industry)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Advertisements will often try to change your view of large companies by
showing imagery of tiny, home businesses, and family owned/operated business
that they are supposedly helping but when they make claims of their involvement
with "small businesses" they're usually using the definitions…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ni9dvv/ysk_when_huge_companies_like_amazon_banks_and_etc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ni9dvv/ysk_when_huge_companies_like_amazon_banks_and_etc/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 07:03:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Advertisements will often try to change your view of large companies by showing imagery of tiny, home businesses, and family owned/operated business that they are supposedly helping but when they make claims of their involvement with &amp;quot;small businesses&amp;quot; they&amp;#39;re usually using the definitions the U.S. Small Business Association (SBA) uses&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecfr.gov/cgi-bin/text-idx?SID=0ff5f0839abff4eec707b4478ed733c6&amp;amp;mc=true&amp;amp;node=pt13.1.121&amp;amp;rgn=div5#se13.1.121_1101&quot;&gt;uses&lt;/a&gt; which allows for companies that employ between 250 and 1500 employees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK The car warranty scam calls are about collecting sensitive information.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: You Should know this to defend yourself from the scam if you're
susceptible to it, if you're not you should know so you can help make it an
unviable scam.

Step 1.) Spoof a number from the targets area, read your script about their
extended warranty

Step 2.) Collect Make of vehicle and…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nhus2x/ysk_the_car_warranty_scam_calls_are_about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nhus2x/ysk_the_car_warranty_scam_calls_are_about/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 17:11:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: You Should know this to defend yourself from the scam if you&amp;#39;re susceptible to it, if you&amp;#39;re not you should know so you can help make it an unviable scam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 1.) Spoof a number from the targets area, read your script about their extended warranty&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 2.) Collect Make of vehicle and target zip code&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 3.) Call ACTUAL sales department of specified Make of vehicle and merge the calls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 4.) Listen in as target feeds sensitive information to the sales department.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doesn&amp;#39;t matter which make/model/year you say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you can do&lt;/strong&gt;: Feed the warranty scammer fake/false information, this is make/model/zip so prepare a fake zip. As soon as they transfer you to the actual sales office for the make of &amp;quot;your&amp;quot; vehicle inform them of how this scam works. It needs to be just annoying enough for vehicle manufacturers so they change their phone practices so this scam no longer works. This whole process should take ~2 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: So far I&amp;#39;ve gotten to Honda and Toyota sales departments. I tried to do Chevy but the scammer un-merged the call while I was explaining to the Chevy rep what was going on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK sleep is not an optional lifestyle luxury.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Matthew Walker, an expert on the subject of sleep, said that sleep is a
non-negotiable biological necessity.

But some people don't care about their sleeping schedule which not only affects
their professional life but personal life as well.

If you don't know how it affects our day-to-day…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nhlefq/ysk_sleep_is_not_an_optional_lifestyle_luxury/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nhlefq/ysk_sleep_is_not_an_optional_lifestyle_luxury/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 10:47:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  Matthew Walker, an expert on the subject of sleep, said that sleep is a non-negotiable biological necessity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But some people don&amp;#39;t care about their sleeping schedule which not only affects their professional life but personal life as well. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don&amp;#39;t know how it affects our day-to-day activities and productivity, or hamper our biological cycle, then take some time and read some articles and watch some videos written and made by some experts. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have a look at this short video: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ted.com/talks/matt_walker_hacking_your_memory_with_sleep?utm_campaign=tedspread&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_source=tedcomshare&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full video:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ted.com/talks/matt_walker_sleep_is_your_superpower?utm_campaign=tedspread&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_source=tedcomshare&quot;&gt;Sleep is your superpower&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Many Universities have surplus department that sell to the public, and can be a good source of inexpensive furniture.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Furnishing a new place can be expensive, and Universities always have
stuff to get rid of. Sometimes even cool vintage stuff. At my local U surplus,
I've seen everything from basic office supplies, file cabinets, monitors, desks,
to pianos and weird old lab equipment. It's a crap-shoot, and…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nhaxni/ysk_many_universities_have_surplus_department/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nhaxni/ysk_many_universities_have_surplus_department/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 21:48:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Furnishing a new place can be expensive, and Universities always have stuff to get rid of. Sometimes even cool vintage stuff. At my local U surplus, I&amp;#39;ve seen everything from basic office supplies, file cabinets, monitors, desks, to pianos and weird old lab equipment. It&amp;#39;s a crap-shoot, and places may or may not be open at the moment, but take a look. You might find something great.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that washers need to be drained before you move or store them. An easy way to do this is by using a shop vac on the black hose on the back and letting it suck the water out.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Not draining a washer before it is stored or moved will not only make
it heavier, but it will cause water to stagnate and mold inside the tank. Even a
little bit of moisture in storage can wreck your whole world. All you have to do
is put a shop vac hose on the black drainage hose on the…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nh05u7/ysk_that_washers_need_to_be_drained_before_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nh05u7/ysk_that_washers_need_to_be_drained_before_you/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 18:05:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Not draining a washer before it is stored or moved will not only make it heavier, but it will cause water to stagnate and mold inside the tank. Even a little bit of moisture in storage can wreck your whole world. All you have to do is put a shop vac hose on the black drainage hose on the back of the washer make a tight seal with your hand or tape and let it suck the moisture out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: How your credit score is actually calculated]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: There is a lot of bad guidance floating around about what you should
and should not do with regards to credit.

This post will focus on the FICO Score since it is the most prolific type of
credit score used today. So, what is a FICO score? First, FICO stands for the
Fair Isaac Corporation.…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ngklcz/ysk_how_your_credit_score_is_actually_calculated/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ngklcz/ysk_how_your_credit_score_is_actually_calculated/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 08:55:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: There is a lot of bad guidance floating around about what you should and should not do with regards to credit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This post will focus on the FICO Score since it is the most prolific type of credit score used today. So, what is a FICO score?  First, FICO stands for the Fair Isaac Corporation. The FICO score was created in 1989 as a standardized way for lenders to interpret your credit report and determine whether or not to give you a loan.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How is a FICO score different than a credit report? A FICO score is simply a summarized version of your credit report. Your credit report lists all your credit history, but it doesn’t keep track of everything forever. Good credit is maintained for 10 years and bad credit is tracked for 7. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s on your credit report? If you have a credit card, auto loan, or mortgage all of that will be included. Why does your score matter? A quick caveat, if you follow Dave Ramsey’s philosophy, be aware an undeterminable score (AKA a score of 0) is very different from having a bad score. Dave cites 6-12 months after you close your last account to reach an undeterminable score, but I was not able to verify this number with a third party. If that’s what you want to do, that’s perfectly fine, but your credit score will potentially affect you until it reaches “zero”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some areas your score will affect: Better terms when you get a loan, lower insurance premiums, the ability to rent in some apartment complexes, potentially new jobs who require a credit check on new employees. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your FICO score is composed of five categories: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Payment history (35% of your scores) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amounts owed (30% of your scores) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Length of credit history (15% of your scores) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New credit (10% of your scores) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Credit mix (10% of your scores) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you get your credit score? There are lots of free and paid ways to get your score, but the easiest is probably through your credit card company of choice. Personally, with AMEX I can check my credit score whenever I want through their website. To get your actual credit report the three big credit bureaus: Experian, Equifax, and TransUnion offer your credit report (different from your credit score) once each year for free as mandated by federal law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, it’s a myth that checking your credit score will lower it. The reason why is because there are two different types of ways credit is checked: 1) Soft check occurs anytime you check your own score or when a lender checks your score to preapprove you 2) A hard credit check occurs when a lender checks your credit to determine if you met their lending criteria such as applying for a mortgage or new credit card, this would lower your credit score slightly &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What can you do to improve your FICO score? 1) Always pay in full and on time 2) Keep your credit utilization rate low, one way to reduce your credit utilization rate is to increase your credit limits. So long as you pay everything off every month you should be able to request a credit limit increase every 9 months 3) Keep your credit cards open for a long time 4) Only open new lines of credit when you need to, such as when applying for a mortgage &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some links you might find helpful!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FICO Score Website &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ficoscore.com/home&quot;&gt;https://www.ficoscore.com/home&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Free Credit Report &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.annualcreditreport.com/index.action&quot;&gt;https://www.annualcreditreport.com/index.action&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experian &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.experian.com/&quot;&gt;https://www.experian.com/&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Equifax &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.equifax.com/personal/&quot;&gt;https://www.equifax.com/personal/&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TransUnion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.transunion.com/&quot;&gt;https://www.transunion.com/&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And here is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/8vtnh5kYxj8&quot;&gt;video&lt;/a&gt; that goes a little more in depth than this post if you&amp;#39;re interested in learning more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK "Notorious" means famous for a bad reason. "Acclaimed" means famous for a good reason.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK:

Unless you're talking Christopher Wallace, if you say that someone is
"notorious" that implies that what they're known for is some well-known fault or
reprehensible action. Nobody wants to insult someone they meant to lift up.
Instead, if you want to compliment someone, use "acclaimed",…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ngni7j/ysk_notorious_means_famous_for_a_bad_reason/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ngni7j/ysk_notorious_means_famous_for_a_bad_reason/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 03:48:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unless you&amp;#39;re talking Christopher Wallace, if you say that someone is &amp;quot;notorious&amp;quot; that implies that what they&amp;#39;re known for is some well-known fault or reprehensible action. Nobody wants to insult someone they meant to lift up. Instead, if you want to compliment someone, use &amp;quot;acclaimed&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;celebrated&amp;quot;, or just plain &amp;quot;famous&amp;quot; (&lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; &amp;quot;infamous&amp;quot;). If you would put it on the outside of confectionery, it&amp;#39;s acclaimed. If you hear a news anchor use it to describe a serial killer, it&amp;#39;s notorious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Someone might be &lt;strong&gt;acclaimed&lt;/strong&gt; for making people smile and baking people pies but &lt;strong&gt;notorious&lt;/strong&gt; for &lt;em&gt;making&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;people smile&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;baking people-pies&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s a &lt;strong&gt;big&lt;/strong&gt; difference, and &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;you should know&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;it&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now you do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: You can easily control the text cursor on iPhone by holding down the spacebar and moving your thumb around]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: When trying to edit posts on Reddit, or trying to fix a typo in a link
on your mobile web browser, it can be a pain since you can’t really see the
cursor and when you let go of the cursor it snaps to odd places. Holding down
spacebar on the iPhone keyboard and moving your thumb around gives…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nfuzgs/ysk_you_can_easily_control_the_text_cursor_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nfuzgs/ysk_you_can_easily_control_the_text_cursor_on/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 09:19:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: When trying to edit posts on Reddit, or trying to fix a typo in a link on your mobile web browser, it can be a pain since you can’t really see the cursor and when you let go of the cursor it snaps to odd places. Holding down spacebar on the iPhone keyboard and moving your thumb around gives you full control of the cursor. I personally didn’t know this. Ever since Apple removed the magnifying glass when highlighting text, it has been a serious pain to navigate text.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: If you are sad that Avatar The last Airbender was so short, there is something else you could watch.]]></title><description><![CDATA[And no, I am not talking about Korra. I am talking about the underclaimed show,
The Dragon Prince. This show has many of the same writers and voice actors as
Avatar, and has an amazing plot and animation style. It is on Netflix and I have
no idea why it isn't promoted better.

Why YSK: People are…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nfuqlf/ysk_if_you_are_sad_that_avatar_the_last_airbender/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nfuqlf/ysk_if_you_are_sad_that_avatar_the_last_airbender/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 05:55:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;And no, I am not talking about &lt;em&gt;Korra&lt;/em&gt;. I am talking about the underclaimed show, &lt;em&gt;The Dragon Prince&lt;/em&gt;. This show has many of the same writers and voice actors as &lt;em&gt;Avatar&lt;/em&gt;, and has an amazing plot and animation style. It is on Netflix and I have no idea why it isn&amp;#39;t promoted better.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: People are obsessed with &lt;em&gt;Avatar&lt;/em&gt;, and yet for some reason many of them don&amp;#39;t know about &lt;em&gt;The Dragon Prince&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that if you're hoarding gas, it goes bad much faster than you might think]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: people are starting to freak out and hoard gas, but it probably won't
do them much good if a shortage really does develop.

While it varies a little based on composition (E15 goes bad faster than E10) and
how you store it, gas blended with ethanol
[https://www.jdpower.com/cars/shopping…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nan4dg/ysk_that_if_youre_hoarding_gas_it_goes_bad_much/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nan4dg/ysk_that_if_youre_hoarding_gas_it_goes_bad_much/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 04:04:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: people are starting to freak out and hoard gas, but it probably won&amp;#39;t do them much good if a shortage really does develop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While it varies a little based on composition (E15  goes bad faster than E10) and how you store it, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jdpower.com/cars/shopping-guides/how-long-can-gas-sit-in-a-car-before-it-goes-bad&quot;&gt;gas blended with ethanol&lt;/a&gt; (which is almost all gas) has a very short shelf life of less than three months. Ethanol is hydrophilic, so water will be introduced to your gas; at the same time as the compound itself oxidizes and degrades, creating non combustible residue. Even ethanol free premium only keeps for three to six months or so in the best possible conditions. A fuel stabilizer can extend that up to a year or more, but it reduces the octane rating of your gas and will generally &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/chsGBhB5g7o&quot;&gt;make your car run worse&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your car will &lt;em&gt;probably&lt;/em&gt; still run on old gas, but it won&amp;#39;t run well, and if you use enough of it, you are likely to damage injectors, or clog up a fuel filter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s plenty of gas, folks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK - When you ring your utilities company or mobile/ISP supplier, the agent on the other end of the line probably hates the company as much as you do.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK - Having worked in these industries a lot during my twenties I'd say
about 95% of the employees hated their job and the company purely because of the
way they tend to treat their employees. These companies tend to screw over the
customers and their staff.

Although you might be frustrated…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nfavm4/ysk_when_you_ring_your_utilities_company_or/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nfavm4/ysk_when_you_ring_your_utilities_company_or/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 17:23:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK - Having worked in these industries a lot during my twenties I&amp;#39;d say about 95% of the employees hated their job and the company purely because of the way they tend to treat their employees. These companies tend to screw over the customers and their staff. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although you might be frustrated try to keep your composure with the person on the end of the phone as you&amp;#39;re more likely to get what you need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that if you have medical debt from a non profit hospital, you can have the bill significantly reduced or completely written off if your income says you can't afford to pay it.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: It does not matter how old the debt is or if it was sent to
collections. It doesn't even matter if you had insurance when the bill was
created. As long as the non profit hospital owns the debt and it wasn't sold off
then you'll be eligible for financial assistance if you can't afford to pay…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nf2icd/ysk_that_if_you_have_medical_debt_from_a_non/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nf2icd/ysk_that_if_you_have_medical_debt_from_a_non/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 08:33:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It does not matter how old the debt is or if it was sent to collections. It doesn&amp;#39;t even matter if you had insurance when the bill was created. As long as the non profit hospital owns the debt and it wasn&amp;#39;t sold off then you&amp;#39;ll be eligible for financial assistance if you can&amp;#39;t afford to pay the debt at all. Don&amp;#39;t let them run you in circles. They will lie, they will tell you false info even if they&amp;#39;re not supposed to. The billing might claim &amp;quot;oh, we can&amp;#39;t do anything about it. The account was sent to &amp;quot;x&amp;quot; collection company. We can&amp;#39;t change anything anymore since we don&amp;#39;t have it, you have to speak with them.&amp;quot; If your bill is as little as 2 years old, the collections agency will tell you &amp;quot;there&amp;#39;s nothing we can do. The bill has aged out already. You can&amp;#39;t do payment plans on 2, 3, 4 year old bills. The most I can do is give you a discount but it has to be paid in lump sum.&amp;quot; This is a lie, and they will continue to lie and play dumb. My conversation with collections went something like &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Hi, I have a problem. I was eligible for free care at the hospital back in 2019 but the hospital never provided me with any information like they were supposed to (in my state, there is a law that says hospitals MUST provide patients with info on financial assistance) I only just recently got &amp;quot;x&amp;quot; health care and, had the hospital told me like they were required to, I would&amp;#39;ve had no bill&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;I don&amp;#39;t understand what you want me to do? Theres nothing you can do &lt;em&gt;my name&lt;/em&gt; these bills are 2, 3, years old. They&amp;#39;ve aged out already. And you have 22 accounts,  TWENTY TWO. I don&amp;#39;t mean to be rude but why would you wait so long to try and fix it?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;I did try and fix it before it was sent to collections but they gave me incorrect info. They told me my only options were a payment plan or pay in full. The hospital also never gave me financial assistance info like they&amp;#39;re supposed to&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;em&gt;my name&lt;/em&gt; you&amp;#39;re an adult, you&amp;#39;re supposed to find that info on your own. If you wanted to set up a payment plan or something then you should&amp;#39;ve dealt with this in a timely manner before it was sent to collections. Its aged out, you can&amp;#39;t do that anymore&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After arguing with billing and collections for 5 hours, someone finally connected me with a financial assistance counselor. She apologized profusely for the lies I was told and said the debt doesnt age out and the debt can still be dealt with. Apparently this is something she&amp;#39;s contacted Upper management about many times. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t let them lie to you and try to play stupid. Look up your states laws and never back down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: For a successful relationship, it's not just about the compromises. Most importantly, after each compromise, you should still like both yourself and the other person.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Everyone is saying that relationships require compromises. Healthy
relationships should be based on support and understanding, therefore
compromises should aim to better each other and the relationship. Admitting
mistakes and character weaknesses is difficult but leads to character…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nf0sbo/ysk_for_a_successful_relationship_its_not_just/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nf0sbo/ysk_for_a_successful_relationship_its_not_just/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 07:51:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Everyone is saying that relationships require compromises. Healthy relationships should be based on support and understanding, therefore compromises should aim to better each other and the relationship. Admitting mistakes and character weaknesses is difficult but leads to character growth. However, changing one&amp;#39;s self to fit a relationship to the point where you don&amp;#39;t like or recognise yourself is not healthy and will not lead to a long lasting relationship. Love yourself, love each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: BBQ brushes with metal bristles are deadly.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: The small wire pieces can break off and be ingested, and those little
shards can cause significant damage to your body, and require emergency surgery
for perforated organs. Keep your family safe this summer and use a plastic (or
wood, as others have pointed out) BBQ brush.

Article…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/neyc8s/ysk_bbq_brushes_with_metal_bristles_are_deadly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/neyc8s/ysk_bbq_brushes_with_metal_bristles_are_deadly/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 04:53:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: The small wire pieces can break off and be ingested, and those little shards can cause significant damage to your body, and require emergency surgery for perforated organs. Keep your family safe this summer and use a plastic (or wood, as others have pointed out) BBQ brush.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Article 1: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/manitoba/wire-barbecue-brushes-health-canada-review-1.4205997&quot;&gt;https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/manitoba/wire-barbecue-brushes-health-canada-review-1.4205997&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Article 2: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/manitoba/bbq-wire-brushes-new-standard-1.5456886&quot;&gt;https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/manitoba/bbq-wire-brushes-new-standard-1.5456886&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Article 3: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.consumerreports.org/food-safety/wire-grill-brush-danger/&quot;&gt;https://www.consumerreports.org/food-safety/wire-grill-brush-danger/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: If you're considering seeking professional help for mental issues but are not sure if you're feeling''bad enough'' to do so, definitely do it]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: I know a lot of people who have considered this, and one of the most
common things that held them back was the thought that they weren't feeling bad
enough to have the right to seek and receive help. It's important to recognize
your thoughts and feelings as real, and the fact that some…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/neh0yl/ysk_if_youre_considering_seeking_professional/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/neh0yl/ysk_if_youre_considering_seeking_professional/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 15:55:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I know a lot of people who have considered this, and one of the most common things that held them back was the thought that they weren&amp;#39;t feeling bad enough to have the right to seek and receive help. It&amp;#39;s important to recognize your thoughts and feelings as real, and the fact that some people might feel worse does not mean you don&amp;#39;t have the right to talk to someone about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I am lucky enough to live in a country where you can get a certain amount of hours for free. I am aware of the fact that in some countries it is not available at a reasonable price, which is pretty fucked up if you ask me. My point is just that if there are no other (financial) factors that hold you back, you should go for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: If you sit at a chair for hours a day, raise the armrests (if adjustable) such that they promote your shoulders to be even and your back straight]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: this will help prevent you from slouching to one arm rest for support
and overall promote a more healthy resting posture.

Reference:

https://www.physiomed.co.uk/uploads/guide/file/22/Physiomed_Sitting_Guide_-_Working_at_a_Desk_Digital.pdf]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nawktg/ysk_if_you_sit_at_a_chair_for_hours_a_day_raise/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nawktg/ysk_if_you_sit_at_a_chair_for_hours_a_day_raise/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 14:55:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: this will help prevent you from slouching to one arm rest for support and overall promote a more healthy resting posture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reference:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.physiomed.co.uk/uploads/guide/file/22/Physiomed_Sitting_Guide_-_Working_at_a_Desk_Digital.pdf&quot;&gt;https://www.physiomed.co.uk/uploads/guide/file/22/Physiomed_Sitting_Guide_-_Working_at_a_Desk_Digital.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that getting frequent car washes is important for your vehicle]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: The amount of dirt and grime that comes from the road builds up in
places you wouldn’t think of. Plus people who live in areas that have snow/ice
on the roads deal with the salt that their respective municipalities or counties
put on the roads to maintain them. Get a car wash at least once…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ne1ag7/ysk_that_getting_frequent_car_washes_is_important/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ne1ag7/ysk_that_getting_frequent_car_washes_is_important/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 01:49:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: The amount of dirt and grime that comes from the road builds up in places you wouldn’t think of. Plus people who live in areas that have snow/ice on the roads deal with the salt that their respective municipalities or counties put on the roads to maintain them. Get a car wash at least once a month regardless of the weather, and take the time to clean the undercarriage every 6 months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 40% of university students are addicted to their smartphone, which seriously damages their sleep]]></title><description><![CDATA[Context: article
[https://medlifestyle.news/2021/05/16/40-of-university-students-found-to-be-addicted-to-their-smartphone-study-says/]

Why YSK: Multiple studies have recently been published showing not only the
increase in 'smartphone addiction' amongst the general population, specifically
within…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ndzskv/ysk_40_of_university_students_are_addicted_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ndzskv/ysk_40_of_university_students_are_addicted_to/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 01:49:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Context: &lt;a href=&quot;https://medlifestyle.news/2021/05/16/40-of-university-students-found-to-be-addicted-to-their-smartphone-study-says/&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Multiple studies have recently been published showing not only the  increase in &amp;#39;smartphone addiction&amp;#39; amongst the general population,  specifically within the teenage and young adult age groups, but also showing a very particularly link between smartphone use and poor sleep  quality. We know that poor sleep quality has been linked to dementia, obesity, and lower cognitive function.  Smartphones have not been around long enough for researchers to be able to study the multi-decade effects that they may have, which is why it&amp;#39;s important that we stay cautious and aware of how long we are spending  on our devices and understand the known detriments that they can cause.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: only pouring water on your dog to cool them down could make things worse.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: This can weigh down the fur and create a layer of insulation that can
increase body temperature. If you are going to pour water on your dog please
also use fans/ventilation to utilize evaporative cooling.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ndqev9/ysk_only_pouring_water_on_your_dog_to_cool_them/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ndqev9/ysk_only_pouring_water_on_your_dog_to_cool_them/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 22:56:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This can weigh down the fur and create a layer of insulation that can increase body temperature.  If you are going to pour water on your dog please also use fans/ventilation to utilize evaporative cooling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK placing raw vegetables such as spring mix/mesclun and carrots within smoothies will allow one to eat more vegetables with less volume.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Many people can not bring themselves to eat vegetables, while mixing
them within a smoothie would allow more vegetables to be eaten in the same
volume as a non vegetable smoothie. Use banana as a sticky binder for the
vegetables within the smoothie.















Some like me can eat…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n84p90/ysk_placing_raw_vegetables_such_as_spring/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n84p90/ysk_placing_raw_vegetables_such_as_spring/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 07:31:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Many people can not bring themselves to eat vegetables, while mixing them within a smoothie would allow more vegetables to be eaten in the same volume as a non vegetable smoothie. Use banana as a sticky binder for the vegetables within the smoothie. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some like me can eat spring mix alone without dressing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Don't Forget to Apply Sunscreen on Cloudy Days]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Most clouds can at most block 50% of UV rays and thus sun rays can
still, unbeknownst to you, manage to damage your skin. 8000 Americans lose their
life to melanoma annually, try not to be one of them.

Source [https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3364536/]]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/natqa9/ysk_dont_forget_to_apply_sunscreen_on_cloudy_days/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/natqa9/ysk_dont_forget_to_apply_sunscreen_on_cloudy_days/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 03:49:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Most clouds can at most block 50% of UV rays and thus sun rays can still, unbeknownst to you, manage to damage your skin. 8000 Americans lose their life to melanoma annually, try not to be one of them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3364536/&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: You can learn a language for free by downloading these comprehensive audio lessons!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK:

I recently purchased a course in Italian from Living Language. It comes with 3
workbooks to follow along with during the audio lessons. The audio lessons are
provided via CD, but the website also states you can download the content if you
prefer. What I didn't realize until today is that…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n9c333/ysk_you_can_learn_a_language_for_free_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n9c333/ysk_you_can_learn_a_language_for_free_by/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 02:00:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently purchased a course in Italian from Living Language. It comes with 3 workbooks to follow along with during the audio lessons. The audio lessons are provided via CD, but the website also states you can download the content if you prefer. What I didn&amp;#39;t realize until today is that the downloadable content is just posted to their website and you do not need a referral or access code to download it! So there you have it. I paid for an Italian course, but you should all know you can access their downloads (of any available language) for free by visiting the Living Language website, selecting &amp;quot;Support&amp;quot; and then &amp;quot;Downloads&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*For best results, use the &amp;quot;Complete Edition&amp;quot; rather than &amp;quot;Basics&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: Linking for easy access, hope that is okay: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.livinglanguage.com/faq/downloads&quot;&gt;https://www.livinglanguage.com/faq/downloads&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and they also have free literature which I didn&amp;#39;t know either! &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.livinglanguage.com/additional&quot;&gt;https://www.livinglanguage.com/additional&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK used pizza boxes are almost never recyclable]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: According to the City of San José
[https://sanjoserecycles.org/guide/pizza-boxes/], "Greasy pizza boxes
contaminate clean recycling and are expensive for the recycling industry: it’s
estimated that contamination costs recyclers $700 million per year, because of
damaged machinery, the cost…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nas163/ysk_used_pizza_boxes_are_almost_never_recyclable/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nas163/ysk_used_pizza_boxes_are_almost_never_recyclable/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:41:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: According to &lt;a href=&quot;https://sanjoserecycles.org/guide/pizza-boxes/&quot;&gt;the City of San José&lt;/a&gt;, &amp;quot;&lt;em&gt;Greasy pizza boxes contaminate clean recycling and are expensive for the recycling industry: it’s estimated that contamination costs recyclers $700 million per year, because of damaged machinery, the cost of disposing of non-recyclable materials and wasted time.&lt;/em&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, even if your pizza box has recycle logos on it, it&amp;#39;s probably not,  because those logos are &lt;em&gt;marketing&lt;/em&gt;, not informational. A clean pristine pizza box &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; recyclable and that&amp;#39;s why they they label it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your municipality has a &amp;quot;green bin&amp;quot;, a bin for compost and organic waste, that might be the place to discard pizza boxes. As is the case for many assumed-recycleable items, check the website to see where your waste-collectors want it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: The weird smelling hand sanitizer that has recently become popular in stores uses ethyl alcohol instead of isopropyl alcohol. If you want to avoid the bad smell, look at the "Active Ingredient" section to confirm that it doesn't include ethyl alcohol.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Everyone hates the smell of cheap drinking alcohol, but it's usually
too late by the time you've put the sanitizer on your hands. A quick check
before you buy or use a bottle of hand sanitizer will save you the bad
experience of smelling Crystal Palace for the next 15 minutes. I'm afraid…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nchvkj/ysk_the_weird_smelling_hand_sanitizer_that_has/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nchvkj/ysk_the_weird_smelling_hand_sanitizer_that_has/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 22:34:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Everyone hates the smell of cheap drinking alcohol, but it&amp;#39;s usually too late by the time you&amp;#39;ve put the sanitizer on your hands. A quick check before you buy or use a bottle of hand sanitizer will save you the bad experience of smelling Crystal Palace for the next 15 minutes.
I&amp;#39;m afraid I can&amp;#39;t help with that weird goopy consistency that some brands have. You&amp;#39;re on your own for that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>