<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 04:35:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that Mother’s Day (US) is next Sunday, May 9.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: if you’re going to mail something, you need to send it soon.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n1tqzn/ysk_that_mothers_day_us_is_next_sunday_may_9/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n1tqzn/ysk_that_mothers_day_us_is_next_sunday_may_9/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 18:00:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: if you’re going to mail something, you need to send it soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: If you pay for something in cash and you're asked "Did you give me a $X bill?", it's to save the staff member's job. Just say yes or no.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: (Note: I'm from the US) When you hand money to a staff member at any
establishment, they should be asking you to verify how much you gave them. The
last thing they need is to give you $6 in change because you gave them a $10
bill, and have you yell at them because you thought you handed…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n1oq16/ysk_if_you_pay_for_something_in_cash_and_youre/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n1oq16/ysk_if_you_pay_for_something_in_cash_and_youre/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 09:52:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: (Note: I&amp;#39;m from the US) When you hand money to a staff member at any establishment, they should be asking you to verify how much you gave them. The last thing they need is to give you $6 in change because you gave them a $10 bill, and have you yell at them because you thought you handed them a $20 bill (and should therefore get $16 in change).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apparently at my job (I&amp;#39;m a pharmacy tech), someone in the drive-thru left a terrible review because he gave me a $10 bill to pay for a $4 medication, and I had the audacity to ask him &amp;quot;you sent me a $10 bill, correct?&amp;quot; He said it was &amp;quot;bizarre and unnecessary&amp;quot;. He gave us a 1/10 JUST for that. Don&amp;#39;t be that guy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best thing is to tell them exactly what you&amp;#39;re giving them right from the get-go. &amp;quot;Here&amp;#39;s a $20&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;ve got a dollar and 15 cents here&amp;quot; removes any doubts about what money has been exchanged, and prevents issues about money and change down the line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Someone made a good point that if you&amp;#39;re an employee, you can just state the amount of money the customer gave you, no need to ask them to verify the amount. Saying &amp;quot;out of a $20&amp;quot; is fine, and then the customer can correct you if it&amp;#39;s wrong. I do that when it&amp;#39;s a face-to-face transaction, but in this scenario, the patient was in the far drive-thru lane so I had to make sure he heard me correctly, hence why I needed to phrase it as a question&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that "etc" is short for "et cetera" and is pronounced that way, not "eck cetera”]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: This is a small but extremely common mispronunciation, I’ve heard it
pronounced this way by television presenters, lecturers, singers, and many more.
Oftentimes the distinction is barely audible, and in informal speech it wouldn’t
matter. BUT if delivering a formal speech or something…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n16and/ysk_that_etc_is_short_for_et_cetera_and_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n16and/ysk_that_etc_is_short_for_et_cetera_and_is/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 07:46:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This is a small but extremely common mispronunciation, I’ve heard it pronounced this way by television presenters, lecturers, singers, and many more. Oftentimes the distinction is barely audible, and in informal speech it wouldn’t matter. BUT if delivering a formal speech or something similar, it’s definitely worth knowing this so your pronunciation is impeccable, and so any listeners who are aware of this aren’t distracted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK That you can check whether specific passwords have been exposed in a databreach]]></title><description><![CDATA[There are new data breaches occurring everyday and it's pretty easy to make sure
you stay ahead of it. This site: https://breachdirectory.tk
[https://breachdirectory.tk/] uses AI to monitor and parse new data breaches
automatically. Just enter your email or username and it will tell you which…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0pr2o/ysk_that_you_can_check_whether_specific_passwords/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0pr2o/ysk_that_you_can_check_whether_specific_passwords/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 03:35:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are new data breaches occurring everyday and it&amp;#39;s pretty easy to make sure you stay ahead of it. This site: &lt;a href=&quot;https://breachdirectory.tk/&quot;&gt;https://breachdirectory.tk&lt;/a&gt; uses AI to monitor and parse new data breaches automatically. Just enter your email or username and it will tell you which of your passwords have been leaked and from where. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK? It&amp;#39;s important to make sure you are using passwords that have not been leaked before to protect yourself from account hijacking and credential stuffing attacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: If a woman is following you closely in a store, it means the person accompanying them is likely stalking them. And they are reaching out for help.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: I've seen it time and time again on the internet. Usually with a woman
walking up to someone they don't know, with a guy following behind her. If it
weren't for my girlfriend noticing I likely wouldn't of noticed when it happened
to me today. I was getting a Red Bull at the market, and a…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n1hnyq/ysk_if_a_woman_is_following_you_closely_in_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n1hnyq/ysk_if_a_woman_is_following_you_closely_in_a/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 03:00:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I&amp;#39;ve seen it time and time again on the internet. Usually with a woman walking up to someone they don&amp;#39;t know, with a guy following behind her. If it weren&amp;#39;t for my girlfriend noticing I likely wouldn&amp;#39;t of noticed when it happened to me today. I was getting a Red Bull at the market, and a young girl came very close to me with who I thought was her boyfriend. I don&amp;#39;t pay much attention, and move out of their way because I figured they wanted to get to the drinks in front of me. I then walk 10 feet over to a cooler to get some salami motz rolls. And again, the girl is right by my side. It still didn&amp;#39;t click with me until my girlfriend whispered in my ear that this guy is stalking her. Apparently my girlfriend overheard him ask her how old she is, and she said &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m in High school&amp;quot; and him saying &amp;quot;Let&amp;#39;s get a coffee&amp;quot;. So I stood right there and didn&amp;#39;t say a word to either of them, until the guy ran off to the other side of the store. I watched the guy from there on, and made sure the girl wasn&amp;#39;t being followed by him afterwards and all was well. I will always notice the signs from here on out, and I hope you all will take notice too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK theres a browser called "Torch" that has a built in video downloader that works for 99% of videos on the web.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Title +Its built off chrome and is pretty fast. I couldn't find much on
the web about it but the consensus seems to be that torch is safe, but probably
records your data.

just trying to throw them a bone because downloading any sort of videos nowadays
is a huge pain in the ass.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n16xs7/ysk_theres_a_browser_called_torch_that_has_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n16xs7/ysk_theres_a_browser_called_torch_that_has_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 22:37:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Title +Its built off chrome and is pretty fast. I couldn&amp;#39;t find much on the web about it but the consensus seems to be that torch is safe, but probably records your data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;just trying to throw them a bone because downloading any sort of videos nowadays is a huge pain in the ass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: If you are taking care of a loved one who is chronically ill or disabled there are programs that will pay you to become an unskilled caregiver]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: you shouldn't have to choose between making a living and taking care of
your loved one. You don't need credentials or any type of certification to
become an unskilled caregiver.

My grandma was diagnosed with lung cancer in January, and my grandpa's dementia
has gotten so much worse as a…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n13iok/ysk_if_you_are_taking_care_of_a_loved_one_who_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n13iok/ysk_if_you_are_taking_care_of_a_loved_one_who_is/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:25:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: you shouldn&amp;#39;t have to choose between making a living and taking care of your loved one. You don&amp;#39;t need credentials or any type of certification to become an unskilled caregiver.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My grandma was diagnosed with lung cancer in January, and my grandpa&amp;#39;s dementia has gotten so much worse as a result. Its come to the point where they need someone there to help out and take care of them just about 24/7. I quit my job in February so I can take care of them full time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naturally, I was worried about how I was gonna make my bills every month. I refuse to choose one or the other and I made that decision as soon as I committed to taking care of them. They went above and beyond as far as helping raise me when I was a kid. My mother struggled with drug addiction for most of her life and they took me on to raise when I was about 8 without any hesitation, even though they were both past 65 at that point. They provided me with the opportunity to be stable enough to go on and graduate high school. So honestly I feel honored to have this opportunity even if the situation is shitty. Its the least I can do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you find yourself in a similar situation, just know that there are programs that will enable you to take care of your loved ones when they need you most without the possibility of becoming homeless in the process. Im sure the programs vary from state to state, Im in Texas and the program is through Medicaid. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone should know about this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: If you receive a packet from the Nielsen Family, it’s not junk mail. Often times there’s 2-5 dollars of cash in the envelope. You can earn more by sending in logs of what TV shows you watch.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’ve been selected before and earned a small bit of cash. Why YSK? You’re
throwing away money!]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0rr8m/ysk_if_you_receive_a_packet_from_the_nielsen/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0rr8m/ysk_if_you_receive_a_packet_from_the_nielsen/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 06:59:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been selected before and earned a small bit of cash. Why YSK? You’re throwing away money!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that when buying a bra, it should fit you on the last hook (giving you the largest band)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: When purchasing a new bra, it should fit on the last hook because the
elastic in the band will naturally stretch over time. You should be gradually
moving the hook in towards the first one as this occurs so that your bra will
continue to fit you correctly for a longer span of time.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzavvd/ysk_that_when_buying_a_bra_it_should_fit_you_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzavvd/ysk_that_when_buying_a_bra_it_should_fit_you_on/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 04:47:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: When purchasing a new bra, it should fit on the last hook because the elastic in the band will naturally stretch over time. You should be gradually moving the hook in towards the first one as this occurs so that your bra will continue to fit you correctly for a longer span of time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK if you randomly see a dryer sheet in the back of your mailbox, your mail carrier put it there for a reason]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: it could save your carrier from being stung

Letter Carrier here.

We’re almost to the month of May which means nice weather, hanging out outside,
school closing for the summer, and the return of those dastardly devils:
Yellowjackets and Wasps.

I’m sure you’ve noticed. But just in case you…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0qs06/ysk_if_you_randomly_see_a_dryer_sheet_in_the_back/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0qs06/ysk_if_you_randomly_see_a_dryer_sheet_in_the_back/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 01:18:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: it could save your carrier from being stung&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Letter Carrier here. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re almost to the month of May which means nice weather, hanging out outside, school closing for the summer, and the return of those dastardly devils: Yellowjackets and Wasps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m sure you’ve noticed. But just in case you haven’t, this time of the year wasps and Yellowjackets (especially Yellowjackets) like to make nests inside of mailboxes. In a lot of places this time of the year, it’s just beginning to warm up outside, but it’s still fairly cold at night. So mailboxes provide nice, easy shelter for them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t tell you how many times, especially during this part of the year, where I’ve opened up a box to see a little nest with 3-5 Yellowjackets just chillin. If I’m really unlucky, they will have made their nest at the very back of the box so I wind up sticking my hand in not knowing they are there. We all know how temperamental these little douchebags are and merely existing in their presence is enough to piss them off. Last year alone I was stung 10 times on 10 separate occasions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getting to my point. We’ve found that they hate scented dryer sheets. If we encounter a box that is a problem for nests, we’ll often put one in there and it does the trick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So please, if you one day randomly see a dryer sheet at the back of your mailbox, just know that your carrier more than likely put it there to deter these Satanic creatures from building their home in it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK "every day" vs "everyday"]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: "every day" means recurring every 24 hours or so and "everyday" means
mundane, boring or trite. That space between the words actually changes the
meaning of your sentence and using the correct version makes your intent clearer
and stops people from thinking you're an idiot.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0mxr2/ysk_every_day_vs_everyday/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0mxr2/ysk_every_day_vs_everyday/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 23:50:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: &amp;quot;every day&amp;quot; means recurring every 24 hours or so and &amp;quot;everyday&amp;quot; means mundane, boring or trite. That space between the words actually changes the meaning of your sentence and using the correct version makes your intent clearer and stops people from thinking you&amp;#39;re an idiot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK You are not legally required to take a breathalyzer while on foot in most US states.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Police officers can arrest you for public intoxication if, and only if,
you consent to taking a breathalyzer test and you fail the test. Typically, the
officer will just start telling you instructions about how to take the
breathalyzer without ever asking for consent. If you kindly decline…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0e58r/ysk_you_are_not_legally_required_to_take_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0e58r/ysk_you_are_not_legally_required_to_take_a/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 21:47:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Police officers can arrest you for public intoxication if, and only if, you consent to taking a breathalyzer test and you fail the test. Typically, the officer will just start telling you instructions about how to take the breathalyzer without ever asking for consent. If you kindly decline the test, there is little they can do, assuming you have not broken any laws.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: A New Car will depreciate in value rapidly.]]></title><description><![CDATA[why YSK: you could be paying lots of extra money for essentially the same car.

The price difference between a new car and one that is used and 1 or 2 years old
is very big. Why? because when you buy a car it loses value because it's no
longer new, secondly just about after year when the next model…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mw9wec/ysk_a_new_car_will_depreciate_in_value_rapidly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mw9wec/ysk_a_new_car_will_depreciate_in_value_rapidly/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 18:35:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;why YSK: you could be paying lots of extra money for essentially the same car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The price difference between a new car and one that is used and 1 or 2 years old is very big. Why? because when you buy a car it loses value because it&amp;#39;s no longer new, secondly just about after year when the next model releases it&amp;#39;s now  not a new car anymore and never will be. Suddenly your car has depreciated by a huge chunk it&amp;#39;s worth a LOT LESS. But by buying a used car you can skip those problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So just buy your dream car but buy one that is 1 or 2 years(or more) old.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that giving money to food pantries is a more effective way to donate than donating food]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: If you want to maximize the positive impact you can make for your
fellow beings, then giving cash instead of goods (especially food,) can be much
more effective.

For example, here are six reasons for giving money instead of food to food
pantries:

 1. Money is much cheaper to store than…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0i1cy/ysk_that_giving_money_to_food_pantries_is_a_more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0i1cy/ysk_that_giving_money_to_food_pantries_is_a_more/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 17:54:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  If you want to maximize the positive impact you can make for your fellow beings, then giving cash instead of goods (especially food,) can be much more effective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, here are six reasons for giving money instead of food to food pantries:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Money is much cheaper to store than food: less space; doesn&amp;#39;t need refrigeration; doesn&amp;#39;t require manual labor to manage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Even canned goods eventually expire. Cash doesn&amp;#39;t.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The types of food you give may not be what is needed by the recipient families. Everybody donates cans of beans. However, did you know that baby formula is one of the most needed foods? People tend to give what&amp;#39;s in their pantry, which just happens to be what they bought and haven&amp;#39;t eaten.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Food pantries get discounts on their purchases. They can make your dollars go farther in helping needy people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Food pantries have bills, too. They still pay rent, employees, transportation, utilities, just like any other operation. They can&amp;#39;t deliver their services without money to pay for those. It&amp;#39;s hard to convince the electric company to taken payment in cans of beans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Food pantries often do much more than provide food. Baby diapers, for example. Also, they will often help their recipients financially, such as utility bill assistance and housing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When giving cash, don&amp;#39;t forget to verify the legitimacy and effectiveness of the organization first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK Biodegradable plastics can still pollute the environment.]]></title><description><![CDATA[In order for biodegradable plastics (which are different from Bioplastics) to
decompose properly they need to be disposed of in a special way:

> This typically involves temperatures of over 50°C and the right combination of
moisture, air and microbes – meaning that these plastics won’t break down…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0aa9f/ysk_biodegradable_plastics_can_still_pollute_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0aa9f/ysk_biodegradable_plastics_can_still_pollute_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 10:51:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;In order for biodegradable plastics (which are different from Bioplastics) to decompose properly they need to be disposed of in a special way:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt; This typically involves temperatures of over 50°C and the right combination of moisture, air and microbes – meaning that these plastics won’t break down if left in the ocean or on domestic compost heaps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencefocus.com/science/what-does-biodegradable-plastic-degrade-into/&quot;&gt;https://www.sciencefocus.com/science/what-does-biodegradable-plastic-degrade-into/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK? You should make sure when you dispose of Biodegradable plastics that they are being disposed of properly, just putting them in the trash is a bad idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK McDonald's ice cream machines are made to break easily]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: McDonald's employees are not being lazy. The ice cream machines that
always seem to break down are designed to malfunction. They're purposefully
difficult for employees to fix because the machine's manufacturer makes a profit
whenever McDonald's calls in their repair…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzx36r/ysk_mcdonalds_ice_cream_machines_are_made_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzx36r/ysk_mcdonalds_ice_cream_machines_are_made_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 23:50:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; McDonald&amp;#39;s employees are not being lazy. The ice cream machines that always seem to break down are designed to malfunction. They&amp;#39;re purposefully difficult for employees to fix because the machine&amp;#39;s manufacturer makes a profit whenever McDonald&amp;#39;s calls in their repair technicians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McDonald’s franchisees can only purchase one type of ice cream machine: the Taylor ice cream machine that’s specifically designed for McDonald’s. This particular machine is very difficult to repair. When it malfunctions, the screen shows a series of cryptic error codes. The manual is long, technical, and contains little helpful information. Most “solutions” it proposes end up being “call a technician.” McDonald’s has a contract with Taylor and franchisees can only call an authorized Taylor technician. The technician has their own handbook and secret menu to operate the machine. Employees are not allowed to have this better manual; only Taylor technicians can see it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Calling in a Taylor repairman costs the franchisee hundreds of dollars an hour. Despite the fact that Taylor has worked with the McDonald’s corporation since the beginning, none of their system updates help the problem. Some of them make the error codes longer and more cryptic. McDonald’s partnership with Taylor means that the corporate heads benefit from Taylor&amp;#39;s success. 25% of Taylor’s profits come from repairs. So when the machine breaks down, Taylor makes a profit repairing it, and the McDonald&amp;#39;s corporate leaders also profit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McDonald’s and Taylor continue to prioritize maximizing profit at the expense of franchisees, employees, and customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s a video released four days ago explaining the investigative journalism behind this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/SrDEtSlqJC4&quot;&gt;The REAL reason Mcdonald’s Ice Cream Machines are Always Broken&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that if you are a stay at home parent, the work you do, while it holds no economic value, holds a lot of monetary value when you pay someone else to do it. You need life insurance.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Imagine paying someone to do what you do every day for an entire year.
On average, a Nanny can make around $30,000 a year, and daycare can cost around
$10,000 per year, but these costs don’t get close to the monetary value of the
combined work and effort you provide. Although, according to…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzv2n3/ysk_that_if_you_are_a_stay_at_home_parent_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzv2n3/ysk_that_if_you_are_a_stay_at_home_parent_the/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 22:55:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Imagine paying someone to do what you do every day for an entire year. On average, a Nanny can make around $30,000 a year, and daycare can cost around $10,000 per year, but these costs don’t get close to the monetary value of the combined work and effort you provide. Although, according to the economy, your work doesn’t hold economic value, your work is incredibly valuable and will cost a lot to replace. You need about 10x the cost of your work in term life insurance to cover the costs of the value that you provide to your kids and/or to your home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that when the gas pump tells you to see the cashier, you can just cancel the transaction and run your card as credit.]]></title><description><![CDATA[WHY YSK: If you do not know, some gas station pumps will say "please see
cashier" after you use a debit card. I have been hearing a lot of people
complaining about this saying they do not want to walk inside because they are
either antisocial or I myself for instance am just lazy. Well you are in…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mznm0s/ysk_that_when_the_gas_pump_tells_you_to_see_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mznm0s/ysk_that_when_the_gas_pump_tells_you_to_see_the/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 20:48:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK: If you do not know, some gas station pumps will say &amp;quot;please see cashier&amp;quot; after you use a debit card. I have been hearing a lot of people complaining about this saying they do not want to walk inside because they are either antisocial or I myself for instance am just lazy. Well you are in luck because I have never had to actually go inside the gas station because when that message appears simply hit the cancel button on the keypad and wait. Then reinsert your card and do not run your card as debit even though it is a debit card. There should be an instruction on how to run as credit and this is what you want to do. You may have to enter a zip code, you may not. Either way you now can pump your gas in peace without having to go inside. None of my friends or family knew this was possible and have been going inside to pay for their gas for as long as they can remember so I hope this helps someone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Someone said this is probably just a US/ North American issue! Sorry, I&amp;#39;m from a small town in Mississippi and can sometimes forget the world around me&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: If you know someone who is abusive and you tell a victim of that abuser you don't want to take sides, you ARE taking a side. You are choosing the abuser's side.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Saying that to a victim is you trying to justify your decision or make
yourself feel better directly at the victim’s expense. Stop it. Make your
choices, process all of the weird feelings that come up when you find out that
your friend hurts other people on your own, without the abuse…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzv3y6/ysk_if_you_know_someone_who_is_abusive_and_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzv3y6/ysk_if_you_know_someone_who_is_abusive_and_you/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 19:43:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: 
Saying that to a victim is you trying to justify your decision or make yourself feel better directly at the victim’s expense. Stop it. Make your choices, process all of the weird feelings that come up when you find out that your friend hurts other people on your own, without the abuse victim as your audience/feelingshelper. Don’t ask abuse victims for their blessing to keep your monthly “Abuser Bowling Night” going or do your processing of your feelings on their time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Having good posture and ergonomics is actually very serious]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Having poor posture and ergonomics can cause a lot of surprising
problems throughout your body, and it doesn't wait until you're elderly to show
up. Hopefully a lot of people know this already, but if you're like I was a few
months ago, you might think of posture like some people think of…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzg70w/ysk_having_good_posture_and_ergonomics_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzg70w/ysk_having_good_posture_and_ergonomics_is/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 09:41:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Having poor posture and ergonomics can cause a lot of surprising problems throughout your body, and it doesn&amp;#39;t wait until you&amp;#39;re elderly to show up. Hopefully a lot of people know this already, but if you&amp;#39;re like I was a few months ago, you might think of posture like some people think of diet, sort of like &amp;quot;this won&amp;#39;t affect me until I&amp;#39;m older, so I don&amp;#39;t need to worry about it yet&amp;quot; (not that that&amp;#39;s a good mindset either).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some things that can happen from poor posture are degenerated discs, upper-crossed syndrome, thoracic outlet syndrome (this can result in blot clots and aneurysms, no lie), arthritis, all kinds of pinched nerves, fatigue, and many other painful conditions that can require physical therapy, medications, and even surgery.  I couldn&amp;#39;t find an academic article about this that fits well, but here&amp;#39;s something &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/adult-health/in-depth/posture-align-yourself-for-good-health/art-20269950&quot;&gt;from the Mayo Clinic&lt;/a&gt; about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To prevent these problems, you should of course have a proper ergonomic setup for work/gaming/whatever you&amp;#39;re doing. Sitting on a yoga ball or using a standing desk is a good idea. When driving, try to adjust your seat properly. Even when standing, walking around, and relaxing on your couch try to have your shoulder blades down and together, your shoulders back, and your neck back so that your ears align with your shoulders. Also, this is slightly unrelated, but drinking enough water everyday &lt;a href=&quot;https://cospineandjoint.com/2018/11/hydration-important-spinal-health/&quot;&gt;helps keep your spinal discs healthy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not in the medical field, so anyone who knows more about this is of course welcome to correct me on stuff. I just thought I&amp;#39;d spread the word in case it can help anyone prevent their own problems. I for one didn&amp;#39;t know all this before, and now I&amp;#39;m sitting here, only in my 20s, with tingly, tired arms and a heating pad on my shoulder because I had bad ergonomics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be well everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK this to begin mastering public speaking. Is public speaking a fear of yours, or something you lament? I want you to know this:]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Public speaking proficiently improves your confidence and ability to
lead. You will need it to manage people and lead teams in the future.

A decade of Public speaking to crowds up to 1000 people has taught me alot about
myself and Public speaking. Here are some the points to help you.

-Do…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/myaesj/ysk_this_to_begin_mastering_public_speaking_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/myaesj/ysk_this_to_begin_mastering_public_speaking_is/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 08:53:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Public speaking proficiently improves your confidence and ability to lead. You will need it to manage people and lead teams in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A decade of Public speaking to crowds up to 1000 people has taught me alot about myself and Public speaking. Here are some the points to help you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Do your prep, know your material.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Do your rehearsal without notes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Butterflys/anxiety:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have butterflys, 👍good. That feeling is great, it focuses you, adrenaline is preparing for a fight/flight. I do not feel that anymore so I actually take an energy drink immediately before an important class/presentation to simulate that hyperness (not reccomended for you), just embrace this feeling it benefits you and you will miss it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Getting sweaty/sick:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you feel nervous think about the guy in the back playing candy crush, why would you be afraid of him? He&amp;#39;s a jerk, not listening, but also not judging, just and oxygen thief.  The opposite is true as well, someone taking notes and making eye contact with you wants to hear what you have to say next and is supporting you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-The group you are speaking to is far smaller than you realize:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you get better you can command the room and have most people&amp;#39;s attention for small spans. You cannot have everyone&amp;#39;s attention for 20-30 minutes, people are just not wired that way. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Generally half of the audience isn&amp;#39;t listening, a good portion of the audience lack the mental capacity or self confidence to be judging you and listening to you at the same time.  The attentive ones you are able to make eye contact with are engaged and rooting for you, because they want to hear what&amp;#39;s next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this is some type of public speaking class where everybody is taking turns, 75% of the class you are speaking to has knots in their stomach about their own presentation and are reciting their nore cards in their head. The teacher, is a Saint and superhuman if you think they can focus on every word of 25 consecutive presentations about what someone did over summer vacation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-The person judging you most harshly is you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-You are going to crush it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: put your blinker on BEFORE you hit the brakes]]></title><description><![CDATA[Don't do both simultaneously.

WHY YSK: Not only will this prevent you from getting rear-ended by someone
driving & not paying attention behind you, but it'll also greatly increase the
flow of traffic. It's extremely difficult for truck drivers to stop on a dime
and, likewise, takes a long time to…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzd6bp/ysk_put_your_blinker_on_before_you_hit_the_brakes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzd6bp/ysk_put_your_blinker_on_before_you_hit_the_brakes/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 03:57:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t do both simultaneously. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK: Not only will this prevent you from getting rear-ended by someone driving &amp;amp; not paying attention behind you, but it&amp;#39;ll also greatly increase the flow of traffic. It&amp;#39;s extremely difficult for truck drivers to stop on a dime and, likewise, takes a long time to crawl back up to cruising speed (because their vehicles &amp;amp; their tow loads weigh a lot more than you realize they do). Learn how your vehicle operates. You are not the only one using the road. Everyone wants to make it to their destination on time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that Google maps will no longer always show you the fastest route to your destination by default.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: it's a pain having to remember to check and select the faster route.
Google maps is starting to default to displaying the route with the lightest
emissions rather than the shortest travel time. Apparently it's only when the
ETA for both routes is similar, but nearly 10 minutes is…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mz7nww/ysk_that_google_maps_will_no_longer_always_show/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mz7nww/ysk_that_google_maps_will_no_longer_always_show/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 23:44:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: it&amp;#39;s a pain having to remember to check and select the faster route.
Google maps is starting to default to displaying the route with the lightest emissions rather than the shortest travel time.
Apparently it&amp;#39;s only when the ETA for both routes is similar, but nearly 10 minutes is significant for my morning commute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: There are tons of websites to get scientific articles, books, news articles, and journals for FREE! Links below :)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Those scientific article paywalls are BS. None of that goes to the
actual authors and researchers. Paywalls on news articles are stupid too.
Luckily, it's not too hard to get around that! Especially if you're a student,
these sites are amazing.

outline.com [https://outline.com/] - Place…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/myhvlk/ysk_there_are_tons_of_websites_to_get_scientific/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/myhvlk/ysk_there_are_tons_of_websites_to_get_scientific/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 13:45:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Those scientific article paywalls are BS. None of that goes to the actual authors and researchers. Paywalls on news articles are stupid too. Luckily, it&amp;#39;s not too hard to get around that! Especially if you&amp;#39;re a student, these sites are amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://outline.com/&quot;&gt;outline.com&lt;/a&gt; - Place &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.outline.com/&quot;&gt;www.outline.com/&lt;/a&gt; before any news article URL behind a paywall, and it&amp;#39;ll give you a non-ad-covered, annotateable, and easily shareable version!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://libgen.rs/&quot;&gt;libgen.rs&lt;/a&gt; - Library Genesis, a search engine for scientific articles, books, comics, and magazines&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sci-hub.do/&quot;&gt;sci-hub.do&lt;/a&gt; - Sci-Hub, specifically for research articles! You can stick in the URL or DOI and be taken right to the document!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://z-lib.org/&quot;&gt;z-lib.org&lt;/a&gt; - Z-library, another big search engine for books/articles!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For most of these, you don&amp;#39;t have to download the actual document unless you want to, you can read it in-browser as well! I&amp;#39;ve never had any issues with any downloads from these sites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK, if you're going camping/hiking with young children, avoid dressing them in camouflage or neutral colors.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Children go missing while camping or on nature outings often. Dressing
them in camouflage will only hinder them from being found if they were to wind
up lost. Bright colors are much easier to locate , and keeps the child safer
around off road vehicles anf hunting activities.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/myof6t/ysk_if_youre_going_campinghiking_with_young/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/myof6t/ysk_if_youre_going_campinghiking_with_young/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 05:43:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Children go missing while camping or on nature outings often. Dressing them in camouflage will only hinder them from being found if they were to wind up lost. Bright colors are much easier to locate , and keeps the child safer around off road vehicles anf hunting activities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK Financial Guru Robert Kiyosaki, known best for his book "Rich Dad, Poor Dad" is the subject of a class action suit filed by people who attended his seminars and was featured by CBC in an expose on scams and his company Rich Global LLC filed for bankruptcy in 2012]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: If you are reading a self-help book, it is most likely written by a
proven professional scammer or someone who's only accomplishments in life are
writing self-help books. Their advice, CDs, DVDs, seminars, workshops will have
no lasting impact on you whatsoever. At best, they are placebos.…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mykdsy/ysk_financial_guru_robert_kiyosaki_known_best_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mykdsy/ysk_financial_guru_robert_kiyosaki_known_best_for/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 02:50:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If you are reading a self-help book, it is most likely written by a  proven professional scammer or someone who&amp;#39;s only accomplishments in  life are writing self-help books. Their advice, CDs, DVDs, seminars,  workshops will have no lasting impact on you whatsoever. At best, they  are placebos. People can be so gulable when searching for help. Do not  make the mistake of continuously looking for &amp;quot;that one self-help book&amp;quot;  that will change your life. Get better at doing searches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Research  the author&amp;#39;s background before reading a book. Question the &amp;quot;facts&amp;quot; you  are presented while reading a book. Make actions according to what  you&amp;#39;ve learned from a book, if there are any. Else, you&amp;#39;d be wasting a  lot of time reading trashy books while allowing trash into your mind and  then wonder why you&amp;#39;re feeling worse before you started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Kiyosaki&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Kiyosaki&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK- If you hear a bell ringing or a beeping from an closed elevator or shaft, you should call for help.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Most (all?) elevators have an "Alarm" button inside the cab as a
secondary alert if the phone doesn't work. This will ring, beep, or play a siren
on the cab and occasionally on the ground floor. It could mean that the elevator
is stuck, and you hearing it could be the only way those inside…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mya4j7/ysk_if_you_hear_a_bell_ringing_or_a_beeping_from/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mya4j7/ysk_if_you_hear_a_bell_ringing_or_a_beeping_from/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 18:17:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Most (all?) elevators have an &amp;quot;Alarm&amp;quot; button inside the cab as a secondary alert if the phone doesn&amp;#39;t work. This will ring, beep, or play a siren on the cab and occasionally on the ground floor. It could mean that the elevator is stuck, and you hearing it could be the only way those inside could get help. Call either the security or management of the building or facility or the local fire department.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK common types of small fires, how to put them out, and how to operate a fire extinguisher. On TV people run out of the house during a small fire but good practice can save your home. Always call 911 if you are in danger or the fire has already spread.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: How to recognize and put out small fires because many can be prevented
from causing major damage or harm before they spread. Here are some of the most
common and how to put them out:

Class A Fires: This type of fire ignites from common fuel sources, like wood,
trash, fabric, paper and…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/my3dmd/ysk_common_types_of_small_fires_how_to_put_them/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/my3dmd/ysk_common_types_of_small_fires_how_to_put_them/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 12:52:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: How to recognize and put out small fires because many can be prevented from causing major damage or harm before they spread. Here are some of the most common and how to put them out: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Class A Fires: This type of fire ignites from common fuel sources, like wood, trash, fabric, paper and plastics.  Extinguish with Water or a Red Fire Extinguisher.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Class B Fires: Result from an explosion of flammable liquids or gases. Extinguish by Depleting Oxygen. Smother but never try to put water on these fires as it will make the fire grow.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Class C Fires: Result from electricity. Extinguish by removing the power source. Know where your houses main breakers are. Use a red extinguisher to suppress flames once the electricity is out.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Class K Fires: Result from grease, lard, olive oil, butter, animal fats and vegetable fats. Do NOT extinguish with water as it will spread extremely fast. Use only a Chemical Fire Extinguisher. If you do not have one do not try to put out this fire alone. These flames burn extremely hot and spread fast. Call the fire department immediately and leave the area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One more tip: Many people don’t know that fire extinguishers can’t just be left under a cabinet indefinitely without some maintenance. Look at the gauge and make sure it’s in the green square. It it’s moving out of the green or starting to rust or leak, call your local FD on a non-emergency line and ask if they service extinguishers. Some do. The one I did was happy to as the community safety is the FD’s priority. Other than that they can tell you where to go in your community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK You shouldn't use food delivery apps]]></title><description><![CDATA[I work for a sandwich shop that has doordash and Uber Eats but they all are
fairly similar.

Why YSK: In the food industry you run on a thin margin so when a food delivery
service says theya re going to take 20-30% from each sale that means you will
essentialy make no money on that sale after all is…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/my2w00/ysk_you_shouldnt_use_food_delivery_apps/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/my2w00/ysk_you_shouldnt_use_food_delivery_apps/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 08:53:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I work for a sandwich shop that has doordash and Uber Eats but they all are fairly similar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: In the food industry you run on a thin margin so when a food delivery service says theya re going to take 20-30% from each sale that means you will essentialy make no money on that sale after all is said an done. If you care about the restaurants you order from use their app or call in and order and pick it up yourself. The companies that run these apps do not have a sustainable business model. If you look at these companies earnings they are all fairly young campanies heavily relying on investments and are yet see significant profit. Once these companies need to start functioning without the initial investment dollars you will see the prices rise even more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TDLR: by using delivery apps you are adding an unnecessary middleman that will cost you more and make the restaurant less money, don&amp;#39;t use food delivery apps if you care about the business you are ordering from&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(If you want to read more about it this areticle breaks it down even more:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eatthecapital.com/post/why-you-shouldn-t-be-ordering-from-grubhub-or-uber-eats&quot;&gt;https://www.eatthecapital.com/post/why-you-shouldn-t-be-ordering-from-grubhub-or-uber-eats&lt;/a&gt; )&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: You should not get your address engraved on an AirTag / Tile or other tracker if it’s attached to your keys]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Some companies offer free engraving so many people might be tempted to
put their details on the tracker, perhaps even their address.

This might seem to make sense since the tracker could run out of battery or be
damaged in some way, however if the person has your keys and address...…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx6nyy/ysk_you_should_not_get_your_address_engraved_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx6nyy/ysk_you_should_not_get_your_address_engraved_on/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 06:48:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Some companies offer free engraving so many people might be tempted to put their details on the tracker, perhaps even their address. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This might seem to make sense since the tracker could run out of battery or be damaged in some way, however if the person has your keys and address... they know where you live and could gain access to your house or vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that food delivery apps inflate menu prices in addition to all the crazy fees]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Literally go on the chipotle website right now. A burrito bowl will be
$8.20. If you go on DoorDash, Ubereats, etc. that same burrito bowl will be
$9-11. Restaurants are FORCED to inflate menu prices because of the 20-30%
delivery service fees. Another misleading fact is that those ads you…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mxwp26/ysk_that_food_delivery_apps_inflate_menu_prices/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mxwp26/ysk_that_food_delivery_apps_inflate_menu_prices/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 03:07:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Literally go on the chipotle website right now. A burrito bowl will be $8.20. If you go on DoorDash, Ubereats, etc. that same burrito bowl will be $9-11. Restaurants are FORCED to inflate menu prices because of the 20-30% delivery service fees. Another misleading fact is that those ads you see all the time for “free delivery” really mean “no delivery fee.” There are also 15-20% service fees, surge fees, and minimum cart fees. Sales taxes are also calculated differently from app to app! I usually avoid these fees by picking up the food myself or calling in my order for delivery. If I really want to splurge, I&amp;#39;ll order delivery, but because I&amp;#39;m cheap, I&amp;#39;ll use a food delivery aggregator. This &lt;a href=&quot;https://foodboss.org/&quot;&gt;aggregator&lt;/a&gt; has a website and compares Ubereats and Eatstreet. I used them for a while and saved a good amount of money. The only other option is this other &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mealme.ai/&quot;&gt;aggregator&lt;/a&gt; that compares DoorDash, Ubereats, GrubHub, Postmates, and some other ones. They messed up my first order but they gave me a promo code, so I&amp;#39;ve been using this one more since they compare more services. Whatever you choose, make sure to always tip-- the drivers definitely deserve/need it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: In the U.S. saying yes sir or yes ma’am has nothing to do with age.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK:

I know this is a takeoff of another post, but I want to clarify that it's not
just a southern thing. It's an American thing.

It's rare in the U.S., but sometimes people from other countries (especially in
Northern Europe or other only-English speaking countries) get offended, like
you're…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mxq14v/ysk_in_the_us_saying_yes_sir_or_yes_maam_has/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mxq14v/ysk_in_the_us_saying_yes_sir_or_yes_maam_has/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 20:38:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know this is a takeoff of another post, but I want to clarify that it&amp;#39;s not just a southern thing. It&amp;#39;s an American thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s rare in the U.S., but sometimes people from other countries (especially in Northern Europe or other only-English speaking countries) get offended, like you&amp;#39;re being too formal. It’s mostly just how we talk, but also shows respect for others. Americans say it to the 16 year old kid bagging the groceries because everyone deserves respect until they prove they don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Believe it or not, I have a lot of experience with this (fwiw, I live in NY and have been to the south for about 10 months). I personally don&amp;#39;t ever use &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am&amp;quot; because my mom specifically used it to kiss authority figures&amp;#39; asses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve talked to lots of other people from the UK, Australia, and Scandinavia, and they have identified &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am&amp;quot; as an outdated mode of address because it wasn&amp;#39;t egalitarian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I worked customer service at a Home Depot as a late teenager and insisted on never using &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am&amp;quot; in my day-to-day life (although there was one exception that I will explain later). I found that most people, but young people especially, would always address me as &amp;quot;sir.&amp;quot; I even told some of them &amp;quot;dude, there&amp;#39;s no need to call me that; my name is Explorer as you&amp;#39;ll see on my apron,&amp;quot; but the response was &amp;quot;yes sir.&amp;quot; They disregarded my request and continued to call me &amp;quot;sir,&amp;quot; which goes to show how ingrained these words are, even in New York.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One day, I was intrigued enough with the &amp;quot;sir&amp;quot; shit that I decided to take it to the other extreme. Instead of never using &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am,&amp;quot; I used them in every sentence I would say to a customer. Sometimes, I would go full metal jacket and use the &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am sandwich;&amp;quot; for example, I would say, &amp;quot;Sir, the ant killer is in aisle 38 sir.&amp;quot; Although the idea was ludicrous and insane, believe it or not, people fucking loved it, and I was called &amp;quot;sir&amp;quot; at least 50 times that day (I started counting at some point).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, for anyone from another country who is wondering about this, in the U.S., anyone who&amp;#39;s providing a service and any stranger of any age had best be seen as an authority figure and warrants &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am&amp;quot; and the commensurate degree of deference and formality. Most people in the U.S. who say &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m not old enough to be called &amp;#39;sir/ma&amp;#39;am&amp;#39;&amp;quot; will still get a warm feeling inside from being shown that respect. In fact, if you call these people (and most others) &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am&amp;quot; enough times, they will begin to address you in that way too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a formal nation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Putting a flat square cushion on the couch ensures your cat won’t get hair on the rest of the furniture.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: If he fits, he sits and you get to spend a lot less quality time with a
lint roller on your couches. ](https://imgur.com/gallery/iiQ8ffT)]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mxpfy8/ysk_putting_a_flat_square_cushion_on_the_couch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mxpfy8/ysk_putting_a_flat_square_cushion_on_the_couch/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 19:45:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If he fits, he sits and you get to spend a lot less quality time with a lint roller on your couches. ](&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/gallery/iiQ8ffT&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/gallery/iiQ8ffT&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that being dehydrated drops your blood pressure which can make you feel depressed. This can also cause your heart to beat harder, causing anxiety.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: if you are already prone to depression or anxiety, dehydration makes it
feel much worse, and it's so easy to do by accident. Because you don't have
enough volume of blood, its harder for your body to maintain blood flow. This
causes your body to mimic the symptoms of depression (fatigue,…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx96ip/ysk_that_being_dehydrated_drops_your_blood/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx96ip/ysk_that_being_dehydrated_drops_your_blood/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 03:04:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: if you are already prone to depression or anxiety, dehydration makes it feel much worse, and it&amp;#39;s so easy to do by accident. Because you don&amp;#39;t have enough volume of blood, its harder for your body to maintain blood flow. This causes your body to mimic the symptoms of depression (fatigue, brain fog, dizziness), which can cause you to think the depressed thoughts, causing your brain to make depression chemicals. When that makes you feel shitty enough, your heart will try to fix it by beating harder, raising your blood pressure, mimicking anxiety. Additionally, it becomes harder for your blood to carry oxygen, making you breathe harder, which for me is the one that causes me to panic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn&amp;#39;t a WoW tHaNkS iM cUrEd, but for me personally makes a huge difference. For hours today my anxiety was unmanageably high for no particular reason. After an almost-breakdown I chugged 20oz of water, took a few deep breaths, and 20 minutes later felt so much better it spawned me to write this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nopanic.org.uk/dehydration-anxiety/&quot;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This message brought to you by &lt;a href=&quot;/r/hydrohomies&quot;&gt;r/hydrohomies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that when online shopping, the same online shop can display different pricing depending on what device you are using.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: As crazy as it sounds, the data you have amassed while online shopping
is being used by online stores to determine prices they think you’re willing to
pay! You can go to the same site and see different prices depending on what
device you are using which uses your online history as a base.…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx5z1v/ysk_that_when_online_shopping_the_same_online/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx5z1v/ysk_that_when_online_shopping_the_same_online/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 01:49:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: As crazy as it sounds, the data you have amassed while online shopping is being used by online stores to determine prices they think you’re willing to pay! You can go to the same site and see different prices depending on what device you are using which uses your online history as a base. You can find a lot of articles online that talk about it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before you go online shopping, you should always clear your cache and history. You may even consider downloading a VPN or using a proxy server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I came across this information because one day I was online shopping with my husband while I was at work. We both had reported different prices and exchanged pictures. There was a $20 dollar difference! I searched it up, and sure enough it is a real problem. Do you self a favor and stay informed so that you don’t spend unnecessary extra money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I can’t say all websites do it, but I know that a good amount do. Just stay weary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: In the south saying yes sir or yes ma’am has nothing to do with age.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: It's rare in the south, but sometimes people from other parts of the
country get offended, like you're calling them old. It’s mostly just how we
talk, but also shows respect for others. I say it to the 16 year old kid bagging
the groceries because everyone deserves respect until they prove…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx7g8d/ysk_in_the_south_saying_yes_sir_or_yes_maam_has/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx7g8d/ysk_in_the_south_saying_yes_sir_or_yes_maam_has/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 01:49:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It&amp;#39;s rare in the south, but sometimes people from other parts of the country get offended, like you&amp;#39;re calling them old. It’s mostly just how we talk, but also shows respect for others. I say it to the 16 year old kid bagging the groceries because everyone deserves respect until they prove they don’t.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Bragging about never taking a sick day because you go to work even when sick does not make you a better employee.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Often I hear folks ridiculing other for calling out of work when they
are sick.

The comment is usually along the lines of "I never call out of work. I will come
to work even if I am sick."

That doesn't make you a better employee or a hero. It in fact makes you the
exact opposite.

It…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx4wdo/ysk_bragging_about_never_taking_a_sick_day/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx4wdo/ysk_bragging_about_never_taking_a_sick_day/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 22:56:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Often I hear folks ridiculing other for calling out of work when they are sick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The comment is usually along the lines of &amp;quot;I never call out of work. I will come to work even if I am sick.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That doesn&amp;#39;t make you a better employee or a hero. It in fact makes you the exact opposite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It shows that you&amp;#39;ve no care for your well being or the well being of others. It also shows that you&amp;#39;re willing to compromise a typically (mostly)sterile environment and possibly make others sick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay the f**k home, friendo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that rest stops are a great place to sleep if you are living out of your car, especially with children]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: They might be a little out of the way, and depending on where you live
you might have to pay a fee (turnpikes, etc), but they are safe spaces with 24/7
access to bathrooms, and food sometimes. Nobody will think twice about you
sleeping in your car, and you generally will not be noticed…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mwyjrx/ysk_that_rest_stops_are_a_great_place_to_sleep_if/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mwyjrx/ysk_that_rest_stops_are_a_great_place_to_sleep_if/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 20:38:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: They might be a little out of the way, and depending on where you live you might have to pay a fee (turnpikes, etc), but they are safe spaces with 24/7 access to bathrooms, and food sometimes. Nobody will think twice about you sleeping in your car, and you generally will not be noticed because there are different people staying there every night. It&amp;#39;s a safe place if you are working and saving up, and especially if you have small children while doing so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK Difference between head full of memories and head full of regrets is your ability to forgive yourself.]]></title><description><![CDATA["Why YSK:" People often blame themselves for what they did in the past and the
regret starts eating them from inside.

They aren't able to move past that incident(s) and their "head full of regrets"
makes it impossible for them to grow and become a better person in future.

People should forgive…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx0dkz/ysk_difference_between_head_full_of_memories_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx0dkz/ysk_difference_between_head_full_of_memories_and/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 19:45:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Why YSK:&amp;quot; People often blame themselves for what they did in the past and the regret starts eating them from inside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They aren&amp;#39;t able to move past that incident(s) and their &amp;quot;head full of regrets&amp;quot; makes it impossible for them to grow and become a better person in future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People should forgive themselves and try to create memories and not life long regrets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What happened, cannot be changed, they should move forward and become a better human being.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Even IF you have no service at all, still call 911 if you are in an emergency!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Unless you are in the center of the earth or hundreds of miles off from
any city, there is most likely a carrier network nearby.


CAN YOU STILL CALL 911 WITHOUT SERVICE?

> Thanks to the FCC, network providers must transmit an emergency call (911)
> regardless of whether you use their…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mwf4au/ysk_even_if_you_have_no_service_at_all_still_call/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mwf4au/ysk_even_if_you_have_no_service_at_all_still_call/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 04:37:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Unless you are in the center of the earth or hundreds of miles off from any city, there is most likely a carrier network nearby.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Can you still call 911 without service?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to the FCC, network providers must transmit an emergency call (911) regardless of whether you use their service or not. This means if your provider doesnt have coverage in that area, your phone will show that it has no service. ... As long as it has battery power and can reach a signal, the phone can connect to 911.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.puretalkusa.com/blog/article?p=how-to-use-your-cell-phone-in-these-3-emergencies&quot;&gt;PureTalk USA via Google&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see so many damn people saying “and if you have no service” when being told to call 911. It’s unlikely it’ll happen, but this could very well save your life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that if you care about the bees, you shouldn't be mowing or killing the dandelions on your lawn in the early springtime.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: According to experts, in early spring dandelions can be a crucial food
source for the bees after a long winter of living off their reserves. Spring can
be a difficult time for the bees as they become active at 10C/50F, which is
usually well before many pollinating flowers have bloomed.…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mwerxp/ysk_that_if_you_care_about_the_bees_you_shouldnt/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mwerxp/ysk_that_if_you_care_about_the_bees_you_shouldnt/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 23:00:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: According to experts, in early spring dandelions can be a crucial food source for the bees after a long winter of living off their reserves. Spring can be a difficult time for the bees as they become active at 10C/50F, which is usually well before many pollinating flowers have bloomed. Dandelions grow early in the season in large numbers, and quickly generate lots of pollen for the bees to collect. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theweathernetwork.com/ca/news/article/heres-why-you-shouldnt-mow-dandelions-spring-lawn-care-benefits-and-save-bees&quot;&gt;https://www.theweathernetwork.com/ca/news/article/heres-why-you-shouldnt-mow-dandelions-spring-lawn-care-benefits-and-save-bees&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that the realtors "fee" - aka the % of sales price commission structure is outdated and should no longer be used]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Sales price commission fee structures were only applicable 20-30 years
ago when the price of real estate was much, much lower and more closely related
to salary. Using the same pricing structure today (e.g. 3-7% of sale or purchase
price) does not make any sense whatsoever - and do not let…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mw9z7a/ysk_that_the_realtors_fee_aka_the_of_sales_price/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mw9z7a/ysk_that_the_realtors_fee_aka_the_of_sales_price/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 22:24:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Sales price commission fee structures were only applicable 20-30 years ago when the price of real estate was much, much lower and more closely related to salary. Using the same pricing structure today (e.g. 3-7% of sale or purchase price) does not make any sense whatsoever - and do not let a realtor convince you that it does!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most realtors today agree on lump sum payments for their services, and agreeing with your realtor on some pre-set price that has nothing to do with the value of your home is completely fine. There are still a few realtors that will prey on naive customers. The total cost of paying your realtor shouldn&amp;#39;t be more than what a paralegal or (at best) lawyer would charge in your area for a similar amount of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since we&amp;#39;ve had a crazy upward spiral in real estate prices recently, I&amp;#39;m seeing a lot of naive old people who agree with outrageous commission structure some realtors offer. No realtor is worth that much money, and don&amp;#39;t let them convince your grandparents that they are!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: The Breath Method — Simple way to get through a Panic Attack]]></title><description><![CDATA[Breathing exercises work by adjusting your nervous system according to your
breathing depth & pace. Which makes them ultra useful for high-alertness type of
situations like panic attacks and anxiety attacks.

The Breath Method for Panic Attacks

 * Inhale from your nose for 4 seconds,
 * Hold your…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mw2v7v/ysk_the_breath_method_simple_way_to_get_through_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mw2v7v/ysk_the_breath_method_simple_way_to_get_through_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 16:10:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Breathing exercises work by adjusting your nervous system according to your breathing depth &amp;amp; pace. Which makes them ultra useful for high-alertness type of situations like panic attacks and anxiety attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Breath Method for Panic Attacks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inhale from your nose for 4 seconds,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold your breath for 4 seconds,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exhale from your mouth for 6 seconds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And repeat this pattern for as long as you want. Focus on your bodily sensations, and affirm yourself in your mind that it&amp;#39;ll all be fine - because it really will!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Panic Attacks are the worst, but this might help you - as it did me and my friends &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So yeah. I&amp;#39;m aware of this exercise because of a breathing exercises app, and here&amp;#39;s the screenshot of the exercise (in case you have visual memory, or just save it on your phone): &lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/kNa4GdV.png&quot;&gt;Panic Button breathing exercise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: People have been asking me about the app, the app&amp;#39;s name is &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;Huma Breath&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;quot; - I use it on Apple but it should be available for Android too. There are other exercises for anxiety, sleep, energy etc too, recommend it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Btw, if you ever feel down or want to talk to someone, please feel free to PM me!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 'Alot' is not a word. It's 'a lot'.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: This is one of the most common misspellings and people learn to spell
certain things by example, therefore the more this cancer typo is spread around
the more people will continue to get it wrong. Join me in my efforts to let the
world know that 'a lot' is two words, not one.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvuuuq/ysk_alot_is_not_a_word_its_a_lot/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvuuuq/ysk_alot_is_not_a_word_its_a_lot/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 10:51:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This is one of the most common misspellings and people learn to spell certain things by example, therefore the more this cancer typo is spread around the more people will continue to get it wrong. Join me in my efforts to let the world know that &amp;#39;a lot&amp;#39; is two words, not one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK, be very careful letting your dog swim as summer approaches, blue green algae is toxic and often fatal to dogs.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Blue green algae, or cyanobacteria can grow in nearly any body of fresh
water under the right circumstances. Seventeen states reported blue green algae
related deaths in 2019. You cannot be sure that any algae is or isn't toxic, so
if you plan on being near water especially stagnant bodies…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvvz07/ysk_be_very_careful_letting_your_dog_swim_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvvz07/ysk_be_very_careful_letting_your_dog_swim_as/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 07:02:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  Blue green algae, or cyanobacteria can grow in nearly any body of fresh water under the right circumstances. Seventeen states reported blue green algae related deaths in 2019. You cannot be sure that any algae is or isn&amp;#39;t toxic, so if you plan on being near water especially stagnant bodies during warm weather take precautions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keep your dog leashed near bodies of water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Try not to let them drink any.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you notice any foam or films on the surface of the water it&amp;#39;s best not to let them swim or play in it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This toxin can be fatal very quickly and by the time your pet displays symptoms it&amp;#39;s often too late. There is no antidote, so look before you leap!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: If you go to a restaurant, and there are water spots on your silverware, it does NOT mean the silverware is dirty]]></title><description><![CDATA[All it means is the person who rolled the silverware (likely not even your
server) was too lazy to polish it.

Why YSK: it’s unnecessary to ask for new silverware, especially if your server
is slammed. The silverware is clean! It just sat out wet for a bit after going
through the wash]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvtoh7/ysk_if_you_go_to_a_restaurant_and_there_are_water/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvtoh7/ysk_if_you_go_to_a_restaurant_and_there_are_water/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 05:51:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;All it means is the person who rolled the silverware (likely not even your server) was too lazy to polish it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: it’s unnecessary to ask for new silverware, especially if your server is slammed. The silverware is clean! It just sat out wet for a bit after going through the wash&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Mother's Day is May 9th (in 18 days)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: It's a good time to order things online if you intend to.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvubbt/ysk_mothers_day_is_may_9th_in_18_days/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvubbt/ysk_mothers_day_is_may_9th_in_18_days/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 05:01:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It&amp;#39;s a good time to order things online if you intend to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that Succulents are the subject of a great deal of damaging and illegal trade. It can be helpful to ask vendors their sources.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: because succulents are one of the more unique varieties of plants out
there, they've become a target for "poaching." Many people think they're helping
preserve the species when they purchase them, but can inadvertently hurt them if
contributing to illegal supply. Some more info can be found…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvn7ix/ysk_that_succulents_are_the_subject_of_a_great/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvn7ix/ysk_that_succulents_are_the_subject_of_a_great/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 21:47:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: because succulents are one of the more unique varieties of plants out there, they&amp;#39;ve become a target for &amp;quot;poaching.&amp;quot; Many people think they&amp;#39;re helping preserve the species when they purchase them, but can inadvertently hurt them if contributing to illegal supply. Some more info can be found in this piece by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KirP2ef1lJ0&quot;&gt;Cheddar&lt;/a&gt;. Ultimately, it&amp;#39;s OK to have succulents! But if we want them to stay around, it&amp;#39;s good to spread info on best-buying habits. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a post on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/interestingasfuck&quot;&gt;r/interestingasfuck&lt;/a&gt; that showed off a living rock cactus, which is a common victim of illegal trade. Made me think I should share the video I had recently seen on it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK Save the Bees focuses more on Native Bees than Honeybees]]></title><description><![CDATA[Honeybees are in no danger of dying out; lots of native bees are endangered or
threatened. A lot of post I've seen online with 'save the bee' captions have
been focusing on honeybees and beekeeping.

Why YSK: Lots of people are taking an interest in honeybees rather than native
bees. Efforts to help…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mv8dcp/ysk_save_the_bees_focuses_more_on_native_bees/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mv8dcp/ysk_save_the_bees_focuses_more_on_native_bees/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 13:42:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Honeybees are in no danger of dying out; lots of native bees are endangered or threatened. A lot of post I&amp;#39;ve seen online with &amp;#39;save the bee&amp;#39; captions have been focusing on honeybees and beekeeping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Lots of people are taking an interest in honeybees rather than native bees. Efforts to help honeybees often end up hurting native bee populations. If you&amp;#39;re able, plant native plants and wildflowers, go pesticide free, buy/build nesting houses, and find out about local conservation efforts. Native bees are an essential part of local ecosystems and are necessary pollinators.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: It’s easy to use a Bluetooth tracker app to locate misplaced items, headphones and devices.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: A lot of people including me tend to misplace items like keys,
headphones (like AirPods), or even phones. A good Bluetooth tracking app can
help locate items and devices. Most of the devices today have Bluetooth built in
and can be easily located. For keys and for other everyday items, you…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mv2w3k/ysk_its_easy_to_use_a_bluetooth_tracker_app_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mv2w3k/ysk_its_easy_to_use_a_bluetooth_tracker_app_to/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 05:00:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: A lot of people including me tend to misplace items like keys, headphones (like AirPods), or even phones. A good Bluetooth tracking app can help locate items and devices. Most of the devices today have Bluetooth built in and can be easily located. For keys and for other everyday items, you can use trackers like Tile or the recently announced Apple AirTag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>