<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 04:40:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK To only put one name on a cheque that is intended for a wedding gift]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: It makes it a lot more difficult for the newlyweds to deposit a cheque
with two names on it - especially if you have addressed them as having the same
last name. Not everybody assumes their partner’s last name, and even if intend
to, their last name won’t be legally changed for a while.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qjp67k/ysk_to_only_put_one_name_on_a_cheque_that_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qjp67k/ysk_to_only_put_one_name_on_a_cheque_that_is/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 14:45:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It makes it a lot more difficult for the newlyweds to deposit a cheque with two names on it - especially if you have addressed them as having the same last name. Not everybody assumes their partner’s last name, and even if intend to, their last name won’t be legally changed for a while.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that fire extinguishers expire.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Most people don’t realize this and it’s rare but if the extinguisher is
out of date, it can malfunction when you need it. That can obviously be
extremely dangerous. You can find the date on the tag attached to the top of the
unit.

“Although they don't have a true "expiration date,"…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qjalo0/ysk_that_fire_extinguishers_expire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qjalo0/ysk_that_fire_extinguishers_expire/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 23:57:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Most people don’t realize this and it’s rare but if the extinguisher is out of date, it can malfunction when you need it. That can obviously be extremely dangerous. You can find the date on the tag attached to the top of the unit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Although they don&amp;#39;t have a true &amp;quot;expiration date,&amp;quot; traditional fire extinguishers generally have a 10-12 year life expectancy. Disposable fire extinguishers should be replaced every 12 years. Rechargeable fire extinguishers should be taken to an experienced fire equipment company and recharged every 10 years.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://support.firstalert.com/s/article/How-long-do-fire-extinguishers-last&quot;&gt;https://support.firstalert.com/s/article/How-long-do-fire-extinguishers-last&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK figures and plots in Word can be easier manipulated by imbedding them within a table.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: It saves a lot of time and effort (and mental breakdowns). I've seen
too many memes to not say anything.

For example, I want to include a figure in a Word document. What I do is:

1) Create a 2x1 table,

2) Copy my plot in the first row,

3) Include my caption in the bottom row,

4) Make…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qizkf6/ysk_figures_and_plots_in_word_can_be_easier/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qizkf6/ysk_figures_and_plots_in_word_can_be_easier/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 15:42:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It saves a lot of time and effort (and mental breakdowns). I&amp;#39;ve seen too many memes to not say anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, I want to include a figure in a Word document. What I do is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Create a 2x1 table,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Copy my plot in the first row,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Include my caption in the bottom row,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Make the table borders invisible, and Tada!, you&amp;#39;ve got a beautiful plot, with a caption, which can be easily manipulated around the page!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s also scalable. You can create an adjacent column to have legends and arrows pointing to elements in the picture, or even have 2 graphs with 2 distinct captions along the same row.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that everything you post on reddit is being stored by a third party (pushshift) so deleting on reddit isn't a complete removal of your digital footprint.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK:

What they are doing is illegal (against Art. 17 GDPR) but unless someone sues
them they're gonna keep doing it. There have been threads where users try to
request to opt out, but ppl have been waiting for months to no avail, and the
dev is impossible to reach. So word of advice, watch what…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qiwwap/ysk_that_everything_you_post_on_reddit_is_being/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qiwwap/ysk_that_everything_you_post_on_reddit_is_being/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 09:42:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What they are doing is illegal (against Art. 17 GDPR) but unless someone sues them they&amp;#39;re gonna keep doing it. There have been threads where users try to request to opt out, but ppl have been waiting for months to no avail, and the dev is impossible to reach. So word of advice, watch what you say online, all the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: The poisoned Halloween candy scare myth]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: No cases of strangers killing or permanently injuring children this way
have been proven. Commonly, the story appears in the media when a young child
dies suddenly after Halloween.

In rare cases, adult family members have spread this story in an effort to cover
up murder or accidental…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qirqcs/ysk_the_poisoned_halloween_candy_scare_myth/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qirqcs/ysk_the_poisoned_halloween_candy_scare_myth/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 03:41:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: No cases of strangers killing or permanently injuring children this way have been proven. Commonly, the story appears in the media when a young child dies suddenly after Halloween.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In rare cases, adult family members have spread this story in an effort to cover up murder or accidental deaths. In other incidents, a child who has been told about poisoned candy places a dangerous object or substance in a pile of candy and pretends that it was the work of a stranger. This behavior is called the copycat effect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, always take caution and inspect but know that it is not as big of a threat as media might make it each year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Poisoned_candy_myths&quot;&gt;Wiki Info&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbc.ca/news/health/halloween-candy-tampering-urban-legend-truth-1.5341734&quot;&gt;4 cases of tampering reported between 2008 and 2019, but none resulted in injury or death, CFIA says (Canada)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/30/health/halloween-candy-panic-conversation-wellness/index.html&quot;&gt;CNN article 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that if you dislike the official site for a website, there is almost always a third party app available]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Official apps are designed to make money, and may be full of ads or
other frustrations. Third party apps often have no ads, cleaner interfaces, and
more advanced features.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhz2b8/ysk_that_if_you_dislike_the_official_site_for_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhz2b8/ysk_that_if_you_dislike_the_official_site_for_a/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 13:04:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Official apps are designed to make money, and may be full of ads or other frustrations. Third party apps often have no ads, cleaner interfaces, and more advanced features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that there are plenty of open courses to help you choose a degree or learn in general]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Getting a degree is one of the most serious decisions you make in life
and determining if a course is right for you can be difficult. To help you
decide, there are free online resources where you can actually see the kind of
introductory lectures you'd take.

eg. you can search the MIT…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qi9wt8/ysk_that_there_are_plenty_of_open_courses_to_help/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qi9wt8/ysk_that_there_are_plenty_of_open_courses_to_help/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 12:35:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Getting a degree is one of the most serious decisions you make in life and determining if a course is right for you can be difficult. To help you decide, there are free online resources where you can actually see the kind of introductory lectures you&amp;#39;d take.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;eg. you can search the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCEBb1b_L6zDS3xTUrIALZOw&quot;&gt;MIT OpenCourseWare&lt;/a&gt; by subject (they have playlists) or a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/reddit.com/comments/cktxy/reddit_lets_compile_a_list_of_the_best_online/&quot;&gt;whole list of other channels and websites&lt;/a&gt; compiled by reddit (even if 10 years ago, haven&amp;#39;t tried them all but the 5 I checked works fine).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: There's a fair chance your TPM 1.2 chip can be upgraded to TPM 2.0 with a simple update]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Because many people get "Unsupported PC" warning when trying to install
Windows 11 for having TPM 1.2 instead of 2.0. Some OEM's however, provides tools
for a TPM 2.0 upgrade.

First, for those who don't know what's the entire thing:
https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/enable-tpm-2…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhwl3d/ysk_theres_a_fair_chance_your_tpm_12_chip_can_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhwl3d/ysk_theres_a_fair_chance_your_tpm_12_chip_can_be/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 10:44:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Because many people get &amp;quot;Unsupported PC&amp;quot; warning when trying to install Windows 11 for having TPM 1.2 instead of 2.0. Some OEM&amp;#39;s however, provides tools for a TPM 2.0 upgrade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, for those who don&amp;#39;t know what&amp;#39;s the entire thing: &lt;a href=&quot;https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/enable-tpm-2-0-on-your-pc-1fd5a332-360d-4f46-a1e7-ae6b0c90645c&quot;&gt;https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/enable-tpm-2-0-on-your-pc-1fd5a332-360d-4f46-a1e7-ae6b0c90645c&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MS&amp;#39; justification as why it&amp;#39;s required: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tg9QUrnVFho&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tg9QUrnVFho&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And for those wondering what is TPM: &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trusted_Platform_Module&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trusted_Platform_Module&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL:DR if you want to install Windows 11 officially, you need TPM 2.0 support. There&amp;#39;s ways to bypass this, but MS says they won&amp;#39;t guarantee that you&amp;#39;ll get updates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s a chance, however, that your OEM is providing means to upgrade it to 2.0. As an example&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HP: &lt;a href=&quot;https://support.hp.com/au-en/document/c05381064&quot;&gt;https://support.hp.com/au-en/document/c05381064&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dell: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dell.com/support/kbdoc/tr-tr/000184894/how-to-successfully-update-the-tpm-firmware-on-your-dell-computer?lang=en&quot;&gt;https://www.dell.com/support/kbdoc/tr-tr/000184894/how-to-successfully-update-the-tpm-firmware-on-your-dell-computer?lang=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should be able to find your own OEM&amp;#39;s instructions on Google&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Vaping near a computer or any kind of electronic can have consequences]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK:

To my fellow vapers who made the poor decision to pick up a nicotine addiction,
yes, It can and will damage your PC if it gets near it.

I noticed a weird sound coming from my pc, given it's been almost a year since
I've cleaned the thing, I decided it was time to do so and that it might…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhsznv/ysk_vaping_near_a_computer_or_any_kind_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhsznv/ysk_vaping_near_a_computer_or_any_kind_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 21:41:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To my fellow vapers who made the poor decision to pick up a nicotine addiction, yes, It can and will damage your PC if it gets near it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I noticed a weird sound coming from my pc, given it&amp;#39;s been almost a year since I&amp;#39;ve cleaned the thing, I decided it was time to do so and that it might be the cause of the issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I noticed a weird sticky substance around my CPU and GPU fans. At first I thought It was just because I haven&amp;#39;t cleaned it in so long. So I used a Q-tip and wiped it off a bit, or at least tried. It was stubborn. I later looked at it wondering what it was, and I smelled it. Smelled like pineapple. My favorite flavor at the time (haven&amp;#39;t touched a vape in three months :))&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only can it build up like what happened to me, but with research I found that many of the common ingredients in E-liquid are conductive, would could cause permanent damage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I never smoked and I&amp;#39;m just a teenager who made stupid decisions, but in stressful times I was going through 3 packs of cigs worth of nicotine in a day. Majority of those days was spent at my computer doing my online classes. my friend came over one day and she said my whole room smelled like the pineapple vape i was using. she&amp;#39;s used mine before and could instantly detect the smell, that&amp;#39;s how much i was using it. I cant imagine have badly it could be for someone who used/uses for a much longer time on their computer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This also applies to cigarettes, smoking and vaping THC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Side note 1: Nicotine isn&amp;#39;t cool and just because you discovered a gas station that doesn&amp;#39;t check ID&amp;#39;s isn&amp;#39;t an excuse to keep vaping and kick the habit,(most ppl here are gonna be 21 anyways but my point still stands) I was getting cheap fake disposables before from sketchy ppl and made the excuse of &amp;quot;i can keep doing it since it is legit and won&amp;#39;t hurt me as much and I&amp;#39;m safer from these people&amp;quot;. I don&amp;#39;t have the luxury of an older sibling like most of my friends, and when I discovered this gas station my usage went through the roof, and i made the mistake of telling people and now some friends beg me to go over there for them, especially girls because they don&amp;#39;t want to meet up with people. Not needing to pump nicotine in your system at least every few hours is nice, healthier, cheaper, less worrying, and if you&amp;#39;re like me you don&amp;#39;t have to worry about parents or getting pulled over. notice how this side note is almost as long as the post? Because the whole post wouldn&amp;#39;t be needed if people didn&amp;#39;t struggle like me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Side note 2: Please open your computer every few months and clean it out and look for any build up, this goes to everybody, not just vapers/smokers. But if you are a vaper/smoker you should definitely do it more often if you use in the same room as your computer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR : Don&amp;#39;t vape near your pc in an enclosed space, will build up and can cause issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ysk that you can turn off gambling and alcohol ads in Google ads settings]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why ysk: It's gonna be horse racing season in Australia soon and some of us may
be sick of seeing an increase of gambling ads. Or maybe you want to quit
gambling or drinking. It's good to know that you can go to google ads settings
and turn it off.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhjh9r/ysk_that_you_can_turn_off_gambling_and_alcohol/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhjh9r/ysk_that_you_can_turn_off_gambling_and_alcohol/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 19:44:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why ysk:
It&amp;#39;s gonna be horse racing season in Australia soon and some of us may be sick of seeing an increase of gambling ads. Or maybe you want to quit gambling or drinking. It&amp;#39;s good to know that you can go to google ads settings and turn it off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Your hard drive/SSD can predict when it's going to fail, and it's easy to check this data]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: It’s simple and helps you avoid hard drive failure.

Storage devices predict when they will fail with a technology called SMART. For
hard drives, it predicts 75% of all failures.

Back in the Windows 7 era, computers would tell you when SMART predicted a
failure. The computer would say a…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhein4/ysk_your_hard_drivessd_can_predict_when_its_going/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhein4/ysk_your_hard_drivessd_can_predict_when_its_going/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 11:06:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It’s simple and helps you avoid hard drive failure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Storage devices predict when they will fail with a technology called SMART. For hard drives, it predicts 75% of all failures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back in the Windows 7 era, computers would tell you when SMART predicted a failure. The computer would say a SMART failure is predicted when booting up, Windows 7 would give you errors every few minutes saying your hard drive is going to fail, and you couldn’t even install Windows 7 onto a failing drive unless you turned off the SMART check.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, for some reason, windows 10 has none of that. My hard drive was predicting a failure for 6 months before I caught it, because I was testing a diagnostic utility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, if you want to check, Download CrystalDiskInfo. It will say OK, Caution, or Bad. If it’s Caution, it means there are errors, (bad sectors), but the hard drive or SSD has reallocated them. This is still an indication of a bad drive. If it’s Bad, it means it’s , well, bad. Discontinue use of this drive. SSDs will have percentages instead. These are usually accurate, and measure the amount of life left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was running on a HDD with hundreds of bad sectors before I caught it. Before I pulled it, it had almost 1000. That drive was likely to crash at any moment. Luckily, I was able to catch it and copy off all the data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/S.M.A.R.T&quot;&gt;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/S.M.A.R.T&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Anyone can have an abortion pill mailed to them.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: You don’t need a clinic. You can take care of yourself safely and
anonymously HERES A LINK
[https://nwhn.org/safe-online-delivered-how-to-get-the-abortion-pill-by-mail/]
Please share this openly and often. The pill can be taken up until the 10th week
of pregnancy.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhddco/ysk_anyone_can_have_an_abortion_pill_mailed_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhddco/ysk_anyone_can_have_an_abortion_pill_mailed_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 03:34:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: You don’t need a clinic. You can take care of yourself safely and anonymously &lt;a href=&quot;https://nwhn.org/safe-online-delivered-how-to-get-the-abortion-pill-by-mail/&quot;&gt;HERES A LINK&lt;/a&gt; Please share this openly and often. The pill can be taken up until the 10th week of pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK about the post offices "General Delivery" for those without an address. It's free and requires no application.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: the smallest P.O. Box is $70/3 months. $70 upfront. My situation is
that the barn that was given to me to teach a free class to teenagers on how to
remove engines from cars and install new ones, it's address belongs to the house
next to it, and the barn itself actually needs its own address…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qh1va2/ysk_about_the_post_offices_general_delivery_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qh1va2/ysk_about_the_post_offices_general_delivery_for/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:49:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: the smallest P.O. Box is $70/3 months. $70 upfront. My situation is that the barn that was given to me to teach a free class to teenagers on how to remove engines from cars and install new ones, it&amp;#39;s address belongs to the house next to it, and the barn itself actually needs its own address because people live in the house. The properties are separate but share the same address.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go to your local post office, ask for general delivery instructions, and they will tell you how to receive mail to that post office. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My city only has one post office, so to format the address on my envelopes, it&amp;#39;s simply:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Name&lt;br/&gt;
General Delivery&lt;br/&gt;
City, State Zip  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, don&amp;#39;t forget to put in a change of address to whatever they format the post office gives you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: address format&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK the differences between cooking and baking]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: with cooking, there's infinite room to experiment with different
ingredients and ratios in your recipes. However, when you're baking
bread/cake/etc. the recipe functions as a chemical reaction between the yeast,
flour, sugar, and heat. The ratios need to be followed accurate to create a…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qh02wu/ysk_the_differences_between_cooking_and_baking/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qh02wu/ysk_the_differences_between_cooking_and_baking/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 17:48:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: with cooking, there&amp;#39;s infinite room to experiment with different ingredients and ratios in your recipes. However, when you&amp;#39;re baking bread/cake/etc. the recipe functions as a chemical reaction between the yeast, flour, sugar, and heat. The ratios need to be followed accurate to create a good final product. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You cook with your heart, you bake with a recipe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK these websites if you are a broke college student who doesn't want to pay huge amounts of money for your required textbooks]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: I regret paying hard copies of all my books, especially after an online
year. Here is where you can usually find them.


LIBRARY GENESIS

This is the go-to site for most ebooks. Some of the engineering textbooks comes
with the solution manual as well. Searching for the title + "solution…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qgr59x/ysk_these_websites_if_you_are_a_broke_college/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qgr59x/ysk_these_websites_if_you_are_a_broke_college/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 09:41:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I regret paying hard copies of all my books, especially after an online year. Here is where you can usually find them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Library Genesis&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the go-to site for most ebooks. Some of the engineering textbooks comes with the solution manual as well. Searching for the title + &amp;quot;solution manual&amp;quot; will give you some results. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Ch36650lut10n5 (cheggsolutions)&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A website which has textbook solutions ripped from chegg. It has quite a lot of books and free, no need to sign up or give any credentials. You can find many textbook solutions that are not on libgen or zlibrary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Zlibrary&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is another site where you can try if you can&amp;#39;t find it in Library Genesis.
You may need an account if you exceed the download limit. If you do not like to use your personal email, you can opt to use a temporary mail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Slader&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for textbook solutions for free, check Slader. You have to sign up to access materials, after that you can access many solution manuals written by teachers and professors. 
They recently installed a limit, trying to make access to answers a paid service unfortunately. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Studylib&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the name itself says it’s like a library, where you can have a large number of assignments and solutions. You can also share your notes with your friends which would help them to solve the problems. It will provide you with a solution for all the subjects. You can also upload your documents and find the solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Pdfdrive&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An online PDF search engine that lets you search, preview and download PDFs. According to the site as of right now, there are over 75 million eBooks, magazines, articles, and more that are indexed and discoverable directly on PDF Drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Sci-Hub&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great place for finding published journal/conference papers that are (usually) paywalled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;AudioBookBay&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If what you want is audiobooks then audiobookbay is the go-to place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good luck on your new semester everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that eating disorders are the mental illness most likely to cause death]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Eating disorders are often not taken as seriously as other mental
illnesses but they should be. By now we are all very aware of the dangers of
suicide caused by mental health problems, but depression and similar conditions
aren’t even the most deadly of mental illnesses. Body shaming and…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qgoc3c/ysk_that_eating_disorders_are_the_mental_illness/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qgoc3c/ysk_that_eating_disorders_are_the_mental_illness/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 07:23:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Eating disorders are often not taken as seriously as other mental illnesses but they should be.
By now we are all very aware of the dangers of suicide caused by mental health problems, but depression and similar conditions aren’t even the most deadly of mental illnesses. Body shaming and the pressure to be thin has very serious risks for vulnerable people in society. Be mindful of what you say about food and weight around vulnerable people and if you suffer from an eating disorder please know that you matter and please seek help.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK the length of your hand, forearm and at least a finger. It will be useful to measure things when there's no ruler nearby]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: if you ever find yourself needing to know the approximate size of an
object but have no ruler or measurer tape near you, being able to measure it
with your body becomes extremely useful.

I was looking for a new couch and found an awesome one at the store for a great
price. The only problem…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qgjqp0/ysk_the_length_of_your_hand_forearm_and_at_least/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qgjqp0/ysk_the_length_of_your_hand_forearm_and_at_least/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 05:43:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: if you ever find yourself needing to know the approximate size of an object but have no ruler or measurer tape near you, being able to measure it with your body becomes extremely useful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was looking for a new couch and found an awesome one at the store for a great price. The only problem is that I didn&amp;#39;t know if it was slim enough to go through my front door. Fortunately I know that my open hand is about 20cm wide, and coincidentally knew that my front door is 90cm wide. Got it wrong by 3cm but the couch fitted alright.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another useful thing to learn is being able to measure larger distances by steps, but that&amp;#39;s a skill I have not yet mastered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK most states have online maps of current road conditions so you can safely plan winter travel.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Road conditions are constantly changing and can vary considerably over
the same stretch of road, so having an up to date map of conditions is very
useful for making safe travel plans in winter. The NOAA has compiled a list of
states that have road condition maps…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qg6orj/ysk_most_states_have_online_maps_of_current_road/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qg6orj/ysk_most_states_have_online_maps_of_current_road/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 20:35:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Road conditions are constantly changing and can vary considerably over the same stretch of road, so having an up to date map of conditions is very useful for making safe travel plans in winter. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weather.gov/cys/unitedstatesroadconditions&quot;&gt;NOAA has compiled a list of states that have road condition maps available.&lt;/a&gt; Safe travels!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Walmart conducted an audit of their accounting system and is quietly sending back pay checks to very old addresses of former associates]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: I last worked there from 2014-2015. I only worked there for 6 months
and got a $13 check sent to the address I last used 6 years ago. I know it
wasn't a significant amount of money to me but I've heard it being in the $200
range for employees who worked there longer. I'd like the word to be…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qg9x0z/ysk_walmart_conducted_an_audit_of_their/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qg9x0z/ysk_walmart_conducted_an_audit_of_their/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 17:46:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I last worked there from 2014-2015. I only worked there for 6 months and got a $13 check sent to the address I last used 6 years ago. I know it wasn&amp;#39;t a significant amount of money to me but I&amp;#39;ve heard it being in the $200 range for employees who worked there longer. I&amp;#39;d like the word to be spread so former associates can get the money they are entitled to if they have moved since they last worked at walmart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: When someone says “What?” it’s most likely not because they didn’t hear you, but because they didn’t understand you or they need time to formulate a response.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Most of the time, when someone says “What?”, you will simply repeat
yourself. This will usually fail, and they will just say “What?” again.

Instead of just repeating yourself, you should slow down, speak more clearly,
and say it again but using different words. This will give them time to…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qg51ph/ysk_when_someone_says_what_its_most_likely_not/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qg51ph/ysk_when_someone_says_what_its_most_likely_not/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 14:45:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Most of the time, when someone says “What?”, you will simply repeat yourself. This will usually fail, and they will just say “What?” again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of just repeating yourself, you should slow down, speak more clearly, and say it again but using different words. This will give them time to process your question/statement and formulate a response.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Example 1 (This actually happened to me):&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy (speaking quickly): So did you stay at Ben’s?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me (thinking something about a Mercedes Benz): … What?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy (same speed): Did you stay at Ben’s?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me: … … Sorry, what?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy (probably frustrated): Did you stay at Ben’s?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me (finally getting it): Oh… yeah, I did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Example 2 (How it should have gone):&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy (speaking quickly): So did you stay at Ben’s?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me (thinking something about a Mercedes Benz): … What?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy (slower): Did you stay over at Ben’s place last night?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me: Yeah, I did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Walmart .com, in an attempt to compete with Amazon, has allowed 3rd party scammers to sell using their site]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: People often expect that if they're buying from Walmart's website,
they're buying from a retailer.

This is not necessarily true. 3rd party sellers are allowed to sell on their
website, and some of them are scammers who sell faulty products, or simply take
the consumer's money and give them…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qfzbhw/ysk_walmart_com_in_an_attempt_to_compete_with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qfzbhw/ysk_walmart_com_in_an_attempt_to_compete_with/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 08:39:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: People often expect that if they&amp;#39;re buying from Walmart&amp;#39;s website, they&amp;#39;re buying from a retailer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not necessarily true. 3rd party sellers are allowed to sell on their website, and some of them are scammers who sell faulty products, or simply take the consumer&amp;#39;s money and give them nothing. Reviews are sometimes skewed using fake reviews and bot reviews. You&amp;#39;ll know when you&amp;#39;ve got enough real reviews on a seller. The point you should take home here is that buying from walmart .com is not buying from a retailer at all. It&amp;#39;s a marketplace full of individual sellers, and some of them don&amp;#39;t have any qualms scamming you -which they will if you let them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Streamlined for efficiency&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK if you delete a post after it makes it to the front page, people can still read it]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: In case you think you can post anything and simply remove it after,
there is actually a glitch that loads the text for about half a second before
displaying the “deleted” message. Even if you back out and click again it will
keep displaying the text before loading the “deleted” message.…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qfrxao/ysk_if_you_delete_a_post_after_it_makes_it_to_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qfrxao/ysk_if_you_delete_a_post_after_it_makes_it_to_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 23:40:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: In case you think you can post anything and simply remove it after, there is actually a glitch that loads the text for about half a second before displaying the “deleted” message. Even if you back out and click again it will keep displaying the text before loading the “deleted” message. This means anyone can actually screencap your “deleted” message.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Your Android phone comes set to reset itself after 15 wrong PIN entries]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: This setting is good for business phones which may have sensitive
information on them, but not necessarily for personal phones which are typically
tossed in a pocket or purse. Body parts or objects touching the screen can
trigger it, causing it to come on and accept "input". Quickly and…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qfhk5p/ysk_your_android_phone_comes_set_to_reset_itself/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qfhk5p/ysk_your_android_phone_comes_set_to_reset_itself/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 17:32:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  This setting is good for business phones which may have sensitive information on them, but not necessarily for personal phones which are typically tossed in a pocket or purse. Body parts or objects touching the screen can trigger it, causing it to come on and accept &amp;quot;input&amp;quot;. Quickly and suddenly you could find yourself looking at the initial setup screen. Pictures, messages, contacts, etc. - all could be lost completely if not backed up, and require a lengthy restore if they are backed up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Settings, Lock Screen, Secure Lock Settings (requires PIN), you can turn off &amp;quot;Auto factory reset&amp;quot; if you wish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: studies have found that the more you drink regularly over time, the higher your chances of having breast cancer. If you’re a woman and you have 3 drinks/week, your odds are 15% higher than a woman who doesn’t drink at all. And this risk goes up an estimated 10% for each extra drink/week.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: everyone loves ta-tas
https://www.webmd.com/breast-cancer/guide/link-between-breast-cancer-and-alcohol]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qf6zfz/ysk_studies_have_found_that_the_more_you_drink/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qf6zfz/ysk_studies_have_found_that_the_more_you_drink/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 03:39:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: everyone loves ta-tas &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.webmd.com/breast-cancer/guide/link-between-breast-cancer-and-alcohol&quot;&gt;https://www.webmd.com/breast-cancer/guide/link-between-breast-cancer-and-alcohol&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: if you have Funko pop figures in the box you can scan them on the Funko app to value them based on internet sales across websites]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Pop figures are widely collectable with limited edition or vaulted
figures no longer in production can be worth hundreds If not thousands. I found
out about the app where you scan the barcode at the bottom of the box and found
out one I own is worth $200, it's not limited edition or…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qf5dyu/ysk_if_you_have_funko_pop_figures_in_the_box_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qf5dyu/ysk_if_you_have_funko_pop_figures_in_the_box_you/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 02:42:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Pop figures are widely collectable with limited edition or vaulted figures no longer in production can be worth hundreds If not thousands. I found out about the app where you scan the barcode at the bottom of the box and found out one I own is worth $200, it&amp;#39;s not limited edition or anything it&amp;#39;s just older (2015-2018) around then which has stopped production on so that figure is worth alot more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was shocked when I saw my collection was worth triple what I spent only 4-5 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: To avoid supposedly healthy foods with chicory root high on the list of ingredients.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Because it's a cheap fiber additive that causes gas and other symptoms
of gastrointestinal discomfort.

There is a type of fiber called inulin, which in low to moderate amounts is a
good prebiotic and source of soluble fiber. However, in large amounts it can
cause gas, bloating, and…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qetzbp/ysk_to_avoid_supposedly_healthy_foods_with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qetzbp/ysk_to_avoid_supposedly_healthy_foods_with/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 21:47:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Because it&amp;#39;s a cheap fiber additive that causes gas and other symptoms of gastrointestinal discomfort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a type of fiber called inulin, which in low to moderate amounts is a good prebiotic and source of soluble fiber. However, in large amounts it can cause gas, bloating, and abdominal pain. Chicory root is one of the most common sources of inulin because it&amp;#39;s cheap, abundant, and in powder form can be added to almost anything to boost that food&amp;#39;s total fiber numbers without significantly impacting taste or texture. Everything from cereals to granola bars to fiber gummies and beyond has it these days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chicory root at near the bottom of the ingredients list doesn&amp;#39;t worry me. But, when it&amp;#39;s towards the top, I avoid it. Also, don&amp;#39;t assume because you bought a product once and it didn&amp;#39;t have chicory root that it never will. Food manufacturers change up the ingredients subtly all the time and it&amp;#39;s not at all uncommon for me to check a box of cereal I&amp;#39;ve been eating for a long time and suddenly notice it now has it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that when you get asked to verify being human on Google while using a VPN, it’s them trying to purposefully annoy you so you turn the VPN off]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK this? Because privacy]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qer7kz/ysk_that_when_you_get_asked_to_verify_being_human/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qer7kz/ysk_that_when_you_get_asked_to_verify_being_human/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 14:14:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK this? Because privacy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK That not all abuse is physical and if someone is making you feel bad emotionally all the time, that's still 100% abuse and just as bad.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Mental.Abuse drives thousands of people to depression and suicide and
nobody deserves that.

If you're struggling with someone that has never touched you but they are
degrading you and harming your mental state, that's still 100% abuse. If someone
makes you question yourself constantly and…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qeqkyc/ysk_that_not_all_abuse_is_physical_and_if_someone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qeqkyc/ysk_that_not_all_abuse_is_physical_and_if_someone/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 12:34:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Mental.Abuse drives thousands of people to depression and suicide and nobody deserves that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#39;re struggling with someone that has never touched you but they are degrading you and harming your mental state, that&amp;#39;s still 100% abuse. If someone makes you question yourself constantly and forces you to ask yourself constantly why it&amp;#39;s your fault? That&amp;#39;s 100% abuse. You&amp;#39;re not an asshole,.you&amp;#39;re not a bad person you just need another human that will appreciate you for you. If you need or want to talk to someone that can understand, message me or ANYONE in your life that you know loves you. Trust me, if can save your sanity, maybe even your life. You don&amp;#39;t need to feel bad for being alive. There is hope and love for your out there, don&amp;#39;t let yourself be taken down this way. You deserve better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Amazon is notorious for selling expired and useless Carbon Monoxide Detectors. Read the reviews and know what to look for.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK : Carbon Monoxide detectors expire, on average, after 7 years.

Expired detectors will fail to alarm when carbon monoxide levels are deadly, and
will also go off at ridiculous times for something that is no danger. This
creates a secondary danger as it creates the "boy who cries wolf"…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qeg5ro/ysk_amazon_is_notorious_for_selling_expired_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qeg5ro/ysk_amazon_is_notorious_for_selling_expired_and/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 00:34:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK : Carbon Monoxide detectors expire, on average, after 7 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expired detectors will fail to alarm when carbon monoxide levels are deadly, and will also go off at ridiculous times for something that is no danger. This creates a secondary danger as it creates the &amp;quot;boy who cries wolf&amp;quot; effect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amazon is notorious of selling very expired carbon monoxide detectors that will waste your money, your time, and not save your life in the event of high levels of carbon monoxide in your home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s is a great example of something to NEVER buy, that is shown as the top recommended on Amazon, sold by Amazon:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B002GP7CZS/ref=cm_sw_em_r_mt_dp_dl_GK3039N6GJWWJGX8WWSS?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;psc=1&quot;&gt;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B002GP7CZS/ref=cm_sw_em_r_mt_dp_dl_GK3039N6GJWWJGX8WWSS?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;psc=1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Always check the manufacture date on the back of a carbon monoxide detector. Replace after 7 years&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: if you ever have to quickly leave a room always tell the person you have to use the restroom]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: There are many reasons why you might need to quickly leave a room, and
you can always use "nature calls" as a reason. If you're in a situation where
they don't want you to go to the bathroom, it might not be safe to be there.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qec8ko/ysk_if_you_ever_have_to_quickly_leave_a_room/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qec8ko/ysk_if_you_ever_have_to_quickly_leave_a_room/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 23:38:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: There are many reasons why you might need to quickly leave a room, and you can always use &amp;quot;nature calls&amp;quot; as a reason. If you&amp;#39;re in a situation where they don&amp;#39;t want you to go to the bathroom, it might not be safe to be there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that if you are going to be away from home for several hours, your pets will probably enjoy chill instrumental music at a low volume]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Pet's lives can get monotonous when left home alone and music is one of
the best ways to make their lives more enjoyable! My cats love lofi chillhop &
remixes of old video game tracks, for example]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qecptt/ysk_that_if_you_are_going_to_be_away_from_home/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qecptt/ysk_that_if_you_are_going_to_be_away_from_home/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 22:34:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Pet&amp;#39;s lives can get monotonous when left home alone and music is one of the best ways to make their lives more enjoyable! My cats love lofi chillhop &amp;amp; remixes of old video game tracks, for example&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK organic fruits and veggies have chemical residues, just not from synthetic pesticides]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Organic produce can include the same chemical compounds as conventional
produce sprayed with synthetic pesticides (but at more variable rates), and
needs to be rinsed to avoid ingesting.

In the US, organic produce can also have chemical residue, but the difference is
organics can only be…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qe4l09/ysk_organic_fruits_and_veggies_have_chemical/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qe4l09/ysk_organic_fruits_and_veggies_have_chemical/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 16:25:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Organic produce can include the same chemical compounds as conventional produce sprayed with synthetic pesticides (but at more variable rates), and needs to be rinsed to avoid ingesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the US, organic produce can also have chemical residue, but the difference is organics can only be treated with certain classes of chemicals. Most traditional pesticides are synthetically produced chemical compounds, and these aren&amp;#39;t allowed to be applied to organic crops. Organic crops can have the same chemical compounds applied, if they&amp;#39;re not produced synthetically, but are produced by a bacteria that &amp;#39;poops&amp;#39; out the same chemical (along with many additional chemical compounds). These safe, beneficial bacteria are sprayed on the plants or soil. The chemical compound is exactly the same, but because it&amp;#39;s a biological pesticide, it&amp;#39;s okay to apply. Chemical products like pesticides are regulated much, much more heavily than other products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chemical applications have to follow a lot of rules, for example,  they usually can&amp;#39;t be applied after flowering, and since the fruit develops from a pollinated flower, it&amp;#39;s really the leaves and stems that take the chemical load, not the fruit. And vegetables that grow underground like potatoes and onions don&amp;#39;t get exposed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a PhD in an agricultural plant genetics, and have worked in the biological agriculture industry (but don&amp;#39;t anymore). Personally, I don&amp;#39;t worry too much about organic, and believe it&amp;#39;s better to buy local (from a conventional or organic farmer). If the produce has been picked more quickly, it will have a better nutritional profile (higher nutrient and micronutrient levels, greater diversity of flavonoids like carotenoids and anthocyanins, and other antioxidants). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to buy organic, focus on leafy greens and international fruit, especially bananas -- where organic means a better quality of work and life for the workers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Sometimes your bathroom session will require more than one flush. And that's okay]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: This is mostly pertaining to public toilets, though I'm sure your
housemates will approve as well. If you leave poop or toilet paper floating in a
public toilet people tend to get grossed out and not want to use that toilet.
Also, if you're having a particularly smelly poop in a multi-stall…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qe62lg/ysk_sometimes_your_bathroom_session_will_require/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qe62lg/ysk_sometimes_your_bathroom_session_will_require/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 16:25:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This is mostly pertaining to public toilets, though I&amp;#39;m sure your housemates will approve as well. If you leave poop or toilet paper floating in a public toilet people tend to get grossed out and not want to use that toilet. Also, if you&amp;#39;re having a particularly smelly poop in a multi-stall bathroom, it&amp;#39;s okay to have periodic courtesy flushes so your stank isn&amp;#39;t just sitting there under you. Plus, who wants to be the nasty dude at work who leaves gross toilets? Bathroom etiquette goes a long way&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK It's that time of year again to check your tire pressures. Colder air will occupy less volume.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: weather cold, pressure low.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qdtd07/ysk_its_that_time_of_year_again_to_check_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qdtd07/ysk_its_that_time_of_year_again_to_check_your/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 01:49:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: weather cold, pressure low.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK if you work in public service in the US, you may be eligible to receive credit for past ineligible payments towards federal loan forgiveness.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: This is a limited opportunity offered to public service workers through
the US Dept of Education, has received very little press, and requires you to
submit a PSLF (Public Service Loan Forgiveness) form by Oct 31, 2021. Since you
can get credits for payments as far back as October 2007,…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qdp5hp/ysk_if_you_work_in_public_service_in_the_us_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qdp5hp/ysk_if_you_work_in_public_service_in_the_us_you/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 00:42:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; This is a limited opportunity offered to public service workers through the US Dept of Education, has received very little press, and requires you to submit a PSLF (Public Service Loan Forgiveness) form by &lt;strong&gt;Oct 31, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;. Since you can get credits for payments as far back as October 2007, this could potentially eliminate your debt or get you significantly closer to forgiveness. You can find out more information, how to apply, and if you would qualify at &lt;a href=&quot;https://studentaid.gov/announcements-events/pslf-limited-waiver&quot;&gt;https://studentaid.gov/announcements-events/pslf-limited-waiver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are you a public service worker?&lt;/strong&gt;
If you are employed by any federal government agency full time, you count as a public service worker. But that&amp;#39;s not all! You are also considered one if you work full time for a state government, local government, tribal government, the US military, or a not-for-profit organization. You also may qualify if you work in education, public health, law enforcement, emergency management, elder or disability care, or at a library. The website linked above provides more specific information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do not work for the federal government or in finance or with student loans, so I cannot provide advice or any guarantees. I just figured I should share this because I literally found out about this yesterday, the deadline is October 31st, and the form was easy to complete and submit, at least in my case. Hope this helps someone in these rough times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: if you have trouble getting out of bed in the morning, try sleeping with your curtains open.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Getting good sleep is essential for a healthy day to day life. As
someone who slept terribly for a few years, this small tip helped me out
immensely.

During my college years, i slept in a room with no windows. Pitch black. I'd
wake up at 6am every morning feeling like i had been hit by a…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qds8sb/ysk_if_you_have_trouble_getting_out_of_bed_in_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qds8sb/ysk_if_you_have_trouble_getting_out_of_bed_in_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 00:42:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Getting good sleep is essential for a healthy day to day life. As someone who slept terribly for a few years, this small tip helped me out immensely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During my college years, i slept in a room with no windows. Pitch black. I&amp;#39;d wake up at 6am every morning feeling like i had been hit by a truck and it would take me pretty much half of the morning to get my brain going. After that, i moved and had a bedroom with one window over my bed. Out of lazyness, i started sleeping with the curtains open and over time noticed i slept better, woke up fresher and not feeling as heavy as before. I looked it up and basically what happens is that the gradual increase in the level of light in the room will stop the melatonin production in your brain, essentially making you less sleepy over time, even while you are still asleep, so you don&amp;#39;t jump from deep sleep state to awake. This will help you get out of bed easier and up and running much faster. Here&amp;#39;s a short article on how to sleep better: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.sciencefocus.com/the-human-body/how-to-get-the-perfect-nights-sleep/amp/&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.sciencefocus.com/the-human-body/how-to-get-the-perfect-nights-sleep/amp/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope someone finds this useful. For me it was a game changer. Everyone&amp;#39;s sleep is different, so give it a try, you&amp;#39;ve got nothing to lose :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: You should check your debit/credit card statement right now for anything titled "POS DEBIT GOOGLE [random person's name]" with charges for around $12.99-$13.01. It's a new scam going around, I just noticed it yesterday]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK:

Checked my debit card statement randomly yesterday, noticed a strange charge,
since I hardly ever use my debit card. Cancelled the card and am getting
refunded, but when I looked into it more, it looks like this is a new scam going
around, possibly some data breach, since myself and a few…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qdn2h0/ysk_you_should_check_your_debitcredit_card/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qdn2h0/ysk_you_should_check_your_debitcredit_card/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 20:00:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Checked my debit card statement randomly yesterday, noticed a strange charge, since I hardly ever use my debit card. Cancelled the card and am getting refunded, but when I looked into it more, it looks like this is a new scam going around, possibly some data breach, since myself and a few other comments I&amp;#39;ve read rarely/never use their cards for any physical purchases. See more info here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/personalfinance/comments/q2eyyv/got_a_random_charge_under_pos_google_debit/&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/personalfinance/comments/q2eyyv/got_a_random_charge_under_pos_google_debit/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/personalfinance/comments/pgmvw7/google_charged_me_two_1299_charges_and_i_dont/&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/personalfinance/comments/pgmvw7/google_charged_me_two_1299_charges_and_i_dont/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.callercenter.com/650-253-0000.html&quot;&gt;https://www.callercenter.com/650-253-0000.html&lt;/a&gt; (this is the phone number listed in the info of the debit card charge, it&amp;#39;s for google apparently, but most of the responses on that site are people complaining of similar fraudulent charges on their cards)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK if you see yourself as a character, hero or author of the story you’re telling about yourself. It can explain a lot about your inner life.]]></title><description><![CDATA[WHY YSK: There’s always some unwritten story you tell about yourself without
being aware of it, and it guides how you respond to stressors - whether you see
them as threats or challenges, struggles or obstacles that are part of life. In
psychology, this is called narrative…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qdi1y3/ysk_if_you_see_yourself_as_a_character_hero_or/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qdi1y3/ysk_if_you_see_yourself_as_a_character_hero_or/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 17:02:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK: There’s always some unwritten story you tell about yourself without being aware of it, and it guides how you respond to stressors - whether you see them as threats or challenges, struggles or obstacles that are part of life. In psychology, this is called &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/269603657_Narrative_Identity&quot;&gt;narrative identity&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;A character&lt;/strong&gt; is someone who thinks that stuff happens to them, that their successes or failures result from external factors beyond their control.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;A hero&lt;/strong&gt; is someone who isn’t afraid to go to battle to overcome the curveballs life throws at them.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;An author&lt;/strong&gt; embraces everything that happens to them and takes responsibility for creating something beautiful and meaningful out of their experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s more about this concept in &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@Ellie_/3be15461d9bd&quot;&gt;this article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: when driving on a highway in America, the left lane is for passing!]]></title><description><![CDATA[I, like I'm sure many other people, was not taught how to drive on highways and
multi-lane roads correctly by my driving instructor. I learned the correct way
later on by my dad.

Many people call the left lane the "fast lane" because they assume if they are
going faster than the speed limit they…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qd853j/ysk_when_driving_on_a_highway_in_america_the_left/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qd853j/ysk_when_driving_on_a_highway_in_america_the_left/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 06:29:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I, like I&amp;#39;m sure many other people, was not taught how to drive on highways and multi-lane roads correctly by my driving instructor. I learned the correct way later on by my dad. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people call the left lane the &amp;quot;fast lane&amp;quot; because they assume if they are going faster than the speed limit they are in the correct Lane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is just not true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The left lane is for passing folks in the right lane and when you&amp;#39;ve cleared them and have space, MOVE OVER TO THE RIGHT LANE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There will ALWAYS be someone moving faster than you, don&amp;#39;t try to &amp;quot;help them control their driving speed.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: driving on highways incorrectly causes traffic which causes accidents. Everyone has somewhere they&amp;#39;d rather be so why not make it easier for everyone by making the roads better to drive on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: true it&amp;#39;s not &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; for passing, check w your states laws&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: You should know that Polygraph Machines are NOT lie detectors.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: It is just a perpetuated myth that I think people should know about.
While I do like the fact that it gives police an edge against real criminals, it
could also be abused to frighten innocent individuals in an attempt to force a
confession. Also, it is used by some companies and government…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qd64p4/ysk_you_should_know_that_polygraph_machines_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qd64p4/ysk_you_should_know_that_polygraph_machines_are/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 03:41:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It is just a perpetuated myth that I think people should know about. While I do like the fact that it gives police an edge against real criminals, it could also be abused to frighten innocent individuals in an attempt to force a confession. Also, it is used by some companies and government organizations when they are hiring, which makes absolutely no sense since they are far less than accurate and they know that. Even the inventor of the original polygraph machine said it wasn&amp;#39;t a lie detector and would be vocal about how it&amp;#39;s bullshit. It only has around a 40% success rate when it comes to &amp;quot;spotting lies&amp;quot;. It has an even lower success rate when you take into account people with anxiety, or people on drugs. Additionally, pathological liars and psychopaths usually pass polygraphs with flying colors. And people can be trained to pass the polygraph, you can alter results just by thinking stressful thoughts and clenching your butthole (seriously). Police know that it&amp;#39;s BS and tend to stick to using it as an interrogation tool, but fuck that shit if a company tries to get you to take a polygraph to apply for a job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK - You can give yourself the Heimlich Maneuver in a car.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: People often eat while driving, and experiencing choking while you're
driving a car is right up there with discovering a spider in your motorcycle
helmet while doing 70 on the interstate.

In the event that you begin choking while driving, pull over immediately and in
your seat try Plan…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qceeq9/ysk_you_can_give_yourself_the_heimlich_maneuver/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qceeq9/ysk_you_can_give_yourself_the_heimlich_maneuver/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 13:44:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: People often eat while driving, and experiencing choking while you&amp;#39;re driving a car is right up there with discovering a spider in your motorcycle helmet while doing 70 on the interstate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the event that you begin choking while driving, pull over immediately and in your seat try Plan A.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make a fist (it&amp;#39;s best to do this with your non-dominant hand but it doesn&amp;#39;t really matter). Put the thumb of your fist against your stomach, below your ribs and above your belly button. Grab your fist firmly with the other hand and jam it AS HARD AS YOU CAN up and under your ribcage with a fast punching movement. You&amp;#39;re literally trying to suckerpunch yourself. It doesn&amp;#39;t matter if it hurts. If it works you&amp;#39;ll have plenty of time to complain. If it doesn&amp;#39;t, it won&amp;#39;t bother you for long. So lean into it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this doesn&amp;#39;t work within fifteen seconds (or your arm gets too tired). Stand up, open your car door, and lean over your car door. Same idea (this is commonly done with a chair), quick thrusts until the object clears from your throat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of people are taught the chair technique, but almost nobody knows that you can use a car door with the same training and results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay safe out there kids.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK Mental health apps can be stigmatising and superficial, and AI doesn’t make things better.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I just read an article
[https://hazelgale.medium.com/mental-health-tech-is-broken-were-betting-on-games-to-fix-it-e1c413890a25]
that stunned me and it seemed like something important to share with you.

WHY YSK:

So, it turns out that only a small minority of people (less than 20%) live…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qcoxa1/ysk_mental_health_apps_can_be_stigmatising_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qcoxa1/ysk_mental_health_apps_can_be_stigmatising_and/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 13:30:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just read &lt;a href=&quot;https://hazelgale.medium.com/mental-health-tech-is-broken-were-betting-on-games-to-fix-it-e1c413890a25&quot;&gt;an article&lt;/a&gt; that stunned me and it seemed like something important to share with you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, it turns out that only a small minority of people (less than 20%) live with positive levels of mental health, and over 80% of us will likely experience clinical symptoms at some point in our lives. Mental healthcare is broken pretty much everywhere and many of us will count on digital solutions for help. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, there are a lot of problems with those, and you should be aware of them so you can make well-informed decisions about how you take care of your wellbeing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To cite just two examples from the article:&lt;br/&gt;
One, AI therapists/chatbots are nowhere close to mimicking human conversations that make you feel connected, heard and seen. They are machine-like, shallow and often insensitive. “For example, one chatbot, when told “I am depressed,” responded dismissively: ‘Maybe the weather is affecting you’.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two, mental health apps can create self-stigma. “Users who are experiencing low-level symptoms of a disorder may feel labeled by an app that assumes that they have a clinical diagnosis. Self-stigma from this labeling can be harmful, lowering self-esteem and self-efficacy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://hazelgale.medium.com/mental-health-tech-is-broken-were-betting-on-games-to-fix-it-e1c413890a25&quot;&gt;Here’s&lt;/a&gt; the full article.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: “Ms.” is a marriage-neutral honorific for women and used exactly the same as “Mr.” is used for men]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: You should know this so you can select the appropriate term to use when
addressing women in formal contexts, and to avoid misinterpreting this term. I
often see a lot of confusion and misconceptions about this term.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ms.

"Miss," "Mrs." and "Ms." are all…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qcbond/ysk_ms_is_a_marriageneutral_honorific_for_women/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qcbond/ysk_ms_is_a_marriageneutral_honorific_for_women/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 22:33:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: You should know this so you can select the appropriate term to use when addressing women in formal contexts, and to avoid misinterpreting this term. I often see a lot of confusion and misconceptions about this term. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ms&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ms&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Miss,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Mrs.&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Ms.&amp;quot; are all abbreviations of &amp;quot;Mistress.&amp;quot; Originally, all three abbreviations were in common use and used interchangeably, but over time &amp;quot;Miss&amp;quot; came to mean an unmarried woman, &amp;quot;Mrs.&amp;quot; a married woman, and &amp;quot;Ms.&amp;quot; fell out of favor. This forced women to be addressed according to their marital status, while &amp;quot;Mr.&amp;quot; (short for Mister) remained marriage-neutral. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently, &amp;quot;Ms.&amp;quot; (pronounced &amp;quot;mizz&amp;quot;) has been revived as a marriage neutral honorific for women and it has become increasingly popular. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few misconceptions I&amp;#39;ve noticed: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;People think &amp;quot;Ms.&amp;quot; means a woman is divorced or widowed (it does not- though divorced women might be more likely to use it)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;People think &amp;quot;Ms.&amp;quot; is short for &amp;quot;miss&amp;quot; and means the same thing (it does not- Miss means an unmarried woman, Ms. is marriage-neutral).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;People think &amp;quot;Ms.&amp;quot; is pronounced the same as &amp;quot;miss.&amp;quot; (some regional accents pronounce &amp;quot;miss&amp;quot; as &amp;quot;mizz&amp;quot; so in those places they are pronounced similarly, but for places where &amp;quot;miss&amp;quot; is pronounced with an s sound they are pronounced differently). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So  in conclusion, if you&amp;#39;re not sure if a woman is married (or you want to just skip the whole marriage issue altogether) you can use the honorific Ms. Use it exactly how you would use &amp;quot;Mr.&amp;quot; for men. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bonus YSK: a common gender-neural honorific for non-binary people is &amp;quot;Mx.&amp;quot; (pronounced like &amp;quot;mix&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;meks&amp;quot;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK if you purchased a maintenance warranty through the dealer, you can get a refund if you’re trading in a vehicle or if that vehicle was totaled]]></title><description><![CDATA[WHY YSK… maintenance warranties can be refunded if you end up trading in a
vehicle purchased through a dealer, or if you total out a vehicle from an
accident. Possibly resulting in a favorable refund.

I recently traded in an suv that still had an extended maintenance warranty
purchased through a…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qc60ln/ysk_if_you_purchased_a_maintenance_warranty/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qc60ln/ysk_if_you_purchased_a_maintenance_warranty/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 20:22:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK… maintenance warranties can be refunded if you end up trading in a vehicle purchased through a dealer, or if you total out a vehicle from an accident. Possibly resulting in a favorable refund. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently traded in an suv that still had an extended maintenance warranty purchased through a major named dealer. As we were signing paperwork for the a new vehicle, I asked if there was a refund option from the traded in vehicle, the finance guy was hesitant and didn’t answer my question directly. I let it slide, until we were about to leave. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find the finance manager and asked the same question. And again….. was greeted with hesitation. He eventually steers me to the proper process to receive a refund, but the hinkyness to it was all to shady as they made me feel I was stealing from them. Which I wasn’t, I’m rightfully getting my money back. The dealers are pocketing an exorbitant amount of money that people have no clue about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK Self-awareness, “the metaskill of the 21st century”]]></title><description><![CDATA[WHY YSK:
Psychologist and researcher Dr. Tasha Eurich calls self-awareness “the metaskill
of the 21st century”. It’s the ability to see yourself clearly, understand who
you are and how you fit in the world. Studies show that self-awareness is a
powerful factor underlying happiness, good…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qbycnp/ysk_selfawareness_the_metaskill_of_the_21st/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qbycnp/ysk_selfawareness_the_metaskill_of_the_21st/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 15:58:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK:&lt;br/&gt;
Psychologist and researcher Dr. Tasha Eurich calls self-awareness “the metaskill of the 21st century”. It’s the ability to see yourself clearly, understand who you are and how you fit in the world. Studies show that self-awareness is a powerful factor underlying happiness, good relationships, effective parenthood, job performance, leadership, creativity, confidence and a lot more.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@Ellie_/self-awareness-the-metaskill-of-the-21st-century-2334d840d8fa&quot;&gt;Here’s an article&lt;/a&gt; explaining more of the research and some ways to put it into practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that if your plane makes a water landing, resist the urge to inflate your life jacket immediately.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: Resist the impulse to inflate your life jacket immediately if a plane
is making an emergency landing on water. The buoyancy of the jacket could make
it harder for you to run inside the cabin if water rushes in. So swim to an
exit, then inflate your jacket to stay afloat.]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qbwivz/ysk_that_if_your_plane_makes_a_water_landing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qbwivz/ysk_that_if_your_plane_makes_a_water_landing/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 11:00:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Resist the impulse to inflate your life jacket immediately if a plane is making an emergency landing on water. The buoyancy of the jacket could make it harder for you to run inside the cabin if water rushes in.
So swim to an exit, then inflate your jacket to stay afloat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK what percentage points are.]]></title><description><![CDATA[The notion of "points" when discussing percentages tells you what the words
"more" and "less" actually mean -- the word "points" in these cases means
addition instead of multiplication.

For example, if you are negotiating for royalties on a project, and the opening
offer is for 10% of the profits.…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qbsib8/ysk_what_percentage_points_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qbsib8/ysk_what_percentage_points_are/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 06:55:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The notion of &amp;quot;points&amp;quot; when discussing percentages tells you what the words &amp;quot;more&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;less&amp;quot; actually mean -- the word &amp;quot;points&amp;quot; in these cases means addition instead of multiplication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, if you are negotiating for royalties on a project, and the opening offer is for 10% of the profits. Asking for 5% more is very different than asking for 5 percentage points more! Asking for five percentage points more than 10% means 10%+5%=15%, whereas 5% more then 10% means 10% + (10% x 5%) = 10.5%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Without the notion of percentage points, discussing percentages is ambiguous. This will definitely come up when refinancing your house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As another example, a home loan might be 3% per year. If you are renegotiating the loan for lower monthly payments, they may mention increasing the percentage by some number, like 1.5 percentage points. That means your new interest rate will be 3% + 1.5% = 4.5%. This sounds small, but really your interest rate just went up by 50%!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK that “an 80% increase of 10% does not mean something is now 90%. It has been increased by 80% of 10%, so now it’s 18%]]></title><description><![CDATA[A lot of people seem to misunderstand how percentages work, so i’m here to give
a little explanation.

For example if you have a base 10% chance of something happening, and your
chances are increased by 50%, they are now 15%, not 60.

Why YSK: it’s never a bad thing to learn about percentages and…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qbdkqn/ysk_that_an_80_increase_of_10_does_not_mean/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qbdkqn/ysk_that_an_80_increase_of_10_does_not_mean/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 17:02:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lot of people seem to misunderstand how percentages work, so i’m here to give a little explanation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example if you have a base 10% chance of something happening, and your chances are increased by 50%, they are now 15%, not 60. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: it’s never a bad thing to learn about percentages and how they work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK The average height for men in the US is 5'9.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: For the boys out there stressing on their height let me tell you that
it's not a big deal and you are probably pretty close to average. There are
people asking for 6'+ but those are usually younger people who are living their
lives and not settling down yet, it's much less common as you get…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qb75bh/ysk_the_average_height_for_men_in_the_us_is_59/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qb75bh/ysk_the_average_height_for_men_in_the_us_is_59/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 13:04:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: For the boys out there stressing on their height let me tell you that it&amp;#39;s not a big deal and you are probably pretty close to average. There are people asking for 6&amp;#39;+ but those are usually younger people who are living their lives and not settling down yet, it&amp;#39;s much less common as you get older and see more people looking for serious relationships. Also most people really don&amp;#39;t care about your height so don&amp;#39;t let the relative few that do bother you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And 5&amp;#39;9 is still pretty tall, you can reach most high shelves and the tops of the fridge. And for my guys in the lower range let me tell you, have a taller partner  is pretty cool cause you get to either be the little spoon or the jet pack while cuddling and both are a good time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t let your height be something that hold you back or keeps you down because it&amp;#39;s not a big deal, and honestly as a 5&amp;#39;10-5&amp;#39;11 guy (depends on the time of day) the world just seems more comfortable if your a bit shorter. So accept it and let your confidence grow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: The Firefox Add-on Bypass Paywall Clean allows you to bypass paywalls on sites like The New York Times, etc]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK:

To anyone who doesn't want to sign up for something like a NY Times subscription
in order to read their articles, I just found a solution. Bypass Paywall Clean
by magnolia1234 lets you read it. I've only used it for 1 day, but so far it's
been awesome and super easy!]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qayisg/ysk_the_firefox_addon_bypass_paywall_clean_allows/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qayisg/ysk_the_firefox_addon_bypass_paywall_clean_allows/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 01:52:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To anyone who doesn&amp;#39;t want to sign up for something like a NY Times subscription in order to read their articles, I just found a solution. Bypass Paywall Clean by magnolia1234 lets you read it. I&amp;#39;ve only used it for 1 day, but so far it&amp;#39;s been awesome and super easy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>