<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 15:04:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK手机上的黑色荧光笔功能并不是遮挡图像或文字的有效方法。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：如果你分享有个人信息的东西
个人信息，并认为你把个人信息涂黑了。
你可能会不小心将这些信息透露给陌生人。我知道从
经验告诉我，被涂黑的东西可能看起来很黑......。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcc2xf/ysk_the_black_highlighter_feature_on_phones_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcc2xf/ysk_the_black_highlighter_feature_on_phones_is/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 14:42:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: if you share something that has personal information, and think that you blacked out the personal information, you could accidentally be revealing that information to strangers. I know from experience that something &amp;amp;#39;blacked out&amp;amp;#39; can look jet black on the phone screen without that being the case on other devices; even if it does appear jet black, raising the brightness can reveal the hidden image.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，你的牙齿和牙龈与你的心脏直接相关，通过保持良好的牙齿卫生来保持它们的健康，也有助于保护你的心脏。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p><strong>为什么是YSK:</strong>虽然牙齿健康非常重要
往往被忽视的一个原因是，你的牙齿和牙龈与你的心脏直接相关。
牙齿和牙龈与你的心脏直接相关，而不良的牙齿卫生可以
如果不加注意，有可能导致心脏问题。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcw7ap/ysk_that_your_teeth_and_gums_are_linked_directly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcw7ap/ysk_that_your_teeth_and_gums_are_linked_directly/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 04:54:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Why YSK:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; While dental health is very important in general, one reason that often gets overlooked is that your teeth and gums are directly linked to your heart, and poor dental hygiene can potentially lead to heart problems if left unattended.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some of those can include:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Gum disease, which can increase your risk of developing heart disease.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;If you don&amp;amp;#39;t take care of your mouth, you risk developing a bacterial infection in your bloodstream. This, in turn, can potentially affect your heart (specifically heart valves -- be very careful if you&amp;amp;#39;ve had heart surgery to repair/replace them).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Poor dental care can lead to type 2 diabetes, and there&amp;amp;#39;s an apparent link between type 2 and cardiovascular disease.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s worth noting that more research is needed to determine exactly what the links are, why they occur and how prevalent they are. But studies seem to indicate that they do, at the very least, exist in some capacity, and you can never be too careful when it comes to your health (especially not with your heart).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Practice good dental hygiene by doing some or, ideally, all of the following:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Brushing your teeth twice a day for 2 minutes at a time (make sure you are brushing all the way to the back).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Flossing once a day.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Using mouthwash frequently.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;If possible, use toothpaste with or drink water that contains fluoride.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;See a dentist regularly for check-ups and cleanings.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Obviously, you can have heart issues regardless of the state of your teeth. And if you &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;do&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; have heart issues (of any kind, whether congenital or adult), it&amp;amp;#39;s still important to maintain good oral hygiene so that you don&amp;amp;#39;t potentially make those problems worse.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Regardless, it&amp;amp;#39;s still a good idea to brush your teeth twice a day. It keeps more than just your mouth happy!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sources:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/adult-health/expert-answers/heart-disease-prevention/faq-20057986&quot;&amp;gt;Mayo Clinic&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.heart.org/en/news/2018/11/07/bad-tooth-brushing-habits-tied-to-higher-heart-risk&quot;&amp;gt;American Heart Association&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/health/gum-disease-and-heart-disease&quot;&amp;gt;Healthline&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(Disclaimer: I am not a dentist or a doctor, so please let me know if I have misinterpreted any of the sources, or if they are somehow not considered legit.)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK："非品牌 "麦片与 "名牌 "麦片完全一样，只是它们通常保留了（更好的）经典配方，而且在盲测中，几乎每次都表现得更好。凯洛格公司解雇了1400名工人，请记住，支付更多的美元并不意味着更好。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK</p> <p>当考虑每份支付0.27美元与0.14美元时
时，你应该知道，大多数品牌与非品牌之间的差异很小（如果有的话）。
大多数品牌与非品牌之间的差异（如果有的话），而且通常情况下，差异在于
不同的是，非品牌保留了更好的产品。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcp9gv/ysk_offbrand_cereals_are_identical_to_name_brand/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcp9gv/ysk_offbrand_cereals_are_identical_to_name_brand/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 21:44:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When considering paying $0.27 per serving vs $0.14 per serving, you should know that there is very little difference (if any) between most brands and their off-brand, and often times the difference is that the &amp;amp;quot;off-brand&amp;amp;quot; retains the better tasting original recipe vs the name brand Cereals cost-cutting, recipe changing, etc;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Name Brand cereal seems better due to their superior marketing, however in almost every instance (depending on the off-brand) the non-name brand cereal beats the name brand cereal in blind taste tests.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This means that their marketing is working, however they are in reality NOT better, in almost every instance.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Note:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; I &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;know&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; there are some cereal off-brands out there which clearly do not match/beat the name brand, however for the most part, the majority of them are identical or better than the original.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And... &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;With Kellogg firing 1400 workers rather than providing better wages or working environment&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, it&amp;amp;#39;s important to remember that, for the most part, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;your extra $ is going toward their superior marketing and trickery to make their brand seem &amp;amp;quot;better&amp;amp;quot;, not a truly better product.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Spend your money in places that share your values, and in this case, on an often identical or superior product. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Paying more $, in this case does not equal a better product, and in fact only gets you a more commonly marketed name, and often a more poorly performing brand in taste tests.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Edit:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; For those looking for taste tests, there are simply too many to link here, depending on which &amp;amp;quot;off brand&amp;amp;quot; you want to see tested vs the big name cereals. Google &amp;amp;quot;off brand cereal taste test&amp;amp;quot; and you&amp;amp;#39;ll find many in-depth reviews and even videos describing the look, and the taste difference (if any) of whatever brand they&amp;amp;#39;re testing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你要减薪了]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>可能只是在雇主中不受欢迎，但是
你应该知道，通货膨胀率约为6%，对我们大多数人来说可能要高得多。
对我们大多数人来说，所以如果你今年没有收到至少6%的加薪
你就会被减薪。你应该要求你的雇主...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcmrzm/ysk_you_are_getting_a_paycut/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcmrzm/ysk_you_are_getting_a_paycut/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 21:44:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Probably only unpopular among employers, but you should know that the inflation rate is around 6% and probably much higher for most of us, so if you are not receiving a raise this year for at least 6% you are getting a pay-cut.  You should ask your employer to explain to you why they think you are worth less now then you were last year.   Why ysk: Inflation generally hits lower income people a lot faster and harder than higher income earners and some owners/employers may not realize how badly it is affecting you.  Also, you have to shoot your shot.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 说外语的一半是了解其独特的音调、旋律和节奏，这可以通过听母语者的录音和模仿 "哒哒哒 "等方式进行练习。学习词汇只是学习外语的一半。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p><strong>为什么选择YSK</strong>: 因为旅行
因为旅行和说一门外语，除了基本的流利，没有浓重的
口音，是很困难的。如果一个短语使用熟悉的轻声/重声，讲母语的人可以更容易地理解外国人。
如果一个短语使用了熟悉的轻音/旋律/节奏，就可以更容易地理解外国人，这需要...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcjbsp/ysk_half_of_speaking_a_foreign_language_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcjbsp/ysk_half_of_speaking_a_foreign_language_is/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 18:38:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Why YSK&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: Because traveling and speaking a foreign language, beyond rudimentary fluency without a thick accent, is difficult. Native speakers can understand foreigners much easier if a phrase uses the familiar lilt/melody/rhythm, which requires muscle memory of tongue placement and mouth movement.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For example, Spanish and Italian share a lot of the same vocabulary, but the words and phrases themselves are spoken in vastly different ways. Spanish is very staccato, while Italian tends to chain words together with a circular intonation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你在找工作，尽管普遍认为求职信并不重要，而且会被忽视，但公司绝对会阅读求职信，如果你至少没有努力提交求职信，有些公司会放弃你的申请。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么选择YSK：我曾帮助过好几年的公司。
1，公司确实使用系统（ATS）来自动过滤非相关的帖子。
1，公司确实使用系统（ATS）来自动过滤掉不相关的帖子，2，当他们真的接触到
2，当他们接触到人时，他们寻找的最大东西之一，除了你的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rciits/ysk_if_youre_job_hunting_despite_the_widespread/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rciits/ysk_if_youre_job_hunting_despite_the_widespread/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 16:42:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: I worked for several years helping companies with their recruitment efforts and 1, companies do use systems (ATS) to automatically filter out non-relevant posts and, 2, when they do get to the human, one of the biggest things they look for, beyond your personal work and educational history, is the effort put into applications - someone that has put together a Cover Letter will always stand out over someone that doesn&amp;amp;#39;t. As someone that&amp;amp;#39;s also applied for lots of jobs, I know how shitty companies are at not getting back to candidates, but if you want to win a job, you&amp;amp;#39;ve got to go the extra mile.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，美国各地的工人对加入工会表现出越来越大的兴趣，如果你想支持这股暗流，你能做的就是在一家公司表现出采取破坏工会或一般的反工会措施时，抵制该公司的产品。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：过去几年，阶级意识在美国劳动力中迅速增长。
在过去的几年里，阶级意识在美国的劳动力中迅速增长。最好的办法是
对这一势头做出贡献的最佳方式是做一个有良心的消费者，并有选择地购买
在一个人的购买中。许多消费者忘记了他们有这个非常...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rc7j7b/ysk_that_workers_all_over_the_us_are_showing_an/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rc7j7b/ysk_that_workers_all_over_the_us_are_showing_an/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 03:49:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Class consciousness is growing rapidly among the American workforce for the past few years. The best way to contribute to this momentum is to be a conscientious consumer and be selective in one&amp;amp;#39;s purchases. Many consumers forget that they have this very effective tool in their arsenal against bad corporate practices.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：日本没有公平使用法。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：最近我看到了一些
的声明，这些人在他们的视频中不断地被索赔，或者因为审查日本产品而面临日本公司的法律威胁。
的视频，或者因为审查日本内容（主要是动漫）而面临日本公司的法律威胁。
内容（主要是动漫）。这是因为即使在Youtubes指南中...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbks00/ysk_japan_does_not_have_fair_use_laws/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbks00/ysk_japan_does_not_have_fair_use_laws/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 02:49:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Recenty I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen a few statements about youtubers/influencers who are constantly being claimed on their videos or facing legal threats by Japanese companies for reviewing Japanese content (mostly anime). This is because even though in Youtubes guide lines of fair use, what they post is ok. But fair use doesn&amp;amp;#39;t exist in Japan so big companies like Toei for example would see it just as a copyright violation or stealing products that they made. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Recently Three Japanese men were convinced of violating copyright laws for making and uploading movie reviews for Japanese movies. So this is something companies are willing to sue individuals for and have them sentenced to jail.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;edit (Hopefully I haven&amp;amp;#39;t broken any rules, I&amp;amp;#39;m on mobile so hopefully I&amp;amp;#39;ve covered everything.)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你知道软件没有问题，在把笔记本带到维修店时，不要把硬盘或固态硬盘留在里面。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：这些公司可能会进行备份和
也许没有正确地存储它们。数据是有价值的，你不希望它到处都是。
到处都是。不要把你的数据放在没有保护的地方！</p> <p>移除你的
硬盘或固态硬盘对大多数笔记本电脑来说并不难，它将...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbry7i/ysk_dont_leave_your_hard_drive_or_ssd_in_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbry7i/ysk_dont_leave_your_hard_drive_or_ssd_in_your/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 22:50:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: These companies may make backups and maybe not store them properly. Data is valuable and you don&amp;amp;#39;t want it to be everywhere. Don&amp;amp;#39;t keep your data somewhere unprotected!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Removing your hard drive or SSD is not hard for most laptops, it will only take a few minutes once you know how to do it and in most cases, it won&amp;amp;#39;t hurt your laptop.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s not always neccesary. Here&amp;amp;#39;s when you should and when you should:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You should when:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You&amp;amp;#39;re bringing it to a local shop that just does repairs(small businesses with just a few people working there)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;There&amp;amp;#39;s something physically broken, like the screen, the keyboard or the charging hole.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You got sensitive data on your laptop(passwords, private media etc)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t when:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You&amp;amp;#39;re sending your laptop back for warranty&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;There&amp;amp;#39;s warranty stickers on screws, and you still have warranty on your laptop(in that case, just send it back)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You don&amp;amp;#39;t have the proper tools to do it&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 在晚上使用止汗剂]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么选择YSK：作为一个曾经超级爱出汗的青少年，了解到这一点改变了游戏规则。
患有多汗症的青少年，了解到这是一个改变游戏规则的方法。止汗剂必须要
如果你在洗完澡后直接涂抹止汗剂，而且还是在湿润的情况下，那么你的皮肤必须吸收止汗剂才能发挥作用。
如果你在淋浴后直接涂抹，而且还是湿的；或者在早上出汗后涂抹，它就不会起作用......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbvhey/ysk_apply_antiperspirant_at_night/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbvhey/ysk_apply_antiperspirant_at_night/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:51:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: As a formerly super sweaty teenager with hyperhidrosis learning this was a game changer. Anti-perspirant has to absorb into your skin to work and if you apply it directly after a shower while still wet; or in the morning and sweat it out it will not work (and just stain your tees!)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Applying at night, to clean DRY armpits is key. Even if you start getting sweaty before sleep, once you sleep you usually will sweat less which will allow enough time for the active ingredient to absorb. Once built up this will last days at a time and you can often get form to applying only once a week at night.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This was inspired by the EMSKR and how to apply anti perspirant was way too low on list.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: I should probably mention that antiperspirant shouldn’t be used to prevent normal sweating. It’s a natural part of the body that helps you keep cool. If you are however excessively sweaty, first consider seeing your doctor or dermatologist. If you choose to include an anti perspirant in your routine, it’s most effective when used at  night. You also probably don’t need to use it as often as you think. Usually only every other night or a couple nights a week. Continue to apply normal deodorant in mornings as usual.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：有一个浏览器扩展，将 "不喜欢 "按钮重新整合到YouTube中。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么是YSK：因为它使浏览更快乐
清楚地知道你可以显示你对某些内容的潜在不屑。
</div><!-- SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rak6pw/ysk_there_is_a_browser_extension_that_integrates/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rak6pw/ysk_there_is_a_browser_extension_that_integrates/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 11:48:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Because it makes for happier browsing knowing full well you can show your potential disdain for certain content.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在进行基因检测之前，你要购买人寿、残疾和长期护理保险。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>YSK：人寿、残疾和长期护理
保险公司可以根据基因测试结果进行歧视。健康
</p> <p>为什么YSK：健康保险公司被禁止根据基因测试结果进行歧视。
</p> <p>为什么YSK：健康保险公司被禁止以遗传学为由进行歧视。其他保险公司--如人寿保险、...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbhh2k/ysk_you_want_to_get_your_life_disability_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbhh2k/ysk_you_want_to_get_your_life_disability_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 05:42:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;YSK: Life, disability, and long-term care insurance providers can discriminate based on genetic testing results. Health insurance providers can&amp;amp;#39;t.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Health insurers are forbidden to discriminate on the basis of genetics. Other insurers--like life, disability, and long-term care--aren&amp;amp;#39;t. So if you think you&amp;amp;#39;ll want genetic testing--and odds are you will someday--it&amp;amp;#39;s wise to get your life, disability, and long-term care policies set up first.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在美国，你可以通过在IRS数据库中搜索一个组织，来检查它是否真的是一个非营利组织。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：特别是每年的这个时候，有很多公司试图假装自己是慈善机构，而他们却不知道。
有很多公司试图假装他们是慈善机构，而实际上他们是盈利公司。
实际上是营利性公司。美国国税局有一个完整的数据库向公众开放。
公众在线<a href="https://apps.irs.gov/app/eos/">这里</a>...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rb1s93/ysk_that_in_the_us_you_can_check_if_an/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rb1s93/ysk_that_in_the_us_you_can_check_if_an/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 02:49:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: especially this time of year, there are plenty of companies that try to pretend that they are charities when they are actually for profit companies. The IRS keeps a full database open to the public online &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.irs.gov/app/eos/&quot;&amp;gt;here&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; where you can simply search for an organization to see if its a real non profit.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Further, if it is a nonprofit, both the organization and the IRS are required to disclose their 990 tax form, which provides their financial statements including the salary of their directors and chief officers, so you can see if half of your donation is simply going into the chairperson&amp;amp;#39;s pocket.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如何区分紧张性头痛和偏头痛，因为它们的治疗方法是非常不同的]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：偏头痛和紧张性头痛之间有着巨大的区别。
偏头痛和紧张性头痛有很大的区别。紧张性头痛是最常见的头痛类型。
紧张性头痛是最常见的头痛类型，但大多数人在不知情的情况下将其称为紧张性头痛并将其视为
偏头痛。</p> <p>偏头痛是一个神经系统问题，而紧张性头痛则是一个神经系统问题。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rajzla/ysk_how_to_tell_the_difference_between_tension/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rajzla/ysk_how_to_tell_the_difference_between_tension/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 17:57:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: There is a HUGE difference between migraines and tension headaches. Tension headaches are the most common type of headache though most people unknowingly refer to them and treat them as migraines. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Migraines are a neurological problem and tension headaches are more of a muscular problem. Of course it is much more complicated than this but I’m trying to keep it as basic as possible.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ve suffered from tension headaches for the past 7 years that have been so bad they cost me friendships, relationships, and multiple jobs. Because of this I am very educated on tension headaches (but not so much migraines).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here’s how you can tell if you have tension headaches (and not migraines):&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Next time you have a headache take a muscle relaxer than contains ibuprofen (this is usually the purple coloured bottle). Robax platinum or any store brand version will work.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you find relief from the muscle relaxer, you likely have tension headaches, not migraines.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There are many other ways to test it such as using ice and heat as those tend to do good for tension headaches but they can also help some people with migraines, so it’s not a definite answer. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If the muscle relaxer does not relieve your pain you either have migraines or another type of headaches such as cluster headaches. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here are somethings to consider if you have tensions headaches as these are common factors in those that do. Consider fixing them as they can be the cause of your pain:
- do you grind your teeth? 
- are you low on magnesium?
- do you sleep on your side or stomach?
- do you have poor posture? 
- do you have proper tongue posture/where does your tongue sit in your mouth (it’s should be firmly pressed against the roof of your mouth). &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;not&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; relaxed. I used  to grind my teeth at night and would try to relax my whole mouth during the day to stop it. In reality this was causing more damage as one of the most important parts of good posture is having your tongue pressing against the roof of your mouth as frequently as possible) &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I have so much more advice but I don’t want to make this post too long. I hope I can help at least one person with this info :)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 如果你的车被撞坏了，告诉你的保险公司在市场上找三辆类似的车，以他们提供的金额为准。你不必接受他们的第一个报价，也不必同意修理一辆往往不应该修理的汽车。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK:</p> <p><strong>1.)</strong> Insurance
始终试图首先提供低价，有时会让你在旧的车辆贷款上欠下余额，或让你无法更换车辆。
贷款，或者让你无法用类似价值的车辆来替换你的车辆。
vehicle of similar value.</p> <p><strong>2.)</strong> They may…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/raro9d/ysk_if_your_car_is_totaled_tell_your_insurance/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/raro9d/ysk_if_your_car_is_totaled_tell_your_insurance/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 08:46:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;1.)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Insurance will ALWAYS try to offer low first, sometimes leaving you with a balance owed on your old vehicle loan or leaving you unable to replace your vehicle with a vehicle of similar value.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;2.)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; They may also try to force you to repair a vehicle which is so damaged that it will be nearly worthless &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;(or dangerous)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; after the repair.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With the price of used (and new) vehicles skyrocketing, insurance companies are pushing heavily to &amp;amp;quot;repair&amp;amp;quot; vehicles with fire damage, frame damage, firewall damage, etc; due to the high cost of replacing your vehicle often leaving you with something unsafe and also worthless to any potential buyer in the future.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What to do:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Situation 1.)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Ask the insurance company to provide you with a list of 3 of the exact same trim of vehicle, in the same condition, with the same mileage for the $ they&amp;amp;#39;re giving you. They will be forced to give you a proper amount, in order to replace the vehicle you were paying them to insure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Situation 2.)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Get an &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;independent estimate&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; from a reputable body shop, and if you believe your vehicle is beyond repair and ask the body shop if it were their car, would they repair it? If the answer is &amp;amp;quot;no&amp;amp;quot;, then fight your insurance company because you&amp;amp;#39;re about to get a raw deal..and possibly end up with a vehicle that&amp;amp;#39;s now dangerous and also possibly worthless to any lender or any future buyer (or any future insurance payout..)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在穿新衣服之前要先洗干净。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：许多纺织品都经过化学处理，包括甲醛树脂。
包括甲醛树脂，以防止衣服在运输过程中发生霉变和霉菌生长。
在运输过程中防止衣服发霉和发霉，以及染料固定剂、阻燃剂和抗菌处理。
抗菌处理，以及为防止起皱和起皱而进行的处理。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rap5y5/ysk_wash_your_new_clothes_before_wearing_them/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rap5y5/ysk_wash_your_new_clothes_before_wearing_them/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 06:40:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Many textiles are treated with chemicals including formaldehyde resins to prevent mildew and mold growth on clothes during transport as well as dye fixatives, fire retardant and antibacterial treatments, and treatments to prevent wrinkling and shrinkage.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You may be able to smell it on your new clothes. It&amp;amp;#39;s recommended that you wash all garments that will come into direct contact with your skin. Any remaining resins will come out as you wash them. At the acceptable levels present in clothing, the main risk to you is contact dermatitis. But you should still wash your new clothes.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m sharing this because I bought new pajamas and they reek.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.co.in/books/edition/Principles_of_Textile_Finishing/p_9PCwAAQBAJ?hl=en&amp;amp;amp;gbpv=1&amp;amp;amp;dq=finishing+textiles&amp;amp;amp;printsec=frontcover&quot;&amp;gt;Principles of Textile Finishing&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gao.gov/assets/gao-10-875.pdf&quot;&amp;gt;Formaldehyde in Textiles&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007%2Fs40521-019-0197-5&quot;&amp;gt;Textile Contact Dermatitis&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2010/12/11/your-money/11wrinkle.html&quot;&amp;gt;NYT Formaldehyde Fumes&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK政府管理的无人认领财产项目持有你所欠的钱。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：它是免费的，它是合法的，而且
它是你的钱</p> <p><strong>这个项目在美国、加拿大和英国都存在。
至少，所以虽然我说的是美国，但你的国家可能也有一个
也有</strong></p> <p>假设8年前你辞去了一份工作....]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/raizy7/ysk_the_govrun_unclaimed_property_program_holds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/raizy7/ysk_the_govrun_unclaimed_property_program_holds/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 04:42:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: it&amp;amp;#39;s free, it&amp;amp;#39;s legit, and it&amp;amp;#39;s your money&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;This program exists in the US, Canada, and UK AT LEAST, so while I&amp;amp;#39;m talking about the US, your country probably has one too&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Let&amp;amp;#39;s say 8 years ago you quit a job. Later, that business discovered you were owed $50 in overtime. Legally, they have to get it to you, but realistically they aren&amp;amp;#39;t going to hire a PI to find &amp;amp;amp; verify your identity. Maybe you inherited some stocks/bonds and weren&amp;amp;#39;t notified. Where does the money go? Why, the Unclaimed Property Program! &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://unclaimed.org/search/&quot;&amp;gt;https://unclaimed.org/search/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Government-run and totally legitimate, it&amp;amp;#39;s free to search your name, your business name, your sister&amp;amp;#39;s name....anyone&amp;amp;#39;s name, and see if they are owed money. I found I was owed hundreds of dollars from my college apartment. My best friend was owed about $75 from an old gig. My current employer had cash from an overpaid utility bill.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s your money and it&amp;amp;#39;s free to get it back. There are BILLIONS OF DOLLARS left unclaimed in the US every year.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is not a scam. I get nothing from this. You won&amp;amp;#39;t be asked to pay a dime - if you are, it&amp;amp;#39;s a scam website. Every state has its own. You can search anywhere - make sure to search in states you&amp;amp;#39;ve lived in the past.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Steps:
Search name - find $$$ - fill out form - get a check in the mail a few weeks later&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;GET YOUR MONEY Y&amp;amp;#39;ALL!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在计划参观国家森林/公园的行程时，森林/公园管理员可以提供大量关于附近住宿或交通的信息。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：计划去另一个州旅行可能是令人生畏的。
是令人生畏的。所有的国家森林和公园都是由其中一个森林/公园管理局经营的。
所有的国家森林和公园都由其中一个森林/公园服务机构运营。所有这些服务都有带联系表格的网站。护林员
护林员就像图书管理员一样，但却是为土地服务的。</p> <p>他们拥有所有的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rad2oo/ysk_when_planning_a_trip_to_see_a_national/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rad2oo/ysk_when_planning_a_trip_to_see_a_national/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 23:45:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Planning a trip to another state can be daunting. All national forests and parks are operated by one of the forest/park services. All of these services have sites with contact forms. The rangers are like librarians but for the land.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They have all been in the area for a long time and are very familiar with tourism to their park. And they typically are very kind and informative and don&amp;amp;#39;t mind helping you out with the info.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It makes planning a trip so much easier to have all of that information up front.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK直截了当地切割指甲，以防止嵌甲。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：不正确的修剪指甲是导致嵌甲的一个原因。
ingrown nails.</p> <p><a
href="https://puretherapyclinic.files.wordpress.com/2017/01/infection-after-ingrown-toenail-1.png">Here&#39;s
an example of how to cut them</a></p> <p>Causes:</p> <p>The etiology of…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rabskj/ysk_cut_nails_straight_across_to_prevent_ingrown/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rabskj/ysk_cut_nails_straight_across_to_prevent_ingrown/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 18:42:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Improper nail trimming is 1 cause of ingrown nails.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://puretherapyclinic.files.wordpress.com/2017/01/infection-after-ingrown-toenail-1.png&quot;&amp;gt;Here&amp;amp;#39;s an example of how to cut them&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Causes:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The etiology of ingrown toenails includes direct trauma to the toe that forces the nail corners into the surrounding nail fold, genetic predisposition, improper nail trimming, poorly fitting shoes, and constant and repetitive microtrauma from normal day-to-day activities. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After a painful procedure this afternoon and now typing this with throbbing pain, I wish I have knew about this MUCH SOONER.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC1472971/&quot;&amp;gt;Source&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/d5qh3a/&quot;&amp;gt;Old YSK post&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://theawkwardyeti.com/comic/ingrown-nail/&quot;&amp;gt;Comic&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK有一个名为Be My Eyes的应用程序，可以让视障人士通过视频呼叫志愿者，请求提供视觉援助。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么选择YSK：该应用程序是免费下载的，你可以作为志愿者或视障/盲人注册。
你可以以志愿者或视障/盲人的身份注册。如果你需要
视觉帮助（举例说明挑选正确的衣服颜色。
或在购物时选择正确的产品品牌），并且你是...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r9lzqz/ysk_there_is_an_app_called_be_my_eyes_that_allows/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r9lzqz/ysk_there_is_an_app_called_be_my_eyes_that_allows/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 04:48:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: The app is free to download and you can sign up as a volunteer or a visually impaired / blind person. If you need visual help (examples given are picking the right colour of an item of clothing, or the right brand of product when shopping) and you are visually impaired, you press a button on the app. The app will call multiple volunteers (volunteers do not need to have the app open to recieve a call, they just have to be logged in) , and whoever picks up the quickest is connected by video call. The volunteer can then assist you in whatever task you need help with.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thought it was a great idea and a helpful app. Currently there are over 4 million volunteers signed up, but only 310, 000 visually impaired or blind people. Thought I&amp;amp;#39;d share in case anyone would find this useful.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你应该定期将白醋倒入马桶的蓄水池/水箱中，以避免钙质在马桶的冲水系统中堆积，从而损坏它。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么是YSK：自来水是用来填充马桶水箱的。
厕所的水箱，其中可能含有大量的钙质硬度。如果不加处理
如果不加以控制，随着时间的推移，钙质堆积物会在马桶的几乎所有地方形成
马桶的冲水系统，这将损害垫圈......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r9tj6r/ysk_you_should_regularly_pour_white_vinegar_into/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r9tj6r/ysk_you_should_regularly_pour_white_vinegar_into/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 02:52:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Tap water, which is used to fill a toilet&amp;amp;#39;s water tank, can contain a lot of calcium hardness in it. If left unchecked, over time, calcareous buildups will form pretty much everywhere in the toilet&amp;amp;#39;s flushing system, which will damage the gaskets and other components in it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This also goes for pretty much anything that has tap water running through it in your home. Faucets, dishwasher, washing machine, kettle, shower head, etc. A little bit of vinegar is very efficient at getting rid of calcium deposits.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Steps:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Turn off the water&amp;amp;#39;s supply to the toilet&amp;amp;#39;s water tank, there&amp;amp;#39;s usually a knob or valve on the wall next to your toilet that you have to turn.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Open up the water tank/cistern by removing the top lid. (You may need a screwdriver to do this, depending on the model of your toilet)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;If the water tank is full, flush the water and empty it. (Because you&amp;amp;#39;ve turned off the water&amp;amp;#39;s supply, it shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t fill back up again)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Pour white vinegar all over the flushing system and fill half of the tank with it.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Fill the remaining half of the tank with hot water (not boiling, slightly hot, max 50°C/120°F temp) and let the mixture do its thing for 15-20 minutes. You should be able to see small bubbles, that&amp;amp;#39;s a result of the white vinegar dissolving the deposits.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;If you have thick hard deposits, wear latex gloves and use a sponge to scrape off the deposits.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Once all the deposits have dissolved, flush it all down the toilet.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Turn the water&amp;amp;#39;s supply to the toilet&amp;amp;#39;s tank back on and put the lid back on.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Do this once a month, or maybe even once a week, depending on how calcareous your tap water is.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ve just had to clean mine thoroughly because my toilet&amp;amp;#39;s flushing system stopped working properly, the water kept flushing/running. When I opened up the lid of the water tank, I was pretty horrified by the state of the flushing system. I had to replace the gaskets and had to scrape a lot of thick deposits. It was a real pain to clean... So, I now have a reminder in my phone to pour white vinegar into the toilet&amp;amp;#39;s water tank once a month to prevent this.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hopefully this is useful to someone!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：漂白剂过期，几乎无用]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：漂白剂会随着时间的推移降解成其
组成的部分。它不会变得更危险，但它绝对会
它不会变得更危险，但绝对会失去效力，从而限制了它的清洁能力。如果你
如果你很难让漂白剂像你期望的那样发挥作用，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r9ef6v/ysk_bleach_expires_and_becomes_almost_useless/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r9ef6v/ysk_bleach_expires_and_becomes_almost_useless/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 14:44:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Bleach degrades over time into its constituent parts. It doesn&amp;amp;#39;t become more dangerous but it will absolutely lose its potency, thus limiting it&amp;amp;#39;s cleaning capabilities. If you&amp;amp;#39;re having a hard time getting bleach to work as you&amp;amp;#39;d expect, think back to how long ago you bought it, as it could be almost completely inert if it&amp;amp;#39;s a few years old.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：阿芙乐可导致一种严重的医学症状，称为反跳性充血]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：&quot;虽然它不被视为一种
在通常意义上，你的身体<em>可以</em>变得依赖
对药物的依赖。医生称这种现象为&#39;反弹性充血,&#39;或<a
href="https://www.jacionline.org/article/S0091...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r92nwx/ysk_afrin_can_cause_a_serious_medical_condition/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r92nwx/ysk_afrin_can_cause_a_serious_medical_condition/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 13:46:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:  &amp;amp;quot;While it’s not considered an &amp;amp;#39;addiction&amp;amp;#39; in the usual sense, your body &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;can&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; become dependent on the drug. Doctors call this phenomenon &amp;amp;#39;rebound congestion,&amp;amp;#39; or &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jacionline.org/article/S0091-6749(06&quot;&amp;gt;rhinitis medicamentosa&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;01370-4/fulltext), and it is a very real problem. In fact, it could be responsible for up to 9% of visits to allergists and ENT doctors. &amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.singlecare.com/blog/rebound-congestion-nasal-spray-addiction/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.singlecare.com/blog/rebound-congestion-nasal-spray-addiction/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：吊扇有一个冬季设置。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：大多数吊扇能够
暖房间，这是很反常的。很多风扇上都有一个开关。
侧面的某个地方有一个开关，可以是向上或向下的，翻开这个开关将
切换叶片的旋转，所以不是向下吹风，而是......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r91xer/ysk_ceiling_fans_have_a_winter_setting/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r91xer/ysk_ceiling_fans_have_a_winter_setting/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 09:26:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Most ceiling fans are capable of warming a room which is counterintuitive. On a lot a fans there&amp;amp;#39;s a switch somewhere on the side that can be either up or down, flipping this switch will switch the blades rotation so instead of blowing air down, it sucks air up (so having some space between the fan blades and the ceiling is ideal) which moves the cool air from below disturbing the warm air above which warms the room. (This is probably common knowledge that is worth repeating for those who didn&amp;amp;#39;t know)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: Really important point not in my original post brought up by a smart comment: Vacuum/dust the top of your blades before doing this! (thank you aquaman67!)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：教孩子们如何安全、适当地与狗相处。被狗咬伤是儿童时期最容易预防的一些伤害。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么是YSK：作为一个照顾者，保护儿童安全是非常重要的。
照顾儿童的安全是非常重要的。如果你想在你的家庭中养狗，那么教孩子们如何与狗安全互动是非常重要的。
</p> <p>编辑：是的!
人们应该训练他们的狗! 但是，这也是非常重要的，孩子们...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r911j3/ysk_teach_children_how_to_be_around_dogs_safely/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r911j3/ysk_teach_children_how_to_be_around_dogs_safely/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 00:56:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: as a caregiver it is incredibly important to keep children safe. If you want to have a dog in your family it is important to teach kids how to interact with dogs safely.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT: Yes! People should train their dogs! But also it’s really important kids are taught certain elements of how to protect themselves. These are what I teach kids with families with dogs to work on safety. I am never excusing untrained dogs. I became a dog trainer because I care about dog training and well trained dogs. I am not blaming children for dog bites at all. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;One thing I routinely see as a dog trainer is how many dogs are absolutely terrified of children. It’s not necessarily due to bad experience. Rather, kids move sporadically and unpredictably; they vocalize in unusual patterns. Dogs are used to human movement but children do not move in ways dogs can easily read. Many dogs will not chase an adult out for a run but will chase a child that is skipping or sprinting down the side walk. This is partially due to the unpredictable nature of the way kids move; when dogs see those kinds of movement patterns instincts to herd/chase can be activated. To keep children in your care safe around dogs here are a few simple rules I used to explain to children I worked with:
1) If you see a dog, stop running. Try not to run or skip around dogs. A lot of dogs have herding and chasing instincts, and they may see these sudden movements an invitation to run towards you. They do not want to hurt you but they may also not want to play with you. It is safest for you to never run around when you see a dog. 
2) If a dog is scared of you, it does not mean you have done something wrong. Lots of dogs have had different experiences and do not know whether strangers will be nice to them. 
3) Do not scream or shout near or at dogs, try to lower your voice if you are playing with a dog. Screaming may scare them and many dogs will act defensively when scared. They do not want to hurt you but they may be concerned that you may hurt them.
4) If you want to say hi to a dog and the owner says it is okay, make sure the dog can see your hand. Instead of reaching for the top of their head see if they will let you pet them under the chin. Instead of approaching them from the front, you can try approaching the dog from the side with your hand extended. Dogs will approach each other from the side to indicate non threatening and friendly behavior.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：大多数公司和ISP通过DNS追踪你，通过使用Adguard DNS这样的开源服务器，你可以阻止整个设备上的广告/追踪器/恶意软件。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：任何人都需要DNS服务器来连接互联网。
连接到互联网。公司和ISP喜欢在法律允许的范围内尽可能多地追踪你。
在法律允许的范围内尽可能地跟踪你。他们主要是通过DNS服务器来做到这一点
他们自动配置你的设备来使用。通过切换到...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8wdhg/ysk_most_corporations_and_isps_track_you_through/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8wdhg/ysk_most_corporations_and_isps_track_you_through/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:42:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: DNS servers are required for anyone to connect to the internet. Corporations and ISPs like to track you as much as humanly possible within the law. They do this mostly through the DNS servers they automatically configure your devices to use. By switching to an encrypted dns server with filters that block these tracking/ad domains you won&amp;amp;#39;t see any more on your entire device. DNS is being used for tracking/ads more than any time previously in the last twenty years. It&amp;amp;#39;s only a few numbers, it&amp;amp;#39;s an easy and effortless switch. Adguard is open source and free to use like Bitcoin and Ethereum, Linux, Firefox and Tor for example.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit (for no confusion): &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://adguard-dns.com/en/public-dns.html&quot;&amp;gt;https://adguard-dns.com/en/public-dns.html&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit 2: May not work with streaming services or youtube on phones or xboxes, play stations. Google loads all their ads on one domain, so to block those domains you&amp;amp;#39;d be blocking youtube itself, alas. You can sideload cercube youtube through altstore on IOS or use youtube vanced on Android to get premium for free though (I myself use altstore, also have spotify premium for free)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你能证明你的收入很低，美国的一些医院会提供大幅折扣。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：美国的医疗保健可能是非常难以负担的。
负担不起，并有可能在经济上毁掉人们。没有多少人
没有多少人知道<em>一些</em>医院会对你的账单提供折扣。你必须
你必须要求这些折扣，它们不会像其他医院那样被分发出去。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8qwut/ysk_some_hospitals_in_the_usa_will_offer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8qwut/ysk_some_hospitals_in_the_usa_will_offer/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 20:36:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Healthcare in the USA can be very unaffordable and has the potential to financially ruin people. Not many people are aware that &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;some&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; hospitals will offer discounts to your bill. You MUST ASK for these discounts, they aren&amp;amp;#39;t handed out like candy. Some discounts may be applied simply because you asked and were polite in doing so. Other potentially larger discounts may be applied if you can prove your income is relatively low and you are unable to pay in a timely fashion. Generally speaking, some hospitals will prefer to lower your bill and get you to pay that amount rather than send the full bill to collections. You might want to seek out hospitals that offer these discounts as opposed to ones that do not. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As an anecdote, I had low wages and a hospital bill a number of years ago. I asked for a discount and got 45% off the bill, as well as 35% off any future bills for a whole year. I did have sign a document attesting to my wages. I had insurance at the time but the bill was slightly less than my deductible.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK, wary, weary, leery都是不同的词。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK，警觉和警惕都意味着
对一个潜在问题的谨慎&quot;。疲惫是指&quot;疲惫&quot;。
</p> <p>你一次又一次地看到人们说他们对一个问题感到厌烦。
问题，那是因为他们把 "警觉 "和 "警惕 "这两个词混为一谈......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r5rb87/ysk_wary_weary_leery_are_all_different_words/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r5rb87/ysk_wary_weary_leery_are_all_different_words/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 18:37:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK, wary and leery both mean &amp;amp;quot;cautious about a potential problem&amp;amp;quot;. Weary means &amp;amp;quot;tired&amp;amp;quot;. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Over and over you see people say they are &amp;amp;quot;weary&amp;amp;quot; of a problem, that&amp;amp;#39;s because they are conflating wary and leery, two words that means roughly the same thing, but combining those words leaves you with &amp;amp;quot;weary&amp;amp;quot;, which, again, just means tired. You are not tired of the problem, you are sceptical of the problem, so either wary or leery is what you mean. 
Unless the issue has exhausted you, you aren&amp;amp;#39;t &amp;amp;quot;weary&amp;amp;quot; of it, you&amp;amp;#39;re &amp;amp;quot;wary&amp;amp;quot; or &amp;amp;quot;leery&amp;amp;quot; of it. Learn the difference and you won&amp;amp;#39;t sound like a tool.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：大多数洗碗皂（如黎明）都是在装满水的水槽中使用的，而不是直接用在海绵上。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：一些肥皂公司正在改变配方。
一些肥皂公司正在改变他们的配方，因为现在很多人都是一个一个地洗碗，把洗碗剂放在海绵上，然后用流水擦洗。
肥皂放在海绵上，然后用流动的水擦洗，而不是在水槽里填满。
水槽。如果你没有一个两部分的水槽，那就很难...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8f5fq/ysk_most_dish_soaps_like_dawn_are_designed_to_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8f5fq/ysk_most_dish_soaps_like_dawn_are_designed_to_be/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 04:58:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Some soap companies are changing their formula because so many people wash dishes now one by one, by putting dish soap on the sponge and then scrubbing with running water, rather than filling the sink. If you don’t have a 2 part sink, it makes it harder to wash by hand (maybe consider using a tub), but if you do have 2 sides, fill one side w water and soap, soak dishes, scrub them while submerged, and then rinse them in the other side of the sink. It not only saves on both water and soap, but will get your dishes cleaner.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：有一种免费且简单的方法可以使日常办公任务自动化。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么是YSK：几乎所有我曾经去过的办公室都做得很好。
都是用手来做许多无聊、重复的事情。仅仅花了
几天的时间来学习像Python这样的脚本语言的基础知识，就可以减少
小时的乏味工作。计算机真的很好...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r85t6g/ysk_theres_a_free_and_easy_way_to_automate/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r85t6g/ysk_theres_a_free_and_easy_way_to_automate/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 03:52:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Nearly every office I&amp;amp;#39;ve ever been in has done so many boring, repetitive things by hand. Spending just a couple of days learning the basics of a scripting language like Python can cut hours of tedious work out of your routine. Computers are really good at monotonous things, so if there&amp;amp;#39;s something you do the exact same way every day at work, there&amp;amp;#39;s probably a decent way to automate it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A good resource for this is &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://automatetheboringstuff.com/&quot;&amp;gt;Automate the Boring Stuff with Python&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; by Al Sweigart. It&amp;amp;#39;s free to read online.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：使用YYYMMDD格式对文件进行约会，将使它们按时间顺序排列，从而实现更好的文件管理。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：这在你的时候特别有用
当你需要在一段时间内保存一个文件的多个版本时，这一点特别有用。
日期，而不是 "修改日期 "或 "创建日期"。例如
例如，如果我今天保存一个文件，我会将其命名为 "示例文本......"。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8dg01/ysk_dating_files_using_yyyymmdd_format_will_keep/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8dg01/ysk_dating_files_using_yyyymmdd_format_will_keep/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 02:57:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: This is especially useful when you need to save multiple versions of a file over time and can quickly reference the date from the file name instead of “date modified” or “date created”. For example, if I save a file today, I would name it “Example Text 20211203”. If I needed to save a new version in the same day, it would be “Example Text 20211203v2”.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Putting the date at the end instead of the front allows your files to be sorted alphabetically&amp;amp;gt;chronologically. Putting the date at the front will sort your files chronologically&amp;amp;gt;alphabetically.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：人工甜味剂木糖醇存在于许多常见的家用物品/食品中，如牙膏甚至花生酱，对狗来说是非常有毒的。如果你的狗摄入了哪怕是少量的木糖醇，它们就会死亡。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：随着肥胖症的流行和Keto
在美国发生的热潮中，木糖醇的使用一直在明显上升。它
它对人类是安全的（但大量使用会导致腹泻），但会很快杀死你的
除非立即送往兽医处，否则会很快杀死你的狗。当5毫克...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8bg42/ysk_the_artificial_sweetener_xylitol_found_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8bg42/ysk_the_artificial_sweetener_xylitol_found_in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 02:57:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: with the obesity epidemic and Keto craze happening in the US, Xylitol use has been on the rise, significantly. It is safe for humans (but will cause diarrhea in large amounts) but CAN kill your dog very quickly unless taken to the vet IMMEDIATELY. When 5mg per 1lb of body weight is ingested, it quickly causes liver failure followed by death and the effects will begin 10-15 minutes after ingesting. Any amount less than this can cause liver cirrhosis, seizures from severe hypoglycemia, tremors, and coma in under an hour. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This sweetener is found in most “sugar free” snacks, gum, toothpaste, candies, and if you know anyone who follows a Keto Diet or is just simply diabetic, they most likely have a whole bag of the stuff in their cupboard because it tastes and bakes very similar to regular sugar. It’s even in some brands of peanut butter. With the holidays going on and everyone baking sweet treats, I thought I would mention this because until my own dog ate toothpaste with Xylitol, I had NO idea it was so dangerous. She’s fine, now. Thankfully she threw the majority of it up herself. It’s extremely easy for a pup to eat this amount of Xylitol. If you bake a sugar free cake and your dog eats it off the counter while it’s cooling, or you forget to put your toothpaste in the drawer and your curious puppy eats it like puppies do… you could have your heart broken in under an hour. So please be careful! Also never give your pup a homemade treat that you didn’t make yourself!! This info is not well known at all and a good-intending person may use xylitol in place of sugar to make the treats “healthier”. So just be careful, fellow pet owners :) &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here is some more info! &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://vcahospitals.com/know-your-pet/xylitol-toxicity-in-dogs&quot;&amp;gt;https://vcahospitals.com/know-your-pet/xylitol-toxicity-in-dogs&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：慢速驾驶并不总是等同于安全驾驶]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：有很多情况下
驶快比驶慢更安全。</p> <p>例如，如果你&#39;是
的时候，尤其是像大风车这样的东西，以最快的速度通过，是最安全的。
尽可能快地通过它是最安全的。我总是使用这样的规则，即...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r85o02/ysk_driving_slow_isnt_always_the_same_as_driving/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r85o02/ysk_driving_slow_isnt_always_the_same_as_driving/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 22:42:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: there are a lot of situations where driving fast is safer than driving slow. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For example if you&amp;amp;#39;re passing something, especially something like a truck with high winds, it&amp;amp;#39;s safest to pass it as quickly as possible. I always use the rule of thumb that passing should take 10 seconds maximum.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Another example is with weather that causes bad sight (think heavy fog or rain) a lot of people just slam their brakes. But it&amp;amp;#39;s way safer to just keep driving the recommended speed, since that makes you predictable. If you don&amp;amp;#39;t trust the poor vision, go to the right lane and gradually lower your speed, if you plan to go slower than 80 km/h on the highway turn on your hazards.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Read the situation on the road, sometimes speeding up/not slowing down is the right course of action. (Note: read sometimes. Don&amp;amp;#39;t go blasting 200 on the daily just because of this post)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 玉米饼还没有完全熟透。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>TL;DR: 刚从袋子/包装中取出的玉米粉饼
没有完全熟透。在热的不粘锅、平底锅、刨锅或调好味的铸铁锅上加热它们
在热的不粘锅、平底锅或调好味的铸铁锅上每面加热30秒至1分钟，直到微微发黄和热/热的状态。
棕色和热/热是享受玉米饼的必要条件....。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r85ye9/ysk_tortillas_are_not_fully_cooked_yet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r85ye9/ysk_tortillas_are_not_fully_cooked_yet/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 21:42:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TL;DR: Tortillas fresh out of a bag/package are not fully cooked. Heating them on a hot non-stick, flattop, plancha, or well seasoned cast iron pan for 30 seconds to a minute on each side until light browning and warm/hot is essential for enjoying the tortillas. Store in a clean folded towel or aluminum foil after cooking before eating to retain heat/moisture.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;[ EDIT ] The way this is going, I should have posted this on &amp;lt;a href=&quot;/r/unpopularopinion&quot;&amp;gt;r/unpopularopinion&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; lol. You can still have your &amp;amp;#39;not fully cooked tortillas&amp;amp;#39;, I understand they are also delicious and &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;safe to consume&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. Hopefully, my internet opinion does not take that joy away from you. We can all unite knowing our fiery passion for tortillas, at any stage of their beautiful lifecycle. &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;But cooking them again is better and since I must find at least one hill these days on which to fall on my own bayonet, this will be it!&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After moving from a town in the southwest United States to a more northern, college town it has become abundantly, even PAINFULLY clear that this is not common knowledge. After seeing scores of undergrads, graduate students and grown people alike reaching their clueless hands towards a half cooked, chewy bitter tortilla for their burrito/taco/etc needs, I have elected to take a stand.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Tortillas are not fully cooked. Corn, Flour, or any other grain that has been wrangled into a circular shape under the name of tortillas do not come fully cooked. If they had been fully cooked prior to being packaged, they would be stiff, crunchy and frankly some unholy center point between a tortilla chip and a malleable, fresh tortilla. Thus the onus falls on you, the consumer to bring these glorious circles of flavor up to the correct temperature, finish the cooking/rising, and bring a bitter/raw flavor of uncooked corn and flour to their glorious savory and delicious conclusion.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How: The best and most traditional way would be a &amp;amp;#39;plancha&amp;amp;#39; (think: a flat top griddle that gets exceptionally hot), but a non-stick pan or well seasoned cast-iron pan will do the job just as well. Get your choice of heat delivery device rippin&amp;amp;#39; hot (mid-high) and start dropping tortillas. Times will vary based on heat of your burners, type of pan etc, but you should look for some light to medium browning and spots on each side. Tortillas are cheap! Try a few different levels of done-ness to see how you like them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;NOTE: Huge bonus points to use your fingers when grabbing a flipping tortillas. You will make a Mexican/South American grandmother very happy somewhere. The technique varies from surface to surface, but my preferred way is a light pinch to flip, or using the curved edge of the pan and my four fingers to draw it up, allowing my thumb to get under the tortilla and toss it down on the other side. Obviously, don&amp;amp;#39;t do anything you are not comfortable with, and this technique benefits from both speed and the presence of &amp;amp;quot;kitchen fingers&amp;amp;quot; (Where my food service people at?). This saves scratches on a pan, and is much faster/efficient than some metal tool or spatula.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As soon as the tortilla leaves the griddle, you should be tossing it somewhere that helps it retain its heat and moisture. My personal favorite is making a small foil pouch, pinched on 3 sides with a fold on the forth, that can perfectly be sealed and unsealed as I build a stack of hot and steamy tortillas inside. The same technique can be done with a clean, folded towel. This steam is part of the cooking process, it softens to tortillas up a bit, and helps retain moisture, and finishes the cooking process with the heat. (In fact this is a great technique for many other foods. ever wonder why ballpark hotdogs, wrapped burritos, wrapped burgers taste so good? Part of that process is letting the heat from the steam and meat flow into the bread and keep it warm and moist. A good technique for other items too!)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Take these tortillas out as you are ready to eat them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;BONUS:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;carniceria/tortilleria : While most places may not have access to one of these stores, it is worth a quick map search. Tortillas from actual Latino/Hispanic grocers are much better than anything from a grocery store. Same rules apply for finishing cooking these tortillas. Plus, you will be supporting small businesses! These stores additionally often have a plethora of other Latin/Hispanic ingredients, seasonings, meats, pastries etc. and are often cheaper than chain grocery store equivalents (and better tasting!). Be kind and respectful of culture and language here too. I have never had a negative experience even though my Spanish is &amp;amp;#39;mierda&amp;amp;#39;, and the same service industry rules apply here: Hardworking people deserve respect and empathy, so don&amp;amp;#39;t be an asshole. Should go without saying, but still.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：当对一个公司感到沮丧时，不要告诉CSR "你对我做了XYZ的坏事"，而是说 "公司对我做了XYZ的坏事"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：客服代表
(CSRs)有一个令人难以置信的困难工作。把你的挫折感归结为是
你的挫折是公司的错，而不是CSR个人的错，这不仅是一种善意的做法，也增加了你的机会。
这不仅是一件好事，而且还能增加客服代表超越自我的可能性。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r83u0x/ysk_when_frustrated_with_a_company_instead_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r83u0x/ysk_when_frustrated_with_a_company_instead_of/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 20:42:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Customer Service Representatives (CSRs) have an unbelievably difficult job. Framing your frustration as being the fault of the company, and not the CSR personally is not only the kind thing to do, it also increases the odds that the rep will go above and beyond to help you since you are not being unduly adversarial.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你有一个CareerBuilder账户，即使是旧的和废弃的，他们已经开始代表你申请工作，即使不相关。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>我最近开始收到电子邮件，感谢我申请了我不想要也不合格的工作。
最近，我开始收到电子邮件，感谢我申请我不想要也不符合条件的工作。其中一个
其中一位招聘人员很好地回应了我的追问，并告诉我：</p> <p>我是一个很好的人。
<blockquote> <p>谢谢你给我发邮件谈及此事。我已经收到了一封邮件。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r81h2u/ysk_if_you_have_a_careerbuilder_account_even_if/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r81h2u/ysk_if_you_have_a_careerbuilder_account_even_if/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 18:49:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I started getting emails thanking me for my application to jobs I don’t want and am not qualified for recently. One of the recruiters was kind enough to respond to my follow up and informed me:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thank you for Emailing me about this. I received an application through Career Builder for a Truck Driver/Warehouse position yesterday. I spoke with the manager of my company and she advised me that if your resume and information is on CareerBuilder; CareerBuilder will apply on behalf of the candidate. I greatly apologize for the mix up and inconvenience.  I have deleted your information and you will no longer be contacted by our staffing company.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: If you have received similar notifications, you did not have your identity compromised, apparently CareerBuilder is just resorting to desperate measures to increase their numbers. Time to delete!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK开始健身计划需要更多的心理体操，而不是体力。你需要建立心理结构，以保持动力，并推动每年每周都做，永远做下去的操练。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：这个流行的新年决议是
就在不远处。太多的焦点被放在锻炼本身，而没有解决为什么这么多人开始锻炼又放弃的真正问题。
的真正问题，即为什么这么多人开始锻炼，然后又放弃。每个人都
挣扎，但有些人已经找到了关键，正确的心理体操......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r7xqkx/ysk_starting_a_workout_regimen_requires_more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r7xqkx/ysk_starting_a_workout_regimen_requires_more/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 17:47:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: This popular New Years resolution is just around the corner. Too much focus is put on the workout itself without addressing the real problem of why so many start and then quit. Everyone struggles, but some have sourced the key, the right mental gymnastics to continue the regimen despite regular life pressures getting in the way.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After a lifetime of joking the #1 cause of injury is exercise, I found myself at a crossroads when I had to run about 30 meters (100 feet). I was a mess, barely able to breathe. I loosened my shirt and my pants. I knew i wasn’t in good shape but I hadn’t considered I was in terrible shape.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I started walking around the block, then longer, then jogging small parts, then jogging most of it, then moved on to hiking. I learned my body prefers Interval training, so I focused on this whether it was around the neighbourhood or into the woods.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After 3 months I was noticeably more fit but I was still struggling mentally with just getting out the door. I always had SO MANY reasons to not exercise today, mostly related to urgency of other matters. Put simply, I would find important distractions and then convince myself it was “too late” to do it today and to try again tomorrow.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It took about 6 months of mental retraining to stop this bad habit while also convincing myself I enjoyed it. Some tricks I used:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;1 - Whatever other urgent thing you have to do, don&amp;amp;#39;t argue with yourself on the priority  If you have a nagging mind like I do, I found it easier to just agree with the thought to skip today and then just do the exercise anyways.  Its like the old adage of not what you say, but what you do.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;2 - Any opportunity I had to talk about my training, I did so and said how much I loved it. Even though I was lying, I said I loved it and I said it to myself regularly as well. Weirdly, after awhile you start to actually love it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;3 - Meditation, It helped a lot learning how to “let thoughts go”, even important valid thoughts. Just because something is important, it doesn’t mean it’s more important than your health. Let the valid and important thought go along with any other thoughts and do your exercises&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;4 - Find anyone to do it with. Your friends keep you honest. Or get a dog. That sad look they give you, or excited when they hear keys, it really works. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;5 - Upper body and general muscle development are key not just for balance, but muscles burn more calories. You may not be as toned as the person putting in a couple hours a day, but any increase in muscle makes a better working body that burns more calories for the same amount of work. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;6 - Even if its just 5 minutes. This is my go to when nothing else is working. It&amp;amp;#39;s amazing how taking 5 minutes can turn into 15 and then into 30. And you feel like a boss afterwards.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;7 - Keep mixing it up. I go one day at the gym, then a neighborhood walk, then Beat Sabre, then a good hike, and then just drive somewhere new. I found I failed when it&amp;amp;#39;s just the same thing over and over, every week, forever. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It’s been 4 years now and I do love it and look forward to it each week. BUT!... I still mentally struggle with it. Or I should say the desire to skip it is always on the perimeter trying to get back in, and when it does, I just take my toolkit out and use one of my tricks to get back into it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Make this the year you make it stick. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nbcnews.com/better/health/6-mental-tricks-tricks-help-make-exercise-habit-ncna914386&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.nbcnews.com/better/health/6-mental-tricks-tricks-help-make-exercise-habit-ncna914386&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：当你在网上购买数字媒体时，你并不拥有它，你只是获得了观看它的许可，这可以被剥夺。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：只是因为你&quot;买&quot。
你买的东西是数字的，并不意味着你实际购买的东西是一样的。
你购买的是内容的访问权。
如果公司取消了访问权，请不要惊讶。</p>...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r7tija/ysk_when_you_buy_digital_media_online_you_dont/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r7tija/ysk_when_you_buy_digital_media_online_you_dont/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 09:43:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: just because you &amp;amp;quot;buy&amp;amp;quot; something digitally, doesn&amp;amp;#39;t mean the same when you physically buy something. you are buying ACCESS to the content. don&amp;amp;#39;t be surprised if the company revokes access. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnarcher/2018/09/17/apple-responds-to-disappearing-itunes-movie-purchases-issue/1&quot;&amp;gt;A user lost access to his movies in apple&amp;amp;#39;s ecosystem&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. it was a &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.macobserver.com/analysis/apple-isnt-deleting-itunes-movies/&quot;&amp;gt;licensing issue&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you look at amazon&amp;amp;#39;s policy for the content providers that want to use Amazon&amp;amp;#39;s platform: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://videodirect.amazon.com/home/agreement?ref_=avd_hm_ft_la&quot;&amp;gt;https://videodirect.amazon.com/home/agreement?ref_=avd_hm_ft_la&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Under Section &amp;amp;quot;6. General Description of the Service; Distribution Modes:&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(a) &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;purchase a license to access&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; digital copies ...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(b) &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;purchase a license to access&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; digital copies ...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(c) &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;access&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; audio visual content via ...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(d) &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;access&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; audio visual content ....&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Nowhere does it mention you own a copy of the audio/visual content. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://screencrush.com/do-you-own-movies-you-buy-in-itunes-forever/&quot;&amp;gt;A lawsuit against Apple for using &amp;amp;quot;buying&amp;amp;quot; when you don&amp;amp;#39;t really buy anything&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;Apple tried to get the lawsuit dismissed, claiming that consumers know that buying something on iTunes doesn’t mean buying it forever.&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://tos.ea.com/legalapp/WEBTERMS/US/en/PC/#section2&quot;&amp;gt;You don&amp;amp;#39;t own games from EA, only a license to the content&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;The EA Services are licensed to you, not sold&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. EA grants you a personal, limited, non-transferable, revocable and non-exclusive license to use the EA Services to which you have access for your non-commercial use, subject to your compliance with this Agreement.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK指出，吞下纽扣电池（看起来像硬币的电池）会烧伤人的食道内部，是一种威胁生命的紧急情况。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：儿童发现这些电池并
吞下它们。我们在节日前后尤其看到这些电池，因为它们是
在装饰品、卡片、玩具和其他各种各样的东西中。我是一名护士。
我是一名护士，看到有几个孩子需要用管子喂养，以度过余下的时间。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r7p2js/ysk_that_button_batteries_the_batteries_that_look/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r7p2js/ysk_that_button_batteries_the_batteries_that_look/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 08:23:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: children find these batteries and swallow them. We especially see these batteries around the holidays as they are in decorations, cards, toys and all sorts of other things. I work as a nurse and have seen several children need to be tube fed for the rest of their lives and/or have permanent vocal damage. Please keep items with button batteries up and away from toddlers and young children. And if it does happen (happens to the best parents so don&amp;amp;#39;t freak out) get your kid to the emergency room immediately. If the x-ray shows a &amp;amp;quot;coin with a halo&amp;amp;quot; get your kid into surgery asap.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在将自己或宠物介绍给不认识的狗之前，你应该始终询问YSK]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么ysk：即使是有好主人的狗也会有攻击性或心情不好。
攻击性或心情不好。许多狗都是从糟糕的环境中被救出来的，或者有
不幸的经历，导致它们不喜欢新的人或其他狗
狗。</p> <p>这些狗仍然有权利在周围散步......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r7f7wm/ysk_that_you_should_always_ask_before_introducing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r7f7wm/ysk_that_you_should_always_ask_before_introducing/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 23:53:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why ysk: even dogs with good owners can be aggressive or in bad moods. Many dogs are rescued from bad situations or had unfortunate experience that cause them to either not like new people or other dogs. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;These dogs still have every right to be walked around as long as the owner is conscious and doesn’t cause danger to anyone else, but if they are out of the way and you come up to them without asking you are putting yourself at risk.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also, not all dog owners are good owners and always use caution with dogs you don’t know. Be ready to remove yourself or your dog from their reach if nescessary &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source: experience and friend with rescued bait dog&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 一个研究小组正在使用一个选择自己的冒险游戏，让你改变你的内心对话--而且这项研究仍然开放给参与者。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：我们开始意识到
我们开始意识到自我保健的重要性，并及早投资于我们的心理健康。
而不是在事情已经出了问题的时候再去寻求治疗。虽然
专业的帮助可能永远是最好的选择（如果你能负担得起...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r76qnq/ysk_a_team_of_researchers_are_using_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r76qnq/ysk_a_team_of_researchers_are_using_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 15:40:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: We’re beginning to realise the importance of self-care and investing in our mental wellness early enough, instead of reaching for treatment when things have already gone awry. While professional help is probably always the best option (if you can afford it), technology can surely play a role in terms of education and prevention.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Games for Emotional and Mental Health lab is a group of behaviour change researchers and game designers, pioneering a model that combines evidence-based wellbeing tools with play and storytelling, because they’ve found that most existing apps fail to engage people long enough to deliver any benefits.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The lab recently opened a &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://utwentebs.eu.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_9uwhwDopngYIocu&quot;&amp;gt;study&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; that you can take part in, focusing on a new iOS game that teaches self-awareness through a choose-your-own-adventure story. If you’re the kind of person with a more creative mind, it could be worth trying this approach and push science forward while you’re at it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，2021年6%的通胀率到2022年2%的通胀率，相对而言是 "过渡性的"，但绝对而言是实际的增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：确保你的年薪增长至少达到通货膨胀率。
确保你的年薪增长至少与通货膨胀率持平。否则，就是减薪。</p>
<p>通货膨胀通常显示为同比百分比变化。请不要被
不要被政府愚弄，当通货膨胀被 "过渡 "到2%时......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6q20e/ysk_that_6_inflation_in_2021_to_2_inflation_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6q20e/ysk_that_6_inflation_in_2021_to_2_inflation_in/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 02:45:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: make sure that your yearly salary increase is at least that of inflation. Otherwise, it’s a pay cut.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Inflation is often shown as year over year percentage change. Do not be fooled by the government when the inflation is “transitioned” into 2% the following year.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For example, an item that costs 100 dollar in 2020 will cost 106 dollar in 2021 with 6% inflation, but will costs 108.12 dollar in 2022 with 2% inflation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 你的锅碗瓢盆底部堆积的黑色烟尘是不正常的。它可能是一氧化碳过多的迹象。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：一氧化碳（CO）被称为 "无声的杀手"。
一氧化碳被称为 "无声杀手 "是有原因的。它是无色无味的，因此
它很难被发现。出于这个原因，最好的办法是
确保您的火灾探测器/烟雾报警器也具有CO检测功能...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6su7n/ysk_the_buildup_of_black_soot_on_the_bottom_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6su7n/ysk_the_buildup_of_black_soot_on_the_bottom_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 01:38:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:   Carbon monoxide (CO) is known as the &amp;amp;quot;silent killer&amp;amp;quot; for a reason.  It&amp;amp;#39;s odourless and colourless, so it&amp;amp;#39;s very hard to detect.   For this reason, it&amp;amp;#39;s always a good idea to ensure your fire detector/smoke alarm also has CO detection  (most of the newer fire detectors come standard with this nowadays).      &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m making this post because I noticed a lot of black soot (black powdery substance) building up on the bottom of my girlfriend&amp;amp;#39;s pots and pans when we cook at her condo.  I also have a gas range stove at my place but have never seen build-up of soot on my cooking equipment.  This soot will come off as black dust on your finger if you rub the bottom of a pan after it cools.  Recently, the CO alarm went off on the smoke detector at my girlfriend&amp;amp;#39;s place, which obviously caused some concern and I started to look into the potential causes while she called the fire department.  Be sure to get out of the house and/or ventilated it by opening the windows.  Getting out of the home right away is the safest option and highly recommended. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;One of the best articles I found was this one:   &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.abe.iastate.edu/extension-and-outreach/carbon-monoxide-poisoning-checking-for-complete-combustion-aen-175/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.abe.iastate.edu/extension-and-outreach/carbon-monoxide-poisoning-checking-for-complete-combustion-aen-175/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The article shows that soot can be a sign that your natural gas stove is has an incorrect mixture of air and gas, which can lead to an incomplete burn.  This incomplete burn can cause the build-up of soot and carbon monoxide in your home.   While this typically creates CO in amounts that are not deadly, they can cause a lot of health problems over time and if the ventilation in your home is poor, it can potentially be fatal. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some symptoms of CO poisoning are headaches, shortness of breath, dizziness, weaknesss, confusion, and nausea.  If you have any of these symptoms that seem to clear up when you leave home, check the bottom of your pots and pans for clues.    The article above goes into a lot better detail than I ever could, and I&amp;amp;#39;m definitely no expert in this field.   I figured this could be life-saving information and was worth a share.     If anyone who&amp;amp;#39;s an expert in this that has corrections for my info and/or more information on this, I encourage you to share it in the thread. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Stay safe out there,&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sillyist&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为Revolut默认与第三方共享你的私人数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>如果你在使用Revolut，我建议你
看看该应用程序的隐私设置。第三点是在
"营销 "部分允许他们分享数据，如 "姓名、电子邮件地址和
与社交媒体和广告平台分享应用程序的事件"，而 "营销 "部分的第三点允许他们分享数据，如 "姓名、电子邮件地址和应用程序事件"。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r513bd/ysk_that_revolut_shares_your_private_data_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r513bd/ysk_that_revolut_shares_your_private_data_by/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:43:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In case you‘re using Revolut, I recommend you to take a look at the app‘s privacy settings. The third point under the „marketing“ section allows them to share data such as „name, email address and app events with social m*dia and advertising platforms“, and the toggle is turned on by default.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: The concerned data, especially in context with your bank activities, tells a lot about you and your behavior, it should therefore be treated confidential. I strongly recommend to turn off that setting.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK - 随着天气越来越冷，小心使用防冻剂绝对是至关重要的；确保防冻剂安全地保存在你的棚子里，并清理任何溢出物。防冻剂对猫咪的杀伤力很小，而且大多数防冻剂对猫咪（和狗）来说味道不错，所以它们会继续吃。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：</p> <p>最小量的
防冻液可以杀死猫，而且是可怕的杀死。摄入防冻剂后30分钟内就会出现症状
摄入后30分钟内就会出现迹象；它们开始像喝醉了一样蹒跚，开始发现
呼吸困难。他们会呕吐，会有癫痫发作。最后，他们的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r5spih/ysk_as_weather_gets_colder_it_is_absolutely_vital/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r5spih/ysk_as_weather_gets_colder_it_is_absolutely_vital/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The smallest amount of antifreeze can kill cats, and kill them horribly. Signs can show within 30 minutes of ingestion; they begin to stumble like they are drunk, start to find breathing difficult. They vomit, they can have seizures. Finally, their kidneys give out. It is absolutely horrific for pet and owner.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know this from experience, having lost &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/gallery/4ZzwTLh&quot;&amp;gt;two cats&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; to antifreeze poisoning in the space of one week.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;*The worst thing about antifreeze is it&amp;amp;#39;s active ingredient, Ethylene Glycol, has an appealing, sweet taste. Once found, your pet will continue you eat it. Not knowing they are killing themselves.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s also vital to know &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rspca.org.uk/adviceandwelfare/pets/cats/health/poisoning/antifreeze&quot;&amp;gt;the symptoms&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; of antifreeze poisoning, as depending on dosage it only takes 2-3 days for your kitty&amp;amp;#39;s kidneys to fail, and the cat to pass.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please please please, save a cat this Christmas. Store, dispose of and use any antifreeze safely, or buy pet-safe antifreeze (that doesn&amp;amp;#39;t contain ethylene glycol).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为浏览器在流媒体质量方面有限制。对于观看节目或电影，Edge和Safari实际上提供了比Chrome或Firefox更好的体验。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：特别是如果你订阅了
尤其是当你订阅了一个高质量的流媒体计划时，你应该考虑你的首选浏览器（至少对你的流媒体而言）。
至少对你的流媒体而言）。否则，你基本上没有任何好处，从
额外的钱，如果你不只是出钱的话，你就没有好处。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6h98n/ysk_that_browsers_have_limitations_when_it_comes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6h98n/ysk_that_browsers_have_limitations_when_it_comes/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Especially if you&amp;amp;#39;re subscribed to a high-quality streaming plan, you should consider your go-to browser (at least for your streams). Otherwise you basically have zero benefits from the extra money you&amp;amp;#39;re paying if you&amp;amp;#39;re not just out for the multiple profiles in order to split the costs.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;These are the resolution limits of the most common browsers:&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Google Chrome:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Up to 720p (although you can get 1080p using Chrome OS)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Firefox:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Up to 720p&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Opera:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Up to 720p&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Safari:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Up to 4K (requires a select 2018 Mac or later with an Apple T2 Security Chip and MacOS 11.0 Big Sur or later)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Microsoft Edge:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Up to 4K (requires HDCP 2.2-compliant connection to a 4K display, with at least Intel&amp;amp;#39;s 7th-gen Core CPU, plus the latest version of Windows)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.digitaltrends.com/home-theater/getting-hd-netflix/&quot;&amp;gt;this site&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;Why you’re not getting Netflix in HD or 4K and how to fix it&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(Also, just to clarify: 720p = HD, 1080p = Full HD)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;[Please keep in mind that this post refers to streaming as in Netflix, Amazon Prime, etc. and not e.g. YouTube videos. Also, this isn&amp;amp;#39;t meant to promote or shame any particular browsers. They all have their benefits/downsides and in the end, everyone should decide for themselves which browser suits them and their needs best.]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为深呼吸来平静下来，用横膈膜呼吸效果更好。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：如果你试图冷静下来。
特别是在惊恐发作时，横膈膜或腹式呼吸将是
帮助你放松。胸腔或胸部呼吸更适合于体力消耗，实际上可能使你更加紧张。
实际上可能使你更加紧张....]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6bw6t/ysk_that_taking_a_deep_breath_to_calm_down_works/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6bw6t/ysk_that_taking_a_deep_breath_to_calm_down_works/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: If you’re trying to calm down, especially during a panic attack, diaphragmatic or belly breathing is what will help you relax. Thoracic or chest breathing is better for physical exertion and may actually make you more tense. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/stress-management/in-depth/decrease-stress-by-using-your-breath/art-20267197&quot;&amp;gt;(Source: Mayo Clinic)&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; Knowing how to use diaphragmatic breathing can help you calm down in stressful situations and potentially avoid a panic attack. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;From the link above, for those who don’t want to read the whole thing: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;•Get into a comfortable position. Close your eyes and bring your attention to your body and breath.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;•Inhale deeply through your nose, allowing your abdomen to fill with air, gently expanding out. Exhale by relaxing and releasing all of the air through your nose.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;•Place one hand on your abdomen, right below your navel, and the other hand on your upper chest. Take a deep breath in through your nose and out through your nose. Feel the coolness of the air as it enters in and the warmth as it flows out.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;•As you breathe in and out through your nose, focus on shifting your breath so that you can feel the rise and fall of your breathing in your abdomen more than in your chest. In other words, make the hand that rests on your abdomen move more than the hand on your chest. Take a deep breath in through your nose, sending it through the back of your throat and down to your belly. Let your abdomen slowly deflate as you exhale through your nose.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;•Take three more slow, deep breaths with conscious focus on the rise and fall of your abdomen. Continue to breathe fully and deeply, allowing and trusting the body as the breath slows and becomes more relaxed.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit 1: Thank you to &amp;lt;a href=&quot;/u/inspirationisagift&quot;&amp;gt;u/inspirationisagift&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; for adding this info in a comment, because it’s actually really useful!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Using a breathing method like box breathing/square breathing has been empirically supported as an alternative method that helps with panic attacks and times of high stress/anxiety as it brings the oxygen level down. This method deactivates the &amp;amp;#39;fight flight freeze&amp;amp;#39; stress response which relies on increased levels of oxygen.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Deep breathing can sometimes give the body that extra oxygen which keeps the body in a stressed state, wheras by reducing respiration/oxygen intake, it helps to activate the &amp;amp;#39;rest and digest&amp;amp;#39; system instead. Just in case anyone has found deep breathing to not be helpful 🙂&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：室内植物在冬季会进入休眠期，所以要减少浇水。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：由于寒冷的天气减缓了它们的
新陈代谢速度减慢，植物对水的需求就会比夏天少。它
重要的是，不要给家里的植物浇水过多，因为它们会发霉、发臭或
浇水过多容易感染真菌和其他疾病。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r5ooh7/ysk_houseplants_go_dormant_in_winter_so_reduce/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r5ooh7/ysk_houseplants_go_dormant_in_winter_so_reduce/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: As the cold weather slows down their metabolic rate, plants will require water less frequently than in the summer. It is important to not overwater your houseplants as they can grow mold, mildew, or be susceptible to fungus and other diseases with excessive water. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A good rule of thumb is to touch the soil with your finger to see if the substrate is moist, and avoid watering again until it is dry. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also, leaf tips can go brown from cold. Do not cut these off until warmer weather arrives, as this is one of the plant’s protection against frost. They essentially write off a part of themselves to take the damage from the cold in order to protect the rest of them. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Good luck, and happy gardening!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：SciHub是一个免费的渠道，可以获得大多数研究论文的信息。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：这么多科学领域的期刊文章
尤其是最近发表的文章，都被锁在极端的付费墙后面。
激动人心的信息的论文。我见过的付费墙范围从
50-200美元，只是为了获得一篇文章。SciHub是由一个人创立的。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r69hrq/ysk_scihub_is_a_free_recourse_to_get_access_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r69hrq/ysk_scihub_is_a_free_recourse_to_get_access_to/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: So many journal articles in science specifically are locked behind extreme paywalls, especially recently published papers with exciting information. I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen paywalls that range from $50-$200 just to get access to one article. SciHub was founded by a Kazakhstan woman, Alexandra Elbakyan, to make scientific information more accessible to the general public. As a STEM major, I look through tons of research papers every week and a friend of mine recently told me about this, so I wanted to share incredible resource for anyone who is unaware, especially people in the scientific community.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: So glad to see everyone sharing additional resources &amp;amp;amp; information about the inner workings of publishing research in general. I had no idea that it was such a monopolized industry &amp;amp;amp; scientists actually have to pay if they want people to read their research. Thanks to everyone &amp;amp;amp; please continue sharing this vital info! - signed a future scientist.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 有一个扩展，可以让你看到YouTube视频上的不喜欢的数量。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>不清楚直接链接到事物的政策。
但如果你在谷歌上搜索：&quot;Return Youtube Dislike&quot;你就可以找到正确的扩展。
找到正确的扩展。它适用于Chrome和Firefox。</p> <p>为什么是YSK。
显然，我必须解释为什么Youtube的不喜欢计数是...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r63i5k/ysk_there_is_an_extension_that_lets_you_see_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r63i5k/ysk_there_is_an_extension_that_lets_you_see_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Not sure about the policy of linking directly to things, but if you just google: &amp;amp;quot;Return Youtube Dislike&amp;amp;quot; you can find the right extension. It works for Chrome and Firefox.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: apparently I have to explain why youtube dislike counts are important. Well it&amp;amp;#39;s helpful when you&amp;amp;#39;re trying to sniff out a scam, or maybe it&amp;amp;#39;s helpful when looking up instructional video&amp;amp;#39;s or DIY stuff. It&amp;amp;#39;s also amusing to look at youtube rewind and see how many dislikes it gets.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Basically you should know because youtube took away it&amp;amp;#39;s functionality and this brings it back.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>