<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 17:26:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：联邦调查局分享据称参与制作儿童色情制品的人、房间、物品和物体的图像。任何信息都是有帮助的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p><a
href="https://www.fbi.gov/wanted/ecap">https://www.fbi.gov/wanted/ecap</a></p>
</div><!-- SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmmeno/ysk_the_fbi_shares_images_of_people_rooms_items/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmmeno/ysk_the_fbi_shares_images_of_people_rooms_items/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 17:07:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fbi.gov/wanted/ecap&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.fbi.gov/wanted/ecap&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为腰高比（WtHR）是比BMI更强的预测体重相关健康问题的因素。理想情况下，你的腰围大约是你身高的一半。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么是YSK：</p> <p>与体重有关的疾病是一些最具毁灭性的疾病。
一些最具破坏性的疾病，也是一些最容易预防的疾病，而且
BMI（可能是最受欢迎的指标）实际上在预测与体重有关的疾病方面做得很差。
</p> <p>这篇文章的目的不是要...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmppwp/ysk_that_waist_to_height_ratio_wthr_is_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmppwp/ysk_that_waist_to_height_ratio_wthr_is_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 11:38:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Weight related illnesses are some of the most devastating and also some of the most preventable diseases, and BMI (likely the most popular metric) actually does a poor job of predicting weight-related illnesses.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This post is not intended to body shame anyone. No measure is perfect.  It is simply meant to inform people of an easy, high-predictive-power way to assess your own risk for weight-related illnesses.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/14674615/&quot;&amp;gt;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/14674615/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，你身体中95%的5-羟色胺（稳定情绪的荷尔蒙，负责健康的感觉）是在你的肠道中产生。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：你肠道中的菌群负责生产许多重要的激素，包括血清素。
肠道菌群负责生产许多重要的激素，包括血清素。
保持健康的肠道微生物群在降低压力水平、保持身体健康方面起着巨大作用。
压力水平，保持抑郁症，获得足够的睡眠，等等。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmjnod/ysk_that_95_of_your_bodys_serotonin_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmjnod/ysk_that_95_of_your_bodys_serotonin_the/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 05:36:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: The flora in your gut is responsible for the production of a lot of important hormones, including serotonin. Maintaining a healthy intestinal micro-biome plays a huge role in lowering stress levels, keeping depression at bay, getting enough sleep, and so many other things that can improve your quality of life. Eating a balanced diet not only keeps you healthy physically, but it promotes a healthy mental state too.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TLDR: A lot of mental health issues can potentially be treated by eating a balanced, healthy diet. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/health/irritable-bowel-syndrome/serotonin-effects&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.healthline.com/health/irritable-bowel-syndrome/serotonin-effects&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apa.org/monitor/2012/09/gut-feeling&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.apa.org/monitor/2012/09/gut-feeling&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，如果你与服务行业的好工人交往，给他们工作的公司打电话表扬该工人，通常会给这个人的生活带来切实的好处。只是不要提到折扣或偷工减料。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：</p> <ol> <li><p>它使你的生活更美好，让他们付出额外的努力对你好。
让他们付出额外的努力对你好，所以让他们的生活变得更好是很好的
让他们的生活更美好。Usually they don&#39;t see a ton of reward.</p></li>
<li><p>it costs you nothing to call, and only 5 minutes of…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmheie/ysk_that_if_you_interact_with_a_nice_worker_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmheie/ysk_that_if_you_interact_with_a_nice_worker_in/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 02:52:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;it makes your life better to have them put in the extra effort to be nice to you, so it&amp;amp;#39;s nice to make their life better. Usually they don&amp;amp;#39;t see a ton of reward.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;it costs you nothing to call, and only 5 minutes of time usually. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s a powerful statement, because people usually just call to complain. A compliment speaks loudly. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s good for the businesses too, to have workers that are pleasant. Everyone benefits from them rewarding solid and friendly employees. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Tip: don&amp;amp;#39;t mention them giving you discounts etc. Do mention the solid experience they provided you as a customer, and how friendly they were.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 用激光瞄准飞机是非法的，可能导致罚款和/或监禁。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：在美国上空飞行的飞机受到
受联邦法律的管辖和保护。干扰飞行中的飞机是
是一项联邦罪行。当飞行员从地面上看到激光时，会使他或她失明几分钟。
当飞行员从地面上看到激光时，会使他或她失明数分钟，严重危害到他或她的安全。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmbarc/ysk_targeting_an_aircraft_with_a_laser_is_illegal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmbarc/ysk_targeting_an_aircraft_with_a_laser_is_illegal/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 21:37:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Aircraft flying over the US are governed and protected by federal law. Interfering with an aircraft in flight is a federal offense. When a pilot sees a LASER from the ground it can blind him or her for several minutes, seriously endangering the safety of the flight, the aircraft, the pilots, and all passengers onboard the aircraft.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.avweb.com/aviation-news/mississippi-man-faces-prison-time-for-targeting-aircraft-with-a-laser/&quot;&amp;gt;Here&amp;amp;#39;s an example of a recent penalty&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你在美国为非营利组织或政府全职工作，你可能能够通过PSLF计划摆脱你的一些学生贷款。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：学生债务在美国是巨大的。
任何能够帮助人们摆脱一些债务的东西都是伟大的。美国教育部
美国教育部于10月6日宣布临时扩大PSLF的范围。
计划。趁着这个机会，赶快行动吧！</p> <p>美国的全职非营利组织和...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmafgj/ysk_if_you_work_fulltime_in_the_us_for_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmafgj/ysk_if_you_work_fulltime_in_the_us_for_a/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 19:34:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Student debt is HUGE in the US, and anything that can help people get rid of some of that debt is great. The U.S. Department of Education announced a temporary expansion on Oct. 6 for the PSLF program. Get it while you can!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;US full-time nonprofit and government workers that have Federal Direct Loans student debt may be eligible for loan forgiveness, cancellation and/or consolidation of federal student loans under the Public Service Loan Forgiveness (PSLF) program. You could have your outstanding debt forgiven tax-free, after making 120 qualifying monthly payments under a qualifying repayment plan. Go to the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://studentaid.gov/pslf/&quot;&amp;gt;PSLF Help Tool&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; to find out if you&amp;amp;#39;re eligible.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK。贸易工作并不适合所有人。来自一个有13年工作经验的商人]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么是YSK；我听到很多人淡化了学校，炒作了交易。
我听到很多人贬低学校，炒作贸易。虽然对某些人来说，贸易可能是通往成功未来的最佳途径。
虽说对某些行业来说，可能是通往成功未来的最佳途径，但这并不适合于所有人。</p> <p>我已经培训了
至少有80％的人在声称他们已经成功后被淘汰。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlicqy/ysk_trade_work_isnt_for_everyone_coming_from_a_13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlicqy/ysk_trade_work_isnt_for_everyone_coming_from_a_13/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 23:41:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK;  I hear a lot of people downplay school and hype up trades. While for some trades may be the best way to a successful future, this does not hold true for everyone. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ve trained dozens of people and watched at least %80 wash out after claiming they could handle it. Why? It’s hard, depressing, you’re going to miss your family get no thanks, and it’s out right demoralizing until you’ve mastered it unless you’re a true die hard country boy or handy man. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you or your child considers trade work you have to be In perfect physical condition to even have a shot at the big bucks(some, or most tbh, forego that for hard drugs to cope). There is no I’m tired or hungry when you’re at the mercy of people that have done this for years. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I will not quit my trade although I am in the process of getting an education. I take pride in building. Aliens didn’t build the pyramids people like you and I  did. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Concrete finisher here. The broken bones, missing time with my family and pissing blood from dehydration was enough to make me reconsider my choice. 2022 college freshman at age 28&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TLDR; do your research before joining trade work. You may be in for a surprise.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你在面试中被问到是否打算生孩子，你不必回答，你可以直接说不。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：最近在一次采访中被问到这个问题。
采访中被问到了这个问题，作为最后的问题之一，他们为什么要问我这个问题，这一点非常明显。
我很清楚他们为什么要问我这个问题。作为一个主要由男性组成的行业中的女性，我感到
因为我确信他们不会问男人的问题。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlgusb/ysk_if_you_get_asked_in_an_interview_whether/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlgusb/ysk_if_you_get_asked_in_an_interview_whether/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 19:40:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: was recently asked this in an interview as one of the final questions and it was super obvious why they were asking me it. As a women in an industry that is made mostly of men, I felt slightly unfairly treated as I&amp;amp;#39;m sure they don&amp;amp;#39;t ask men going for the role that question. I&amp;amp;#39;ve also read that it is illegal to ask that question in some countries. Has anyone else been asked this in interviews? Or is it just me?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，你从雇主那里收到的 "廉价 "礼物实际上可能是从你的经理的口袋里掏出来的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：我知道现在是拉屎的季节。
我知道现在是拉屎的季节，我也很支持，因为这些钱确实是来自于企业的预算。
但在你收到礼物时点燃你的火把之前
但在你收到礼物时点燃火把之前，考虑一下你收到的东西是由......支付的。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlhqbh/ysk_that_the_cheap_gifts_that_you_receive_from/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlhqbh/ysk_that_the_cheap_gifts_that_you_receive_from/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 18:37:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: I know it&amp;amp;#39;s the season to shit on shitty corporate gifts, and I&amp;amp;#39;m all for it in the event that the money does come out of the corporate budget, but before you light your torches when you get your present, consider that what you received was paid from the pocket of someone not too far removed from you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;25 years ago, when we all got our first &amp;amp;#39;real jobs&amp;amp;#39; out of college, I remember many of my mates bragging about their company-funded golf games and company-expensed dinners and amazing Christmas bonuses. In retrospect I think most of them were exaggerating/lying, but I always wondered why I never had those perks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Come Christmas, my immediate manager (we were a team of 12) went around and gave envelopes to everyone. &amp;amp;#39;Here&amp;amp;#39;s the fat Christmas bonus I hear everyone talk about&amp;amp;#39;, I thought to myself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I open the envelope and see a $15 gift certificate to a retail store. &amp;amp;#39;That&amp;amp;#39;s it?&amp;amp;#39; I thought to myself &amp;amp;#39;I bust my chops all day for $15?&amp;amp;#39; I was livid.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I was livid all the way home. Livid that evening. Livid that weekend. I told my gf how livid I was. I expected her to be livid along with me.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Instead, she said &amp;amp;quot;That was nice of her, spending her own money like that.&amp;amp;quot; That&amp;amp;#39;s when I realized that this wasn&amp;amp;#39;t a cheap gift, but an amazing, thoughtful gift. I was so obsessed with myself, that I didn&amp;amp;#39;t realize that we were the only team to get something.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My manager - who wasn&amp;amp;#39;t getting paid much more than us, but who had way more financial responsibilities than us - took it upon herself to go out and get each of her team something with her own money - almost $200.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I felt terrible for feeling the way I did, but it taught me a valuable lesson in life.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Happy holidays, everyone!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，能量饮料的酸度很高，因此对你的牙齿/胃酸倒流有害。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：饮料可能是酸性的，即使它们吃起来不酸不苦。
饮料可能是酸性的，即使它们的味道不是酸或苦。</p> <p>一般能量饮料的PH值为2.8。
实际上与苏打水相同。</p> <p>The acidity of energy drinks can contribute to
enamel degradation and/or acid reflux.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rkubb0/ysk_that_energy_drinks_are_very_acidic_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rkubb0/ysk_that_energy_drinks_are_very_acidic_and/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 02:53:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Drinks can be acidic even if they don’t taste sour or bitter. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The average energy drink has a PH of 2.8, really the same as soda. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The acidity of energy drinks can contribute to enamel degradation and/or acid reflux.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在美国，没有无铝止汗剂这种东西。它们被认为是药物，美国食品和药物管理局只批准在止汗剂中使用源自铝的活性成分。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：FDA认为止汗剂是药物，因为它们可以防止出汗。
因为它们可以防止出汗。在美国的OTC专著中，唯一被批准的活性成分
美国的OTC专著中批准的唯一活性成分都是铝制的。所以在美国
因此，在美国，任何 "不含铝 "的产品都是除臭剂，而且...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rk7hkf/ysk_in_the_united_states_there_is_no_such_thing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rk7hkf/ysk_in_the_united_states_there_is_no_such_thing/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 21:36:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: The FDA considers antiperspirants as drugs as they prevent perspiration. The only active ingredients approved in the United States in the OTC monograph are all aluminum derived. So in the United States, anything that is “aluminum-free” is a deodorant and will only cover up the scent, but does nothing for sweat prevention, which causes the bad smell in the first place. Any company that tells you their aluminum-free deodorant is an antiperspirant is making either a mislabeled claim, or might be adulterated depending on the situation the FDA deems fit.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://ecfr.io/Title-21/Section-350.10&quot;&amp;gt;OTC monograph active ingredients&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你在加油站加油时，燃料流被点燃，不要将喷嘴从接收器上移开。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>如果你遇到这种情况，请将喷嘴保持在原位。
如果发生这种情况，请将喷嘴留在原地，用开关或紧急开关关闭泵的燃料，并告诉服务员。
告知服务员，服务员将关闭主泵并呼叫紧急服务。
为什么是YSK：我已经看到了大约69个视频，这些人经历了...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rki013/ysk_if_youre_pumping_at_a_gas_station_and_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rki013/ysk_if_youre_pumping_at_a_gas_station_and_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 12:52:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If this happens to you, keep the nozzle in place, shut off the fuel at the pump with the on/off or emergency switch, and tell the attendant who will shut off the main pump and call emergency services.  Why YSK:  I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen about 69 videos of people who experience this and immediately remove the nozzle and wave the stream of fire around. This will be your first instinct and it is WRONG. To lower the chance this happening, ground yourself when you exit your car by touching the door frame.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，删除你的数据并不总是删除它]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：你的数据往往仍然可以被恢复
你的数据经常可以被恢复，并被黑客攻击，甚至在你要求删除数据的请求被公司确认后也是如此。
</p> <p>我曾在大技术领域担任数据科学家，并观察到数据删除是一件棘手的事情。
数据删除是一件棘手的事情。数据治理法律因人而异。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rkf6e1/ysk_that_deleting_your_data_doesnt_always_delete/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rkf6e1/ysk_that_deleting_your_data_doesnt_always_delete/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 10:39:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: your data can often still be recovered, and hacked, even after your request that it be deleted was confirmed by a company.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I worked as a data scientist in big tech, and observed that data deletion is tricky business. Data governance laws vary by country and even state, and range quite widely. In some jurisdictions, there are no requirements: a company owns the data generated through your interactions with its services. Other countries/states do have data ownership/privacy requirements, but even the most stringent laws often require that data not be actually deleted.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Many large companies retain data for &amp;amp;quot;compliance&amp;amp;quot; reasons. A request to delete personal data, while often honored for marketing purposes by companies seeking to operate legally (not all do), is often considered legally compliant if a company only locks your data away rather than deletes it. Data access in these cases is usually limited to a handful of people dedicated to the data privacy compliance effort, but the data is often kept for months and even years. This is not a company&amp;amp;#39;s fault, but rather is mandated by other laws--ones that help identify corruption, market manipulation, anti-consumer actions, etc.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;While retaining data is useful for the above reasons, this legal mess can create confusion for ordinary people. In practice, your data is often accessible even after a company &amp;amp;quot;deletes&amp;amp;quot; it. Given that data breaches in today&amp;amp;#39;s world are effectively only a matter of time at any given company, you can pretty much assume that any online interaction you make can one day surface. Companies do have an obligation to try to keep this from happening, but can seldom be counted on as software often relies on hundreds and thousands of other pieces of software as dependencies--consistently updating all of which is incredibly difficult.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK TurboTax今年不再为低收入的美国人延续其免费文件计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：许多赚取&lt;$72,000的人使用
TurboTax来免费报税。今年，他们将需要找到另一个
供应商。请看<
href="https://www.irs.gov/filing/free-file-do-your-federal-taxes-for-free">https://www.irs.gov/filing/free-file-do-your...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rigvha/ysk_turbotax_is_not_renewing_its_free_file/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rigvha/ysk_turbotax_is_not_renewing_its_free_file/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 19:34:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Many people who make &amp;amp;lt;$72,000 use TurboTax to file taxes for free. This year, they will need to find another provider. Check out &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.irs.gov/filing/free-file-do-your-federal-taxes-for-free&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.irs.gov/filing/free-file-do-your-federal-taxes-for-free&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; for more information about which companies will have partnered with the IRS for free file this year (currently this information is not available yet).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK户外的宠物猫和野猫是一个巨大的捕食问题。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：让你的猫在外面活动可能对它们的心理健康有好处。
对它们的心理健康有好处，但对当地的生态系统却不利。猫咪
是天然的捕食者，因此，它是美国最大和最多的鸟类入侵者。
在美国，猫是天然的捕食者，因此是最大和最丰富的鸟类入侵捕食者。</p> <p>野猫的数量超过5000万只。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rihl9w/ysk_pet_cats_outdoors_and_feral_cats_are_a_huge/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rihl9w/ysk_pet_cats_outdoors_and_feral_cats_are_a_huge/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 19:34:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Letting your cats outside may be great for their mental health, but it is worse for your local ecosystem. Cats are natural predators, and as a result are the largest and most abundant invasive predator of birds in the US. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Feral cats number over 50M in the US, equating to about &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;8 billion&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; small game hunts per year, most of which are small song birds.(2.4 billion) &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why is this important to me?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;a single mating pair of cats can produce 400,000 offspring in 7 years&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;cats kill about 50% of songbird fledglings (baby birds)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; they will never recover at this rate&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;a UNebraska study has pinned 33 bird extinction events on cat predation&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Humans&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, almost 8 billion of us and our cars, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;are responsible for about 400M deaths of song-birds annually, cats are 2.4 billion&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This issue is 100% to blame on irresponsible cat owners because they are an invasive species brought here by pet trade. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source:&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wintuaudubon.org/feral-cats-drive-songbird-decline/&quot;&amp;gt;Wintu Audubon Society - Feral cats drive songbird decline&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为纳洛酮（Narcan）可以逆转阿片类药物过量的影响。它使用起来很安全，而且不需要专门的培训。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：阿片类药物的过量使用导致[每年10万名美国人]。
美国人每年]。如果足够早的话，纳洛酮可以逆转阿片类药物过量的影响，并使其成为一种新的治疗方法。
阿片类药物过量的影响，并恢复正常呼吸。它的作用是关闭大脑中的阿片类药物受体。
它的作用是关闭大脑中的阿片类受体，这意味着它对一个人没有影响。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfsybl/ysk_that_naloxone_narcan_can_reverse_the_effects/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfsybl/ysk_that_naloxone_narcan_can_reverse_the_effects/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 19:34:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Opioid overdoses kit [100,000 Americans per year]. If given early enough, Naloxone can reverse the effects of an opioid overdose and restore normal breathing. It works by turning off opioid receptors in the brain, meaning it has no effects on someone who isn&amp;amp;#39;t being affected by opioids.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In my home state of Minnesota, most pharmacies give it out for free. No special training is required.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Note that it is a controlled substance, so you will need a prescription in some states. More info below. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How Does Naloxone Work?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Naloxone is an opioid receptor antagonist meaning it binds to opioid receptors and reverses or blocks the effects of other opioids. Giving naloxone rapidly reverses the effects of opioid drugs, restoring normal respiration. It can be administered by injection or through a nasal spray.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Is Naloxone Safe?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Yes. There is no evidence of significant adverse reactions to naloxone. Administering naloxone in cases of opioid overdose can cause withdrawal symptoms when the person is dependent on opioids; this is uncomfortable without being life threatening. The risk that someone overdosing on opioids will have a serious adverse reaction to naloxone is far less than their risk of dying from overdose. Naloxone works if a person has opioids in their system and has no harmful effect if opioids are absent. Naloxone should be given to any person who shows signs of an opioid overdose or when an overdose is suspected.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.drugabuse.gov/publications/naloxone-opioid-overdose-life-saving-science&quot;&amp;gt;Source - drugabuse.gov&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;hr/&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Additional Sources:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preventionsolutions.edc.org/services/resources/state-naloxone-access-laws&quot;&amp;gt;State Naloxone Access Laws - Education Development Center&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://doseofreality.mn.gov/need-help/naloxone.asp&quot;&amp;gt;General information on Naloxone - doseofreality.mn.gov&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，AFL-CIO保持着美国所有活跃工人罢工的最新地图]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: if you&#39;re trying to avoid
crossing picket lines this should aid you greatly.</p> <p><a
href="https://aflcio.org/strike-map">Strike Map</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/risckt/ysk_that_the_aflcio_keeps_an_updated_map_of_all/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/risckt/ysk_that_the_aflcio_keeps_an_updated_map_of_all/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 19:34:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: if you&amp;amp;#39;re trying to avoid crossing picket lines this should aid you greatly.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://aflcio.org/strike-map&quot;&amp;gt;Strike Map&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：白色手杖并不是只有全盲的人才会使用。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：</p> <p>全白的手杖可以被用于
任何视力障碍者都可以使用。它们经常被用作向他人发出的信号。我的
我的父亲是法律上的盲人，但一般不需要手杖来行走。
然而，他在外面用它来使过马路更容易....。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfyrub/ysk_white_canes_arent_only_used_by_fully_blind/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfyrub/ysk_white_canes_arent_only_used_by_fully_blind/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 19:34:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Fully white canes can be used by any visually impaired person. They are often used as a signal to others. My dad is legally blind, but doesn&amp;amp;#39;t need the cane to generally walk around. However, he uses it outside to make crossing the street easier. In most places, you are required to stop for people with a white cane (or guide dog).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also, white canes with a red tip are for people who are deaf blind.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know this was posted 6 years ago, but I saw some thread of people arguing about if a person with a white cane could see someone in front of them. Sometimes they can !&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：铝不是除臭剂的成分]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：除臭剂和止汗剂是两回事。
不同的东西。止汗剂通常含有铝这一成分。
除臭剂，在大多数情况下，不包含。我看到人们购买更昂贵的
品牌的除臭剂，因为标签上说它不含铝....。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rjxrki/ysk_aluminum_is_not_an_ingredient_in_deodorants/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rjxrki/ysk_aluminum_is_not_an_ingredient_in_deodorants/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 17:45:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Deodorant and antiperspirant are two different things. Antiperspirants usually contain aluminum as an ingredient. Deodorants, for the most part, do not. I’m seeing people buy the more expensive brand of deodorant, because the label says it’s aluminum free. Aluminum was never an ingredient in deodorant to begin with, don’t pay extra for “Aluminum free” deodorant. If anything, pay extra for the Aluminum free antiperspirants. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goodhousekeeping.com/beauty/anti-aging/a37272089/is-deodorant-aluminum-bad-for-you/&quot;&amp;gt;source&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/health/what-to-know-about-aluminum-in-deodorant&quot;&amp;gt;source2&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，你在网上找到的相当多的建议只适用于美国。特别是带有文化成分的建议几乎不具有普遍性。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：在这个星球上，并不是每个地方都有相同的社会或法律规范来辞去你的工作或组建公司。
辞职、买车或撰写简历的社会或法律规范不尽相同。
简历。因此，请确保用你自己的语言和来自你自己国家的消息来源来仔细检查。
你自己的国家的消息来源。使用常识，并尝试将你的想法与你的国家联系起来。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rjkjq5/ysk_that_a_fair_amount_of_advice_you_find_online/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rjkjq5/ysk_that_a_fair_amount_of_advice_you_find_online/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 14:39:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Not every place on this planet has the same social or legal norms for quitting your job, buying a car or formating a CV. So make sure to double check with a source in your own language and from your own country. Use common sense, and try to relate what you read in thus sub to expercieas from your life before taking any advice at face value.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，无限制的PTO/Vacation不是一项福利，尽管在招聘过程中，它经常被公司作为一个卖点。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：在传统的PTO套餐中，每年有固定的天数。
在传统的PTO套餐中，每年有固定的天数，你的休假时间在每个发薪期都会被累积。
基本上创造了一个假期银行。有些公司甚至会让你将一定数量的休假时间
一些公司甚至会让你将一定数量的天数结转到下一年......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rjnkl2/ysk_that_unlimited_ptovacation_is_not_a_perk_even/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rjnkl2/ysk_that_unlimited_ptovacation_is_not_a_perk_even/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 08:47:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: in a traditional PTO package with a set number of days per year, your vacation time is accrued each payroll period essentially creating a bank of days off. Some companies will even let you carry over a certain amount of days into the following year (although that is becoming increasingly rare these days). If you are allowed 3 weeks per year and you are allowed to carry over 1 week per year, over the course of 5 years, you could build up a pretty substantial amount of accrued PTO. If you leave the company, they have to make you whole… in other words, that company is required to pay back all your accrued vacation time at the end of your employment. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, with an unlimited vacation policy, no vacation time is accrued at any point throughout the year. So if you had a really stressful year which didn’t allow you to take PTO and the company lays you off in December, you receive nothing. In the 3 week PTO example, the company would have to comp you almost 3 weeks of accrued vacation time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also, there is a psychological component in play as well. If employees are given unlimited PTO, most take less time off throughout any given year. If a company says you HAVE to take 3 weeks this year (no carryover), you’re going to plan out that time off. If unlimited, you always think that you’ll get around to planning time off but then that always gets delayed. As one who can speak from experience in my current company, I make sure to assign myself X number of days off per year and track to that. Believe me, it helps.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just remember, a lot of companies are not “cool” or progressive with these perks that make them seem more attractive, they are usually tactics that somehow benefit their bottom lines in the end.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(Seeing a lot of comments about policies outside of US. Apologies, I should have clarified that all my experience is within US based companies. I am not surprised for a second that other countries take better care of their workforce)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，送餐公司不仅收取送餐费，而且还抬高菜单价格，收取服务费、最小推车费等等。平均而言，35美元的食物成本在美国的外卖应用程序上要花费55美元以上]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：你可以通过更多的信息来省钱
你可以通过更多了解食品配送费用来节省开支。你经常看到的那些 "免费送货 "的广告，实际上是指 "没有送货费"。
你经常看到的那些 "免费送货 "的广告，实际上是指 "没有送货费"。还有15-20%的服务费，他们
他们抬高菜单价格，并增加激增费用和最低购物车费用。销售...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rjl2f5/ysk_that_food_delivery_companies_not_only_charge/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rjl2f5/ysk_that_food_delivery_companies_not_only_charge/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 05:40:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: You can save money by being more informed about food delivery fees. Those ads you see all the time for “free delivery” really mean “no delivery fee.” There’s also 15-20% service fees, they inflate menu prices, and add surge fees and minimum cart fees. Sales taxes are also calculated differently from app to app! One item that’s $10 on the menu could very well be $17 on a delivery app. I usually avoid these fees by either 1. Picking up the food myself or 2. Using a food delivery aggregator like FoodBoss or MealMe. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foodboss.net/&quot;&amp;gt;Foodboss&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; has a website, but only operates in a few cities and compares 2 major services. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.apple.com/us/app/mealme-doordash-grubhub-etc/id1460140965&quot;&amp;gt;MealMe&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; works in every city and compares all the apps, but is only on iOS. Whatever you choose, make sure to always tip!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为宠物是一个可怕的礼物。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK: 照顾宠物是一项巨大的工作。
大量的工作。节后，动物收容所经常充斥着不需要的动物。
</p> <p>如果你想让你的朋友们知道你在做什么，那么你就会知道你在做什么。</p> <p>如果有人想养宠物，请给他们玩具或食物。
他们的玩具或食物来代替。他们可以自己去挑选动物....。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rjd476/ysk_that_a_pet_is_a_terrible_gift/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rjd476/ysk_that_a_pet_is_a_terrible_gift/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 20:40:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Caring for a pet is an enormous amount of work. Animal shelters are often flooded with unwanted animals after the holidays as people figure this out. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If someone wants a pet, give them toys or treats instead. They can pick out an animal on their own. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please don&amp;amp;#39;t give someone a puppy because it looks like they need one. Animals aren&amp;amp;#39;t for everyone. They may not have the time, resources or living situation to support it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If your child wants a pet, bring them to a shelter to pick one out instead. Also be ready to care for it when your child slacks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你的衣柜推拉门很难移动吗？你有没有给它上过润滑油？]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>我们的房子有30多年的历史了，大多数
橱柜的滑动门都很难打开和关闭。我看到一个视频，显示
技巧，他们用凡士林（Vaseline）来润滑门。
他们用凡士林来润滑门，现在（2年后）它们仍然可以滑动...。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rj56k7/ysk_is_your_sliding_closet_door_hard_to_move_have/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rj56k7/ysk_is_your_sliding_closet_door_hard_to_move_have/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 16:44:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Our house is 30+ years old and most the sliding closet doors were hard to open and close. I saw a video showing household tips &amp;amp;amp; tricks and they used petroleum jelly (Vaseline) to lubricate the doors and now (2 years later) they still slide along effortlessly. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You have to be tall enough to reach the top of the door. There are usually a two brackets up on top with a small wheel that rides along a rail. If you can&amp;amp;#39;t see it you can move your door back &amp;amp;amp; forth slowly and feel around with your finger until you come across a little wheel spinning. Take some petroleum jelly on the end of your finger and touch it to the wheel as you move the door slowly. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The wheel will spread the jelly on the rail and use it up, which is what you want to happen. You should  have to use about 3 dabs to cover the rail &amp;amp;amp; wheel really well. Move the door as far as you can one way then the other. Repeat with the other bracket. Then repeat on the two brackets on the other door. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When you are done with the jelly just use the door handle to move the doors back &amp;amp;amp; forth as far as you can about a dozen times. This makes sure the lubricant is spread the entire length of the rails. You should already notice how easily it is gliding along. If not, then you have other problems. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: A sliding door has moving pieces just like hinges move on swinging doors and need lubrication. Most people don&amp;amp;#39;t think about lubricating the moving pieces because they are hidden. You won&amp;amp;#39;t believe how easily some will open &amp;amp;amp; shut afterwards.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：快餐业的可怕之处]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：你可以通过避免快餐工作来拯救你自己的许多痛苦
你可以避免从事快餐工作，我将告诉你发生在你身上的故事。
我告诉你一些食物的故事，会让你不想再去那里吃饭。
<p>&#x200B;</p> <p>作为一个做过无数快餐工作的人，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rivgly/ysk_the_horrors_of_the_fast_food_industry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rivgly/ysk_the_horrors_of_the_fast_food_industry/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 09:40:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: You can save yourself a lot of misery by avoiding fast food jobs, and the stories I will tell you about what happened to some of the food will make you not want to eat there anymore.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As someone who has worked numerous fast food jobs, I can tell you these are some of the absolute worst working conditions in America. I have worked at Popeye&amp;amp;#39;s, Jack in the Box, and Burger King. Do you like being tremendously under-compensated for your work? Then fast food is for you. Popeye&amp;amp;#39;s paid $10/hr, Burger King paid $9.50, Jack in the Box paid $9. Now imagine you work an 8 hour shift at Jack in the Box and come away with $70 for your efforts. They&amp;amp;#39;re making $70 in sales &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;within 100 seconds.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; Seriously, it takes them 2-3 sales to earn what you get paid over an entire 8 hour shift. The pay is insulting and impossible to live off of.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Oh, and that&amp;amp;#39;s not all. While the tasks may be &amp;amp;quot;easy&amp;amp;quot;, they are CONSTANT. Imagine making dozens and dozens and dozens of sandwiches in  a row, and the line never slows down or ceases. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;I have made food poorly out of spite, and so have my coworkers. You should know that if you join an already long line, thus putting more stress on grossly underpaid workers, they may make your food poorly out of frustration.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; And that&amp;amp;#39;s not all. Most fast food places don&amp;amp;#39;t offer a break. You&amp;amp;#39;re expected to work 8 hours straight, only getting to rest when the line stops.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And that&amp;amp;#39;s not all either. The conditions are poor. You&amp;amp;#39;re surrounded by multiple fryers, causing the air in the restaurant to get hot and humid, causing you to sweat. Not only that, but the air is filled with grease and you will feel gross by the end of your shift. Not to mention that eating the unhealthy food on a daily basis can lead to weight gain and health problems. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Not here&amp;amp;#39;s another kicker. Because you are working in a low-paying industry that will basically hire anyone, you are going to meet some bad people.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; I worked with a man who would literally clock in, go to the manager&amp;amp;#39;s office (This was the overnight so there was no manager there), and just go to sleep. Then he&amp;amp;#39;d wake up, call his girlfriend, and start screaming at her. This was a nightly occurrence. Another guy I worked with frequently went to the bathroom to do meth and crack. He was homeless, spent his checks on drugs, and would get so high he would spend the entire shift talking to himself. He called women &amp;amp;quot;Skynet&amp;amp;quot; and said he needed to take them out, and asked me where to get a gun. Another woman and her boyfriend quit after his repeated abuse. There are plenty of bad people in fast food.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Ok, ok, I get it, you don&amp;amp;#39;t care about the working conditions. All you want is a decent meal. Let me tell you about the things I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen sandwich buns dropped on the floor, and instead of throwing them away, the employee will continue to make the sandwich with those buns. I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen entire buckets of raw chicken dropped onto the ground, only to be thrown in the fryer instead of the garbage. I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen swarms and swarms of flies in the kitchen, both at Popeye&amp;amp;#39;s and Burger King. Most of the time, employees didn&amp;amp;#39;t wear gloves, they made the food with their bare hands. Those are just a few examples, and I&amp;amp;#39;m sure I could think of more if I tried.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你有一只猫，并且一直在半夜醒来，这可能不是失眠。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：这可能只是你的猫是一个可爱的混蛋。
</p> <p>在过去的一年半里，我一直在半夜醒来。
在过去的一年半里，我不断地在半夜醒来，被吓得睁大了眼睛。我以为我的失眠症已经翻转了 --
没有。(我通常是难以入睡的类型)原来我的猫...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/riqjic/ysk_if_you_have_a_cat_and_keep_on_waking_up_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/riqjic/ysk_if_you_have_a_cat_and_keep_on_waking_up_in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 07:41:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: it might just be your cat being a loveable jerk.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For the past year and a half, I kept waking up in the middle of the night, wide awake startled. I thought my insomnia had flipped- nope. (I usually have the hard to fall asleep type) Turns out my cat just smacks my face in the middle of the night or bites my nose or toes when he is lonely or cold to wake me up. Caught him a couple of times, and now that I have gotten a bigger blanket that covers my head and feet, it doesn&amp;amp;#39;t happen anymore.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：谈论你的工资并不违法，你应该这样做，因为这更有可能使你获得更好的工资/薪水。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：围绕讨论你的工资/薪水的耻辱是不可能的。
雇主想要利用同工不同酬的优势，对你的工资/薪水进行讨论，这是毫无道理的，是由雇主驱动的。
雇主想利用同样的工作向雇员支付不同的金额。你完全有权利
你有权利讨论你的工资，并可能受到法律的保护，这取决于...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rinvl6/ysk_talking_about_your_wages_is_not_against_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rinvl6/ysk_talking_about_your_wages_is_not_against_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 04:46:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: the stigma around discussing your wages/salary is unjustified and is driven by employers wanting to take advantage of paying employees different amounts for the same work. You have every right to discuss your wages and may be protected by law depending on what country/ state you are in.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：某人在邪教中的迹象]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：嗯，2021年教会了我，它非常
很容易被洗脑进入邪教。你知道这些迹象吗？1. 领袖是
如果你不允许批评你的领袖，即使批评是真实的。
批评是真实的，那么你可能是在一个邪教中。2. 2.团体...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rijkbx/ysk_signs_someone_is_in_a_cult/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rijkbx/ysk_signs_someone_is_in_a_cult/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 03:40:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Well 2021 taught me that it’s very easy to get brainwashed into a cult. 
Do you know the signs?
1. The leader is the ultimate authority
If you’re not allowed to criticize your leader, even if the criticism is true, you’re probably in a cult.
2. The group suppresses skepticism
If you’re only allowed to study your organization through approved sources, you’re probably in a cult. Cults view critical thinking as an infectious disease and every effort is made to suppress it. Doubting members are encouraged to isolate themselves from outside influences and focus solely on the doctrine of the cult
4. The group is paranoid about the outside world
5. The group relies on shame cycles
6. The leader is above the law 
7. The group uses “thought reform” methods
If your serious questions are answered with cliches, you’re probably in a cult.
8. The group is elitist
If your group is the solution for all the world’s problems, you’re probably in a cult.
Cults see themselves as the enlightened, chosen, and elect organization tasked with radically transforming individual lives and the entire world.
9. Tell you to stay away from friends and family with different views.
10. No financial transparency&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 超速行驶几乎从来不值得冒险。在60英里的车程中，时速90英里而不是70英里，只能为你节省11分钟。在10英里的车程中，它将为你节省不到2分钟。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：超速是非法的，而且很危险。它
它几乎不能为你节省任何时间，却极大地增加了事故的风险。
伤害和法律后果。顺着交通流走是最安全的。
而且发生任何问题的风险要低得多。</p>...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rilppc/ysk_speeding_almost_never_is_worth_the_risk_on_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rilppc/ysk_speeding_almost_never_is_worth_the_risk_on_a/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:41:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Speeding is illegal and dangerous. It barely saves you any time while dramatically increasing the risk of accidents, injuries, and legal consequences.  Going with the flow of traffic is the safest and has much lower risk of any trouble. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://mindyourdecisions.com/blog/2011/09/30/how-much-time-does-speeding-save/&quot;&amp;gt;How much time does speeding save?&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，大多数人都误解了 "下雨几率 "的实际含义；50%的下雨几率并不意味着那天有50%的机会会下雨。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么是YSK：因为它是一个常见的错误观念
这可能会影响我们如何安排我们的一天。</p> <p>用简单的术语来说。50%的机会
意思是说，预计某个地区有50%的地方会下雨。
</p> <p>计算降水概率的公式是......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/riqpw9/ysk_that_most_people_misunderstand_what_chance_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/riqpw9/ysk_that_most_people_misunderstand_what_chance_of/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 22:41:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: because its a common misperception that can affect how we organize our day. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In simplistic terms: 50% chance of rain means that it is expected that 50% of a certain area is expected to see rain.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The formula to calculate Precipitation Chance (%) = Confidence of Precipitation Developing x Percent of Area Affected.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If the confidence level is 100% then a 30% chance of rain means that 30% of the coverage area will see precipitation. If the confidence level is 50% and only 40% of the coverage area will see precipitation, then the math is (0.50 x 0.40) x 100 = 20 or 20% chance of rain. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Check out more: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nwahomepage.com/weather/weather-101/weather-101-what-does-a-30-chance-of-rain-really-mean/amp/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.nwahomepage.com/weather/weather-101/weather-101-what-does-a-30-chance-of-rain-really-mean/amp/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你习惯于从一个地方的几个员工那里获得交易或折扣，这并不意味着你有权每次都从所有人那里获得。如果你说你习惯于从经理那里得到上述优惠，那么你就是在坑害那些一直为你提供服务的员工。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：他们在帮你的忙，但这并不意味着其他员工会帮你。
并不意味着其他员工会这样做。如果你逼得太紧，你就不会
你不会再从那些员工那里得到你的交易，而且你很可能会被
你很可能会危及他们的就业，所以请闭上你的嘴，并...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rifffo/ysk_if_youre_used_to_getting_a_deal_or_discount/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rifffo/ysk_if_youre_used_to_getting_a_deal_or_discount/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 17:47:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: They&amp;amp;#39;re doing you a favour but it doesn&amp;amp;#39;t mean other employees will. And if you push too hard, you won&amp;amp;#39;t get your deal from those employees anymore, and you could very well be jeopardizing their employment there, so just keep your mouth shut and be happy with what you get.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：当你在工作中进行绩效评估时，你不应该为想要谈判薪酬而感到内疚]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：我最近离开了一份工作，因为我的老板
我最近离开了一份工作，因为我的老板拒绝给我加薪，尽管我在两年的绩效评估中达到了所有的目标。
我最近离开了一份工作，因为我的老板拒绝给我加薪，尽管我在两年的绩效评估中达到了所有的目标。他甚至让我为要求加薪而感到内疚。
他甚至让我为要求加薪而感到内疚，说我很幸运能拥有这个职位，而且...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ridzij/ysk_you_shouldnt_feel_guilty_for_wanting_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ridzij/ysk_you_shouldnt_feel_guilty_for_wanting_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 14:41:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: I recently left a job because my boss refused to increase my salary even though I had met every target set over two years of performance reviews. He even made me feel guilty for asking for a salary increase saying that I was lucky to have the position and that there were plenty of other people out there that would love the opportunity I had. At the end of the day, if a company is growing and you are contributing to that growth, you should never feel guilty for knowing your worth and asking for a salary increase. If your manager can&amp;amp;#39;t see your worth, there will always be another company that will be able to.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: I recently changed jobs and got a 20% payrise - sent my boss an email after I left my previous job saying &amp;amp;quot;thanks for not believing in me and making me realise that others did&amp;amp;quot; lol&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：记住这个圣诞节，如果有人为你买了一份25美元的礼物，而他们赚的是最低工资，他们付出了2-3个小时的生命来给你买这个礼物。要谦虚，礼物不一定要花很多钱才有价值。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么是YSK：朋友或家人可能经历了艰难的一年，可能为我付出了很多努力/思考。
你的朋友或家人可能度过了艰难的一年，他们可能为你的礼物付出了很多努力/思考，所以即使可能不是几百美元，也要记得善待他们。
</p> </div><!
SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rie4ga/ysk_remember_this_christmas_if_someone_buys_a_25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rie4ga/ysk_remember_this_christmas_if_someone_buys_a_25/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 12:50:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Friends or family might have had a tough year and might have put a lot of effort/thought into your gift so even though it may not be hundreds of dollars, remember to be kind!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如果你已经更新了你的iPhone iOS 15或更大，并且讨厌底部的搜索栏，你可以点击搜索栏左边的AA，将搜索栏移回顶部。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>在底部看不到栏杆是很痛苦的，因为你已经习惯了它在页面的顶部。
因为你已经习惯了它在页面的顶部，这就是为什么YSK的这个技巧！希望它能帮助你。
希望能有所帮助。</p> </div><!--SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ri5z9l/ysk_if_youve_updated_your_iphone_ios_15_or/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ri5z9l/ysk_if_youve_updated_your_iphone_ios_15_or/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 07:10:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Aggravating not seeing the bar at the bottom because you’re so use to it being on the top of the page is why YSK this trick! Hope it helps.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你更新到最新版本的iOS 15，不喜欢Safari浏览器中生活在用户界面底部的搜索栏，你可以点击 "aA "符号，将其移回顶部。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：有些人不喜欢这种变化，而且不知道有一个回到location的选项。
不知道有一个选项可以返回到传统的布局。这个小
这个小提示将允许你在两种布局之间来回切换，并使你能够自己选择。
you to choose for yourself.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhxvsx/ysk_if_you_updated_to_the_latest_version_of_ios/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhxvsx/ysk_if_you_updated_to_the_latest_version_of_ios/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 23:36:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Some people don’t like the change and don’t know that there’s an option to return to the legacy layout.  This little tip will allow you to toggle back and forth between the layouts and will empower you to choose for yourself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为吼叫、尖叫、骂人等是不正常的，而且很少存在于健康的关系中。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：如果你像我一样，大喊大叫是你家里唯一的沟通方式。
是你家里唯一的沟通方式。许多人可能没有意识到的是
这种行为的影响对一个人的自尊、对人际关系的看法、对人际关系的看法、对人际关系的看法、对人际关系的看法都会产生长期的影响。
自尊心、对人际关系的看法、心理健康（负面的核心自我评价）。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhxqn1/ysk_that_yelling_screaming_namecalling_etc_is_not/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhxqn1/ysk_that_yelling_screaming_namecalling_etc_is_not/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 21:40:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: If you&amp;amp;#39;re like me, yelling was the only form of communication in your household. What many may not realize is the impact of that kind of behavior has long term effects on one&amp;amp;#39;s self esteem, view of relationships, mental health (negative core self beliefs, trauma, PTSD/CPTSD, anxiety, depression, etc etc) and needs as a person. Thats why its important to stop the cycle and learn to communicate properly. Healing is definitely possible.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It doesn&amp;amp;#39;t matter how well they treat you after or how sincerely they apologize. It doesn&amp;amp;#39;t matter if they are your parents or guardians. This is not normal healthy behavior. Healthy relationships involve talking about problems and working things out. There is no hurtful name-calling or blaming things on the other person. If they are willing to call you names to get a rise out of you on purpose, how do you think that will work out with children or years down the line?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Its hard enough to find a relationship, I get it, but yelling and screaming happen when there is not enough healthy communication. 9/10 times situations that involve yelling or screaming could be solved by a calm, emotionally mature, and honest conversation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you know you do this, own it. Talk to a therapist about why and work on it. You will be so much happier and healthier when you can communicate your feelings through talking rather than the less effective and more hurtful mode of verbal violence&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，如果你在餐厅的等待时间比你想的要长，那么女主人简直就是这栋楼里最不值得被骂的人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么是YSK：餐厅女主人的首要目标是尽快为你的聚会安排座位。
餐馆女主人的首要目标是尽可能快地安排你的聚会。这符合她自己的最佳利益
为了她自己的利益，她会让你直接进入餐厅，所以请你放心，如果她有什么需要帮助的地方，她会帮助你。
如果她能做什么来减少您的等待时间，请放心。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rht67a/ysk_that_if_your_wait_at_a_restaurant_is_longer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rht67a/ysk_that_if_your_wait_at_a_restaurant_is_longer/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 18:40:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: The primary goal of the hostess at a restaurant is to seat your party as quickly as possible. It is in her own best interest to move you right on through to the dining room, so please be assured that if there was anything she can do to lower your wait time, she would do it. She does not deserved to be yelled at because your wait is 15 minutes longer than you expected. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Pretty much every restaurant is woefully understaffed right now. Those that survived the last couple of years are trying to operate as lean as possible. Until the restaurant industry has time to recover, this is likely to remain the case. Even then, I imagine they will have a tough time attracting enough workers to become fully staffed unless they make dramatic improvements to how their employees are compensated. The hostess that you are taking your frustrations out on is one of, if not the lowest paid, employees in the restaurant, and in many cases it is their very first job. With the staffing situation the way it is now, she is very likely having to bus tables, answer the phone, pack to-go orders, and do cleanliness checks on the restrooms, as well as manage the waitlist and coordinate the seating of diners. On top of that, she is going to be the first one to get grief from her managers when customers start to pile up waiting to be seated.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The hostess at a restaurant cannot seat you if there isn’t a table available for you. It’s as simple as that. Just because you see an empty table, or a dozen empty tables, doesn’t mean that there are enough servers on duty to work those tables. The hostess cannot put you at a table that doesn’t have a server assigned to it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you MUST yell at someone, first of all, get some psychiatric help at the first opportunity, but until then maybe yell at other diners who loiter for an hour after their meal is finished. Or yell at the manager, who at least to some degree has some control over how the restaurant is staffed at any given time. Maybe write a scathing email or make an irate phone call to the corporate office, if it’s a chain, or the owner if it’s privately owned, and insist that they raise wages or do whatever they need to do to attract more staff.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please, if you are not capable of being patient and showing a little bit of grace, please just eat at home. You never know the battles someone else is fighting in their life, and your harsh words at that particular time may have an impact that on them that you never intended.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：无论你的工作场所如何推崇 "家庭文化"--记住，他们不是你的朋友，它仍然是一个工作场所。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么是YSK：我的女朋友学到了这一点，她很难受--她在阳光下为创业公司工作了每一个小时。
她为一家初创公司工作了每一个小时，当她不工作的时候
会以社交身份与他们共度晚间。她去年被解雇了，原因是
因为公司有现金流问题，他们所有人都停止了......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhnerx/ysk_no_matter_how_much_your_workplace_pushes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhnerx/ysk_no_matter_how_much_your_workplace_pushes/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 12:43:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: my gf learned this the hard - she worked every hour under the sun for a startup and when she wasn&amp;amp;#39;t working would spend evenings with them in a social capacity. She got fired last year due to the company having cash flow issues and all of them stopped responding to her messages. She put so much work into trying to make the company successful and sacrificed other parts of her life for them, but they didn&amp;amp;#39;t really give a shit about her. I&amp;amp;#39;m not saying go around and be a dick to people for no reason, but it&amp;amp;#39;s better to build relationships outside of work or in places where there aren&amp;amp;#39;t any power imbalances or incentives to screw people over.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK不同类型的性虐待/骚扰/攻击行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK是因为我最近刚被性骚扰了。
我想说的是，我最近被性骚扰了，而且没有得到公正的对待。
所以这里有一些不同的类型，如果不是所有的类型，只是没有人和我一样受到伤害。
所以这里有一些，如果不是所有不同的类型，只是没有人遭受和我一样的痛苦，请务必联系......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhh0fc/ysk_the_different_types_of_sexual_abuse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhh0fc/ysk_the_different_types_of_sexual_abuse/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 08:36:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;why YSK is because i recently just got sexually harassed , and no justice came from it . all because people didn’t seem like it was “ a big deal “
so here’s some if not all the different types , just so nobody has to suffer the same as me . make sure to reach out to someone you love or trust :))&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;• rape
• attempted rape 
• unwanted touching or physical contact 
• unwelcome sexual advances
• unwanted sexual photos , texts , emails , etc . ( not just nudes )
• unwanted flashing 
• making conditions of employment or advancement dependent on sexual favors, either explicitly or implicitly.
• remarks of a sexual nature about a persons clothing , personal behavior , clothes , or body .
• purposely brushing up against a person 
• following or standing too close to a person on purpose .
• cat calling
• spreading sexual rumors 
•  taking photos of a person without their consent , especially private parts ( this is what happened to me , he took a photo of my ass and my teacher’s breasts )&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;all types of harassment is important and serious , please never think that it’s not . 
if i missed any on the list please tell me and i’ll add them !&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK在雨中使用你适当的大灯]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: because we can’t see you in our
mirrors. DRLs don’t count.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhcqkz/ysk_to_use_your_proper_headlights_in_the_rain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhcqkz/ysk_to_use_your_proper_headlights_in_the_rain/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 05:51:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: because we can’t see you in our mirrors. DRLs don’t count.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 上瘾的循环很容易被预想（你的旧瘾第一次出现在你脑海中的时刻）重新点燃。接下来是沉思、决心、行动、维持，最后是复发。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：你可以通过注意到以下几点来打破成瘾性
早期的迹象。如果你可以的话，当你发现你的触发点时，告诉你的伴侣你的触发点是什么，这样他们就可以和你一起注意。
</p> <p>这正是我个人上瘾的模式。
这正是我个人上瘾的模式，它完美地遵守了......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhfks8/ysk_the_addiction_cycle_is_easily_reignited_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhfks8/ysk_the_addiction_cycle_is_easily_reignited_by/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: You can break addictions by noticing the early signs. If you can, tell your partner what your trigger is when you find it so that they can be on the lookout with you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is exactly the pattern my personal addiction follows, and it adheres perfectly to the typical model researchers have found. Does it sound familiar?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bonus point for those who made it this far! Advertisements are artificial precontemplation triggers, targeted at ex-addicts.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://addictionresource.com/treatment/stages/&quot;&amp;gt;https://addictionresource.com/treatment/stages/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：男性和女性的中风症状是不同的]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：我们都被告知要注意什么？
我们都被告知，当某人发生中风时要注意什么，但男性和女性实际上有不同的症状，值得了解。
</p> <p><strong>在中风期间，男性和女性都有不同的症状，值得了解。
在中风期间，男性和女性通常都会报告出现这些迹象......。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rh93nx/ysk_stroke_symptoms_are_different_for_men_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rh93nx/ysk_stroke_symptoms_are_different_for_men_and/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 03:48:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: We all get told what to look out for when someone is having a stroke but men and women actually have different symptoms and they are worth knowing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;During a stroke, both men and women typically report these signs appearing suddenly:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Numbness or weakness in the face, arm or leg, especially on one side of the body&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Confusion, trouble speaking or trouble understanding&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Trouble seeing in one or both eyes&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Difficulty walking, dizziness, or loss of balance or coordination&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Severe headache with no known cause&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Women, however, may also report these symptoms:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Hiccups&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Nausea&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Chest pain&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Fatigue&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Shortness of breath&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- A racing heartbeat&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s worth knowing in case a friend or a loved one is ever showing any of these signs as you need to act quickly!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK在涉及伤员的事件中，在周围有很多人的情况下，帮助他们看管好自己的钱包和手机或他们所佩戴的任何贵重物品，或与他们在一起的人确认。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么是YSK：在许多情况下，这些物品经常被其他人偷走。
</p> <p>不要把他们的物品放在你的口袋里，除非你与死者有关系。
他们的物品放在你的口袋里，除非你与该伤亡人员有关系。这可能
这可能会被认为是你在偷东西。最好把它放在地板上......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgwtsg/ysk_in_an_incident_involving_a_casualty_in_public/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgwtsg/ysk_in_an_incident_involving_a_casualty_in_public/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 17:00:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: In many cases, these items are frequently stolen by other people who pretend to be helping.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Do not keep their items in your pocket unless you are related to that casualty. That may come off as you stealing it. It&amp;amp;#39;s best to leave it on the floor next to the casualty so everyone can see who picks up the wallet.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In a scenario where everyone is gathering around, no one would dare to pick up the casualty&amp;amp;#39;s wallet while it&amp;amp;#39;s very noticeable.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As someone living near a junction where the traffic is confusing and prone to accidents, people stealing money/valuables from the casualty has happened more times than I can count.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK开始为小动物进入你的房子或汽车做准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：越来越冷了
天气有时会把不受欢迎的客人带到你的汽车和/或房子里的温暖和安全的地方。
和/或房子里。它们变得饥肠辘辘，会以你的电线、绝缘体和软管为食。
造成昂贵的损害。有一辆2022年的MDX说警告......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgq73g/ysk_to_start_preparing_for_small_animals_entering/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgq73g/ysk_to_start_preparing_for_small_animals_entering/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 15:52:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: it’s getting colder and colder weather sometimes brings unwelcome guests into warm and safe spots in your car and/or house. They get hungry and will feed on your wires, insulation, and hoses causing expensive damage. Had a 2022 MDX come in saying warning lights were all on her brand new car. After inspecting it. I found the communication wire to be completely torn apart. Luckily I was able to fix it for less than $100, if not, it would have costed about $6K to replace being as that wire was part of the complete dash harness. However you handle rodents is entirely up to you but know that they can cause lots of damage; most of the time insurance companies and warranty companies will never back you up for that.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK "最低工资 "是法律允许的最低工资。"起始工资 "是雇主提供给新雇员的实际工资。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：我看到很多雇主现在把提供的最低工资称为
我看到很多雇主把提供的入门工资称为最低工资。虽然我认为他们可以
我想他们是可以使用这些词的，但如果在他们宣布他们的最低工资时造成误解，那就太可惜了。
当他们宣布他们提高了最低工资时，这将是一种耻辱。A...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgmkhq/ysk_minimum_wage_is_the_lowest_wage_allowed_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgmkhq/ysk_minimum_wage_is_the_lowest_wage_allowed_by/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 14:38:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;WHY YSK: I see a lot of employers now calling the entry wage offered their &amp;amp;quot;minimum wage&amp;amp;quot;. While I suppose they are allowed to use those words, it would be a shame if it caused misunderstanding when they announce they &amp;amp;#39;raised their minimum wage&amp;amp;#39;. A raise in minimum wage is something currently being urged on government by many as a way to reduce poverty. A wage policy announced by a single employer is not enough.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你应该质疑你在网上看到的一切。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：有这么多的视频、图片和
事实在互联网平台上。很多时候，这些视频都是伪造的，或者是事实
很多时候，这些视频都是伪造的，或者是将事实归结到与图片的原始目的无关的图像上。
只要看一眼帖子上的评论，你就会发现，这些评论是多么的......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgycx0/ysk_you_should_question_everything_you_see_online/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgycx0/ysk_you_should_question_everything_you_see_online/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 14:38:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: There are so many videos, images and facts on internet platforms. A lot of the time these videos are staged, or facts are attributed to an image that has no relation to the images original purpose. A glance at the comments on a post will show you just how many people lap it up without question.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The reason you should know is that it’s this blind belief that advertisers and scammers exploit daily. We are living in an age where companies have learnt how easy it is to manipulate us. By taking everything you see at face value you are opening yourself up to this manipulation. And basically opening up your wallet, and in some cases your values and belief systems.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It’s quick and easy to do a quick internet search about anything to find out if something is likely to be true. Don’t be one of the people who comment how impressed you are at a particular post because this just adds to the claim and makes it more difficult for others to determine if something is genuine. It should be obvious not to believe everything you see online but it seems like we have started to take that for granted and have forgotten that lately.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 有可能在同一批衣物中清洗你的白色和彩色。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：许多人把白色和深色的衣服分开洗，以防止染上白色。
衣服分开洗，以防止给白衣服上色，占用额外的水和时间。
</p> <p><strong>如果你使用的是标有白色的洗衣粉，那么你就会发现你的衣服是白色的。
</p> <p><strong>如果你使用标有 "对颜色安全 "的增白洗衣粉，并使用冷水洗涤</strong>，那么大多数人都会选择用冷水洗涤。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgly9i/ysk_its_possible_to_wash_your_whites_and_colors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgly9i/ysk_its_possible_to_wash_your_whites_and_colors/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 07:42:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Many people wash their whites and darks in seperate loads to prevent coloring their whites, using up extra water and time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;If you use a whitening laundry powder labeled &amp;amp;quot;Safe on colors&amp;amp;quot; AND wash using cold water&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, then most whites will stay white even when washing them with dark or colored clothes. I&amp;amp;#39;ve done this many times using Oxi-clean White Revive and it&amp;amp;#39;s always worked. I believe there&amp;amp;#39;s other brands with similar products.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just be careful not to wash clothes with heavy ink (e.g. Tie-dye or sharpie) in the same load as whites.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT: To clarify, the whitening powder isn&amp;amp;#39;t strictly necessary unless you want to use a whitener. A lot of people do, but if you don&amp;amp;#39;t, then you can skip it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你在美国，YSK--EBT和SNAP福利可以用来在网上订购食品杂货，以便送货或在路边取货。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：在美国，使用这些福利的人有这种耻辱感。
使用这些福利的人，这使得一些人在申请时感到担心。
这使得一些人担心在第一时间申请。有些人害怕去排队结账，冒着被人评头论足的风险。
说你是如何依靠......的。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgjo1d/ysk_if_you_are_in_the_us_ebt_and_snap_benefits/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgjo1d/ysk_if_you_are_in_the_us_ebt_and_snap_benefits/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 07:42:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: There is this stigma in the US for people who use these benefits and this makes some people worried to apply in the first place. Some fear going to a checkout line and risk someone judging you or making a remark how you are &amp;amp;quot;relying on handouts&amp;amp;quot;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Although these people should just be ignored, it is still there and stopping people from getting food they need. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you&amp;amp;#39;ve ever worked a job, and paid taxes, you&amp;amp;#39;ve already contributed so don&amp;amp;#39;t feel bad. These benefits are a very GOOD thing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anyways, with the help of technology it&amp;amp;#39;s easy to shop online with EBT or SNAP and get curbside delivery, or you can even have your groceries delivered directly to your house.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ll provide a link that details all of the places you can use your benefits. I hope this can help someone who otherwise might not apply.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://foodstampsnow.com/list-of-grocery-stores-that-accept-ebt-online-for-delivery/&quot;&amp;gt;https://foodstampsnow.com/list-of-grocery-stores-that-accept-ebt-online-for-delivery/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK的短信 "741741 "将立即为你联系危机咨询师，只要你需要，他们就会与你沟通，而且对任何人都是免费的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：随着假期的临近，你应该知道。
你应该知道，如果你感到抑郁，或有自杀倾向，或你需要有人
倾诉，<a href="https://www.crisistextline.org/">这是你可以利用的许多工具之一
</p> <p>你可以利用许多工具</p>。</p> <p>你被通缉，你...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/re9m7u/ysk_that_texting_741741_will_immediately_connect/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/re9m7u/ysk_that_texting_741741_will_immediately_connect/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 21:37:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: With the holidays approaching, you should know that if you are feeling depressed, or suicidal or you need someone to talk to, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crisistextline.org/&quot;&amp;gt;this is one of many tools&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; that are available to you. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You are wanted, you belong, and the world is a better place with you in it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：用现金/借记卡支付实际上是在补贴其他用信用卡支付的顾客。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：信用卡网络对其服务收取1-3%的手续费。
办理费，因此，零售商和餐馆通常会提高价格，以补偿大家的损失。
他们的价格对每个人来说都是一种补偿。信用卡持卡人将获得1-3%的返还
的现金返还或积分，因此，即使零售商提高价格，他们也...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/reuuum/ysk_paying_in_cashdebit_effectively_subsidizes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/reuuum/ysk_paying_in_cashdebit_effectively_subsidizes/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 21:37:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Credit card networks charge a 1-3% processing fee for their services, so retailers and restaurants often mark up their prices for everyone to compensate. Credit card holders will get 1-3% back in cashback or points, so even if a retailer raises prices, they effectively get the fair-market value price for the good. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cash payers, otoh, don&amp;amp;#39;t - so they end up paying 1-3% above the normal asking price to compensate for credit card users.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>