<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 16:04:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 一个研究小组正在使用一个选择自己的冒险游戏，让你改变你的内心对话--而且这项研究仍然开放给参与者。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：我们开始意识到
我们开始意识到自我保健的重要性，并及早投资于我们的心理健康。
而不是在事情已经出了问题的时候再去寻求治疗。虽然
专业的帮助可能永远是最好的选择（如果你能负担得起...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r76qnq/ysk_a_team_of_researchers_are_using_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r76qnq/ysk_a_team_of_researchers_are_using_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 15:40:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: We’re beginning to realise the importance of self-care and investing in our mental wellness early enough, instead of reaching for treatment when things have already gone awry. While professional help is probably always the best option (if you can afford it), technology can surely play a role in terms of education and prevention.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Games for Emotional and Mental Health lab is a group of behaviour change researchers and game designers, pioneering a model that combines evidence-based wellbeing tools with play and storytelling, because they’ve found that most existing apps fail to engage people long enough to deliver any benefits.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The lab recently opened a &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://utwentebs.eu.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_9uwhwDopngYIocu&quot;&amp;gt;study&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; that you can take part in, focusing on a new iOS game that teaches self-awareness through a choose-your-own-adventure story. If you’re the kind of person with a more creative mind, it could be worth trying this approach and push science forward while you’re at it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，2021年6%的通胀率到2022年2%的通胀率，相对而言是 "过渡性的"，但绝对而言是实际的增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：确保你的年薪增长至少达到通货膨胀率。
确保你的年薪增长至少与通货膨胀率持平。否则，就是减薪。</p>
<p>通货膨胀通常显示为同比百分比变化。请不要被
不要被政府愚弄，当通货膨胀被 "过渡 "到2%时......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6q20e/ysk_that_6_inflation_in_2021_to_2_inflation_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6q20e/ysk_that_6_inflation_in_2021_to_2_inflation_in/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 02:45:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: make sure that your yearly salary increase is at least that of inflation. Otherwise, it’s a pay cut.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Inflation is often shown as year over year percentage change. Do not be fooled by the government when the inflation is “transitioned” into 2% the following year.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For example, an item that costs 100 dollar in 2020 will cost 106 dollar in 2021 with 6% inflation, but will costs 108.12 dollar in 2022 with 2% inflation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 你的锅碗瓢盆底部堆积的黑色烟尘是不正常的。它可能是一氧化碳过多的迹象。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：一氧化碳（CO）被称为 "无声的杀手"。
一氧化碳被称为 "无声杀手 "是有原因的。它是无色无味的，因此
它很难被发现。出于这个原因，最好的办法是
确保您的火灾探测器/烟雾报警器也具有CO检测功能...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6su7n/ysk_the_buildup_of_black_soot_on_the_bottom_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6su7n/ysk_the_buildup_of_black_soot_on_the_bottom_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 01:38:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:   Carbon monoxide (CO) is known as the &amp;amp;quot;silent killer&amp;amp;quot; for a reason.  It&amp;amp;#39;s odourless and colourless, so it&amp;amp;#39;s very hard to detect.   For this reason, it&amp;amp;#39;s always a good idea to ensure your fire detector/smoke alarm also has CO detection  (most of the newer fire detectors come standard with this nowadays).      &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m making this post because I noticed a lot of black soot (black powdery substance) building up on the bottom of my girlfriend&amp;amp;#39;s pots and pans when we cook at her condo.  I also have a gas range stove at my place but have never seen build-up of soot on my cooking equipment.  This soot will come off as black dust on your finger if you rub the bottom of a pan after it cools.  Recently, the CO alarm went off on the smoke detector at my girlfriend&amp;amp;#39;s place, which obviously caused some concern and I started to look into the potential causes while she called the fire department.  Be sure to get out of the house and/or ventilated it by opening the windows.  Getting out of the home right away is the safest option and highly recommended. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;One of the best articles I found was this one:   &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.abe.iastate.edu/extension-and-outreach/carbon-monoxide-poisoning-checking-for-complete-combustion-aen-175/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.abe.iastate.edu/extension-and-outreach/carbon-monoxide-poisoning-checking-for-complete-combustion-aen-175/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The article shows that soot can be a sign that your natural gas stove is has an incorrect mixture of air and gas, which can lead to an incomplete burn.  This incomplete burn can cause the build-up of soot and carbon monoxide in your home.   While this typically creates CO in amounts that are not deadly, they can cause a lot of health problems over time and if the ventilation in your home is poor, it can potentially be fatal. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some symptoms of CO poisoning are headaches, shortness of breath, dizziness, weaknesss, confusion, and nausea.  If you have any of these symptoms that seem to clear up when you leave home, check the bottom of your pots and pans for clues.    The article above goes into a lot better detail than I ever could, and I&amp;amp;#39;m definitely no expert in this field.   I figured this could be life-saving information and was worth a share.     If anyone who&amp;amp;#39;s an expert in this that has corrections for my info and/or more information on this, I encourage you to share it in the thread. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Stay safe out there,&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sillyist&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为Revolut默认与第三方共享你的私人数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>如果你在使用Revolut，我建议你
看看该应用程序的隐私设置。第三点是在
"营销 "部分允许他们分享数据，如 "姓名、电子邮件地址和
与社交媒体和广告平台分享应用程序的事件"，而 "营销 "部分的第三点允许他们分享数据，如 "姓名、电子邮件地址和应用程序事件"。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r513bd/ysk_that_revolut_shares_your_private_data_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r513bd/ysk_that_revolut_shares_your_private_data_by/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:43:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In case you‘re using Revolut, I recommend you to take a look at the app‘s privacy settings. The third point under the „marketing“ section allows them to share data such as „name, email address and app events with social m*dia and advertising platforms“, and the toggle is turned on by default.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: The concerned data, especially in context with your bank activities, tells a lot about you and your behavior, it should therefore be treated confidential. I strongly recommend to turn off that setting.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK - 随着天气越来越冷，小心使用防冻剂绝对是至关重要的；确保防冻剂安全地保存在你的棚子里，并清理任何溢出物。防冻剂对猫咪的杀伤力很小，而且大多数防冻剂对猫咪（和狗）来说味道不错，所以它们会继续吃。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：</p> <p>最小量的
防冻液可以杀死猫，而且是可怕的杀死。摄入防冻剂后30分钟内就会出现症状
摄入后30分钟内就会出现迹象；它们开始像喝醉了一样蹒跚，开始发现
呼吸困难。他们会呕吐，会有癫痫发作。最后，他们的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r5spih/ysk_as_weather_gets_colder_it_is_absolutely_vital/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r5spih/ysk_as_weather_gets_colder_it_is_absolutely_vital/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The smallest amount of antifreeze can kill cats, and kill them horribly. Signs can show within 30 minutes of ingestion; they begin to stumble like they are drunk, start to find breathing difficult. They vomit, they can have seizures. Finally, their kidneys give out. It is absolutely horrific for pet and owner.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know this from experience, having lost &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/gallery/4ZzwTLh&quot;&amp;gt;two cats&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; to antifreeze poisoning in the space of one week.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;*The worst thing about antifreeze is it&amp;amp;#39;s active ingredient, Ethylene Glycol, has an appealing, sweet taste. Once found, your pet will continue you eat it. Not knowing they are killing themselves.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s also vital to know &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rspca.org.uk/adviceandwelfare/pets/cats/health/poisoning/antifreeze&quot;&amp;gt;the symptoms&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; of antifreeze poisoning, as depending on dosage it only takes 2-3 days for your kitty&amp;amp;#39;s kidneys to fail, and the cat to pass.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please please please, save a cat this Christmas. Store, dispose of and use any antifreeze safely, or buy pet-safe antifreeze (that doesn&amp;amp;#39;t contain ethylene glycol).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为浏览器在流媒体质量方面有限制。对于观看节目或电影，Edge和Safari实际上提供了比Chrome或Firefox更好的体验。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：特别是如果你订阅了
尤其是当你订阅了一个高质量的流媒体计划时，你应该考虑你的首选浏览器（至少对你的流媒体而言）。
至少对你的流媒体而言）。否则，你基本上没有任何好处，从
额外的钱，如果你不只是出钱的话，你就没有好处。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6h98n/ysk_that_browsers_have_limitations_when_it_comes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6h98n/ysk_that_browsers_have_limitations_when_it_comes/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Especially if you&amp;amp;#39;re subscribed to a high-quality streaming plan, you should consider your go-to browser (at least for your streams). Otherwise you basically have zero benefits from the extra money you&amp;amp;#39;re paying if you&amp;amp;#39;re not just out for the multiple profiles in order to split the costs.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;These are the resolution limits of the most common browsers:&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Google Chrome:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Up to 720p (although you can get 1080p using Chrome OS)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Firefox:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Up to 720p&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Opera:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Up to 720p&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Safari:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Up to 4K (requires a select 2018 Mac or later with an Apple T2 Security Chip and MacOS 11.0 Big Sur or later)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Microsoft Edge:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Up to 4K (requires HDCP 2.2-compliant connection to a 4K display, with at least Intel&amp;amp;#39;s 7th-gen Core CPU, plus the latest version of Windows)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.digitaltrends.com/home-theater/getting-hd-netflix/&quot;&amp;gt;this site&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;Why you’re not getting Netflix in HD or 4K and how to fix it&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(Also, just to clarify: 720p = HD, 1080p = Full HD)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;[Please keep in mind that this post refers to streaming as in Netflix, Amazon Prime, etc. and not e.g. YouTube videos. Also, this isn&amp;amp;#39;t meant to promote or shame any particular browsers. They all have their benefits/downsides and in the end, everyone should decide for themselves which browser suits them and their needs best.]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为深呼吸来平静下来，用横膈膜呼吸效果更好。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：如果你试图冷静下来。
特别是在惊恐发作时，横膈膜或腹式呼吸将是
帮助你放松。胸腔或胸部呼吸更适合于体力消耗，实际上可能使你更加紧张。
实际上可能使你更加紧张....]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6bw6t/ysk_that_taking_a_deep_breath_to_calm_down_works/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r6bw6t/ysk_that_taking_a_deep_breath_to_calm_down_works/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: If you’re trying to calm down, especially during a panic attack, diaphragmatic or belly breathing is what will help you relax. Thoracic or chest breathing is better for physical exertion and may actually make you more tense. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/stress-management/in-depth/decrease-stress-by-using-your-breath/art-20267197&quot;&amp;gt;(Source: Mayo Clinic)&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; Knowing how to use diaphragmatic breathing can help you calm down in stressful situations and potentially avoid a panic attack. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;From the link above, for those who don’t want to read the whole thing: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;•Get into a comfortable position. Close your eyes and bring your attention to your body and breath.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;•Inhale deeply through your nose, allowing your abdomen to fill with air, gently expanding out. Exhale by relaxing and releasing all of the air through your nose.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;•Place one hand on your abdomen, right below your navel, and the other hand on your upper chest. Take a deep breath in through your nose and out through your nose. Feel the coolness of the air as it enters in and the warmth as it flows out.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;•As you breathe in and out through your nose, focus on shifting your breath so that you can feel the rise and fall of your breathing in your abdomen more than in your chest. In other words, make the hand that rests on your abdomen move more than the hand on your chest. Take a deep breath in through your nose, sending it through the back of your throat and down to your belly. Let your abdomen slowly deflate as you exhale through your nose.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;•Take three more slow, deep breaths with conscious focus on the rise and fall of your abdomen. Continue to breathe fully and deeply, allowing and trusting the body as the breath slows and becomes more relaxed.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit 1: Thank you to &amp;lt;a href=&quot;/u/inspirationisagift&quot;&amp;gt;u/inspirationisagift&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; for adding this info in a comment, because it’s actually really useful!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Using a breathing method like box breathing/square breathing has been empirically supported as an alternative method that helps with panic attacks and times of high stress/anxiety as it brings the oxygen level down. This method deactivates the &amp;amp;#39;fight flight freeze&amp;amp;#39; stress response which relies on increased levels of oxygen.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Deep breathing can sometimes give the body that extra oxygen which keeps the body in a stressed state, wheras by reducing respiration/oxygen intake, it helps to activate the &amp;amp;#39;rest and digest&amp;amp;#39; system instead. Just in case anyone has found deep breathing to not be helpful 🙂&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：室内植物在冬季会进入休眠期，所以要减少浇水。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：由于寒冷的天气减缓了它们的
新陈代谢速度减慢，植物对水的需求就会比夏天少。它
重要的是，不要给家里的植物浇水过多，因为它们会发霉、发臭或
浇水过多容易感染真菌和其他疾病。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r5ooh7/ysk_houseplants_go_dormant_in_winter_so_reduce/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r5ooh7/ysk_houseplants_go_dormant_in_winter_so_reduce/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: As the cold weather slows down their metabolic rate, plants will require water less frequently than in the summer. It is important to not overwater your houseplants as they can grow mold, mildew, or be susceptible to fungus and other diseases with excessive water. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A good rule of thumb is to touch the soil with your finger to see if the substrate is moist, and avoid watering again until it is dry. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also, leaf tips can go brown from cold. Do not cut these off until warmer weather arrives, as this is one of the plant’s protection against frost. They essentially write off a part of themselves to take the damage from the cold in order to protect the rest of them. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Good luck, and happy gardening!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：SciHub是一个免费的渠道，可以获得大多数研究论文的信息。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>为什么YSK：这么多科学领域的期刊文章
尤其是最近发表的文章，都被锁在极端的付费墙后面。
激动人心的信息的论文。我见过的付费墙范围从
50-200美元，只是为了获得一篇文章。SciHub是由一个人创立的。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r69hrq/ysk_scihub_is_a_free_recourse_to_get_access_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r69hrq/ysk_scihub_is_a_free_recourse_to_get_access_to/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: So many journal articles in science specifically are locked behind extreme paywalls, especially recently published papers with exciting information. I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen paywalls that range from $50-$200 just to get access to one article. SciHub was founded by a Kazakhstan woman, Alexandra Elbakyan, to make scientific information more accessible to the general public. As a STEM major, I look through tons of research papers every week and a friend of mine recently told me about this, so I wanted to share incredible resource for anyone who is unaware, especially people in the scientific community.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: So glad to see everyone sharing additional resources &amp;amp;amp; information about the inner workings of publishing research in general. I had no idea that it was such a monopolized industry &amp;amp;amp; scientists actually have to pay if they want people to read their research. Thanks to everyone &amp;amp;amp; please continue sharing this vital info! - signed a future scientist.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 有一个扩展，可以让你看到YouTube视频上的不喜欢的数量。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>不清楚直接链接到事物的政策。
但如果你在谷歌上搜索：&quot;Return Youtube Dislike&quot;你就可以找到正确的扩展。
找到正确的扩展。它适用于Chrome和Firefox。</p> <p>为什么是YSK。
显然，我必须解释为什么Youtube的不喜欢计数是...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r63i5k/ysk_there_is_an_extension_that_lets_you_see_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r63i5k/ysk_there_is_an_extension_that_lets_you_see_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 21:26:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Not sure about the policy of linking directly to things, but if you just google: &amp;amp;quot;Return Youtube Dislike&amp;amp;quot; you can find the right extension. It works for Chrome and Firefox.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: apparently I have to explain why youtube dislike counts are important. Well it&amp;amp;#39;s helpful when you&amp;amp;#39;re trying to sniff out a scam, or maybe it&amp;amp;#39;s helpful when looking up instructional video&amp;amp;#39;s or DIY stuff. It&amp;amp;#39;s also amusing to look at youtube rewind and see how many dislikes it gets.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Basically you should know because youtube took away it&amp;amp;#39;s functionality and this brings it back.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK的歌词是一首更适合所有年龄段的生日歌。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p><em>Futurama</em> ep.2:14 features an origuous.
为Nibbler勋爵的生日朗诵的原创歌曲。它使用了与
它使用了与&quot;生日快乐&quot;大致相同的旋律，同样是八个小节，但歌词却好得多。
但歌词要好得多。原本的歌词如下：</p> <p><em>什么日子......？]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r55xiq/ysk_the_lyrics_to_a_much_better_birthday_song_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r55xiq/ysk_the_lyrics_to_a_much_better_birthday_song_for/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 15:19:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Futurama&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; ep. 2:14 features an original song recited for Lord Nibbler&amp;amp;#39;s birthday. It uses roughly the same melody as &amp;amp;quot;Happy Birthday&amp;amp;quot; for the same eight bars, but with much better lyrics. The original lyrics are as follows:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;What day is today?&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s Nibbler&amp;amp;#39;s birthday!&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;What a day for a birthday!&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Let&amp;amp;#39;s all have some cake!&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;These lyrics were written for TV in order to avoid infringing the copyright for &amp;amp;quot;Happy Birthday&amp;amp;quot;, but they are good enough to replace &amp;amp;quot;Happy Birthday&amp;amp;quot; entirely if adopted by the public.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Saying the phrase &amp;amp;quot;Happy birthday to you&amp;amp;quot; four times in a row is boring and embarassing for everyone involved, and is often thought of as the least fun part of a birthday party. These lyrics are more fun and creative, and they touch on the most exciting themes for a child: special occasions, attention, and cake.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，你的汽车仪表盘上的警告灯的颜色表明了问题的紧迫性]]></title><description><![CDATA[有些车的仪表盘上有奇怪的、形状混乱的灯，或者你只是
没有阅读手册。无论如何，你不一定需要知道每一个灯是什么意思
每一个灯的意思，只要你注意其颜色。

绿色。没有问题，只是一个通知。像雾灯，或准备继续前进的事情
雾灯，或准备行动......。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r58u24/ysk_that_the_color_of_the_warning_lights_on_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r58u24/ysk_that_the_color_of_the_warning_lights_on_your/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 02:51:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some cars have weird, confusingly shaped lights on the dash, or maybe you just didn&amp;amp;#39;t read the manual. Either way, you don&amp;amp;#39;t necessarily need to know what every light means as long as you pay attention to the color.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Green: Non issue, just a notification. Things like fog lights, or ready to move on hybrids.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Amber: Non urgent issue. These are for issues that are OK to continue driving with, but should be fixed soon. Things like check engine, ABS failure, traction control failure, tire pressure, etc.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Red: Urgent issue. These are for issues that pose an immediate serious danger to you or the car. If a red light comes on, stop immediately. Things like no oil pressure, overheating, or brake failure, or charging system failure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Charging system failure may sound like that should be an amber light, but there&amp;amp;#39;s a good reason it&amp;amp;#39;s red. It&amp;amp;#39;s rare for an alternator to just die all of a sudden, so that could also indicate a broken serpentine belt, which would also stop your water pump and power steering pump. It could also indicate an electrical fault that could, in serious cases, start a fire. Even if it&amp;amp;#39;s neither of those, when your battery dies, you are stranded. So that&amp;amp;#39;s why it&amp;amp;#39;s red.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:  If you don&amp;amp;#39;t know what all the lights in your car mean, just knowing what the color means can save you a lot of money and avoid dangerous situations.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ysk吊扇有夏季和冬季设置。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：风扇上通常有一个开关可以改变风扇的旋转方向
转动的方向。由于叶片的间距，这改变了空气流动的方向。总而言之
夏天，叶片应该逆时针旋转，这将产生一个
下风，以帮助冷却。在冬天，叶片应该旋转。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r51r1p/ysk_ceiling_fans_have_a_summer_and_winter_setting/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r51r1p/ysk_ceiling_fans_have_a_summer_and_winter_setting/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 19:51:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: There is usually a switch on the fan that changes the direction the fan spins. Due to the pitch of the blades this changes the direction air flows. In summer, blades are supposed to spin counter-clockwise and this creates a downdraft to help cool. In winter, blades are supposed to spin clockwise to circulate warm air around for more efficient heating. This is especially important in homes with high or vaulted ceilings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，撇号从来不用于使单数词变成复数。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么YSK：许多人用's来复数单词。这是不正确的。唯一的时间
你应该使用撇号的时候是用于缩略语（don't, haven't, she's），以使某些东西具有占有性（Da's）。
的），或将小写字母复数化（dot
你的i's）。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r4zsyl/ysk_that_apostrophes_are_never_used_to_make_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r4zsyl/ysk_that_apostrophes_are_never_used_to_make_a/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 18:54:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Many people use &amp;#39;s to pluralize words. This is incorrect. The only time you should ever use an apostrophe is for contractions (don&amp;#39;t, haven&amp;#39;t, she&amp;#39;s) to make something possessive (Dave&amp;#39;s), or for pluralizing lowercase letters (dot your i&amp;#39;s).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为警察局可能是在互联网上购买/销售时与陌生人见面的最安全场所]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：如果你正在寻找来自私人当事方的交易，或作为私人当事方出售某物
的时候，交易的会面地点应该是在一个
安全的地方。警察局是你可以公开会面的最安全的地方。
也可以作为一个过滤器，防止有不良企图的人。

我是...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r4qgsn/ysk_that_police_stations_are_probably_the_safest/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r4qgsn/ysk_that_police_stations_are_probably_the_safest/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 11:45:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If you&amp;#39;re looking for deals from private parties, or selling something as a private party, the meeting place for the transaction should be somewhere safe.  Police stations are just about the safest place you can meet publicly, and also act as a filter against people with bad intentions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m currently selling a high-priced item as a private party, and told a prospective buyer who wanted to see the item that he should meet me at my local police station.  He refused, and suggested a McDonald&amp;#39;s parking lot in a sketchy neighborhood instead.  His refusal to meet at the police station sounded my alarm bells, especially when he couldn&amp;#39;t articulate his objections to meeting there.  I called off the deal with him, and instead went with the next prospective buyer who not only had no objections to meeting at the police station, but expressed his appreciation for doing so at such a safe place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S.  Many police stations not only support this activity, but some will also provide a police officer to be present during the transaction upon request.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，酒精极易上瘾，全世界每年大约有300万人死于酒精。酗酒的严重性和潜力被媒体淡化，以增加销售。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么YSK--对所有正在阅读这篇文章的青少年和年轻人来说，你不需要
你不需要通过饮酒来进行社交活动和享受美好时光。广告会
试图说服你，使你对他们的产品上瘾。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r4hzyw/ysk_that_alcohol_is_extremely_addictive_and_kills/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r4hzyw/ysk_that_alcohol_is_extremely_addictive_and_kills/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 02:07:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK - to all the teens and young people out there reading this, you don&amp;#39;t need to consume alcohol to socialize and have a good time. Advertisements will try to convince you otherwise, so that you become addicted to their product.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：大多数灭火器都是一次性使用的，使用后会有漏水现象。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：为了好玩而使用灭火器是很诱人的，用完就放回去。
但大多数灭火器在按下手柄后并不完全密封。
但大多数灭火器在按下手柄后并不完全密封，而且会继续泄漏，直到最终压力耗尽。
压力耗尽。你应该总是得到一个新的火...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r4h1q9/ysk_most_fire_extinguishers_are_single_use_only/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r4h1q9/ysk_most_fire_extinguishers_are_single_use_only/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 02:07:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It can be tempting to use a fire extinguisher for fun, and just put it back when you&amp;#39;re done, but most fire extinguishers don&amp;#39;t seal completely once the handle has been pressed, and will continue to leak until they eventually run out of pressure. You should always get a new fire extinguisher when you&amp;#39;ve used it, even if it was just to put out a small fire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，自动电话推销员（电话机器人）非常容易被发现，这是有原因的--而且--就像真正的推销员一样--他们实际上并不想与你交谈，除非有可能进行真正的销售。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：电话推销员--不管是自动的还是其他的--都没有兴趣
浪费时间，让一个不可能真正花钱的人在线上
钱。因此，如果你接到一个来自未知电话号码的电话，听起来像是
它可能是一个录制的广告，那么就反击他们吧......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3p10x/ysk_that_automated_telephonic_solicitors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3p10x/ysk_that_automated_telephonic_solicitors/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 01:08:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  Phone solicitors -- automated and otherwise -- aren&amp;#39;t interested in wasting time keeping someone on the line who isn&amp;#39;t likely to actually spend money. So if you receive a call from an unknown phone number which sounds like it &lt;em&gt;might&lt;/em&gt; be a recorded advertisement, then turn the tables on them by intentionally providing an unconventional response. Even if the computer on the other end doesn&amp;#39;t bail, it&amp;#39;ll still reveal itself as such pretty quickly, giving you the opportunity to disconnect from an obvious unsolicited phone advertisement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An example: I just received a call which started out with, &amp;quot;Hello! My name is Andrew -- how are you?&amp;quot; No identifying company, no identifying purpose... just those words and nothing else. Of course, that&amp;#39;s not the way a legit phone solicitor starts a conversation, so I already suspected that it was a recording. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thus, I responded by directly asking, &amp;quot;Is this a recording?&amp;quot; My confirmation came in the form of a very brief clip of the first word that the recording was going to say next, which was abruptly interrupted by a line disconnection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So either I confused it enough to force a bail-out, or (more likely in my mind) my question was flagged as the type of thing that &amp;quot;non-spenders&amp;quot; tend to say, triggering the bail-out. Either way, I didn&amp;#39;t have to waste my time listening to the rest of their ad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK的羽绒保温产品（大衣、夹克、背心、枕头、被子等）可能使用活摘的鸭子和鹅的羽毛。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK。

 * 你可能会考虑在假日期间购买羽绒保温产品。
   季节
 * 你可能不知道，鹅和鸭的羽毛可能是在它们还活着的时候被拔掉的。
   你可能不知道，鹅和鸭的羽毛可能在它们还活着的时候就被拔掉了，在它们的一生中经常被拔几次。
 * 即使你不是素食主义者，你可能也不想...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r489d2/ysk_products_with_down_insulation_coats_jackets/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r489d2/ysk_products_with_down_insulation_coats_jackets/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 18:52:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You may be considering purchasing down-insulated products during the holiday season&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You may not know that the geese and duck feathers may be plucked while they are still alive, often several times over the course of their life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Even if you aren&amp;#39;t vegan, you may not want to support this painful and inhumane practice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A single down coat can require feathers from 10-20 geese or ducks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There are alternatives or more ethical sources of down you can consider purchasing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alternatives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many companies offer alternatives (and many have even banned using down altogether) There are several ways to search for down-alternative products. Usually they will have keywords such as:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Synthetic Insulation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;Down-Alternative&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;Featherless&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recycled Insulation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cotton or Rayon Filled&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ethically-Sourced Down Options&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are currently 2 certification standards for ethical down retrieval that work to combat this issue, RDS and GTDS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RDS -&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://certifications.controlunion.com/en/certification-programs/certification-programs/rds-responsible-down-standard&quot;&gt;Responsible Down Standard&lt;/a&gt; is utilized by most ethically-aware companies, however even this standard has many flaws.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Farm inspections are announced in advance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;RDS allows for parallel farm operation (RDS and non-RDS down produced on the same farm)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;RDS does not consider the parent farm (where the geese are hatched and raised)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GTDS -&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://d2evkimvhatqav.cloudfront.net/documents/su_traceble_down_infopaper.pdf&quot;&gt;Global Traceable Down Standard&lt;/a&gt; is only utilized by Patagonia in partnership with the NSF, and is a much stricter certification.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：BlueLab正在关闭，他们所有的VST现在都是免费的]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：对于制作人来说，寻找高质量的VST是一件痛苦的事情，特别是那些
尤其是那些不需要花钱的。

BlueLab正在关闭，他们所有的VST都是免费的，直到该网站关闭。
这是一个很好的机会，制作人可以跳进去，获得一些高质量的
VSTs而不收取任何费用。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3w9st/ysk_bluelab_is_closing_down_and_all_their_vsts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3w9st/ysk_bluelab_is_closing_down_and_all_their_vsts/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 11:42:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Finding high quality VSTs can be a pain for producers, especially ones that don’t break the bank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BlueLab is shutting down and all their VSTs are free until the site closes down. This is a great opportunity for producers to jump in and get some high quality VSTs for no charge at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在安卓系统上，如果你在你的音乐文件夹中放入一个名为.nomedia的文件，它将停止在你的画廊中显示专辑封面图。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：多年来，你一直对你手机中的所有专辑封面感到厌烦
画廊。但现在没有了! 只需在你手机中所有你不想在相册中显示照片的文件夹中粘贴一个名为.nomedia的空白文件
在你的手机中，你不想在画廊中显示照片，你的画廊将
终于有意义了! 摆脱其他应用程序污染的工作...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3kyx5/ysk_that_on_android_if_you_put_a_file_called/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3kyx5/ysk_that_on_android_if_you_put_a_file_called/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 03:54:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: For years you have been annoyed at all the album art in your phone gallery. But no more! Just paste a blank file called .nomedia in all the folders in your phone you don&amp;#39;t want to show pics of in gallery, and your gallery will finally make sense! Works for getting rid of other app pollution too. My life is improved. Yours can be too!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，你的骑手评级被推迟了]]></title><description><![CDATA[我看到这里有几个人说到改变他们对司机的评价
因为他们被打了一星，所以他们 "打回一星"。

YSK：Uber推迟了对乘客（和司机）的评级更新，以 "保护匿名性"，并且不说推迟多久。
不会说延迟的时间有多长。

但他们做了一个糟糕的工作，将其传达给...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3epke/ysk_that_your_rider_rating_is_delayed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3epke/ysk_that_your_rider_rating_is_delayed/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 23:32:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve seen several people on here talk about changing their rating of drivers because they were given one star, so they &amp;quot;one star back&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;YSK: Uber delays rider (and driver) ratings updates to &amp;quot;protect anonymity&amp;quot; and won&amp;#39;t say how long the delay is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But they do a shit job of communicating that to riders. So when you see your rating go down and then downrate your most recent ride because of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: you&amp;#39;re actually retaliating against the wrong person, when it was really the driver maybe 10 or so trips ago that gave you a bad rating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please don&amp;#39;t do this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在寻找大学时，如果你很聪明，并且有一份**好的高中简历，你可以利用一所大学给你的offer，在另一所心仪的大学谈判出一个更好的交易。在许多情况下，你可以为自己谈判出更好的交易。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：你可以通过与潜在的大学谈判来节省成千上万的美元。
潜在的大学。当然，这一切都取决于你对他们的价值有多大。
但分数很高的孩子应该知道，他们有谈判的权力。
权力。

如果你喜欢的学校没有提供你想要的东西......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3czx2/ysk_when_looking_for_a_college_if_you_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3czx2/ysk_when_looking_for_a_college_if_you_are/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 16:54:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: You could save thousands upon thousands of dollars by negotiating with potential colleges. Of course, this is all predicated on how valuable you are to them but kids with very good marks should be aware that they have negotiating power. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your preferred school does not offer what you want use all of your previous offers as leverage and try to negotiate a better deal for yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，小费工资仍需补偿到最低工资标准。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：如果你从事的职业是赚取小费作为工资，并且得到的是
你没有得到全额的最低工资，那么你就有权得到联邦的工资。许多人
许多人在这个系统中被虐待，如果你因为要求得到这个报酬而被解雇
你可以报告它。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3bvmh/ysk_that_tipped_wages_still_have_to_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r3bvmh/ysk_that_tipped_wages_still_have_to_be/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 15:51:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If you work in a career where you earn tips as a wage and are getting short of your full minimum wage pay then your federally entitled to it. Many people get absued in the system, and if you are fired for asking for that pay you can report it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK讲述了 "母亲之吻"，这是一种通过堵住未受影响的鼻孔并向孩子的嘴里吹气来从孩子的鼻孔中取出物体的技术。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：这项技术是清除儿童鼻腔异物的一个有用和安全的一线选择。
的一线选择，它可以为你节省一次去急诊室/外科的机会。
赴急诊室/紧急护理。

来源[https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3503923/]]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r32v27/ysk_about_the_mothers_kiss_a_technique_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r32v27/ysk_about_the_mothers_kiss_a_technique_for/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 15:51:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This technique is a useful and safe first-line option for the removal of foreign bodies from the nasal cavities of children, and it can save you a trip to the ER/urgent care. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3503923/&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK你可以通过使用一个chrome扩展来恢复YouTube的不喜欢计数。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：一个视频的反感度对于了解一个视频是否
是否值得你花时间。它可以帮助你轻松地识别诈骗、点击率、谎言和
彻头彻尾的可怕视频。YouTube删除不喜欢的次数是
迄今为止，这是多年来该平台发生的最糟糕的事情，....]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r33ie8/ysk_you_can_bring_back_the_youtube_dislike_count/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r33ie8/ysk_you_can_bring_back_the_youtube_dislike_count/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 08:37:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:
The dislike count of a video is vital in knowing whether or not a video is worth your time. It can help you easily identify scams, clickbait, lies and downright terrible videos from a glance. YouTube removing the dislike count is by far the worst thing to happen to the platform in years. YouTube’s method of removing the count is to just hide it. So at least for now, it can be re-enabled by this chrome extension:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/return-youtube-dislike/gebbhagfogifgggkldgodflihgfeippi&quot;&gt;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/return-youtube-dislike/gebbhagfogifgggkldgodflihgfeippi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：抑郁症患者往往表现为快乐或 "正常"]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：很多时候，抑郁症患者去世或没有得到帮助是因为人们
因为人们不认为他们有抑郁症。你应该向你所有的朋友/家人了解情况。
成员，即使他们看起来很快乐。

我可以从个人经验谈起，但其他人能证实这一点吗？]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r33zp2/ysk_depressed_people_often_present_as_happy_or/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r33zp2/ysk_depressed_people_often_present_as_happy_or/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 05:47:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Too often, depressed people pass away or don’t get help because people don’t think they’re depressed. You should check in with all your friends/family members, even if they seem happy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can speak from personal experience, but can anyone else corroborate this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你的Uber司机根据你在旅行中的行为给你这个乘客评分。它位于你的个人资料中，最好的是5星级。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：这个等级将决定你在救援过程中被抓获的可能性。
在繁忙的时候，以及在长时间的乘车过程中。对你的司机好一点，不要
成为一个醉醺醺的混蛋!]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r2uq62/ysk_that_your_uber_drivers_rate_you_as_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r2uq62/ysk_that_your_uber_drivers_rate_you_as_a/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 22:50:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This rating will determine the likelihood of you getting picked up during busy times and when getting long rides. Be nice to your drivers and don&amp;#39;t be the drunk asshole!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，除非你无论如何都要买它，否则降价并不是 "交易"。你花的钱比你本来要花的多。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK。

黑色星期五来了，零售商提供 "折扣"，但这适用于一年中的任何时候。
但这一点无论在一年中的什么时候都适用。

如果你想买东西，把它放在一个清单上，并跟踪价格
(像CamelCamelCamel（仅限亚马逊）和TopPreise（瑞士）这样的工具可以帮助你
这里）。如果有...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r2fxgr/ysk_that_unless_you_were_going_to_buy_it_anyway_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r2fxgr/ysk_that_unless_you_were_going_to_buy_it_anyway_a/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 08:23:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Black Friday is here with retailers offering &amp;quot;discounts&amp;quot; but this applies no matter what the time of the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to buy something, put it on a list and keep track of the price (tools like CamelCamelCamel (Amazon only), and TopPreise (Switzerland) can help here). If there&amp;#39;s a &amp;quot;deal&amp;quot;, first check it&amp;#39;s actually money off and not artificially inflated and then buy it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you see something and go &amp;quot;wow! look at that reduction, I would lose money not buying it&amp;quot;, you are taking money from your own pockets and giving it to retailers for something you don&amp;#39;t really need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 你可以用大约20美元买一个灭火器。请为你的厨房和汽车买一个。这对它的影响来说，成本很低，万一你需要的话。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：因为你可以用灭火器阻止火灾变成地狱。
灭火器。如果是油火，除非你有灭火器，否则你无能为力。
有一个灭火器。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r2g1h5/ysk_that_you_can_buy_a_fire_extinguisher_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r2g1h5/ysk_that_you_can_buy_a_fire_extinguisher_for/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 08:23:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: because you can stop a fire from becoming an inferno with a fire extinguisher. And if it&amp;#39;s an oil fire, there&amp;#39;s nothing you can do unless you have a fire extinguisher.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，保险公司经常提供免费会员资格或健身房的会员折扣]]></title><description><![CDATA[我几年前也发过同样的帖子，但我最近在Reddit上看到一个帖子，讨论人们在健身房支付的高额费用，所以我想，我可以在这里说说。
但我最近在Reddit上看到一个帖子，讨论人们在健身房支付的惊人费用，所以我想我
会再次分享。

新年将至，这意味着许多人开始去
健身房或开始在健身房锻炼。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r2bxnm/ysk_that_insurance_companies_often_offer_free/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r2bxnm/ysk_that_insurance_companies_often_offer_free/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 07:12:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I posted this same subject a couple years ago, but I recently saw a post on Reddit discussing the outrageous costs of gyms people were paying so i figured I would share again.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New Years is around the corner and that means that many people start going to the gym again or start at the gym for the first time. If you fall into this category (or currently have an overpriced gym membership) check with your health insurance provider to see if they offer any gym membership deals BEFORE signing up for any gym. Insurance companies know that they will likely save money long term having customers who are in better shape and thus often have deals on gym memberships. Personally, my insurance offers a program that costs me $25/m and in return I receive a nationwide membership to Planet Fitness, anytime fitness, LA fitness, Snap, Crunch, and a ton of other small and local gyms, or I may choose one single gym for free. Personally, I chose the $25/m program and in total, I get access to over 11k fitness facilities nationwide, which is great for when I travel or go on vacation and still wish to get to the gym. It would cost me hundreds of dollars a month to have the same access. My insurance is certainly not the only one. Some companies may not offer as good as options but are normally still cheaper than going through the gym directly. I know not everyone has health insurance and that’s not a discussion I wish to get into, but for those who do and wish to get a gym membership, definitely check with your provider first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: it is almost always cheaper to go through your insurance company (if they offer memberships) for your gym membership than to go through the gym directly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：牙釉质一旦受损，就无法恢复。然而，被削弱的牙釉质可以通过提高其矿物质含量在一定程度上得到恢复。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：尽管牙膏和漱口水不能 "重建 "牙齿，但它们可以促进再矿化过程。
可以促进这一再矿化过程。

因此，在你注定要过着牙齿敏感的生活之前，请照顾好你的牙齿。
和疼痛。睡觉前刷牙尤其重要。

引用：...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r1e4ey/ysk_once_tooth_enamel_is_damaged_it_cannot_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r1e4ey/ysk_once_tooth_enamel_is_damaged_it_cannot_be/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 21:55:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Although toothpastes and mouthwashes can never “rebuild” teeth, they can contribute to this remineralization process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So take care of your teeth before you&amp;#39;re condemned to a life of sensitive teeth, and pain. It&amp;#39;s especially important to brush before going to bed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Citation: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dhamadison.com/news/can-tooth-enamel-be-restored/&quot;&gt;https://www.dhamadison.com/news/can-tooth-enamel-be-restored/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK你可以在Uber应用程序中使用代码 "savethenightct"，在2022年1月14日之前，在你接下来的30次乘车中减免10美元。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：标题是不言自明的。该代码是为康涅狄格州的居民制定的
康涅狄格州的居民，但对我在德克萨斯州的工作。用这个来节省一些Uber的钱
节日期间，不要酒后驾车!]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r1hvsq/ysk_you_can_use_code_savethenightct_in_the_uber/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r1hvsq/ysk_you_can_use_code_savethenightct_in_the_uber/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 20:53:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Title is self explanatory. The code was made for residents of Connecticut but worked for me in Texas. Use this to save some money on Uber during the holidays, don’t drink and drive!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，美国的平均阅读年龄是13岁，所以当为大众传播写东西时，你应该保持你的语言清晰、简单和明确。]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，首先我需要说几件事。

我不是在挑剔美国，只是Reddit上的大多数人都来自美国。
那里。我来自英国，我们的阅读年龄更低，只有9岁，所以这不是一个
灌篮。

这里有一个很好的链接，它在谈论我的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r20634/ysk_that_the_average_reading_age_in_the_us_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r20634/ysk_that_the_average_reading_age_in_the_us_is/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 18:48:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So firstly I need to say a couple of things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not picking on the US, it&amp;#39;s just the majority of people on Reddit are from there. I&amp;#39;m from the UK and our reading age is lower at 9 years, so it&amp;#39;s not a dunk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s a good link which is talking about my point:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://centerforplainlanguage.org/what-is-readability/#:%7E:text=The%20average%20American%20is%20considered,readability%20level%20of%20age%20nine&quot;&gt;https://centerforplainlanguage.org/what-is-readability/#:~:text=The%20average%20American%20is%20considered,readability%20level%20of%20age%20nine&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Secondly some people try to link reading age to intelligence which just isn&amp;#39;t the case. People with a low reading age can be very intelligent. There are many difficulties that people struggle with that can impair their reading age, but doesn&amp;#39;t affect how intelligent they are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If you want to get your message across to the widest number of people you &lt;em&gt;have&lt;/em&gt; to use simple language, you can&amp;#39;t assume everyone has the same vocabulary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being overtly and overly sesquipedalian can make you seem churlish, and alienate your audience. 😜&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：美国的 "帝国 "体系与其他地方实际使用的帝国体系不同]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国的英制系统，实际上被称为美国习惯系统，在测量体积时与英制系统有关键的区别。
当涉及到测量体积时，与英制系统有很大的不同。一个液体
盎司在英制单位中是28.41毫升，但在美国习惯单位中是29.57毫升。一个
英制品脱是20液体盎司，而美国是16液体盎司。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r1fhc0/ysk_the_american_imperial_system_is_different_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r1fhc0/ysk_the_american_imperial_system_is_different_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 13:50:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US imperial system, actually called the US Customary System, has key differences to the imperial system when it comes to measuring volume. A fluid ounce is 28.41ml in British Imperial but 29.57ml in US Customary units. An imperial pint is 20 fl. oz. compared to 16 fl. oz. in the US and an imperial gallon is 160 fl. oz. compared to 128 fl. oz. in the US. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: there are plenty of places where this is relevant, such as fuel prices and value for money, but in a word, baking. When following online recipes it is easy to mistake one for the other, for example for people in the UK who use both imperial and metric at different times, or for people in Canada where there&amp;#39;s a lot of US imports, and this can lead to irredeemable mistakes with some of the more unforgiving recipes. If you&amp;#39;re following an online recipe try to make sure you know which type of pints/fluid ounces is being used. A dead giveaway for US Customary units is Cups, as Cups are not used in the imperial system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：感恩节周末是一年中醉酒驾驶事故最多的时候。不要酒后驾车。让我们确保每个人都能活着回家。]]></title><description><![CDATA[感恩节周末是一年中最危险的时期之一。
大约有800人在感恩节期间死于全国各地的道路。
假期。

为什么是YSK：许多人星期三晚上开始庆祝感恩节假期
不幸的是，这可能导致一些人喝酒......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r1rvoa/ysk_thanksgiving_weekend_is_the_most_drunken/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r1rvoa/ysk_thanksgiving_weekend_is_the_most_drunken/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 11:51:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thanksgiving weekend is one of the most dangerous periods of the year for driving, About 800 people die on roads across the country on Thanksgiving holiday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Many people start celebrating the Thanksgiving holiday Wednesday night and unfortunately that can lead to a number of people drinking and getting behind the wheel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“A $50 Uber ride is better than a $15,000 DUI,”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are going to be several DUI checkpoints across the country  to help save lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果航空公司给你一个航班积分，而不是为他们取消的航班退款，你可以向美国运输部投诉，试图获得退款。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：由于许多航空公司资金紧张，他们很可能会给你
他们更有可能给你一个航班积分，而不是为他们取消的航班退款。如果你希望
如果你希望退款，你首先必须向航空公司的客户投诉部门提出投诉。
投诉部门。如果他们拒绝了你的请求，那么你就...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r180xt/ysk_if_an_airline_gives_you_a_flight_credit_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r180xt/ysk_if_an_airline_gives_you_a_flight_credit_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 17:47:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: With many airlines strapped for cash, they&amp;#39;ll more than likely give you a flight credit and not a refund for a flight that they cancelled. If you wish for a refund, you&amp;#39;ll first have to file a complaint with the airline&amp;#39;s customer complaint department. If they deny your request, then you&amp;#39;ll want to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.transportation.gov/airconsumer/file-consumer-complaint&quot;&gt;file a complaint with the US Department of Transportation.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason I know this is because I had this happen to me with an airline. They cancelled my flight, and then denied my request for a refund. I gather all my documentation together (original itinerary, flight cancellation, airline rejecting my refund request) and filed a complaint with USDT and had my refund within a few weeks. I can&amp;#39;t guarantee that it will work, but it did for me. The moment the airline saw I had actually filed a complaint, I was escalated to another level of customer support and received my refund.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK光明节于12月6日结束。]]></title><description><![CDATA[光明节在4天后（11月28日）开始，12月6日结束。

为什么是YSK：你可能会被认为是无知的，甚至可能是无礼的（对某些人来说）。
在节日结束2-3周后说 "光明节快乐"，会让人觉得无知甚至无礼。所以尽量避免
在圣诞节时对你的犹太朋友说这句话! 为自己节省时间。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r16b4f/ysk_hanukkah_ends_on_december_6th/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r16b4f/ysk_hanukkah_ends_on_december_6th/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 17:00:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hanukkah begins in 4 days (Nov 28th) and ends on December 6th.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: You can come off as ignorant and maybe even rude (to some people) saying ”Happy Hanukkah” 2-3 weeks after the holiday is over.
So try to avoid saying it to your Jewish friends on Christmas! Save yourself the embarrassment.
Hanukkah, and other Jewish holidays follow the Lunisolar calendar, hence why every year Jewish holidays happen on different dates on the Gregorian calendar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: Adding this because I should have when originally posting! Please don’t act mean to people who mean well to you, and don’t celebrate your holiday! This edit is meant for the people who get butthurt over people wishing them ”Happy Hanukkah” when Hanukkah is over.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你想降低你的有线电视/互联网套餐，但在网上没有看到任何比你已经支付的费用更便宜的捆绑交易，你的有线电视供应商很可能隐藏了你的降级选项，如果你想知道完整的降级选项清单，你需要给他们打电话。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：许多人可能会看他们的 "降级 "选项，在他们的
许多人可能会在他们的有线电视供应商的网站上看到他们的 "降级 "选项，并认为没有必要降级。
因为没有比他们已经得到的更便宜的交易。在现实中
实际上，这只是有线电视供应商的另一种阴暗手段，目的是让你...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r0wkok/ysk_if_youre_trying_to_downgrade_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r0wkok/ysk_if_youre_trying_to_downgrade_your/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 08:47:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Many people will probably look at their &amp;quot;downgrade&amp;quot; options on their cable providers website and think that there&amp;#39;s just no point in downgrading because of the lack of deals cheaper than what they&amp;#39;re already getting. In reality, it&amp;#39;s just another shady tactic by cable providers to keep you on the hook for their insane cable costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I myself had been thinking of cutting the cord and switching to internet only, but noticed that my only internet option that was showing online was a $300/month 3000 Mbps option with literally nothing slower or cheaper even offered. I contacted Comcast and they informed me that I was likely seeing only that option because of my &amp;quot;current plan&amp;quot; and that I&amp;#39;d need to call a certain number to downgrade. Of course that number had a highly trained sales rep who fed me a bunch of crappy bundle offers that didn&amp;#39;t fill my needs at all until I just told her to downgrade to Gigabit internet only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t fall for their crap. Take the extra steps and save the money.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果向你提供的服务通常不接受货币小费，那么Yelp/Google的评论对他们来说几乎同样有利。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：帮助你完成预约的医务人员或帮助你找到商品并帮助你决定购买哪种商品的销售人员。
帮助你找到一件商品并帮助你决定购买哪件商品的销售人员，这些
这些人不遗余力地满足公司的客户满意度要求。
要求，更有可能得到雇主的补偿......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r0ly47/ysk_that_if_the_service_provided_to_you_doesnt/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r0ly47/ysk_that_if_the_service_provided_to_you_doesnt/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 03:42:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: The medical staff that helps you through your appointment or the sales person who helped you find an item and helped you decide which one to buy, these people who go out of their way to meet the company’s customer satisfaction requirements, are more likely to be compensated by the employer with every positive reviews left by you. Most places offer a little incentive for these reviews but many places may increase the employees pay. It looks very well on yearly reviews when someone shows their supervisor that they have “X” amount of positive reviews which result in repeat customer or referrals to most consumers which equals more profit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a second and leave a good review for someone today, it can definitely do more than a few bucks would ever do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK作为一名儿科医生，发放抗生素很容易。]]></title><description><![CDATA[作为一名儿科医生，对我来说，给您的孩子服用抗生素（ABX）是世界上最简单的事情。
抗生素（ABX）治疗可能是病毒性疾病。我每周都有几十个病人
每周都有几十名病人因症状和抱怨而来，他们很可能是病毒性疾病。
疾病。我向家人详细解释了病毒性疾病，但在我看来，这是不可能的。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r0jez6/ysk_as_a_pediatrician_passing_out_antibiotics_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r0jez6/ysk_as_a_pediatrician_passing_out_antibiotics_is/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 19:55:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a Pediatrician, it&amp;#39;s the easiest thing in the world for me to give your child antibiotics (ABX) for what is likely a viral illness. I have dozens of patients each week who come in with symptoms and complaints that are likely a viral illness. I explain in detail viral illnesses to family but in the end, it seems most want antibiotics. I even have patients who will then go to urgent care the next day, usually not seeing a Pediatrician, and will then get ABX or steroids as those places pass it out like candy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can easily give antibiotics. In fact, if I give ABX, I can justify billing at a higher level to insurance (99214 vs a 99213). I not only make more money, but parents leave happier. Is it the right thing to do? Not at all. When I don&amp;#39;t give ABX to a family, not only do I risk parents not being happy and leaving me a poor review, but I then likely will have to dedicate time for phone call follow ups as these families tend to call for ongoing symptoms (need to let the viral illness run its course). I understand it&amp;#39;s tough to take a day off from work and take your kid to the doctor just to be told to continue supportive care, but its the right thing to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So please parents, when I don&amp;#39;t prescribe ABX, I do it truly because I care about your child. I have seen children have horrible Clostridium Difficile infections from ABX. I have seen a young girl with UTIs that are now resistant to almost every oral ABX, and she now requires to be routinely admitted for IV ABX.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Passing out ABX like candy is the easy way out. I don&amp;#39;t do it cause I truly care about the wellbeing of your child.  Ongoing ABX use can potentially have devasting side effects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdc.gov/patientsafety/features/be-antibiotics-aware.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cdc.gov/patientsafety/features/be-antibiotics-aware.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 有一个浏览器扩展，可以让YT上的不喜欢计数器重新出现。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：YouTube最近删除了公众不喜欢的内容。不知道有多大用处。
不知道一个视频的有用性、争议性、良好性或帮助性，感觉就像在没有任何负面评价的情况下试图购买一件物品一样。
没有任何负面评论。这个浏览器扩展允许你找回
不把时间浪费在无用的、无趣的或无用的视频上的便利。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r0i8lk/ysk_theres_a_browser_extension_that_brings_back/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r0i8lk/ysk_theres_a_browser_extension_that_brings_back/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 19:55:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: YouTube recently removed public dislikes. Not knowing how useful, controversial, good, or helpful a video is, feels like trying to buy an item without any negative reviews. This browser extension allows you to get back the convenience of not wasting time on unhelpful, unentertaining, or outdated videos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Anarios/return-youtube-dislike&quot;&gt;https://github.com/Anarios/return-youtube-dislike&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It uses YouTube API to show you the dislike counter.  After Dec 13th YT API would stop providing public dislike count, and the extension would switch to an archive of known videos and an estimate from other users. Join now to make the future estimates more precise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK你可以在网上购买成千上万的蒲公英种子。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么YSK是因为蒲公英是伟大的! 蜜蜂也喜欢它们!

不要让混蛋除草剂公司告诉你! 蒲公英很酷
蒲公英很酷。

而且你可以在网上以低廉的价格买到几十万朵。

你的邻居们也会喜欢它们的！！。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r0faoh/ysk_you_can_buy_thousands_of_dandelion_seeds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r0faoh/ysk_you_can_buy_thousands_of_dandelion_seeds/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 16:39:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK is because dandelions are great! And bees love em!    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t let asshole herbicide companies tell you otherwise! Dandelions are cool af.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And you can buy them by the THOUSANDS online for cheap.    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And your neighbours will love them too!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你的大量邮件被追踪了]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：从你打开它们的时间，到你打开它们的次数，有很多
很多邮件都带有追踪器，当你打开它们时，会通知发件人。
发件人也可以访问一个仪表板，向他们显示你查看电子邮件习惯的具体情况。
你查看电子邮件的习惯。

你可以做什么：有...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r0f5zq/ysk_a_large_number_of_your_emails_are_tracked/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r0f5zq/ysk_a_large_number_of_your_emails_are_tracked/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 16:39:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: From what time you opened them, to how many times you opened them, a lot of emails are sent with trackers that notify the sender when you open them. The sender can also have access to a dashboard that shows them the specifics of your email viewing habits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What you can do about it: there&amp;#39;s several chrome extensions, for instance, that show a symbol next to an email&amp;#39;s title that pops up if the email is being tracked. Ugly Emails for chrome is what I use. Its just another example of how your privacy is being breached and also if you&amp;#39;ve ever noticed a boss or coworker seems particularly aware that you haven&amp;#39;t responded to an email, this could be why.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如何去除自己身上的酒味。]]></title><description><![CDATA[不确定这个人是否适合这个子，但我希望它是有用的。

YSK: 柑橘类水果，尤其是橙子，可以掩盖（不是完全掩盖，而是相当好地掩盖）你胸前的酒精气味。
从你的呼吸中隐藏酒精的味道。水会让它变得更糟糕。

为什么是YSK：有没有在一夜狂欢/安静的自我反思中醒来，发现自己浑身发臭？
仿佛...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qzq4n7/ysk_how_to_remove_the_smell_of_alcohol_from/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qzq4n7/ysk_how_to_remove_the_smell_of_alcohol_from/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 01:12:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not sure how well this one fits the sub but i hope it&amp;#39;s useful;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;YSK: Citrus fruits, especially orange, hide(not completely but pretty well) the smell of alcohol from your breath. WATER makes it much, much worse. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Ever woken up from a night of partying/quiet self reflection stinking as if vodka factory exploded in your mouth? And had to go to work/meet people and do things? Have a few orange slices and a bit of lemon. And keep an orange nearby so you can refresh yourself. It wont completely mask it, but as long as nobody is deep in your face you&amp;#39;re fine and could even make an impression of eathing healthy. Drinking water amplifies the alcohol stink so don&amp;#39;t. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It does not, however, reduce alcohol fumes during tests. Do NOT drink and drive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，在离职前向雇主发出两周的通知，在任何州都不是法律要求。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK。几乎所有州的雇主和雇员都受到一套被称为 "随意工作 "的法律的约束。
被称为 "随意工作 "的法律。这意味着，雇主不仅可以以任何理由或无理由解雇你
任何理由或无理由解雇你，工人也可以以任何理由或无理由辞职。
原因而辞职。在这两种情况下都没有时间上的要求，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qzszth/ysk_that_giving_two_weeks_notice_to_your_employer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qzszth/ysk_that_giving_two_weeks_notice_to_your_employer/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 20:42:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK&lt;/strong&gt;. Employers and employees in almost all states are governed by a set of laws known as &amp;quot;work at will.&amp;quot; This means that not only can employers fire you for (almost) any reason or no reason, workers can quit for any reason or no reason. There is no time requirement imposed in either situation, not is there a manner of quitting you must abide by. An employer may request (or claim it is a demand) you follow certain steps, such as a two-weeks notice or partaking in an exit-interview, but these are requests and not. legal requirements. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this general rule is true, there are some exceptions. If you have an employment contract, or are working under a collective bargaining agreement, you may be subject to rules that other work at will workers are not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，很多公司认为每一个人力资源都是可以替换的，并且有积极的计划，每年淘汰他们的非盈利性的最高收入者。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：因为你可能申请的非常高薪的非执行公司职位
你所申请的非执行职务实际上可能会缩短你的任期。在这样的公司里，人力资源部门
组建了一份最高收入者的名单，他们就会靠近大门。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qzjpit/ysk_that_a_lot_of_corporations_believe_each_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qzjpit/ysk_that_a_lot_of_corporations_believe_each_and/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 13:39:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Because the very high paying non-executive corporate position you may be applying for may in fact be shortening your tenure. In such companies HR assembles a list of highest earners and they get near the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：烘烤时，你应该用勺子把面粉舀到量杯里，然后用刀削平（而不是直接用量杯舀面粉）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：如果你直接用量杯舀面粉，面粉会
如果你直接用量杯舀面粉，面粉就会过于紧实，从而导致烘烤食品的密度过大。你可以通过以下方式防止这种情况
你可以用勺子把面粉从袋子里舀到你的量杯里，然后用刀子把它弄平。
刀削平。

我直到最近才知道这一点，现在我明白了...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qyne43/ysk_when_baking_you_should_spoon_flour_into_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qyne43/ysk_when_baking_you_should_spoon_flour_into_a/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 13:22:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: if you scoop flour with your measuring cup directly, the flour will be too compacted and thus result in dense baked goods. You can prevent this by spooning the flour from the bag into your measuring cup, then leveling off with a knife. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t know this until recently and now I understand why my baked goods seemed too dense despite me following the recipe instructions exactly. I learned this and tried the same recipes over again and they came out perfectly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你仍然可以使用FreeTube和NewPipe等开源项目查看YouTube视频的不喜欢。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK？因为像其他人一样，我也讨厌在不知道喜欢与不喜欢的比例的情况下点击一个视频
在不知道喜欢与不喜欢的比例的情况下点击一个视频，并把时间浪费在点击式视频上。但是
还有希望，开放的开源项目，如Freetube [https://freetubeapp.io]
和Newpipe [https://newpipe.net] 仍然显示不喜欢的视频....]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qzfvzx/ysk_you_can_still_view_dislike_on_youtube_videos/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qzfvzx/ysk_you_can_still_view_dislike_on_youtube_videos/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 11:39:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK? Because like everyone else I too hate to click on a video without knowing the like to dislike ratio and watse my time on clickbait videos. But there is hope open open source projects like &lt;a href=&quot;https://freetubeapp.io&quot;&gt;Freetube&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://newpipe.net&quot;&gt;Newpipe&lt;/a&gt; still shows dislike on videos. While you can&amp;#39;t like, dislike, or comment on videos you can freely watch any videos without being tracked by YouTube app or Google. On behalf of the open source community I highly recommend you download both freetube and newpipe and support the projects anyone way you can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK不要从零售店购买VISA礼品卡。盗贼有可能已经偷走了卡片。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我最近犯了一个错误，买了一张VISA礼品卡，并把它作为一个
生日礼物。买卡后不到一周，它就已经被完全用完了。
完全用完了，尽管它甚至还没有从包装中取出。

小偷会在卡在店里的时候刷掉卡上的信息，等...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qyzy8f/ysk_dont_buy_visa_gift_cards_from_retail_stores/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qyzy8f/ysk_dont_buy_visa_gift_cards_from_retail_stores/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 11:26:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I recently made the mistake of buying a VISA gift card and giving it as a birthday gift. Not 1 week after the card was purchased and it was already completely used up, even though it hadn’t even been removed from the packaging. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thieves will swipe the info from the card while it’s in the store, wait for you to purchase and activate it, then use the balance on the card. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s also a huge pain trying to dispute the transaction, and it would have been way easier just to give this person $100 bill rather than a gift card. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; So that you don’t make the same mistake and have your birthday gift stolen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>