<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 06:37:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如果你是個菸民，非菸民也不想在你抽菸的時候和你一起被困在家裏或車裏，但我們太客氣了，當着你的面告訴你這些]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：很多次我和他們一起在朋友家或者車上，而。
他們吸菸的香菸，它是誠實的最糟糕的事情，它讓我不。
想跟那些人混在一起，或者去他們的家裏，根本。那種
事情可能會影響你的友誼，你可能甚至不知道... ...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mhgxvi/ysk_if_youre_a_smoker_nonsmokers_dont_want_to_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mhgxvi/ysk_if_youre_a_smoker_nonsmokers_dont_want_to_be/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 23:48:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: so many times I&amp;#39;ve been in friends houses or cars with them while they&amp;#39;re smoking cigarettes and it&amp;#39;s honestly the worst thing, it makes me not want to hang out with those people or go to their houses at all. That kind of thing could be affecting your friendships and you may not even know it. Most people don&amp;#39;t want to tell you that your smoking is grossing them out because they don&amp;#39;t want to offend you or cause a fuss. I&amp;#39;d rather come outside and stand with you outside while you&amp;#39;re smoking than have you light one up indoors with me in the room. Sure it&amp;#39;s your house, but don&amp;#39;t be surprised if no one wants to come over if you smoke indoors around other people, it should be common courtesy not to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK理查德-朱厄爾可以說是一個被媒體和政府詆譭的英雄，他們需要一個反派。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：重要的是要記住，我們不能急於判斷與。
人，必須聰明客觀。理查德-朱厄爾是一個英雄，他的生命是
毀於不負責任的報道和政府的
官員們需要 "速勝 "來讓人們接受... ...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mh65fn/ysk_richard_jewell_was_arguably_a_hero_who_was/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mh65fn/ysk_richard_jewell_was_arguably_a_hero_who_was/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 21:27:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: it is important to remember that we can not rush to judgement with people and must be smart and objective. Richard Jewell was a hero whose life was ultimately ruined by a combination of irresponsible reporting and government officials needing a &amp;quot;quick win&amp;quot; to get people comfortable with returning to the 1996 Olympics. Due to the FBI being so focused on Richard Jewell the real culprit was able to continue to wreak havoc in Atlanta &amp;amp; Birmingham.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Richard tragically died at a young age, but if it was not for him having an unbelievable amount of courage to keep fighting and not give up that his name was ultimately cleared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to learn more the film by Clint Eastwood &amp;quot;Richard Jewell&amp;quot; and the Netflix series &amp;quot;Manhunt: Deadly Games&amp;quot; are great sources. The article that inspired the Clint Eastwood movie &amp;quot;American Nightmare: The Ballad of Richard Jewell&amp;quot; &lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.vanityfair.com/article/share/1fd2d7ae-10d8-474b-9bf1-d1558af697be&quot;&gt;https://archive.vanityfair.com/article/share/1fd2d7ae-10d8-474b-9bf1-d1558af697be&lt;/a&gt; is a fantastic read.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also the 60 Minutes interview with Mike Wallace was the first time America saw that Richard Jewell really was innocent, and provided an objective look at the evidence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qbx50Gsi9g0&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qbx50Gsi9g0&lt;/a&gt; (original 1996 interview)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hJiottNlPIY&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hJiottNlPIY&lt;/a&gt; (5 year follow up)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We should be teaching children that he was a hero who saved countless lives that night. He may not have been perfect, but none of us are. He was just an every day man who did the right thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如何免費獲得科研論文。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：科學期刊向你收取35美元的論文閱讀費，100%用於閱讀論文。
給出版商，0%給作者。

如果你只是給作者發郵件詢問他們的論文，他們是可以發
他們免費提供給你，並將真正高興地這樣做。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mh093h/ysk_how_to_get_scientific_research_papers_for_free/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mh093h/ysk_how_to_get_scientific_research_papers_for_free/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 13:03:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  The $35 that scientific journals charge you to read a paper goes 100% to the publisher, 0% to the authors. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you just email the authors to ask for their papers, they are allowed to send them to you for free and will be genuinely delighted to do so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK說，在養育孩子的過程中，如何和孩子說話很重要--它會改變他們的大腦。對着孩子說話或對着孩子說話，即使你讓他們接觸到很多詞彙，也不如與孩子進行引人入勝的對話重要，最好是由孩子來主導。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼YSK：家長應該知道這一點，因爲存在着廣泛的誤解。
關於父母教育/收入水平與兒童大腦和
語言發展。即收入較高的父母教給孩子更多的是
詞，然後導致更好的大腦語言... ...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mgwzwi/ysk_that_in_parenting_how_you_talk_to_your_child/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mgwzwi/ysk_that_in_parenting_how_you_talk_to_your_child/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 06:32:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Parents should know this because there is a widespread misunderstanding about the connection between parental education/income level and child brain and language development. Namely, that higher income parents teach their kids &lt;em&gt;more words,&lt;/em&gt; and this then leads to better brain language development. Knowing about this misconception is important for many reasons, perhaps the most important being that the science-backed solution to helping grow your child’s brain development in this area is actually very simple and doable for &lt;em&gt;any parent, regardless of socioeconomic or educational background.&lt;/em&gt; It has nothing to do with dumping fancy words at your kids.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d safely assume that most parents know that talking - and teaching verbal communication - to their children from a young age is vital. But, there is a widespread misconception that parental income or education correlates to a child’s ability to develop strongly in this area. Notably, since research has shown that, on average, children from higher-income families hear millions &lt;em&gt;more words&lt;/em&gt; during their first three years of life, somehow that means that such children are set up for better brain development than children from lower-income families. &lt;strong&gt;This actually isn’t true.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1995, a research study came out that found that children from higher-income families hear about &lt;strong&gt;30 million more words&lt;/strong&gt; during their first three years of life than children from lower-income families.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So was coined the phenomenon of the “&lt;strong&gt;30-million-word-gap&lt;/strong&gt;”, at the time correlated with significant gaps in tests of vocabulary, language development, and reading comp skills of kids from lower vs higher income families as they matured. People ran with this idea. Claiming essentially that kids from higher income families, who on average heard and were taught so many more words, were somehow set up as they got older to have a more &amp;quot;highly developed&amp;quot; brain in terms of language capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More recent science has debunked this correlation, pointing to a very different reality. MIT cognitive scientists have now discovered that &lt;em&gt;it is not the number of words&lt;/em&gt; a parent says &lt;strong&gt;to&lt;/strong&gt; their child that can change their brain (for the better), but instead &lt;em&gt;the nature of open-ended conversation&lt;/em&gt; a parent encourages &lt;strong&gt;with&lt;/strong&gt; their child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Creating lots of opportunity for this kind of open-ended, back-and-forth conversation is actually more critical to brain and language development than the findings of the &amp;quot;word gap&amp;quot;.&lt;/strong&gt; This research from MIT applied to children &lt;em&gt;regardless of parental income&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;or education.&lt;/em&gt; The finding suggests that &lt;em&gt;any&lt;/em&gt; parent can have considerable influence over their child&amp;#39;s language and brain development by simply engaging them in daily conversation where the child has space to drive the conversation and create conversation turns as they please. Encouraging turn-taking conversation, as opposed to one-sided conversation, can be implemented by any parent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key finding from the aforementioned research is that parents should understand they should not just &lt;em&gt;talk to&lt;/em&gt; their child, but instead should consistently &lt;em&gt;talk with&lt;/em&gt; their child. Being interactive is what matters. Creating time and space for casual, story-oriented familial conversation, where there is less talking at or to your child by the parent and more talking with and listening to your child, changes children’s brains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe using excessive flashcards and talking at our children with many words, probably just frustrating or confusing them, should be a thing of the past. Maybe the solution is really as simple as focusing on fun conversation that genuinely encourages children to participate. Not just listen and memorize.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MIT study: &lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/0956797617742725&quot;&gt;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/0956797617742725&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1995 Word Gap study: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aft.org/sites/default/files/periodicals/TheEarlyCatastrophe.pdf&quot;&gt;https://www.aft.org/sites/default/files/periodicals/TheEarlyCatastrophe.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[送餐App上的YSK "漢堡店 "和 "融化 "是變相的 "Dennys"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼YSK - "Dennys "將部分菜單重新列出，實際上是 "漢堡"。
Den "的漢堡和 "Melt Down "的三明治，騙你點菜。
"Dennys"，萬一你以爲你在嘗試新的東西或者支持新的東西，你就會覺得很奇怪。
的業務。

可以確認質量還是 "丹尼斯 "的質量。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mgtuci/ysk_burger_den_and_melt_down_on_food_delivery/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mgtuci/ysk_burger_den_and_melt_down_on_food_delivery/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 03:12:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK - &amp;quot;Dennys&amp;quot; is re-listing portions of thier menu virtually as &amp;quot;Burger Den&amp;quot; for burgers and &amp;quot;Melt Down&amp;quot; for sandwiches to trick you into ordering &amp;quot;Dennys&amp;quot; in case you thought you were trying something new or supporting a new business. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can confirm the quality is still &amp;quot;Dennys&amp;quot; quality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如果你是大學生，一定要在畢業/離校前設置好學生郵箱，轉發到個人郵箱。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：因爲在很多情況下，你將無法訪問該學校的郵箱
或會忘記查看，但你會經常收到電子郵件到它
在你離開學校很久之後，從學校。

有時這些郵件非常重要（例如："你其實欠我們的。"其實你欠我們的
更多的學費，如果你不... ...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mgikth/ysk_if_youre_a_college_student_make_sure_you_set/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mgikth/ysk_if_youre_a_college_student_make_sure_you_set/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 19:58:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: because in many cases you won’t have access to that school email anymore or will just forget to check it but you’ll often receive emails to it from the school long after you’ve left. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And sometimes these emails are VERY important (example: “you actually owe us more tuition and if you don’t pay we’re sending it to collections”) and the school can hide behind “we informed you” because they sent it to your student email account. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully forwarding your email will just let you find out about alumni events or other benign emails that you would have missed otherwise, but if there is something important / dubious like above example, you won’t miss it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 有些人是暗中的虐待、操縱和控制。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：學會識別行爲的技巧和模式將是一個很好的選擇。
幫助您保護自己，更好地支持遭受痛苦的朋友或家人。
心理或情感虐待。已經造成了大量的傷害。
做，如果你要學習這個困難的方式。

濫用權力和...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mg2jgk/ysk_some_people_are_covertly_abusive_manipulative/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mg2jgk/ysk_some_people_are_covertly_abusive_manipulative/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 01:12:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: learning to recognise the techniques and patterns of behaviour will help you protect yourself and better support friends or family suffering psychological or emotional abuse. A significant amount of harm has already been done if you have to learn this the hard way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Abusive_power_and_control&quot;&gt;Abusive power and control&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.verywellmind.com/identify-and-cope-with-emotional-abuse-4156673&quot;&gt;What is emotional abuse?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 有一個叫haveibeenpwned的網站，它可以監控所有的數據泄露，讓你有機會發現你的數據是否已經丟失或被盜。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK，很多人都不知道哪些公司泄露或丟失了你的。
個人數據，包括電子郵件地址和密碼。這樣，您可以檢查是否
您的數據已經泄露，所以如果您使用這些密碼，您可以更改密碼。
在其他網站上結合該郵箱地址。它不會...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mfk5da/ysk_there_is_a_website_called_haveibeenpwned/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mfk5da/ysk_there_is_a_website_called_haveibeenpwned/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 13:22:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK, lots of people don&amp;#39;t know what companies have leaked or lost your personal data, including email-address and passwords. This way you can check if your data has been leaked so you can change passwords if you use those passwords on other sites in combination with that email-address. It won&amp;#39;t stop databreaches, but at least you know that it happened to your data. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://haveibeenpwned.com/&quot;&gt;https://haveibeenpwned.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 當一個人從自己的生活中剔除某人時，這通常是他們所做的最後努力。通常他們在把他們從生活中剔除之前，會先做其他的事情。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：每個人的背景都不一樣。

有時候，如果你來自一個良好的家庭，你不能理解爲什麼有人會
切出一個親戚。"等他們走了，你會後悔的！" 是一個很常見的
句，對於不懂的人來說。

它可能源於不同品種的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mfguip/ysk_when_a_person_cuts_out_someone_from_their/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mfguip/ysk_when_a_person_cuts_out_someone_from_their/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 07:51:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Everyone comes from a different background. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes if you come from a good family, you can&amp;#39;t understand why someone might cut out a relative. &amp;quot;You&amp;#39;ll regret it when they&amp;#39;re gone!&amp;quot; Is a pretty common sentence, for people who don&amp;#39;t understand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It could stem from different variety of abuse, narcissism, parentification, not respecting boundaries, etc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just respect the person and don&amp;#39;t try to guilt them into contacting their relative, if they have cut them out. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/narcissistic-personality-disorder/symptoms-causes/syc-20366662&quot;&gt;https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/narcissistic-personality-disorder/symptoms-causes/syc-20366662&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.verywellmind.com/how-to-recognize-a-narcissist-4164528&quot;&gt;https://www.verywellmind.com/how-to-recognize-a-narcissist-4164528&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://wingsprogram.com/what-is-domestic-violence-blog/&quot;&gt;https://wingsprogram.com/what-is-domestic-violence-blog/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/living-emotional-intensity/201912/did-you-have-grow-too-soon&quot;&gt;https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/living-emotional-intensity/201912/did-you-have-grow-too-soon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.newportacademy.com/resources/mental-health/parentification/&quot;&gt;https://www.newportacademy.com/resources/mental-health/parentification/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://psychcentral.com/blog/how-to-respect-other-peoples-boundaries&quot;&gt;https://psychcentral.com/blog/how-to-respect-other-peoples-boundaries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://livewellwithsharonmartin.com/set-boundaries-toxic-people/&quot;&gt;https://livewellwithsharonmartin.com/set-boundaries-toxic-people/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你媽媽說的對。整天盯着屏幕是很不健康的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[是的，那些坐在電視或電腦前的甜蜜時光。無視我們父母的
呼籲外出。20年後，我在醫學研究團隊工作，爲
pupillary.org[https://pupillary.org/]，並閱讀了很多這方面的論文。
主題行爲。而且，哦，孩子，他們是對的。這裏有幾個小... Here're just a few small...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/meyjbn/ysk_your_mom_was_right_staring_at_a_screen_all/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/meyjbn/ysk_your_mom_was_right_staring_at_a_screen_all/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:25:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes, those sweet times sitting in front of our TV or PC. Ignoring our parent&amp;#39;s calls to go outside. 20 years later I work on the medical research team for &lt;a href=&quot;https://pupillary.org/&quot;&gt;pupillary.org&lt;/a&gt; and read a lot of papers on this topicbehavioral. And, oh, boy,  were they right. Here&amp;#39;re just a few small quotes out of a lot of studies:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot; One-quarter of the students studied experienced physical complaints, and one-fifth had behavioural problems associated with the use of electronic devices“ (S L Ting et al, 2020)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot; The magnitude of arteriolar narrowing associated with each hour daily of  TV viewing is similar to that associated with a 10-mm Hg increase in  systolic blood pressure in children.&amp;quot; ( Bamini Gopinath et al 2011 )&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;longer screen time (≥2 h/day) was associated with lower levels of satisfaction with life and optimism, and higher levels of anxiety and depressive symptoms; shorter screen time (&amp;lt;2 h/day) was associated with favorable mental health and wellbeing&amp;quot; (Eva Oberle et al, 2020)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：抑鬱症的症狀就是把人推開。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：幫助阻止朋友的抑鬱症變得更加嚴重。

如果你有一個朋友可能有抑鬱症，他們很自然地會忽略短信
並取消計劃。黃金法則是永遠不要把它個人化。繼續
嘗試。現在不是失去朋友的時候。生氣或想'好吧，他媽的... ...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mf3vjt/ysk_a_symptom_of_depression_is_pushing_people_away/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mf3vjt/ysk_a_symptom_of_depression_is_pushing_people_away/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 18:52:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: To help stop a friend’s depression becoming even worse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a friend who may be depressed, it’s natural for them to ignore texts and cancel plans. The golden rule is to never take it personally. Keep on trying. It’s no time to lose friends. Getting angry or thinking ‘well fuck them if they’re not making an effort’, is only helping the depression win. They’re not pushing you away, their depression is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：拿自殺開玩笑，是病情危機點的表現。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：這很少是一個笑話這是一個信號，有人在伸手要。
幫忙，他們不一定想死，但可能看不到出路，而且是。
尋求幫助，但由於所有與精神疾病相關的恥辱感，它可以
很難出來說到底是怎麼回事。

這很重要...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mf001z/ysk_joking_about_suicide_is_a_sign_of_a_crisis/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mf001z/ysk_joking_about_suicide_is_a_sign_of_a_crisis/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 15:52:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: it&amp;#39;s rarely a joke this is a sign that someone is reaching out for help, they don&amp;#39;t necessarily want to die but may not see a way out and are looking for help but with all the stigma associated with mental illness it can be hard to come out and say exactly what&amp;#39;s going on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s important to remember that some who is considering suicide likely has a medical condition which affects their thinking processes so someone should not be dismissed or told to get over it (they would if they could) -- it would be equivalent to telling someone with a broken arm that there was nothing wrong with them. (Note how I phrase it as a medical condition instead of mental illness specifically to remove a sense of judgement)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What can you do? Ask them straight whether they are considering suicide and if they are find out if there are family or friends they would feel comfortable knowing and able to call if they feel suicidal. They may not feel comfortable reaching out to family or friends and that&amp;#39;s okay. Instead or as well as that there are divided prevention hotlines in most countries who will help.
Ultimately you want to speak calmly with them and see if they will agree to contact a trusted family member or friend or a suicide prevention number before enacting any plans to die by suicide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t worry, you won&amp;#39;t make someone consider suicide by asking them about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may not be comfortable having this conversation, suicide prevention websites and numbers can often advise on how to have this conversation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also if you notice someone on Reddit with these signs, use the report option and select other and select &amp;#39;someone is considering suicide&amp;#39;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other warning signs: giving things away, seeming hopelessness and despair, seeming flat in mood, drastic changes in weight and apparent signs of insomnia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Source: I am a mental health first aider, see also &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.beyondblue.org.au/the-facts/suicide-prevention/feeling-suicidal/suicidal-warning-signs&quot;&gt;https://www.beyondblue.org.au/the-facts/suicide-prevention/feeling-suicidal/suicidal-warning-signs&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.choc.org/articles/9-signs-your-child-may-be-considering-suicide/&quot;&gt;https://www.choc.org/articles/9-signs-your-child-may-be-considering-suicide/&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also YSK: helping other people through this kind of situation can be draining on ourselves as supports, be sure to be kind to yourself and take time to recharge, you too matter and are important&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay safe&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：友誼是五五開的關係。我們理解抑鬱症和現實生活中的問題是一個東西，但如果一個人做了所有的連接，並被鬼迷心竅，請聯繫他們。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：沒有人喜歡被鬼纏身。雖然我能理解你爲什麼會這樣
諷刺的是，不和他們說話會讓你感到內疚 Feeling guilty about not talking to them can eat at you, ironically enough,
讓你不想聯繫他們。但是，你要麼需要結束友誼
和平地或多做努力。即使你所做的只是發短信和...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/meoks1/ysk_friendship_is_a_5050_relationship_we/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/meoks1/ysk_friendship_is_a_5050_relationship_we/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 05:04:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: No one likes being ghosted. Though I can understand why you might. Feeling guilty about not talking to them can eat at you, ironically enough, making you not want to contact them. But you either need to end the friendship peacefully or make more of an effort. Even if all you do is text and say: &amp;quot;Sorry, I haven&amp;#39;t been talking to you lately, I just haven&amp;#39;t felt myself&amp;quot; Or something similar. Otherwise, the person that is always the one to try and get in contact with you, might feel like they aren&amp;#39;t appreciated/feeling used, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 把土豆和洋蔥放在一起會讓土豆變質得更快。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼 YSK: 我最近才知道洋蔥會產生一種氣體，讓你的身體變得更健康。
土豆長出眼睛，變壞得更快。我必須得到一個新的袋子，每2周。
之前我把它們搬走了，現在它們位於其他地方，我將在一個多月內。
和半，他們仍然是罰款。不要浪費你的土豆，... ...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mejddq/ysk_storing_your_potatoes_next_to_your_onions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mejddq/ysk_storing_your_potatoes_next_to_your_onions/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 20:57:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I just recently learned that onions produce a gas that makes your potatoes sprout eyes and go bad much faster.  I had to get a new bag ever 2 weeks before I moved them, now that they are located elsewhere I&amp;#39;m going over a month and a half and they are still fine.  Don&amp;#39;t waste your potatoes, locate them away from your onions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK說，聯邦貿易委員會有一個網頁，可以舉報通過電子郵件、電話和短信收到的欺詐和詐騙招攬。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：它可以幫助他們跟蹤詐騙和欺詐趨勢，幫助他們更好地瞭解自己的行爲。
讓公衆做好準備，以防止欺詐性的招攬，以及
在某些情況下幫助受害者拿回損失的錢。

如果你是詐騙的受害者，並丟失了錢，你一定要報告的任何
你的信息...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/meg435/ysk_that_the_ftc_has_a_webpage_to_report_fraud/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/meg435/ysk_that_the_ftc_has_a_webpage_to_report_fraud/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 18:46:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: it assists them in tracking scam and fraud trends, aids in better preparing the public to protect themselves against fraudulent solicitations, and in some cases helps victims get lost money back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re a victim of fraud and lost money, you should definitely report any information you have and the amount of money lost. This increase the chance you can recover what is lost (though it isn’t guaranteed).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve all received fake emails and phone calls and text messages. Some of us know how to recognize a scam, or are knowledgeable enough to know how these guys try to get your information. Unfortunately, a lot of people still lose hundreds, if not thousands, of dollars to scamming activities. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you receive communication from a scammer, you can report them and it will be sent to several law enforcement agencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://reportfraud.ftc.gov/#/&quot;&gt;FTC Report Fraud/Scam&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: didn’t want to sound like I was calling to arms!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，你的音樂品味可能會隨着你生活環境的改變而發生根本性的變化。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：通常情況下，人們會聽特定類型的音樂來彌補。
某種感覺。比如我就喜歡聽拉丁節奏和海珊蒂的歌。
在我患抑鬱症的幾個月裏，因爲那些音樂是
非常振奮人心，幫助我忘記了每天的辛苦... ...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mednvq/ysk_that_your_music_taste_may_change/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mednvq/ysk_that_your_music_taste_may_change/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 18:09:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Often times, people listen to a specific type of music to compensate certain feelings. Me for example liked to listen to latin beats and sea shantys during months when I suffered from depression because those kinds of music were very uplifting and helped me forget the grueling everyday life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After getting rid the causes of my depression and helping myself improve, I lost all interest in sea shantys and latin music. I still sometimes listen to the music from back them, but usually only when I feel sad and need distraction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：去掉 "所以 "和 "非常 "這兩個形容詞修飾詞，可以擴大和提高你的詞彙量和寫作水平。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK："所以"、"很 "等詞都是強化詞，並不帶有任何真實的
的含義或進一步的描述。

"非常熱 "的東西可以是任何東西，從炎熱的天氣到中心的溫度。
地球，所以要具體的說出你的意思! 與 "非常熱 "相比，可以試試
"煮"，"燒"，"烤"，或... ...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mdxlzh/ysk_eliminating_the_words_so_and_very_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mdxlzh/ysk_eliminating_the_words_so_and_very_as/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 13:53:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Words like &amp;quot;so&amp;quot;  and &amp;quot;very&amp;quot; are intensifiers and don&amp;#39;t carry any real meaning or further description.    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Something &amp;quot;very hot&amp;quot; could be anything from a hot day to the center of the Earth, so be specific to say what you mean! Instead of &amp;quot;very hot&amp;quot;,  try &amp;quot;boiling&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;searing&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;baking&amp;quot;, or &amp;quot;molten&amp;quot;. Each ones evokes a very &lt;em&gt;specific&lt;/em&gt; type of heat, making your  making your writing more concise, erudite and powerful.    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A character shouldn&amp;#39;t be &amp;quot;very happy&amp;quot;. They should be ecstatic! &amp;quot;Very sad&amp;quot;? Nope! Try &amp;quot;depressed&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;despondent&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;grief-stricken&amp;quot; instead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，你是值得愛的，你現在的樣子已經足夠了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：因爲很容易忘記這一點，沒有外部驗證會
彌補自愛的缺失，不管你認爲自己犯了什麼錯誤
你是美麗的，美好的，我愛你。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/md6g9a/ysk_that_youre_worthy_of_love_and_who_you_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/md6g9a/ysk_that_youre_worthy_of_love_and_who_you_are/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 13:40:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: because it is easy to forget this, no external validation will compensate for a lack of self-love, and no matter what mistakes you think you’ve made you are beautiful and wonderful and I love you&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK關於doesthedogdie.com--你可以查找書籍、電影等，它會告訴你是否有不愉快的場景，而不會破壞情節。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: 有些場景可能會讓人痛苦，特別是對於有創傷後應激障礙的人或者是那些有創傷後應激障礙的人。
遭受了損失。上網搜索小說作品是一個很好的方法，可以有
壞了。本站爲小說作品列出了觸發警告的名單，並不會
破壞任何東西。

https://www.doesthedogdie.com

該網站跟蹤...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mdx4az/ysk_about_doesthedogdiecom_you_can_look_up_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mdx4az/ysk_about_doesthedogdiecom_you_can_look_up_books/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 21:54:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Some scenes can be distressing, especially for people with PTSD or who have suffered a loss. Googling a work of fiction is a good way to have it spoiled. This site has a list of trigger warnings for works of fiction and won&amp;#39;t spoil anything. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.doesthedogdie.com&quot;&gt;https://www.doesthedogdie.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The site tracks 70+ categories like slurs, car crashes, dogs dying, spiders and cancer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK只說 "有一個大驚喜/震撼的結局"，不管是否告訴細節，都已經是SPOILER了。如果你向別人推薦一部電影/電視劇/遊戲/書籍等，請不要這樣做!]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：因爲雖然你想通過提高他們的關注度來吸引他們的注意力
他們的期望，你會毀了他們的經驗。當一些白癡告訴我 "你
會愛上它，你一定猜不到大轉折的結局 "我立刻發現自己
想着結局，而不是專注於當下和... ...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mdj0ml/ysk_just_saying_there_is_a_big_surprize_shocking/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mdj0ml/ysk_just_saying_there_is_a_big_surprize_shocking/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 11:25:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Because although you want to attract their attention by increasing their expectations, you&amp;#39;ll ruin their experience. When some idiot tells me &amp;quot;you will love it, you will not guess the big twist ending&amp;quot; I immediately find myself thinking about the finale instead of focusing the moment and enjoying it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK不喜歡任何類型的音樂都沒關係。3-5%的人無法從中體會到情感。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：許多患有這種情況的人覺得自己永遠被排除在外，因爲他們是一個很好的例子。
不能涉及到有一個最喜歡的歌曲或播放列表爲一個特定的心情。I
認爲重要的是，這些人知道它的好。

這種情況被稱爲特定的音樂焦慮症。 它影響的任何地方從...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mcrnc0/ysk_its_okay_not_to_like_any_kind_of_music_35_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mcrnc0/ysk_its_okay_not_to_like_any_kind_of_music_35_of/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 07:31:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: many people with this condition feel permanently left out because they can&amp;#39;t relate to having a favorite song or a playlist for a particular mood. I think it&amp;#39;s important for these people to know that it&amp;#39;s okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The condition is called specific musical anhedonia. it affects anywhere from 3 to 5% of people, about as common as color blindness, yet hardly anyone has ever heard of this condition in the vast majority of people who have it don&amp;#39;t know that they do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s a neurological syndrome that can occur either through genetics or as a side effect from brain injury. Through some means or another, the part of the brain associated with music comprehension is not properly connected to the part of the brain associated with reward and pleasure. Most often this occurs in the form of an issue with someone&amp;#39;s dopaminergic system, often defective D2 and D3 receptors or interrupted dopamine pathways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The result is a person who doesn&amp;#39;t have any emotional response to music. As you can imagine, it&amp;#39;s sometimes very difficult for this kind of person to fit in with the rest of society, especially considering that despite every culture&amp;#39;s differing religions, laws, traditions and languages, all cultures share music, and this is something that these people just can&amp;#39;t relate to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I always felt left out and as though I were missing something as a kid, before I knew what I had and came to terms with it. Loud noises in the background of someone throwing their voice around while they repetitively recite a crappy poem is weird anyways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can read more here:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Musical_anhedonia&quot;&gt;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Musical_anhedonia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pnas.org/content/113/46/E7337&quot;&gt;https://www.pnas.org/content/113/46/E7337&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 從4/24開始，988是美國全國預防自殺熱線電話。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼YSK：自殺熱線現在更容易記住（類似於911），這
意味着人們在需要的時候會更容易獲得。

我是怎麼知道的 從字面上看，得到這個消息5分鐘前。

> T -Mobile， 聯邦通信委員會已經採用了988作爲一個3位數的號碼 在全國範圍內使用，以
>達到國家...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/md2q9i/ysk_starting_424_988_is_the_us_national_suicide/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/md2q9i/ysk_starting_424_988_is_the_us_national_suicide/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 21:25:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: the suicide hotline is now easier to remember (similar to 911), which means it will be easier for people to access when they need it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How I know. Literally got this message 5 minutes ago:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;T-Mobile: The FCC has adopted 988 as a 3-digit number to be used nationwide to reach the National Suicide Prevention &amp;amp; Mental Health Crisis Lifeline. Eff 4/24/21 impacted area codes will permit 10-digit dialing. See &lt;a href=&quot;https://t-mo.co/T988&quot;&gt;https://t-mo.co/T988&lt;/a&gt; for more info.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK你的車側後視鏡可能沒有設置正確!]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：它能讓你免於意外!

你的汽車側後視鏡不是用來看後方的，而是用來遮蓋你的盲區。
斑點！"如果你能在紅燈時看到後面的司機，他們就沒有設置。如果你能在紅燈時看到後面的司機，他們就沒有設置。
正確地設置它們。

要正確設置它們，請在停車時進入汽車。查看後視圖
鏡而]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/md21p2/ysk_your_cars_side_mirrors_are_probably_not_set/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/md21p2/ysk_your_cars_side_mirrors_are_probably_not_set/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 19:58:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It can save you from an accident!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your cars side mirrors are not for seeing behind you, but to cover your blind spots! If you can see the driver behind you at a red light, they aren&amp;#39;t set properly. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To set them correctly get into the car while parked. Look in the rear view mirror while sitting as though you are driving. Look for an object just at the left side of your rear view mirror. Now adjust the left side mirror to have that object just in view on the right side of the side mirror. Now look back at the rear view and find an object on the right side. Adjust your right side mirror so the object is just in view to the left edge of the mirror. This gives you the widest field of view with no gaps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I work in a garage and see this on almost every single customer car.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，如果你正在用耳機觀看YouTube視頻，而且音頻只通過一隻耳朵，你應該啓用單聲道聲音。]]></title><description><![CDATA[注意：我應該提到的是，如果你的一個耳機揚聲器，這將無法工作。
根本就是破綻百出。發生這種情況的原因不是硬件問題，而是一個
YouTuber/內容創建者如何編輯音頻文件的問題，使
聲音完全平移到右邊或左邊。

爲什麼是YSK：...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/md1sz7/ysk_that_if_youre_watching_a_youtube_video_with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/md1sz7/ysk_that_if_youre_watching_a_youtube_video_with/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 18:59:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Note: I should mention that this won&amp;#39;t work if one of your headphone speakers are simply just broken. The reason this happens is not a hardware issue but an issue with how the YouTuber/content  creator edited the audio files, making the sound completely pan to either the right or left side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Mono sound means the same audio will play through both speakers rather than anything being panned to the left or right (For example majority of all music does this to give the music a more dynamic sound)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Windows literally just search &amp;quot;Mono&amp;quot; after hitting the Windows key and its the first option that comes up. With Mac go to to System Preferences &amp;gt; Accessibility &amp;gt; Audio &amp;gt;  Tick the checkbox for Play stereo &lt;strong&gt;audio&lt;/strong&gt; as &lt;strong&gt;mono&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And  after you&amp;#39;re done watching the video just remember to disable the setting and you&amp;#39;re good to go!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can even do this on mobile, if you&amp;#39;re on IOS go to Settings &amp;gt; Accessibility &amp;gt; Audio/Visual &amp;gt; Mono audio &amp;gt; toggle the switch on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#39;re on Android, its Settings &amp;gt; Accessibility &amp;gt; Hearing Enhancements &amp;gt; Toggle Mono Audio .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope this tip helps anyone out there and if anyone has anything to add (how to enable on other OS etc.) please let me know!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 如果你突然開始不停地收到訂閱註冊到你的電子郵件，你可能是信用卡欺詐的受害者。電腦]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK。

今天早上我就遇到了這種情況（現在還在發生）。我收到了
今天早上大通銀行通知我以2400美元的價格購買了兩件商品
在我家15英里範圍內的Sams Club的筆記本電腦可以在當地取貨。
緊接着，我開始收到數百個... ...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mc71jy/ysk_if_you_all_of_a_sudden_start_receiving/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mc71jy/ysk_if_you_all_of_a_sudden_start_receiving/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 14:25:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This happened to me this morning (and is still occurring right now). I received an alert this morning from Chase advising me of a purchase for $2400 for two laptops from Sams Club for pickup locally within 15 miles of my home. Immediately afterwards I started receiving hundreds of subscription emails to the account associated with it that have been flooding my email box for the last hour. Not all criminals are dumb, they are relying on people not understanding how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They start by making the purchase but as soon as it is confirmed, they begin to flood the email account with subscription sign ups in hopes that you either&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A) Click select all and delete, subsequently deleting the purchase email&lt;br/&gt;
B) Manually go through and click unsubscribe from each&lt;br/&gt;
C) Report spam on everything&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the time I were to do any, they could send their runner to pick it up with the order number and be on their way, leaving me to have to fight the charge for items that were technically picked up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：大多數有 "無鑰匙 "啓動功能的車輛的鑰匙扣裏面都有一把實體鑰匙。]]></title><description><![CDATA[WHY YSK: 我是一名拖車操作員/路邊救援技術員。今天的一份工作提醒了我
的一個不爲人知的細節，幾乎每一個無鑰匙啓動車輛的鑰匙扣都有一個。
裏面的物理鑰匙。如何訪問它們是不同的，每個
品牌/型號的車輛。所以，如果你的車輛電池壞了，而它的... ...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mcn3e4/ysk_most_key_fobs_for_vehicles_that_have_keyless/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mcn3e4/ysk_most_key_fobs_for_vehicles_that_have_keyless/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 07:00:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK: I&amp;#39;m a tow truck op / roadside assistance tech. A job today reminded me of a not so known detail that almost every keyless start vehicle fob has a physical key on the inside. How you access them is different for every make/model vehicle. So if your battery dies on your vehicle and it&amp;#39;s locked. Don&amp;#39;t fret. No need to call for a lockout. (Though you may need a jump start) just Google how to access your key and unlock it yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，如果你的安卓系統今天崩潰了，卸載Webview或Chrome瀏覽器就可以解決了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：安卓最新的更新導致應用不斷崩潰。

只要進入設置->應用，點擊三個點，"顯示系統應用"。然後就可以了。
打開Android Webview或Chrome瀏覽器，卸載更新。希望對大家有所幫助!

來源：https://www.androidauthority.com/android-apps-crashing-1210994/]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mb7y1w/ysk_that_if_your_android_is_crashing_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mb7y1w/ysk_that_if_your_android_is_crashing_today/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 03:54:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Android&amp;#39;s latest update has been causing apps to crash constantly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simply go to Settings-&amp;gt;apps, click the three dots and &amp;quot;Show system apps&amp;quot;. Then, open Android Webview or Chrome and uninstall updates. Hope this helps!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.androidauthority.com/android-apps-crashing-1210994/&quot;&gt;https://www.androidauthority.com/android-apps-crashing-1210994/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：Wolfram Alpha存在。Wolfram Alpha是一門先進的數學，它能一步步地展示解決方案。]]></title><description><![CDATA[WHY YSK：。我在大學裏用它來仔細檢查我在統計學1和2的工作。我在大學裏用它來複查我在統計學1和2中的工作。
它到今天重新學習不同的公式解決方案，以幫助我的孩子與
功課。它通過對Wolfram Alpha是如何幫助刷新遺忘已久的。
計算器得到了解決方案。它甚至會畫一條線。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mcanaw/ysk_wolfram_alpha_exists_wolfram_alpha_is_an/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mcanaw/ysk_wolfram_alpha_exists_wolfram_alpha_is_an/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 23:32:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK:. I used it in college to double check my work in stats 1 and 2.  I use it to this day to relearn different formula solutions to help my kids with homework.  It helps refresh the long forgotten by going through how Wolfram Alpha Calculator got the solution. It will even graph a line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：一個泡沫滾輪的成本和出去喫午飯的成本差不多（或更低），持續時間長，而且可以瞬間讓各種肌肉痠痛、背痛等問題得到巨大改善。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：很多人抱怨肌肉痠痛，但很多人根本不是這樣做的
什麼都沒有，或加載了OTC止痛藥。

對於一個更徹底的好處和爲什麼你應該使用一個，這裏是一個徹底的概述
脊椎按摩/康復中心的清單。
https://www.thorpechiropractic.com/new/index.php/blog/28...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mc9lfl/ysk_a_foam_roller_costs_about_the_same_or_less_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mc9lfl/ysk_a_foam_roller_costs_about_the_same_or_less_as/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:51:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: lots of people complain about sore muscles, but many simply either do nothing, or load up on OTC painkillers.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a more thorough rundown of the benefits and why you should use one, here&amp;#39;s a list from a chiropractic / rehab center: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thorpechiropractic.com/new/index.php/blog/28-11-benefits-of-foam-rolling&quot;&gt;https://www.thorpechiropractic.com/new/index.php/blog/28-11-benefits-of-foam-rolling&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the simple summary from my own use and anyone else I know (including a doctor and a chiropractor) is that they&amp;#39;re practically magic.  I&amp;#39;ve gone from &amp;quot;it hurts to move&amp;quot; to &amp;quot;wow, I&amp;#39;m feeling 80-90%&amp;quot; in just a few minutes more times than I&amp;#39;d like to mention.  Sometimes the actual process of using it can be uncomfortable, but more often than I feel like a new person almost immediately, and after a few sessions over a couple of days I&amp;#39;m back to normal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK你可能有無人認領的財產等着你。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：從禮品卡到保險理賠，再到未兌現的支票，都可以通過YSK來實現。
國家有義務保留它，直到它被合法的所有者要求。
谷歌無人認領的財產無論在哪個州，都可以搜索你的名字。有些
覓得千金，幸不辱命]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m9ibis/ysk_you_may_have_unclaimed_property_waiting_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m9ibis/ysk_you_may_have_unclaimed_property_waiting_for/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 14:31:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Anything from gift cards to insurance claims to uncashed checks, the state is obligated to hold on to it until it&amp;#39;s claimed by the rightful owner. Google unclaimed property in whatever state it&amp;#39;s in and search your name. Some find thousands, good luck!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你的工作不提供加班費，就不要加班。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：這應該是顯而易見的，但太多人加班卻沒有得到。
適當的報酬/報酬來做。你不應該被責備去做加班工作
如果你沒有得到報酬。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mc0xo5/ysk_if_your_job_doesnt_offer_overtime_payment/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mc0xo5/ysk_if_your_job_doesnt_offer_overtime_payment/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 13:01:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It should be obvious, but too many people work overtime without getting the proper payment/paid to do it. You shouldn&amp;#39;t be guilted into doing over-time if you don&amp;#39;t get paid for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK那如果您有一個大黃蜂, 黃蜂, 或黃夾克巢在您的財產, 有人們誰將免費帶走它. 他們把它賣給製造黃蜂過敏藥的製藥公司。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我以前發過這個帖子，但是沒有引起很多人的注意，我覺得這是
重要。我們也快進入春天了，這時那些小屁孩更
活動。

我的丈夫是過敏的黃蜂和幾年前我們發現在我們的大的
我們院子裏的杜鵑花叢是個禿臉馬蜂窩....。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m7urt6/ysk_that_if_you_have_a_hornet_wasp_or_yellow/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m7urt6/ysk_that_if_you_have_a_hornet_wasp_or_yellow/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 02:43:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve posted this before, but it didn&amp;#39;t get a lot of attention and I think it&amp;#39;s important. We&amp;#39;re also coming into spring when those little assholes are more active.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My husband is allergic to wasps and a couple years ago we found in our large Rhododendron bush in our yard a bald-faced hornets nest. It was very well hidden, and was about the size of a volleyball. An in-law gave me the number and email address to a local man who will remove it for free (as long as it hasn’t been sprayed with anything yet). We contacted him immediately and within two days he came and removed the hive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He sells these wasps to companies that use the venom to create allergy shots for people like my husband.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Before you spray, pay hundreds of dollars to an exterminator to remove them, or risk getting stung or chased down the street by a particularly pissed off group of wasps, you can probably find a person in your area that will take it away for free. Your nuisance could turn into life saving medicine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: "永遠的化學品 "或不會在你的身體或環境中分解的化學品，從1940年開始使用，可能是我們這一代人（和世界）必須面對的最大的環境災難，而且幾乎可以肯定現在正在毒害你。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是一場可能會毀滅人類的慢動作災難。

> 這場危機的罪魁禍首是化學品，它存在於所有的東西中，從塑料到塑料，從塑料到塑料，從塑料到塑料，從塑料到塑料。
> 容器和食品包裝，到防水衣服和香料的清潔。
> 從產品，到肥皂和洗髮水，再到電子產品和地毯。其中一些...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mbpcl5/ysk_forever_chemicals_or_chemicals_that_dont/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mbpcl5/ysk_forever_chemicals_or_chemicals_that_dont/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 23:26:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s a slow motion disaster that may potentially wipe out humanity. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The chemicals to blame for this crisis are found in everything from plastic containers and food wrapping, to waterproof clothes and fragrances in cleaning products, to soaps and shampoos, to electronics and carpeting. Some of them, called PFAS, are known as “forever  chemicals”, because they don’t breakdown in the environment or the human body. They just accumulate and accumulate – doing more and more damage, minute by minute, hour by hour, day by day. Now, it seems, humanity is reaching a breaking point.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2021/mar/18/toxic-chemicals-health-humanity-erin-brokovich&quot;&gt;The Guardian&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Swiss researcher covered by that article hypothesizes these chemicals are responsible for worldwide declines in fertility. Shanna Swan, an environmental and reproductive epidemiologist at Icahn School of Medicine at Mount Sinai in New York authored &lt;a href=&quot;https://academic.oup.com/humupd/article/23/6/646/4035689&quot;&gt;a study&lt;/a&gt; that found that sperm counts in the west had plummeted by 59% between 1973 and 2011, and she blames forever chemicals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“In some parts of the world, the average twentysomething woman today is less fertile than her grandmother was at 35,” Swan writes. In addition to that, Swan finds that, on average, a man today will have &lt;em&gt;half&lt;/em&gt; of the sperm his grandfather had. “The current state of reproductive affairs can’t continue much longer without threatening human survival,” writes Swan, adding: “It’s a global existential crisis.” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Swan’s research finds that these chemicals aren’t just dramatically reducing semen quality, they are also &lt;a href=&quot;https://theintercept.com/2021/01/24/toxic-chemicals-human-sexuality-shanna-swan/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;shrinking penis size and volume of the testes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. This echos &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.documentcloud.org/documents/5316830-EDCs-Androgenic-Activity-Perfluoroakyl.html&quot;&gt;other research&lt;/a&gt; that found that PFAS harms sperm production, disrupts male hormones and is correlated to a &lt;strong&gt;“reduction of semen quality, testicular volume and penile length”.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another study &lt;a href=&quot;https://pediatrics.aappublications.org/content/121/2/e260&quot;&gt;found&lt;/a&gt; phthalate exposure “widespread” in infants, and that the chemicals were found in the urine of babies who came into contact with baby shampoos, lotions and powders. Still, aggressive regulation is lacking, not least  because of lobbying by chemical industry giants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.livescience.com/new-environmental-chemicals-pfas-pregnant-woment.html&quot;&gt;Further research&lt;/a&gt; has found that these chemicals pass from mother to child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Guardian article worded it best;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Swan’s research&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/feb/26/falling-sperm-counts-human-survival&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;suggests&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;sperm counts could reach zero by 2045.&lt;/strong&gt; Zero. Let that sink in. That would mean no babies. No reproduction. No more humans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This directly affects you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sources, Citations and additional reading:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2021/mar/18/toxic-chemicals-health-humanity-erin-brokovich&quot;&gt;Plummeting sperm counts, shrinking penises: toxic chemicals threaten humanity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/feb/26/falling-sperm-counts-human-survival&quot;&gt;Falling sperm counts &amp;#39;threaten human survival&amp;#39;, expert warns&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://academic.oup.com/humupd/article/23/6/646/4035689&quot;&gt;Temporal trends in sperm count: a systematic review and meta-regression analysis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.swnewsmedia.com/savage_pacer/news/mpca-forever-chemicals-leaked-into-groundwater-by-local-landfills/article_dcc450ba-79ad-5538-9d58-62299921d02b.html&quot;&gt;MPCA: &amp;#39;Forever chemicals&amp;#39; leaked into groundwater by local landfills&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ewg.org/release/epa-takes-first-step-address-industry-pollution-forever-chemicals&quot;&gt;EPA Takes First Step To Address Industrial Pollution From ‘Forever Chemicals’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/03/03/chemicals-water-denver-colorado-pfas/&quot;&gt;Elevated Levels Of ‘Forever Chemicals’ Found In Some Colorado Drinking Water Districts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mprnews.org/story/2021/03/18/forever-chemicals-found-in-groundwater-at-dozens-of-minn-landfills&quot;&gt;‘Forever chemicals’ found in groundwater at dozens of Minn. landfills&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://dcist.com/story/21/03/10/high-levels-toxic-pfas-forever-chemicals-northern-virginia-drinking-water/&quot;&gt;High Levels Of ‘Forever Chemicals’ Detected In Northern Virginia Drinking Water&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.axios.com/defense-department-afff-pfas-contamination-9e69920d-041e-4035-969a-14cfbb3e18bd.html&quot;&gt;The Pentagon&amp;#39;s multibillion-dollar &amp;quot;forever chemicals&amp;quot; problem&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ewg.org/research/nova-pfas-testing/&quot;&gt;Is Northern Virginia a D.C.-Area Hot Spot for ‘Forever Chemicals’ in Tap Water?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://scitechdaily.com/researchers-unearth-a-ticking-time-bomb-synthetic-chemicals-in-soils/&quot;&gt;Researchers Unearth a ‘Ticking Time Bomb’ – Synthetic Chemicals in Soils&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.livescience.com/new-environmental-chemicals-pfas-pregnant-woment.html&quot;&gt;More than 50 new environmental chemicals detected in people&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK說，如果你知道一個孩子在努力學習閱讀，他們可能有聚合不足。CI是可以通過視力治療來治療的。這種情況經常被遺漏，因爲定期的眼科檢查中不包括對它的測試。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼YSK：CI經常被誤診爲ADD或閱讀障礙。

https://www.optometrists.org/vision-therapy-for-children/convergence-insufficiency-2/]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m7d85c/ysk_that_if_you_know_a_kid_struggling_to_learn_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m7d85c/ysk_that_if_you_know_a_kid_struggling_to_learn_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 19:56:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: CI is often misdiagnosed as ADD or 
Dyslexia.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.optometrists.org/vision-therapy-for-children/convergence-insufficiency-2/&quot;&gt;https://www.optometrists.org/vision-therapy-for-children/convergence-insufficiency-2/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK一個人的手可能會抖動的原因有很多，告訴他們 "放鬆 "是沒有用的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：手部震顫可以由許多不同的事情引起，幾乎沒有任何一種原因。
他們是任何你的業務。焦慮、神經系統疾病、藥物/酒精
戒斷和腦損傷是幾個可能的原因。唯一能
被改善放鬆是焦慮。但呼籲關注...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mbin3p/ysk_there_are_many_reasons_a_persons_hands_might/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mbin3p/ysk_there_are_many_reasons_a_persons_hands_might/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 19:56:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Hand tremors can be caused by many different things and almost none of them are any of your business. Anxiety, a neurological disorder, drug/alcohol withdrawals, and brain damage are a few possible causes. The only one that can be improved by relaxing is anxiety. But calling attention to someone&amp;#39;s anxiety will not help. It&amp;#39;s patronizing and is likely to cause more anxiety. You&amp;#39;re basically just announcing, &amp;quot;Everyone can see your hands shaking!&amp;quot; This is not an appropriate reaction to any medical symptom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Citation: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ninds.nih.gov/Disorders/Patient-Caregiver-Education/Fact-Sheets/Tremor-Fact-Sheet&quot;&gt;https://www.ninds.nih.gov/Disorders/Patient-Caregiver-Education/Fact-Sheets/Tremor-Fact-Sheet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 任何大型建築項目都要進行三次評估。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：到你家給你免費評估的人，往往都是 "你"。
在壓力下，贏取大回報的工作。大多數業主所
不知道的是，很多建築項目都是無利可圖的。
公司，有的還會實際虧損。

免費的點...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mb3jgr/ysk_always_get_three_estimates_for_any_large/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mb3jgr/ysk_always_get_three_estimates_for_any_large/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 12:43:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: People who come to your house and give you a free estimate are often under pressure to win jobs that will make a big return. What most homeowners don&amp;#39;t realize is that many construction projects aren&amp;#39;t profitable for the company, and some will actually lose money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The point of the free estimate is to size up your job, and to see if it will make money. If it seems like a bad bet, contractors will price the job higher, to account for the risk. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should see this as a polite way of refusing the job. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you get three estimates, you&amp;#39;ll notice if one is a lot higher. Don&amp;#39;t go with that one. The contractor is either inexperienced, doesn&amp;#39;t have the time, or doesn&amp;#39;t have the equipment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If all the estimates are roughly the same, congratulations. Your job is one that will be completed without issues. Pick the middle bid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If one bid is a lot lower than the rest, don&amp;#39;t go with that one. The contractor has likely missed a major line item and will be forced to bail on your project, or take a big loss. The quality of the work will likely not be as good as it needs to be. Please don&amp;#39;t see this as a way to get a good deal. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR: in most cases, if you are excellent to your contractor they will be excellent to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: I was a contractor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 你可以很容易地從一英寸左右的高度將AA/AAA電池垂直地摔在桌子上，來估計它們的電量。新電池會靜止不動地落下，而放了電的電池會像球一樣反彈。]]></title><description><![CDATA[所有的一次性電池，包括鹼性電池和鹽基電池都是如此。鹼性電池和鹽基電池都是如此。
電池消耗越大，彈跳越高。這並不適用於
可充電電池。

爲什麼選擇YSK：有時候你的一次性電池堆裏有一團亂麻，這
需要儘快解決，或者你只是需要... ...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/malse0/ysk_you_could_easily_estimate_the_charge_of_aaaaa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/malse0/ysk_you_could_easily_estimate_the_charge_of_aaaaa/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 04:56:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is true for all disposable battery cells, alkaline, and salt-based. The more depleted the battery, the higher it bounces. It doesn&amp;#39;t applies to rechargeable cells.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: sometimes you have a mess in your stack of disposable batteries which needs to be sorted out quickly, or you just need to check if the battery is still alive without having a multimeter at hand. This is the fast and easy way to do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK的平均壽命是78.54歲（美國）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼YSK在美國的平均壽命是78.54歲？

如果你的母親或父親是當前60歲以上的人，請反思一下你的壽命是多少？
每月和他們一起度過。我敢打賭，大多數人很少看到他們的父母1
一個月的時間。意味着大多數人將會有不到100個這樣的時刻留下。
一些少]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mauown/ysk_the_average_life_span_is_7854_us/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mauown/ysk_the_average_life_span_is_7854_us/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 01:34:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK the average life span in the US is 78.54?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your mother or father is current 60 plus reflect on the amount of time you spend with them each month. I would bet most people rarely see their parents 1 time a month. Meaning most people will have less then 100 of these moments left some less then 10. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don’t choose when they go; we do get choose how much of our own time we spend with them. Find it in yourself to make the time for them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 讓你的青少年成爲一個成年人，比你自己的父母爲你準備的還要好。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: 這樣您的孩子就會對未來有更好的認識。

當他們成爲青少年時，和他們談談如何成爲一個成年人。賬單/儲蓄
錢/不同的理財方式，投資理財等。

少年時期是尷尬的歲月。雖然還不算是個孩子，但...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mb05az/ysk_prepare_your_teenagers_to_be_an_adult_better/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mb05az/ysk_prepare_your_teenagers_to_be_an_adult_better/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 01:34:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: That way your child(ren) have a better idea of what is in store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When they become teenagers, talk to them about being an adult. Bills/saving money/different ways to get financial help, investing in money, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Teenage years are the awkward years. Not quite a kid, but not quite an adult. That&amp;#39;s the perfect time to get them prepared for being an adult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make sure to start your kids young at chores as well so they know about responsibility. I knew way too many teenagers and even adults who never did chores because their parents did them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make sure boys and girls do the same kind of chores, so they know how to do them as an adult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://childdevelopmentinfo.com/chores/the-ultimate-list-of-age-appropriate-chores/&quot;&gt;https://childdevelopmentinfo.com/chores/the-ultimate-list-of-age-appropriate-chores/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cmc-pa.com/teens/preparing-teen-adulthood/&quot;&gt;https://www.cmc-pa.com/teens/preparing-teen-adulthood/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://washingtonparent.com/preparing-teens-for-adulthood/&quot;&gt;https://washingtonparent.com/preparing-teens-for-adulthood/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/resolution-not-conflict/201111/prepping-kids-so-theyre-ready-thrive-adults&quot;&gt;https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/resolution-not-conflict/201111/prepping-kids-so-theyre-ready-thrive-adults&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK經常揉眼睛其實會讓你的視力變差]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：你應該知道，這樣才能避免對眼睛的進一步傷害。

長期揉眼睛會對眼睛的健康產生多種影響。
的眼睛。尤其是2種後果，其實會長期影響你的視力。

 1. 持續揉眼會導致角膜變薄，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/maikv8/ysk_rubbing_your_eyes_a_lot_can_actually_make/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/maikv8/ysk_rubbing_your_eyes_a_lot_can_actually_make/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 23:26:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: you should know so you can avoid any further damage to your eyes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chronically rubbing your eyes can have multiple effects on the health of the eye. 2 consequences in particular can actually affect your vision long term. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Continuous eye rubbing can lead to thinning of the corneal tissue, which weakens the cornea and pushes it forward to become more conical. This thinning is an eye disease called keratoconus, which is a serious condition that can lead to distorted vision and may lead to needing a corneal transplant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;People with progressive myopia (near-sightedness which is VERY common) can find that rubbing worsens their eyesight&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used to work at a laser eye surgery clinic and we would do a lot of testing to determine if someone is a candidate for surgery. We could often determine if someone is a chronic eye rubber because we can see signs of it through our testing. Sure enough when we ask our patients if they do have an eye rubbing habit most will admit they do. It goes to show that chronic eye rubbing can and does change the lens of the eye since it is easily noticable when we do our testing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to clarify that this is chronic eye rubbing and not the occasional eye rub. This is for people that may rub their eyes multiple times a day, when they are sleepy, nervous, or are far to rough with certain routines like makeup removal. If you feel you have a habit of rubbing your eyes now would be a good time to become aware of it and try to change the behaviour. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you feel your eye rubbing is due to irritated eyes your best bet is to get an artificial tear drop as the majority of everyday irritation is due to dry eyes. You can also add a fish oil supplement into your diet to help increase natural lubrication to your eyes. Allergies are another reason people may rub their eyes. Visit your doctor for a diagnoses to rule out any other issues. Allergy medicines or antihistamine eye drops can help if the issue is allergy related.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reference and more info:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.visiontexas.com/general/rubbing-eyes-bad-5-reasons-will-get-stop-asap/&quot;&gt;https://www.visiontexas.com/general/rubbing-eyes-bad-5-reasons-will-get-stop-asap/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 如果你的肌肉疼痛不會消失，去做個按摩吧!]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼YSK：我剛剛做了一次按摩，他們找到了我慢性疼痛的根源。
我的肌肉因爲舉重而打結。按摩師說要做
運動後拉伸，防止打結。

/u/LordCongra補充道。"文獻支持在運動後拉伸30秒到1秒
分鐘，每天2-4次，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m84onz/ysk_if_you_have_muscle_pain_that_wont_go_away_get/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m84onz/ysk_if_you_have_muscle_pain_that_wont_go_away_get/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 23:26:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I just got a massage and they found the source of my chronic pain, which were knots in my muscles from lifting weights.  The masseuse said to do stretches after exercise to prevent knots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/u/LordCongra&quot;&gt;/u/LordCongra&lt;/a&gt; adds:  &amp;quot;The literature supports stretching for 30 second to 1 minute 2-4 times daily and past that it was found to not have a profound effect on tissue length.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source to more info:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.betterhealth.vic.gov.au/health/conditionsandtreatments/massage&quot;&gt;https://www.betterhealth.vic.gov.au/health/conditionsandtreatments/massage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK(幾乎所有)的魚缸都是殘忍和不人道的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[你應該知道魚缸是殘忍的，不人道的，爲什麼YSK知道這是
因爲很多原因。

首先是魚缸的面積。對於一些魚類來說，比如常見的金魚，這就是
重要，因爲它們可以達到一尺。把它們擠在一個小空間裏
意味着他們的身體在成長，而他們的器官... ...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/macbux/ysk_almost_all_fishbowls_are_cruel_and_inhumane/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/macbux/ysk_almost_all_fishbowls_are_cruel_and_inhumane/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 18:58:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;You should know that fishbowls are cruel and inhumane. why YSK know this is because of many reasons. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First is the area of the bowl. For some fish like the common goldfish, this is important because they can get up to a foot. Cramming them in a small space means there body grows while their organs don&amp;#39;t. Also for other fish like bettas, it just doesn&amp;#39;t feel right confining them to such a small space. This mean, while a goldfish lives for 10-20 years with GOOD care, you&amp;#39;d be lucky to have one live for 2 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next is because of ammonia nitrite and nitrate and a lack of a filter. You have filters in fish tank for two main reasons. 1. is to agitate the water. 2. Is to grow beneficial bacteria. 
You may wonder, what is beneficial bacteria? It is a type of bacteria that consumes ammonia, a common toxin in a fishes poop. Then it turns it into nitrite which is just as harmful.  Then finally, it converts it to nitrate which is much less harmful. Even having a tiny filter doesn&amp;#39;t fix most stuff,  because some fish like goldfish produce a CRAP ton of waste and the bacteria can&amp;#39;t keep up. Also some fish like bettas are tropical fish and most bowls don&amp;#39;t have a filter. Most bettas that live in bowls don&amp;#39;t last more than 6 months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally bowls are bad because if the surface area. Even with a filter, the surface area doesn&amp;#39;t allow the bowl to oxygenate which is bad for the fish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I say &amp;quot;almost all&amp;quot; because if you were too keep a 10 gallon bowl with cherry shrimp that&amp;#39;s filtered and heater and has a lot of plants that would be ok. Even though the tank size for a betta is 5 Gallons, a bowl of 5 gallons just doesn&amp;#39;t have enough surface area. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could go on and on and on but I will keep this a short as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 如果你每年的調整後總收入（AGI）低於72,000美元，你可以通過IRS免費報稅計劃完全免費報稅。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：（僅限美國）該計劃是美國國稅局和流行的稅務部門之間的合作項目。
報稅軟件如TurboTax, TaxSlayer, TaxAct等......可以讓你
如果你的收入低於72,000美元的AGI截止值，你就可以免費提交整個申報。

這裏的鏈接到國稅局免費... ...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mafb13/ysk_if_you_make_less_than_72000_a_year_adjusted/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mafb13/ysk_if_you_make_less_than_72000_a_year_adjusted/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 14:27:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: (US Only) The program is a partnership between the IRS and popular tax filing software&amp;#39;s like TurboTax, TaxSlayer, TaxAct, etc... that allows you to file your entire return for free if you make less than the $72,000 AGI cutoff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s the link to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.irs.gov/filing/free-file-do-your-federal-taxes-for-free&quot;&gt;IRS Free File&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if you do make more than $72,000/year the electronic forms to file are free to use and file online. Granted I would only do that if you have a pretty straightforward tax return or you really know what you&amp;#39;re doing when it comes to taxes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#39;re unsure of what steps to take, here is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/3KTyTxndOyg&quot;&gt;guide&lt;/a&gt; walking you through the free file program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在基於訂閱的服務上，如果你打電話詢問，通常可以得到更便宜的價格。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：我剛剛遇到了這種情況，我的妻子和我都有衛星廣播。我妻子和我都有衛星廣播
啓用的汽車。我沒有激活我的，因爲我不經常聽音樂。
夠（我更喜歡播客、audibook等）。我還是會收到特別的廣告
所有的時間關於重新啓動我的服務。我碰巧得到一個...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m9dx6u/ysk_on_subscription_based_services_you_can/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m9dx6u/ysk_on_subscription_based_services_you_can/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 09:37:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I just had this happen to me. My wife and I both have satellite radio enabled cars. I don&amp;#39;t have mine active because I don&amp;#39;t listen to music often enough (I prefer podcasts, audibooks, etc). I still get special advertisements all the time about restarting my service. I happened to get one of these just after my wife&amp;#39;s subscription price automatically renewed at the &amp;quot;going rate&amp;quot; (or whatever you call that ridiculously high rate they charge if you don&amp;#39;t call and bother them). I called them up and asked for the special rate I had just been offered. 
The guy pulls up the account and offers me some other offer which is cheaper than regular, but not as good as what I had. I asked him if I couldn&amp;#39;t get the deal I called about. He responded &amp;quot;we have to get an answer on this deal first: do you want it, yes or no.&amp;quot; My response was &amp;quot;not if I can get this other offer&amp;quot;, which he then repeated his line and I realized he was following his script literally and had to offer me some low-ball offer first before proceeding to the offer I was interested in, so I told him no and I could hear him sigh with relief as he proceeded to pull up the offer I wanted and offer it to me. I was tempted to see if there was an even better offer out there by answering no again, but didn&amp;#39;t want to push my luck and end up canceling the service (and making the Mrs. upset). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moral of the story, you can (almost) always get your subscription based service cheaper if you call and ask. You may have to threaten to cancel (and don&amp;#39;t be afraid to follow through if they say no, because sometimes they think your threat is empty and won&amp;#39;t try to sell you until you are serious).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: fixed spelling (I do know how to spell, just on mobile). Also thanks for 1k upvotes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，當你寫個人支票時，你給了收款人你的銀行賬戶和路由號碼。相反，使用銀行的在線賬單支付功能--他們會用不同的賬戶給收款人郵寄支票，以保護您的信息。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼YSK：很多人沒有利用好銀行的網上繳費功能。
包括我自己在內，直到一年前。這不僅節省了時間，銀行
通常會免費提供這項服務，甚至會將你的支票免費郵寄到以下地址。
指定的收款人（所以也不用支付郵費）。當...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m9yqva/ysk_that_when_you_write_a_personal_check_youre/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m9yqva/ysk_that_when_you_write_a_personal_check_youre/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 05:02:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: A lot of people don’t utilize their bank’s online bill pay feature, myself included up until about a year ago. Not only does it save time, the bank usually provides this service for free and will even mail your check for free to the designated payee (so no paying for postage either).
When you go this route, your bank sends a check with a different account number on it while still debiting your account, so you get all of the benefits of writing a check without any of the vulnerability that comes with sharing your account number.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 如果你認識一些很難彎腰的人，比如老人，請確保他們在前門旁有一張桌子，用來放置包裹。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：我是以送貨爲生的。如果我知道有人年紀大了，我會把他們的
包裹放在桌子/椅子上，如果他們家門口有的話。我收到很多
的讚美，因爲想到了這一點。可以找到一個小小的庭院桌，用於
沃爾瑪或同類商店20-40美元。或者更便宜的二手貨。你...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ma3i8x/ysk_if_you_know_someone_who_has_a_hard_time/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ma3i8x/ysk_if_you_know_someone_who_has_a_hard_time/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 03:34:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I deliver for a living. If I know someone is older, I put their packages on a table/chair if they have one in front of their house. I get a lot of compliments for thinking of that. A little patio table can be found for $20-$40 at Walmart or similiar stores. Or even cheaper second hand. You can even get a little sign that just says, &amp;quot;Please put packages here.&amp;quot; It&amp;#39;s just a small thing that could really help people with mobility issues. Especially with more people ordering online instead of going to stores.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 通常的建議是讓你的密碼充滿隨機字符、數字和符號。然而，至少有10個字的句子可以更安全，而且會明顯更容易記住。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：大家可能都收到過這樣的建議，說你的密碼
應該是8*^iHs89%>l7這樣的。然而，這不僅很難
記住，其實不如 "高頭大馬樂馳騁 "來得穩妥。
在寬闊的草地上很快就變得口渴了"。

假設你只...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m5bqm0/ysk_it_is_common_advice_to_make_your_password/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m5bqm0/ysk_it_is_common_advice_to_make_your_password/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 03:34:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: everyone has probably received the advice saying that your password should be something like &lt;code&gt;8*^iHs89%&amp;gt;l7&lt;/code&gt;. However, not only is this hard to remember, it is actually less secure than &amp;quot;The tall horses joyfully galloping across the wide meadow quickly became thirsty&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Assuming that you only use the characters available on a normal keyboard, the first password format has 94&lt;sup&gt;12&lt;/sup&gt; possible combinations, or 4.75E23. Assuming you know 40,000 words, the second password format has 40000&lt;sup&gt;12,&lt;/sup&gt; or 1.67E55 combinations. That is roughly &lt;em&gt;10 septillion times&lt;/em&gt; more secure. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, that doesn&amp;#39;t even take into account that the person attempting to hack your account doesn&amp;#39;t know you&amp;#39;re using words, doesn&amp;#39;t know if you have spaces or they&amp;#39;re right next to each other, doesn&amp;#39;t know if you have numbers between, and doesn&amp;#39;t know which ones are capitalized. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL;DR: a 12 word sentence is &lt;em&gt;much&lt;/em&gt; more secure and memorable than 12 random characters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 當您整理牀鋪時，10次中有9次，製造商的標籤會出現在被子/牀單的右下角（當您站在牀腳下朝它看時）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：知道標籤的位置，並把它放在右下角。
可以避免您在使用時多次調整牀單或被子。
鋪牀。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m7ezdd/ysk_when_making_your_bed_9_times_out_10_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m7ezdd/ysk_when_making_your_bed_9_times_out_10_the/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 22:56:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Knowing where the tag is at and keeping it in the bottom right corner will prevent you from having to readjust the sheet or quilt multiple times while making the bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 如果您在有暫停驅逐令的州買了房子，即使在過戶後，法律上也允許賣方繼續留在房子裏。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why YSK: 在有暫停驅逐令的州，已經有一些案例。
賣方在買方購買房屋後拒絕離開房屋，以及。
在法律上，在暫停令取消之前，沒有人可以做任何事情。如果
如果你是買家，這對你來說是很糟糕的。如果你是賣家，也許... ...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m9wbgz/ysk_if_you_buy_a_house_in_a_state_with_eviction/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m9wbgz/ysk_if_you_buy_a_house_in_a_state_with_eviction/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 20:34:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: In states with eviction moratoriums there have been a few cases of sellers refusing to leave the house after the buyer has purchased it, and legally no one can do anything about it until the moratorium is lifted. If you’re a buyer this would be terrible for you. If you’re the seller maybe this would work to your advantage!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK表示，當收銀員詢問您的地址、姓名、電話號碼或其他個人信息時，"不用謝 "是一個完全可以接受的答案。保護您的隱私。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：我發這個帖子是因爲這一直是我的答案，而且更多的是
他們看我的眼神就像我有三個頭，這告訴我，這不是一個。
他們得到的共同迴應。雖然他們可能需要你獲得5%的折扣。
下次你進去的時候，他們想要它的真正原因是...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m9qkye/ysk_that_when_asked_for_your_address_name_phone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/m9qkye/ysk_that_when_asked_for_your_address_name_phone/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 17:26:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I&amp;#39;m posting this because that has always been my answer, and more often than not they look at me like I have three heads, which tells me that it&amp;#39;s not a common response they get. While they may need that for you to get a 5% discount next time you go in, the real reason they want it is to sell your information and have you receive unsolicited phone calls. To that I say, no thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>