<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 04:35:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK表示，母親節（美國）是下週日，5月9日。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：如果你要郵寄東西，你需要儘快發送。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n1tqzn/ysk_that_mothers_day_us_is_next_sunday_may_9/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n1tqzn/ysk_that_mothers_day_us_is_next_sunday_may_9/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 18:00:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: if you’re going to mail something, you need to send it soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 如果你用現金支付東西，有人問你："你給了我一張X美元的鈔票嗎？"，這是爲了挽救工作人員的工作。只要說是或不是。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：（注：我來自美國）當你把錢交給任何機構的工作人員時，他們應該要求你確認你給他們多少錢。
的時候，他們應該要求你確認你給了他們多少錢。他們最不需要的是給你6美元的零錢。
他們最不需要的就是給你6美元的零錢，因爲你給了他們一張10美元的鈔票。
而讓你對他們大喊大叫，因爲你認爲你給了他們......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n1oq16/ysk_if_you_pay_for_something_in_cash_and_youre/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n1oq16/ysk_if_you_pay_for_something_in_cash_and_youre/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 09:52:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: (Note: I&amp;#39;m from the US) When you hand money to a staff member at any establishment, they should be asking you to verify how much you gave them. The last thing they need is to give you $6 in change because you gave them a $10 bill, and have you yell at them because you thought you handed them a $20 bill (and should therefore get $16 in change).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apparently at my job (I&amp;#39;m a pharmacy tech), someone in the drive-thru left a terrible review because he gave me a $10 bill to pay for a $4 medication, and I had the audacity to ask him &amp;quot;you sent me a $10 bill, correct?&amp;quot; He said it was &amp;quot;bizarre and unnecessary&amp;quot;. He gave us a 1/10 JUST for that. Don&amp;#39;t be that guy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best thing is to tell them exactly what you&amp;#39;re giving them right from the get-go. &amp;quot;Here&amp;#39;s a $20&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;ve got a dollar and 15 cents here&amp;quot; removes any doubts about what money has been exchanged, and prevents issues about money and change down the line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Someone made a good point that if you&amp;#39;re an employee, you can just state the amount of money the customer gave you, no need to ask them to verify the amount. Saying &amp;quot;out of a $20&amp;quot; is fine, and then the customer can correct you if it&amp;#39;s wrong. I do that when it&amp;#39;s a face-to-face transaction, but in this scenario, the patient was in the far drive-thru lane so I had to make sure he heard me correctly, hence why I needed to phrase it as a question&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，"etc "是 "et cetera "的簡稱，並且是這樣發音的，而不是 "ek cetera"]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：這是一個很小但非常普遍的錯誤發音。
我聽到電視主持人、演講者、歌手和其他許多人這樣發音。
很多時候，這種區別幾乎聽不出來，在非正式的講話中，這並不重要。
麼重要。但是，如果發表正式的演講或什麼...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n16and/ysk_that_etc_is_short_for_et_cetera_and_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n16and/ysk_that_etc_is_short_for_et_cetera_and_is/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 07:46:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This is a small but extremely common mispronunciation, I’ve heard it pronounced this way by television presenters, lecturers, singers, and many more. Oftentimes the distinction is barely audible, and in informal speech it wouldn’t matter. BUT if delivering a formal speech or something similar, it’s definitely worth knowing this so your pronunciation is impeccable, and so any listeners who are aware of this aren’t distracted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 你可以檢查特定的密碼是否在數據泄露中被暴露出來]]></title><description><![CDATA[每天都有新的數據泄露事件發生，要確保你走在它的前面很容易。
領先於它。這個網站：https://breachdirectory.tk
[https://breachdirectory.tk/]使用人工智能來監測和解析新的數據泄露事件
自動。只要輸入你的電子郵件或用戶名，它就會告訴你哪些...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0pr2o/ysk_that_you_can_check_whether_specific_passwords/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0pr2o/ysk_that_you_can_check_whether_specific_passwords/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 03:35:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are new data breaches occurring everyday and it&amp;#39;s pretty easy to make sure you stay ahead of it. This site: &lt;a href=&quot;https://breachdirectory.tk/&quot;&gt;https://breachdirectory.tk&lt;/a&gt; uses AI to monitor and parse new data breaches automatically. Just enter your email or username and it will tell you which of your passwords have been leaked and from where. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK? It&amp;#39;s important to make sure you are using passwords that have not been leaked before to protect yourself from account hijacking and credential stuffing attacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果一個女人在商店裏緊緊地跟着你，這意味着陪伴她們的人很可能在跟蹤她們。而且他們正在伸手尋求幫助。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：我在互聯網上一次又一次地看到它。通常是一個女人
走到他們不認識的人面前，身後跟着一個男人。如果
如果不是我的女朋友注意到，我可能不會注意到今天發生在我身上的事情。
今天發生在我身上。我在市場上買了一杯紅牛，然後有一個人跟着我。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n1hnyq/ysk_if_a_woman_is_following_you_closely_in_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n1hnyq/ysk_if_a_woman_is_following_you_closely_in_a/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 03:00:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I&amp;#39;ve seen it time and time again on the internet. Usually with a woman walking up to someone they don&amp;#39;t know, with a guy following behind her. If it weren&amp;#39;t for my girlfriend noticing I likely wouldn&amp;#39;t of noticed when it happened to me today. I was getting a Red Bull at the market, and a young girl came very close to me with who I thought was her boyfriend. I don&amp;#39;t pay much attention, and move out of their way because I figured they wanted to get to the drinks in front of me. I then walk 10 feet over to a cooler to get some salami motz rolls. And again, the girl is right by my side. It still didn&amp;#39;t click with me until my girlfriend whispered in my ear that this guy is stalking her. Apparently my girlfriend overheard him ask her how old she is, and she said &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m in High school&amp;quot; and him saying &amp;quot;Let&amp;#39;s get a coffee&amp;quot;. So I stood right there and didn&amp;#39;t say a word to either of them, until the guy ran off to the other side of the store. I watched the guy from there on, and made sure the girl wasn&amp;#39;t being followed by him afterwards and all was well. I will always notice the signs from here on out, and I hope you all will take notice too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK有一個叫 "Torch "的瀏覽器，它有一個內置的視頻下載器，適用於網絡上99%的視頻。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：標題 +它是基於chrome構建的，速度相當快。我在網上沒有找到很多關於它的信息
我在網上找不到很多關於它的信息，但人們似乎一致認爲火炬是安全的，但可能會記錄你的數據。
記錄你的數據。

我只是想給他們一個機會，因爲現在下載任何類型的視頻
是一個巨大的痛苦的屁股。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n16xs7/ysk_theres_a_browser_called_torch_that_has_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n16xs7/ysk_theres_a_browser_called_torch_that_has_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 22:37:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Title +Its built off chrome and is pretty fast. I couldn&amp;#39;t find much on the web about it but the consensus seems to be that torch is safe, but probably records your data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;just trying to throw them a bone because downloading any sort of videos nowadays is a huge pain in the ass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你正在照顧一個患有慢性病或殘疾的親人，有一些項目可以支付你成爲非熟練的護理人員的費用。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：你不應該在謀生和照顧你的親人之間做出選擇。
你所愛的人。你不需要證書或任何類型的認證就可以
成爲一個不熟練的護理人員。

我的祖母在一月被診斷出患有肺癌，而我祖父的癡呆症
已經變得非常糟糕。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n13iok/ysk_if_you_are_taking_care_of_a_loved_one_who_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n13iok/ysk_if_you_are_taking_care_of_a_loved_one_who_is/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:25:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: you shouldn&amp;#39;t have to choose between making a living and taking care of your loved one. You don&amp;#39;t need credentials or any type of certification to become an unskilled caregiver.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My grandma was diagnosed with lung cancer in January, and my grandpa&amp;#39;s dementia has gotten so much worse as a result. Its come to the point where they need someone there to help out and take care of them just about 24/7. I quit my job in February so I can take care of them full time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naturally, I was worried about how I was gonna make my bills every month. I refuse to choose one or the other and I made that decision as soon as I committed to taking care of them. They went above and beyond as far as helping raise me when I was a kid. My mother struggled with drug addiction for most of her life and they took me on to raise when I was about 8 without any hesitation, even though they were both past 65 at that point. They provided me with the opportunity to be stable enough to go on and graduate high school. So honestly I feel honored to have this opportunity even if the situation is shitty. Its the least I can do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you find yourself in a similar situation, just know that there are programs that will enable you to take care of your loved ones when they need you most without the possibility of becoming homeless in the process. Im sure the programs vary from state to state, Im in Texas and the program is through Medicaid. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone should know about this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你收到來自尼爾森家族的包裹，這不是垃圾郵件。很多時候，信封裏有2-5美元的現金。你可以通過寄來你所看的電視節目的記錄來賺取更多的錢。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我以前被選中過，賺了一點現金。爲什麼是YSK？你是在
扔掉了錢!]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0rr8m/ysk_if_you_receive_a_packet_from_the_nielsen/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0rr8m/ysk_if_you_receive_a_packet_from_the_nielsen/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 06:59:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been selected before and earned a small bit of cash. Why YSK? You’re throwing away money!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，在購買文胸時，它應該適合你的最後一個鉤子（給你最大的帶子）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：當購買一個新的文胸時，它應該適合最後一個鉤子，因爲帶子上的彈性會隨着時間的推移而自然伸展。
因爲帶子中的彈性會隨着時間的推移而自然伸展。你應該逐漸
逐漸將鉤子移到第一個鉤子上，這樣你的胸罩就會繼續適合你。
這樣你的胸罩就能在更長的時間內繼續適合你。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzavvd/ysk_that_when_buying_a_bra_it_should_fit_you_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzavvd/ysk_that_when_buying_a_bra_it_should_fit_you_on/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 04:47:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: When purchasing a new bra, it should fit on the last hook because the elastic in the band will naturally stretch over time. You should be gradually moving the hook in towards the first one as this occurs so that your bra will continue to fit you correctly for a longer span of time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你在郵箱的後面隨意看到一張幹紙，你的郵遞員把它放在那裏是有原因的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：它可以使你的承運人免於被刺傷

我是信使。

我們快到5月了，這意味着天氣好，在外面閒逛。
學校在夏季關閉，以及那些可惡的魔鬼的迴歸。
黃家駒和黃蜂。

我相信你已經注意到了。但是，爲了防止你...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0qs06/ysk_if_you_randomly_see_a_dryer_sheet_in_the_back/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0qs06/ysk_if_you_randomly_see_a_dryer_sheet_in_the_back/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 01:18:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: it could save your carrier from being stung&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Letter Carrier here. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re almost to the month of May which means nice weather, hanging out outside, school closing for the summer, and the return of those dastardly devils: Yellowjackets and Wasps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m sure you’ve noticed. But just in case you haven’t, this time of the year wasps and Yellowjackets (especially Yellowjackets) like to make nests inside of mailboxes. In a lot of places this time of the year, it’s just beginning to warm up outside, but it’s still fairly cold at night. So mailboxes provide nice, easy shelter for them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t tell you how many times, especially during this part of the year, where I’ve opened up a box to see a little nest with 3-5 Yellowjackets just chillin. If I’m really unlucky, they will have made their nest at the very back of the box so I wind up sticking my hand in not knowing they are there. We all know how temperamental these little douchebags are and merely existing in their presence is enough to piss them off. Last year alone I was stung 10 times on 10 separate occasions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getting to my point. We’ve found that they hate scented dryer sheets. If we encounter a box that is a problem for nests, we’ll often put one in there and it does the trick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So please, if you one day randomly see a dryer sheet at the back of your mailbox, just know that your carrier more than likely put it there to deter these Satanic creatures from building their home in it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK "每天 "與 "每天 "的區別]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK："每天 "意味着每24小時左右重複一次，"每天 "意味着
平凡、無聊或老套。這兩個詞之間的空格實際上改變了
使用正確的版本可以使你的意圖更加明確
並使人們不再認爲你是個白癡。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0mxr2/ysk_every_day_vs_everyday/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0mxr2/ysk_every_day_vs_everyday/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 23:50:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: &amp;quot;every day&amp;quot; means recurring every 24 hours or so and &amp;quot;everyday&amp;quot; means mundane, boring or trite. That space between the words actually changes the meaning of your sentence and using the correct version makes your intent clearer and stops people from thinking you&amp;#39;re an idiot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 在美國大多數州，法律上並不要求你在步行時進行酒精檢測。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：警察可以以公共場所醉酒的罪名逮捕你，如果，也只有當。
你同意接受呼氣式酒精測試，但你沒有通過測試。通常情況下，警察會
通常情況下，警察會開始告訴你如何接受
通常情況下，警官會開始告訴你如何進行呼吸式酒精檢測，而不會徵求你的同意。如果你善意地拒絕...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0e58r/ysk_you_are_not_legally_required_to_take_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0e58r/ysk_you_are_not_legally_required_to_take_a/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 21:47:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Police officers can arrest you for public intoxication if, and only if, you consent to taking a breathalyzer test and you fail the test. Typically, the officer will just start telling you instructions about how to take the breathalyzer without ever asking for consent. If you kindly decline the test, there is little they can do, assuming you have not broken any laws.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：一輛新車會迅速貶值。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼YSK：你可能要爲基本相同的汽車多付很多錢。

一輛新車和一輛使用了1或2年的二手車之間的價格差異很大。
是非常大的。因爲當你買了一輛車，它就會失去價值，因爲它不再是新的。
不再是新的，其次，大約在一年後，當下一個模型......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mw9wec/ysk_a_new_car_will_depreciate_in_value_rapidly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mw9wec/ysk_a_new_car_will_depreciate_in_value_rapidly/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 18:35:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;why YSK: you could be paying lots of extra money for essentially the same car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The price difference between a new car and one that is used and 1 or 2 years old is very big. Why? because when you buy a car it loses value because it&amp;#39;s no longer new, secondly just about after year when the next model releases it&amp;#39;s now  not a new car anymore and never will be. Suddenly your car has depreciated by a huge chunk it&amp;#39;s worth a LOT LESS. But by buying a used car you can skip those problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So just buy your dream car but buy one that is 1 or 2 years(or more) old.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，向食品救濟站捐錢是比捐贈食物更有效的捐贈方式。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：如果你想最大限度地發揮你能爲你的同胞帶來的積極影響
如果你想爲你的同胞帶來最大的積極影響，那麼捐贈現金而不是物品（尤其是食物）會更有效。
更爲有效。

例如，以下是向食品店捐贈金錢而不是食物的六個理由
儲藏室的六個理由。

 1. 1.金錢的儲存成本比食物的儲存成本低得多。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0i1cy/ysk_that_giving_money_to_food_pantries_is_a_more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0i1cy/ysk_that_giving_money_to_food_pantries_is_a_more/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 17:54:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  If you want to maximize the positive impact you can make for your fellow beings, then giving cash instead of goods (especially food,) can be much more effective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, here are six reasons for giving money instead of food to food pantries:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Money is much cheaper to store than food: less space; doesn&amp;#39;t need refrigeration; doesn&amp;#39;t require manual labor to manage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Even canned goods eventually expire. Cash doesn&amp;#39;t.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The types of food you give may not be what is needed by the recipient families. Everybody donates cans of beans. However, did you know that baby formula is one of the most needed foods? People tend to give what&amp;#39;s in their pantry, which just happens to be what they bought and haven&amp;#39;t eaten.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Food pantries get discounts on their purchases. They can make your dollars go farther in helping needy people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Food pantries have bills, too. They still pay rent, employees, transportation, utilities, just like any other operation. They can&amp;#39;t deliver their services without money to pay for those. It&amp;#39;s hard to convince the electric company to taken payment in cans of beans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Food pantries often do much more than provide food. Baby diapers, for example. Also, they will often help their recipients financially, such as utility bill assistance and housing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When giving cash, don&amp;#39;t forget to verify the legitimacy and effectiveness of the organization first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK可生物降解的塑料仍然會污染環境。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲了使可生物降解的塑料（不同於生物塑料）能夠適當地分解，它們需要以特殊的方式處理。
爲了使可生物降解的塑料（與生物塑料不同）正常分解，它們需要以特殊的方式進行處理。

> 這通常涉及到超過50°C的溫度和適當的水分、空氣和微生物的組合。
這通常涉及超過50°C的溫度和適當的水分、空氣和微生物的組合--這意味着這些塑料不會被分解...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0aa9f/ysk_biodegradable_plastics_can_still_pollute_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0aa9f/ysk_biodegradable_plastics_can_still_pollute_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 10:51:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;In order for biodegradable plastics (which are different from Bioplastics) to decompose properly they need to be disposed of in a special way:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt; This typically involves temperatures of over 50°C and the right combination of moisture, air and microbes – meaning that these plastics won’t break down if left in the ocean or on domestic compost heaps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencefocus.com/science/what-does-biodegradable-plastic-degrade-into/&quot;&gt;https://www.sciencefocus.com/science/what-does-biodegradable-plastic-degrade-into/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK? You should make sure when you dispose of Biodegradable plastics that they are being disposed of properly, just putting them in the trash is a bad idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK麥當勞的冰激凌機被製造得很容易損壞]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：麥當勞的員工不是在偷懶。冰淇淋機
似乎總是發生故障的冰淇淋機被設計成了故障。它們是有目的性的
因爲只要麥當勞要求維修，機器的製造商就會賺取利潤。
每當麥當勞要求他們維修時......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzx36r/ysk_mcdonalds_ice_cream_machines_are_made_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzx36r/ysk_mcdonalds_ice_cream_machines_are_made_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 23:50:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; McDonald&amp;#39;s employees are not being lazy. The ice cream machines that always seem to break down are designed to malfunction. They&amp;#39;re purposefully difficult for employees to fix because the machine&amp;#39;s manufacturer makes a profit whenever McDonald&amp;#39;s calls in their repair technicians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McDonald’s franchisees can only purchase one type of ice cream machine: the Taylor ice cream machine that’s specifically designed for McDonald’s. This particular machine is very difficult to repair. When it malfunctions, the screen shows a series of cryptic error codes. The manual is long, technical, and contains little helpful information. Most “solutions” it proposes end up being “call a technician.” McDonald’s has a contract with Taylor and franchisees can only call an authorized Taylor technician. The technician has their own handbook and secret menu to operate the machine. Employees are not allowed to have this better manual; only Taylor technicians can see it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Calling in a Taylor repairman costs the franchisee hundreds of dollars an hour. Despite the fact that Taylor has worked with the McDonald’s corporation since the beginning, none of their system updates help the problem. Some of them make the error codes longer and more cryptic. McDonald’s partnership with Taylor means that the corporate heads benefit from Taylor&amp;#39;s success. 25% of Taylor’s profits come from repairs. So when the machine breaks down, Taylor makes a profit repairing it, and the McDonald&amp;#39;s corporate leaders also profit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McDonald’s and Taylor continue to prioritize maximizing profit at the expense of franchisees, employees, and customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s a video released four days ago explaining the investigative journalism behind this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/SrDEtSlqJC4&quot;&gt;The REAL reason Mcdonald’s Ice Cream Machines are Always Broken&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，如果你是一個在家的父母，你所做的工作雖然沒有經濟價值，但當你付錢給別人做的時候，就會有很大的貨幣價值。你需要人壽保險。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：想象一下，花錢請人做你每天要做的事情一整年。
平均而言，一個保姆一年可以賺取約30,000美元，而日託服務的費用約爲100美元。
1萬美元，但這些費用並不接近你所提供的工作和努力的貨幣價值。
但這些費用並沒有接近你所提供的綜合工作和努力的貨幣價值。雖然，根據...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzv2n3/ysk_that_if_you_are_a_stay_at_home_parent_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzv2n3/ysk_that_if_you_are_a_stay_at_home_parent_the/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 22:55:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Imagine paying someone to do what you do every day for an entire year. On average, a Nanny can make around $30,000 a year, and daycare can cost around $10,000 per year, but these costs don’t get close to the monetary value of the combined work and effort you provide. Although, according to the economy, your work doesn’t hold economic value, your work is incredibly valuable and will cost a lot to replace. You need about 10x the cost of your work in term life insurance to cover the costs of the value that you provide to your kids and/or to your home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，當加油機告訴你要見收銀員時，你可以直接取消交易，將你的卡作爲信用卡運行。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK: 如果你不知道，一些加油站的加油機在你使用借記卡後會顯示 "請看
在你使用借記卡後，收銀員會說 "請看"。我已經聽到很多人
抱怨，說他們不想走進去，因爲他們是反社會的，或者說我自己是反社會的。
因爲他們是反社會的，或者我自己就是懶惰的。好吧，你是在...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mznm0s/ysk_that_when_the_gas_pump_tells_you_to_see_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mznm0s/ysk_that_when_the_gas_pump_tells_you_to_see_the/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 20:48:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK: If you do not know, some gas station pumps will say &amp;quot;please see cashier&amp;quot; after you use a debit card. I have been hearing a lot of people complaining about this saying they do not want to walk inside because they are either antisocial or I myself for instance am just lazy. Well you are in luck because I have never had to actually go inside the gas station because when that message appears simply hit the cancel button on the keypad and wait. Then reinsert your card and do not run your card as debit even though it is a debit card. There should be an instruction on how to run as credit and this is what you want to do. You may have to enter a zip code, you may not. Either way you now can pump your gas in peace without having to go inside. None of my friends or family knew this was possible and have been going inside to pay for their gas for as long as they can remember so I hope this helps someone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Someone said this is probably just a US/ North American issue! Sorry, I&amp;#39;m from a small town in Mississippi and can sometimes forget the world around me&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你認識一個有虐待行爲的人，而你告訴那個虐待者的受害者你不想站在哪一邊，那麼你就是站在了某一邊。你是在選擇施暴者的一方。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼YSK：對受害者說這句話是你試圖證明你的決定是正確的，或者直接以犧牲受害者的利益來使自己感覺更好。
你想證明你的決定是正確的，或者直接以受害者的利益爲代價讓自己感覺更好。停止吧。讓你的
做出選擇，處理所有當你發現你的朋友傷害了你時出現的奇怪感覺。
你的朋友傷害了其他人，而你自己卻沒有受到虐待......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzv3y6/ysk_if_you_know_someone_who_is_abusive_and_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzv3y6/ysk_if_you_know_someone_who_is_abusive_and_you/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 19:43:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: 
Saying that to a victim is you trying to justify your decision or make yourself feel better directly at the victim’s expense. Stop it. Make your choices, process all of the weird feelings that come up when you find out that your friend hurts other people on your own, without the abuse victim as your audience/feelingshelper. Don’t ask abuse victims for their blessing to keep your monthly “Abuser Bowling Night” going or do your processing of your feelings on their time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：擁有良好的姿勢和人體工程學實際上是非常嚴肅的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：不良的姿勢和人體工程學會導致很多令人驚訝的問題。
的問題，而且不會等到你年老的時候纔出現。
了。希望很多人已經知道這一點，但如果你像我幾個月前那樣
幾個月前，你可能認爲姿勢就像一些人認爲的......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzg70w/ysk_having_good_posture_and_ergonomics_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzg70w/ysk_having_good_posture_and_ergonomics_is/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 09:41:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Having poor posture and ergonomics can cause a lot of surprising problems throughout your body, and it doesn&amp;#39;t wait until you&amp;#39;re elderly to show up. Hopefully a lot of people know this already, but if you&amp;#39;re like I was a few months ago, you might think of posture like some people think of diet, sort of like &amp;quot;this won&amp;#39;t affect me until I&amp;#39;m older, so I don&amp;#39;t need to worry about it yet&amp;quot; (not that that&amp;#39;s a good mindset either).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some things that can happen from poor posture are degenerated discs, upper-crossed syndrome, thoracic outlet syndrome (this can result in blot clots and aneurysms, no lie), arthritis, all kinds of pinched nerves, fatigue, and many other painful conditions that can require physical therapy, medications, and even surgery.  I couldn&amp;#39;t find an academic article about this that fits well, but here&amp;#39;s something &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/adult-health/in-depth/posture-align-yourself-for-good-health/art-20269950&quot;&gt;from the Mayo Clinic&lt;/a&gt; about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To prevent these problems, you should of course have a proper ergonomic setup for work/gaming/whatever you&amp;#39;re doing. Sitting on a yoga ball or using a standing desk is a good idea. When driving, try to adjust your seat properly. Even when standing, walking around, and relaxing on your couch try to have your shoulder blades down and together, your shoulders back, and your neck back so that your ears align with your shoulders. Also, this is slightly unrelated, but drinking enough water everyday &lt;a href=&quot;https://cospineandjoint.com/2018/11/hydration-important-spinal-health/&quot;&gt;helps keep your spinal discs healthy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not in the medical field, so anyone who knows more about this is of course welcome to correct me on stuff. I just thought I&amp;#39;d spread the word in case it can help anyone prevent their own problems. I for one didn&amp;#39;t know all this before, and now I&amp;#39;m sitting here, only in my 20s, with tingly, tired arms and a heating pad on my shoulder because I had bad ergonomics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be well everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK以此開始掌握公開演講。公開演講是你的恐懼，還是你的感嘆？我想讓你知道這一點。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：熟練的公開演講可以提高你的自信和領導能力。
領導能力。你將需要它來管理人和領導未來的團隊。

十年來，在高達1000人的人羣中進行公開演講，讓我學到了很多東西。
自己和公開演講。這裏有一些要點可以幫助你。

-做到這一點。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/myaesj/ysk_this_to_begin_mastering_public_speaking_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/myaesj/ysk_this_to_begin_mastering_public_speaking_is/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 08:53:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Public speaking proficiently improves your confidence and ability to lead. You will need it to manage people and lead teams in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A decade of Public speaking to crowds up to 1000 people has taught me alot about myself and Public speaking. Here are some the points to help you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Do your prep, know your material.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Do your rehearsal without notes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Butterflys/anxiety:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have butterflys, 👍good. That feeling is great, it focuses you, adrenaline is preparing for a fight/flight. I do not feel that anymore so I actually take an energy drink immediately before an important class/presentation to simulate that hyperness (not reccomended for you), just embrace this feeling it benefits you and you will miss it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Getting sweaty/sick:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you feel nervous think about the guy in the back playing candy crush, why would you be afraid of him? He&amp;#39;s a jerk, not listening, but also not judging, just and oxygen thief.  The opposite is true as well, someone taking notes and making eye contact with you wants to hear what you have to say next and is supporting you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-The group you are speaking to is far smaller than you realize:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you get better you can command the room and have most people&amp;#39;s attention for small spans. You cannot have everyone&amp;#39;s attention for 20-30 minutes, people are just not wired that way. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Generally half of the audience isn&amp;#39;t listening, a good portion of the audience lack the mental capacity or self confidence to be judging you and listening to you at the same time.  The attentive ones you are able to make eye contact with are engaged and rooting for you, because they want to hear what&amp;#39;s next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this is some type of public speaking class where everybody is taking turns, 75% of the class you are speaking to has knots in their stomach about their own presentation and are reciting their nore cards in their head. The teacher, is a Saint and superhuman if you think they can focus on every word of 25 consecutive presentations about what someone did over summer vacation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-The person judging you most harshly is you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-You are going to crush it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在踩剎車之前，先把你的閃光燈打開]]></title><description><![CDATA[不要同時做這兩件事。

爲什麼是YSK：這不僅可以防止你被別人追尾
的追尾，而且還能大大增加
交通的流量。對卡車司機來說，要在一瞬間停下來是非常困難的
而且，同樣地，需要很長的時間來...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzd6bp/ysk_put_your_blinker_on_before_you_hit_the_brakes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzd6bp/ysk_put_your_blinker_on_before_you_hit_the_brakes/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 03:57:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t do both simultaneously. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK: Not only will this prevent you from getting rear-ended by someone driving &amp;amp; not paying attention behind you, but it&amp;#39;ll also greatly increase the flow of traffic. It&amp;#39;s extremely difficult for truck drivers to stop on a dime and, likewise, takes a long time to crawl back up to cruising speed (because their vehicles &amp;amp; their tow loads weigh a lot more than you realize they do). Learn how your vehicle operates. You are not the only one using the road. Everyone wants to make it to their destination on time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK表示，谷歌地圖將不再總是默認顯示你到目的地的最快路線。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：要記住檢查和選擇更快的路線，這很痛苦。
谷歌地圖開始默認顯示排放最輕的路線，而不是最短的旅行時間。
而不是最短的旅行時間。顯然，這只是在
兩條路線的ETA值相近，但近10分鐘是...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mz7nww/ysk_that_google_maps_will_no_longer_always_show/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mz7nww/ysk_that_google_maps_will_no_longer_always_show/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 23:44:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: it&amp;#39;s a pain having to remember to check and select the faster route.
Google maps is starting to default to displaying the route with the lightest emissions rather than the shortest travel time.
Apparently it&amp;#39;s only when the ETA for both routes is similar, but nearly 10 minutes is significant for my morning commute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：有大量的網站可以免費獲得科學文章、書籍、新聞報道和期刊! 鏈接如下:)]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：那些科學文章的付費牆是BS。這些錢都不歸屬於
實際的作者和研究人員。新聞文章的付費牆也很愚蠢。
幸運的是，這並不難。特別是如果你是一個學生。
這些網站都很不錯。

outline.com [https://outline.com/] - Place...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/myhvlk/ysk_there_are_tons_of_websites_to_get_scientific/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/myhvlk/ysk_there_are_tons_of_websites_to_get_scientific/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 13:45:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Those scientific article paywalls are BS. None of that goes to the actual authors and researchers. Paywalls on news articles are stupid too. Luckily, it&amp;#39;s not too hard to get around that! Especially if you&amp;#39;re a student, these sites are amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://outline.com/&quot;&gt;outline.com&lt;/a&gt; - Place &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.outline.com/&quot;&gt;www.outline.com/&lt;/a&gt; before any news article URL behind a paywall, and it&amp;#39;ll give you a non-ad-covered, annotateable, and easily shareable version!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://libgen.rs/&quot;&gt;libgen.rs&lt;/a&gt; - Library Genesis, a search engine for scientific articles, books, comics, and magazines&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sci-hub.do/&quot;&gt;sci-hub.do&lt;/a&gt; - Sci-Hub, specifically for research articles! You can stick in the URL or DOI and be taken right to the document!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://z-lib.org/&quot;&gt;z-lib.org&lt;/a&gt; - Z-library, another big search engine for books/articles!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For most of these, you don&amp;#39;t have to download the actual document unless you want to, you can read it in-browser as well! I&amp;#39;ve never had any issues with any downloads from these sites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，如果你帶着年幼的孩子去露營/遠足，避免給他們穿上迷彩服或中性色。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：孩子們在露營或自然郊遊時經常失蹤。給他們穿上
他們穿上迷彩服只會阻礙他們被找到，如果他們走失的話。
丟失。明亮的顏色更容易被找到，並使孩子在越野車和狩獵活動中更安全。
在越野車和狩獵活動中更安全。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/myof6t/ysk_if_youre_going_campinghiking_with_young/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/myof6t/ysk_if_youre_going_campinghiking_with_young/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 05:43:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Children go missing while camping or on nature outings often. Dressing them in camouflage will only hinder them from being found if they were to wind up lost. Bright colors are much easier to locate , and keeps the child safer around off road vehicles anf hunting activities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以《富爸爸，窮爸爸》一書而聞名的YSK金融大師羅伯特-清崎（Robert Kiyosaki）被參加過他的研討會的人提起集體訴訟，加拿大廣播公司（CBC）曾對他的騙局進行過曝光，他的公司Rich Global LLC於2012年申請破產。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：如果你正在閱讀一本自助書籍，那麼它很可能是由一個被證實的職業騙子或一個一生中唯一的成就是爲了賺錢的人寫的。
的人寫的，或者是那些在生活中唯一的成就是寫自助書的人。
寫自助書籍。他們的建議、CD、DVD、研討會、講習班都不會對你產生
對你沒有任何持久的影響。充其量，它們是安慰劑....。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mykdsy/ysk_financial_guru_robert_kiyosaki_known_best_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mykdsy/ysk_financial_guru_robert_kiyosaki_known_best_for/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 02:50:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If you are reading a self-help book, it is most likely written by a  proven professional scammer or someone who&amp;#39;s only accomplishments in  life are writing self-help books. Their advice, CDs, DVDs, seminars,  workshops will have no lasting impact on you whatsoever. At best, they  are placebos. People can be so gulable when searching for help. Do not  make the mistake of continuously looking for &amp;quot;that one self-help book&amp;quot;  that will change your life. Get better at doing searches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Research  the author&amp;#39;s background before reading a book. Question the &amp;quot;facts&amp;quot; you  are presented while reading a book. Make actions according to what  you&amp;#39;ve learned from a book, if there are any. Else, you&amp;#39;d be wasting a  lot of time reading trashy books while allowing trash into your mind and  then wonder why you&amp;#39;re feeling worse before you started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Kiyosaki&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Kiyosaki&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK-如果你聽到鈴聲或來自封閉的電梯或井道的蜂鳴聲，你應該打電話尋求幫助。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：大多數(所有)電梯在轎廂內都有一個 "報警 "按鈕，作爲在電話無法使用的情況下的二級警報。
如果電話不工作的話，有一個 "報警 "按鈕作爲輔助警報。這個按鈕會在轎廂內響起，發出嗶嗶聲，或者播放警報器
在轎廂內，偶爾也在一樓播放警報器。這可能意味着電梯
它可能意味着電梯被卡住了，而你聽到它可能是裏面的人的唯一辦法...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mya4j7/ysk_if_you_hear_a_bell_ringing_or_a_beeping_from/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mya4j7/ysk_if_you_hear_a_bell_ringing_or_a_beeping_from/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 18:17:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Most (all?) elevators have an &amp;quot;Alarm&amp;quot; button inside the cab as a secondary alert if the phone doesn&amp;#39;t work. This will ring, beep, or play a siren on the cab and occasionally on the ground floor. It could mean that the elevator is stuck, and you hearing it could be the only way those inside could get help. Call either the security or management of the building or facility or the local fire department.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK常見的小火類型，如何撲滅它們，以及如何操作滅火器。在電視上，人們在發生小火災時都會跑出屋外，但良好的做法可以拯救你的家。如果你有危險或火勢已經蔓延，一定要撥打911。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：如何識別和撲滅小火，因爲許多小火可以在蔓延之前就被預防。
因爲許多小火可以在蔓延之前防止造成重大損失或傷害。以下是一些最
的火災，以及如何撲滅它們。

A類火災。這種類型的火是由普通的燃料源點燃的，如木材。
垃圾、布料、紙張和其他物品。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/my3dmd/ysk_common_types_of_small_fires_how_to_put_them/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/my3dmd/ysk_common_types_of_small_fires_how_to_put_them/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 12:52:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: How to recognize and put out small fires because many can be prevented from causing major damage or harm before they spread. Here are some of the most common and how to put them out: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Class A Fires: This type of fire ignites from common fuel sources, like wood, trash, fabric, paper and plastics.  Extinguish with Water or a Red Fire Extinguisher.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Class B Fires: Result from an explosion of flammable liquids or gases. Extinguish by Depleting Oxygen. Smother but never try to put water on these fires as it will make the fire grow.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Class C Fires: Result from electricity. Extinguish by removing the power source. Know where your houses main breakers are. Use a red extinguisher to suppress flames once the electricity is out.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Class K Fires: Result from grease, lard, olive oil, butter, animal fats and vegetable fats. Do NOT extinguish with water as it will spread extremely fast. Use only a Chemical Fire Extinguisher. If you do not have one do not try to put out this fire alone. These flames burn extremely hot and spread fast. Call the fire department immediately and leave the area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One more tip: Many people don’t know that fire extinguishers can’t just be left under a cabinet indefinitely without some maintenance. Look at the gauge and make sure it’s in the green square. It it’s moving out of the green or starting to rust or leak, call your local FD on a non-emergency line and ask if they service extinguishers. Some do. The one I did was happy to as the community safety is the FD’s priority. Other than that they can tell you where to go in your community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 你不應該使用食品配送應用程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在一家三明治店工作，那裏有doordash和Uber Eats，但它們都是
但它們都相當相似。

爲什麼是YSK：在食品行業，你的利潤很低，所以當一個食品配送
服務說他們將從每筆銷售中抽取20-30%，這意味着你將在這筆銷售中賺不到錢。
那就意味着你在那筆交易中根本賺不到錢，畢竟...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/my2w00/ysk_you_shouldnt_use_food_delivery_apps/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/my2w00/ysk_you_shouldnt_use_food_delivery_apps/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 08:53:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I work for a sandwich shop that has doordash and Uber Eats but they all are fairly similar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: In the food industry you run on a thin margin so when a food delivery service says theya re going to take 20-30% from each sale that means you will essentialy make no money on that sale after all is said an done. If you care about the restaurants you order from use their app or call in and order and pick it up yourself. The companies that run these apps do not have a sustainable business model. If you look at these companies earnings they are all fairly young campanies heavily relying on investments and are yet see significant profit. Once these companies need to start functioning without the initial investment dollars you will see the prices rise even more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TDLR: by using delivery apps you are adding an unnecessary middleman that will cost you more and make the restaurant less money, don&amp;#39;t use food delivery apps if you care about the business you are ordering from&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(If you want to read more about it this areticle breaks it down even more:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eatthecapital.com/post/why-you-shouldn-t-be-ordering-from-grubhub-or-uber-eats&quot;&gt;https://www.eatthecapital.com/post/why-you-shouldn-t-be-ordering-from-grubhub-or-uber-eats&lt;/a&gt; )&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果把你的地址刻在AirTag/Tile或其他追蹤器上，你不應該把它掛在鑰匙上。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：一些公司提供免費的雕刻服務，因此許多人可能會被誘惑在追蹤器上寫上他們的詳細資料，甚至是他們的地址。
在追蹤器上寫上他們的詳細資料，甚至是他們的地址。

這似乎是有道理的，因爲追蹤器可能會耗盡電池或以某種方式損壞。
損壞，但是如果這個人有你的鑰匙和地址......。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx6nyy/ysk_you_should_not_get_your_address_engraved_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx6nyy/ysk_you_should_not_get_your_address_engraved_on/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 06:48:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Some companies offer free engraving so many people might be tempted to put their details on the tracker, perhaps even their address. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This might seem to make sense since the tracker could run out of battery or be damaged in some way, however if the person has your keys and address... they know where you live and could gain access to your house or vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，除了所有瘋狂的費用外，食品交付應用程序還擡高了菜單價格]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：從字面上看，現在就去Chipotle網站。一個捲餅碗將是
$8.20. 如果你去DoorDash、Ubereats等網站，同樣的捲餅碗將是
$9-11. 餐館被迫擡高菜單價格，因爲有20-30%的
送餐服務費。另一個誤導性的事實是，你的那些廣告...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mxwp26/ysk_that_food_delivery_apps_inflate_menu_prices/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mxwp26/ysk_that_food_delivery_apps_inflate_menu_prices/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 03:07:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Literally go on the chipotle website right now. A burrito bowl will be $8.20. If you go on DoorDash, Ubereats, etc. that same burrito bowl will be $9-11. Restaurants are FORCED to inflate menu prices because of the 20-30% delivery service fees. Another misleading fact is that those ads you see all the time for “free delivery” really mean “no delivery fee.” There are also 15-20% service fees, surge fees, and minimum cart fees. Sales taxes are also calculated differently from app to app! I usually avoid these fees by picking up the food myself or calling in my order for delivery. If I really want to splurge, I&amp;#39;ll order delivery, but because I&amp;#39;m cheap, I&amp;#39;ll use a food delivery aggregator. This &lt;a href=&quot;https://foodboss.org/&quot;&gt;aggregator&lt;/a&gt; has a website and compares Ubereats and Eatstreet. I used them for a while and saved a good amount of money. The only other option is this other &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mealme.ai/&quot;&gt;aggregator&lt;/a&gt; that compares DoorDash, Ubereats, GrubHub, Postmates, and some other ones. They messed up my first order but they gave me a promo code, so I&amp;#39;ve been using this one more since they compare more services. Whatever you choose, make sure to always tip-- the drivers definitely deserve/need it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在美國，說 "是的，先生 "或 "是的，女士 "與年齡沒有關係。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK。

我知道這是另一個帖子的翻版，但我想澄清，這並不是
只是一個南方的事情。這是一個美國的事情。

這在美國很少見，但有時來自其他國家的人（尤其是在歐洲北部）。
北歐或其他只講英語的國家的人）會被冒犯，就像
你是...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mxq14v/ysk_in_the_us_saying_yes_sir_or_yes_maam_has/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mxq14v/ysk_in_the_us_saying_yes_sir_or_yes_maam_has/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 20:38:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know this is a takeoff of another post, but I want to clarify that it&amp;#39;s not just a southern thing. It&amp;#39;s an American thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s rare in the U.S., but sometimes people from other countries (especially in Northern Europe or other only-English speaking countries) get offended, like you&amp;#39;re being too formal. It’s mostly just how we talk, but also shows respect for others. Americans say it to the 16 year old kid bagging the groceries because everyone deserves respect until they prove they don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Believe it or not, I have a lot of experience with this (fwiw, I live in NY and have been to the south for about 10 months). I personally don&amp;#39;t ever use &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am&amp;quot; because my mom specifically used it to kiss authority figures&amp;#39; asses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve talked to lots of other people from the UK, Australia, and Scandinavia, and they have identified &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am&amp;quot; as an outdated mode of address because it wasn&amp;#39;t egalitarian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I worked customer service at a Home Depot as a late teenager and insisted on never using &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am&amp;quot; in my day-to-day life (although there was one exception that I will explain later). I found that most people, but young people especially, would always address me as &amp;quot;sir.&amp;quot; I even told some of them &amp;quot;dude, there&amp;#39;s no need to call me that; my name is Explorer as you&amp;#39;ll see on my apron,&amp;quot; but the response was &amp;quot;yes sir.&amp;quot; They disregarded my request and continued to call me &amp;quot;sir,&amp;quot; which goes to show how ingrained these words are, even in New York.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One day, I was intrigued enough with the &amp;quot;sir&amp;quot; shit that I decided to take it to the other extreme. Instead of never using &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am,&amp;quot; I used them in every sentence I would say to a customer. Sometimes, I would go full metal jacket and use the &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am sandwich;&amp;quot; for example, I would say, &amp;quot;Sir, the ant killer is in aisle 38 sir.&amp;quot; Although the idea was ludicrous and insane, believe it or not, people fucking loved it, and I was called &amp;quot;sir&amp;quot; at least 50 times that day (I started counting at some point).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, for anyone from another country who is wondering about this, in the U.S., anyone who&amp;#39;s providing a service and any stranger of any age had best be seen as an authority figure and warrants &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am&amp;quot; and the commensurate degree of deference and formality. Most people in the U.S. who say &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m not old enough to be called &amp;#39;sir/ma&amp;#39;am&amp;#39;&amp;quot; will still get a warm feeling inside from being shown that respect. In fact, if you call these people (and most others) &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am&amp;quot; enough times, they will begin to address you in that way too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a formal nation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在沙發上放一個平坦的方形墊子，確保你的貓不會把毛髮弄到傢俱的其他地方。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：如果他適合，他就會坐下來，你就可以少花很多時間與沙發上的棉絨滾筒相處。
絨毛輥在你的沙發上。](https://imgur.com/gallery/iiQ8ffT)]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mxpfy8/ysk_putting_a_flat_square_cushion_on_the_couch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mxpfy8/ysk_putting_a_flat_square_cushion_on_the_couch/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 19:45:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If he fits, he sits and you get to spend a lot less quality time with a lint roller on your couches. ](&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/gallery/iiQ8ffT&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/gallery/iiQ8ffT&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，脫水會使你的血壓下降，這可能使你感到沮喪。這也會導致你的心臟跳動更厲害，引起焦慮。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：如果你已經容易患抑鬱症或焦慮症，脫水會使其感覺更糟糕。
感覺更糟，而且很容易誤事。因爲你沒有
因爲你沒有足夠的血量，你的身體更難維持血流。這
導致你的身體模仿抑鬱症的症狀（疲勞，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx96ip/ysk_that_being_dehydrated_drops_your_blood/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx96ip/ysk_that_being_dehydrated_drops_your_blood/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 03:04:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: if you are already prone to depression or anxiety, dehydration makes it feel much worse, and it&amp;#39;s so easy to do by accident. Because you don&amp;#39;t have enough volume of blood, its harder for your body to maintain blood flow. This causes your body to mimic the symptoms of depression (fatigue, brain fog, dizziness), which can cause you to think the depressed thoughts, causing your brain to make depression chemicals. When that makes you feel shitty enough, your heart will try to fix it by beating harder, raising your blood pressure, mimicking anxiety. Additionally, it becomes harder for your blood to carry oxygen, making you breathe harder, which for me is the one that causes me to panic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn&amp;#39;t a WoW tHaNkS iM cUrEd, but for me personally makes a huge difference. For hours today my anxiety was unmanageably high for no particular reason. After an almost-breakdown I chugged 20oz of water, took a few deep breaths, and 20 minutes later felt so much better it spawned me to write this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nopanic.org.uk/dehydration-anxiety/&quot;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This message brought to you by &lt;a href=&quot;/r/hydrohomies&quot;&gt;r/hydrohomies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，在網上購物時，同一個網店可以根據你所使用的設備顯示不同的價格。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：雖然聽起來很瘋狂，但你在網上購物時積累的數據
被網店用來確定他們認爲你願意支付的價格。
支付的價格! 你可以去同一個網站，看到不同的價格，這取決於你使用的設備。
你所使用的設備使用你的在線歷史作爲基礎....。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx5z1v/ysk_that_when_online_shopping_the_same_online/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx5z1v/ysk_that_when_online_shopping_the_same_online/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 01:49:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: As crazy as it sounds, the data you have amassed while online shopping is being used by online stores to determine prices they think you’re willing to pay! You can go to the same site and see different prices depending on what device you are using which uses your online history as a base. You can find a lot of articles online that talk about it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before you go online shopping, you should always clear your cache and history. You may even consider downloading a VPN or using a proxy server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I came across this information because one day I was online shopping with my husband while I was at work. We both had reported different prices and exchanged pictures. There was a $20 dollar difference! I searched it up, and sure enough it is a real problem. Do you self a favor and stay informed so that you don’t spend unnecessary extra money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I can’t say all websites do it, but I know that a good amount do. Just stay weary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在南方，說 "是的，先生 "或 "是的，女士 "與年齡沒有關係。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：這在南方很罕見，但有時來自其他地區的人
國家的人感到不快，好像你在說他們老。這主要是我們如何
說話的方式，但也顯示了對他人的尊重。我對16歲的孩子說這句話，因爲每個人都應該得到尊重。
因爲每個人都應該得到尊重，直到他們證明...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx7g8d/ysk_in_the_south_saying_yes_sir_or_yes_maam_has/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx7g8d/ysk_in_the_south_saying_yes_sir_or_yes_maam_has/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 01:49:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It&amp;#39;s rare in the south, but sometimes people from other parts of the country get offended, like you&amp;#39;re calling them old. It’s mostly just how we talk, but also shows respect for others. I say it to the 16 year old kid bagging the groceries because everyone deserves respect until they prove they don’t.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 吹噓自己從未請過病假，因爲你即使生病也會去工作，並不能使你成爲更好的員工。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：我經常聽到人們嘲笑其他人在生病時打電話給他們。
生病時打電話出去。

他們的評論通常是這樣的："我從不請假。我一定會來
即使我生病了，我也會來上班"。

這並不能使你成爲更好的員工或英雄。事實上，它使你成爲
恰恰相反。

它...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx4wdo/ysk_bragging_about_never_taking_a_sick_day/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx4wdo/ysk_bragging_about_never_taking_a_sick_day/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 22:56:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Often I hear folks ridiculing other for calling out of work when they are sick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The comment is usually along the lines of &amp;quot;I never call out of work. I will come to work even if I am sick.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That doesn&amp;#39;t make you a better employee or a hero. It in fact makes you the exact opposite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It shows that you&amp;#39;ve no care for your well being or the well being of others. It also shows that you&amp;#39;re willing to compromise a typically (mostly)sterile environment and possibly make others sick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay the f**k home, friendo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，如果你在車外生活，特別是帶着孩子，休息站是一個很好的睡眠場所。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：它們可能有點偏僻，而且根據你居住的地方
你可能需要支付一定的費用（岔路口等），但它們是安全的空間，24/7
但它們是安全的空間，可以使用衛生間，有時還有食物。沒有人會對你
睡在你的車裏，而且你一般不會被注意到......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mwyjrx/ysk_that_rest_stops_are_a_great_place_to_sleep_if/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mwyjrx/ysk_that_rest_stops_are_a_great_place_to_sleep_if/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 20:38:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: They might be a little out of the way, and depending on where you live you might have to pay a fee (turnpikes, etc), but they are safe spaces with 24/7 access to bathrooms, and food sometimes. Nobody will think twice about you sleeping in your car, and you generally will not be noticed because there are different people staying there every night. It&amp;#39;s a safe place if you are working and saving up, and especially if you have small children while doing so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 充滿回憶的腦袋和充滿遺憾的腦袋之間的區別是你原諒自己的能力。]]></title><description><![CDATA["爲什麼是YSK："人們常常爲他們過去所做的事情而責備自己，並且遺憾從內心開始吞噬他們。
遺憾開始從內部侵蝕他們。

他們無法超越那件事，他們的 "滿腦子的遺憾"
他們的 "滿腦子後悔 "使他們無法在未來成長併成爲一個更好的人。

人們應該原諒...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx0dkz/ysk_difference_between_head_full_of_memories_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx0dkz/ysk_difference_between_head_full_of_memories_and/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 19:45:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Why YSK:&amp;quot; People often blame themselves for what they did in the past and the regret starts eating them from inside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They aren&amp;#39;t able to move past that incident(s) and their &amp;quot;head full of regrets&amp;quot; makes it impossible for them to grow and become a better person in future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People should forgive themselves and try to create memories and not life long regrets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What happened, cannot be changed, they should move forward and become a better human being.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：即使你完全沒有服務，如果你遇到緊急情況，仍然可以撥打911。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：除非你是在地球中心或離任何中心數百英里的地方
任何城市，附近很可能有一個運營商網絡。


沒有服務，你還能打911嗎？

> 由於FCC的規定，網絡供應商必須傳輸緊急呼叫（911）。
> 無論你是否使用他們的服務，都必須傳輸緊急呼叫（911）。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mwf4au/ysk_even_if_you_have_no_service_at_all_still_call/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mwf4au/ysk_even_if_you_have_no_service_at_all_still_call/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 04:37:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Unless you are in the center of the earth or hundreds of miles off from any city, there is most likely a carrier network nearby.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Can you still call 911 without service?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to the FCC, network providers must transmit an emergency call (911) regardless of whether you use their service or not. This means if your provider doesnt have coverage in that area, your phone will show that it has no service. ... As long as it has battery power and can reach a signal, the phone can connect to 911.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.puretalkusa.com/blog/article?p=how-to-use-your-cell-phone-in-these-3-emergencies&quot;&gt;PureTalk USA via Google&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see so many damn people saying “and if you have no service” when being told to call 911. It’s unlikely it’ll happen, but this could very well save your life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK說，如果你關心蜜蜂，你就不應該在早春時節修剪或殺死草坪上的蒲公英。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：據專家介紹，在早春，蒲公英可以是一個重要的食物來源。
在經歷了漫長的冬季後，蒲公英可以成爲蜜蜂的重要食物來源，因爲它們要靠自己的儲備來生活。春天可以
春天對蜜蜂來說是一個困難時期，因爲它們在10攝氏度/50華氏度時開始活躍，這通常是在許多授粉的花朵綻放之前。
通常在許多授粉的花朵開花之前....。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mwerxp/ysk_that_if_you_care_about_the_bees_you_shouldnt/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mwerxp/ysk_that_if_you_care_about_the_bees_you_shouldnt/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 23:00:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: According to experts, in early spring dandelions can be a crucial food source for the bees after a long winter of living off their reserves. Spring can be a difficult time for the bees as they become active at 10C/50F, which is usually well before many pollinating flowers have bloomed. Dandelions grow early in the season in large numbers, and quickly generate lots of pollen for the bees to collect. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theweathernetwork.com/ca/news/article/heres-why-you-shouldnt-mow-dandelions-spring-lawn-care-benefits-and-save-bees&quot;&gt;https://www.theweathernetwork.com/ca/news/article/heres-why-you-shouldnt-mow-dandelions-spring-lawn-care-benefits-and-save-bees&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，房地產商的 "費用"--即銷售價格的百分比佣金結構已經過時，不應繼續使用。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：銷售價格的佣金收費結構只適用於20-30年前的房地產價格低得多的時候。
在房地產價格低得多、與工資關係更密切的時候
與工資密切相關。今天使用相同的價格結構（例如銷售或購買價格的3-7%）完全沒有意義。
價格的3-7%）是沒有任何意義的，不要讓...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mw9z7a/ysk_that_the_realtors_fee_aka_the_of_sales_price/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mw9z7a/ysk_that_the_realtors_fee_aka_the_of_sales_price/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 22:24:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Sales price commission fee structures were only applicable 20-30 years ago when the price of real estate was much, much lower and more closely related to salary. Using the same pricing structure today (e.g. 3-7% of sale or purchase price) does not make any sense whatsoever - and do not let a realtor convince you that it does!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most realtors today agree on lump sum payments for their services, and agreeing with your realtor on some pre-set price that has nothing to do with the value of your home is completely fine. There are still a few realtors that will prey on naive customers. The total cost of paying your realtor shouldn&amp;#39;t be more than what a paralegal or (at best) lawyer would charge in your area for a similar amount of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since we&amp;#39;ve had a crazy upward spiral in real estate prices recently, I&amp;#39;m seeing a lot of naive old people who agree with outrageous commission structure some realtors offer. No realtor is worth that much money, and don&amp;#39;t let them convince your grandparents that they are!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：呼吸法--度過恐慌期的簡單方法]]></title><description><![CDATA[呼吸練習的作用是根據你的呼吸深度和節奏來調整你的神經系統。
呼吸深度和節奏。這使得它們對高警覺性類型的情況非常有用
恐慌症發作和焦慮症發作等情況非常有用。

治療驚恐發作的呼吸法

 * 從你的鼻子吸氣4秒鐘。
 * 保持你的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mw2v7v/ysk_the_breath_method_simple_way_to_get_through_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mw2v7v/ysk_the_breath_method_simple_way_to_get_through_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 16:10:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Breathing exercises work by adjusting your nervous system according to your breathing depth &amp;amp; pace. Which makes them ultra useful for high-alertness type of situations like panic attacks and anxiety attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Breath Method for Panic Attacks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inhale from your nose for 4 seconds,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold your breath for 4 seconds,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exhale from your mouth for 6 seconds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And repeat this pattern for as long as you want. Focus on your bodily sensations, and affirm yourself in your mind that it&amp;#39;ll all be fine - because it really will!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Panic Attacks are the worst, but this might help you - as it did me and my friends &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So yeah. I&amp;#39;m aware of this exercise because of a breathing exercises app, and here&amp;#39;s the screenshot of the exercise (in case you have visual memory, or just save it on your phone): &lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/kNa4GdV.png&quot;&gt;Panic Button breathing exercise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: People have been asking me about the app, the app&amp;#39;s name is &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;Huma Breath&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;quot; - I use it on Apple but it should be available for Android too. There are other exercises for anxiety, sleep, energy etc too, recommend it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Btw, if you ever feel down or want to talk to someone, please feel free to PM me!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：'很多'不是一個詞。它是'很多'。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：這是最常見的錯別字之一，人們通過模仿來學習拼寫某些東西。
因此，這種癌症錯別字傳播得越多
就會有更多的人繼續把它弄錯。請加入我的努力，讓全世界都知道
世界知道 "a lot "是兩個詞，而不是一個。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvuuuq/ysk_alot_is_not_a_word_its_a_lot/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvuuuq/ysk_alot_is_not_a_word_its_a_lot/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 10:51:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This is one of the most common misspellings and people learn to spell certain things by example, therefore the more this cancer typo is spread around the more people will continue to get it wrong. Join me in my efforts to let the world know that &amp;#39;a lot&amp;#39; is two words, not one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，在夏季來臨之際，讓你的狗游泳要非常小心，藍綠藻是有毒的，往往對狗是致命的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：藍綠藻，或稱藍細菌，在適當的環境下，幾乎可以在任何淡水體中生長。
在適當的情況下，藍綠藻或藍細菌幾乎可以在任何淡水中生長。17個州報告了藍綠藻
相關的死亡事件，在2019年。你不能確定任何藻類是否有毒，所以
如果你打算靠近水，特別是停滯的水體...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvvz07/ysk_be_very_careful_letting_your_dog_swim_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvvz07/ysk_be_very_careful_letting_your_dog_swim_as/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 07:02:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  Blue green algae, or cyanobacteria can grow in nearly any body of fresh water under the right circumstances. Seventeen states reported blue green algae related deaths in 2019. You cannot be sure that any algae is or isn&amp;#39;t toxic, so if you plan on being near water especially stagnant bodies during warm weather take precautions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keep your dog leashed near bodies of water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Try not to let them drink any.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you notice any foam or films on the surface of the water it&amp;#39;s best not to let them swim or play in it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This toxin can be fatal very quickly and by the time your pet displays symptoms it&amp;#39;s often too late. There is no antidote, so look before you leap!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你去一家餐館，銀器上有水漬，這並不意味着銀器很髒。]]></title><description><![CDATA[所有這一切都意味着滾動銀器的人（可能甚至不是你的
的人（很可能甚至不是你的服務員）懶得去擦拭它。

爲什麼YSK：沒有必要要求新的銀器，尤其是當你的服務員
是很糟糕的。銀器是乾淨的! 它只是在經過清洗後溼漉漉地放了一會兒
通過清洗]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvtoh7/ysk_if_you_go_to_a_restaurant_and_there_are_water/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvtoh7/ysk_if_you_go_to_a_restaurant_and_there_are_water/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 05:51:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;All it means is the person who rolled the silverware (likely not even your server) was too lazy to polish it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: it’s unnecessary to ask for new silverware, especially if your server is slammed. The silverware is clean! It just sat out wet for a bit after going through the wash&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：母親節是5月9日（還有18天）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：如果你打算在網上訂購東西，這是一個好時機。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvubbt/ysk_mothers_day_is_may_9th_in_18_days/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvubbt/ysk_mothers_day_is_may_9th_in_18_days/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 05:01:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It&amp;#39;s a good time to order things online if you intend to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，淫羊藿是大量破壞性和非法交易的對象。詢問供應商的來源可能會有幫助。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：因爲多肉植物是比較獨特的植物品種之一，它們已經成爲 "偷獵 "的目標。
它們已經成爲 "偷獵 "的目標。許多人認爲他們在幫助
許多人認爲他們在購買這些植物時是在幫助保護這些物種，但如果助長非法供應，就會無意中傷害它們。
助於非法供應。可以找到更多信息...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvn7ix/ysk_that_succulents_are_the_subject_of_a_great/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvn7ix/ysk_that_succulents_are_the_subject_of_a_great/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 21:47:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: because succulents are one of the more unique varieties of plants out there, they&amp;#39;ve become a target for &amp;quot;poaching.&amp;quot; Many people think they&amp;#39;re helping preserve the species when they purchase them, but can inadvertently hurt them if contributing to illegal supply. Some more info can be found in this piece by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KirP2ef1lJ0&quot;&gt;Cheddar&lt;/a&gt;. Ultimately, it&amp;#39;s OK to have succulents! But if we want them to stay around, it&amp;#39;s good to spread info on best-buying habits. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a post on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/interestingasfuck&quot;&gt;r/interestingasfuck&lt;/a&gt; that showed off a living rock cactus, which is a common victim of illegal trade. Made me think I should share the video I had recently seen on it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK拯救蜜蜂組織更關注原生蜜蜂而不是蜜蜂]]></title><description><![CDATA[蜜蜂沒有消亡的危險；許多本地蜜蜂都瀕臨滅絕或受到威脅。
受到威脅。我在網上看到很多帶有 "拯救蜜蜂 "標題的帖子
我在網上看到很多帶有 "拯救蜜蜂 "標題的帖子，都是以蜜蜂和養蜂爲主題。

爲什麼YSK：很多人對蜜蜂而不是本地蜜蜂感興趣。
蜜蜂。努力幫助...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mv8dcp/ysk_save_the_bees_focuses_more_on_native_bees/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mv8dcp/ysk_save_the_bees_focuses_more_on_native_bees/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 13:42:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Honeybees are in no danger of dying out; lots of native bees are endangered or threatened. A lot of post I&amp;#39;ve seen online with &amp;#39;save the bee&amp;#39; captions have been focusing on honeybees and beekeeping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Lots of people are taking an interest in honeybees rather than native bees. Efforts to help honeybees often end up hurting native bee populations. If you&amp;#39;re able, plant native plants and wildflowers, go pesticide free, buy/build nesting houses, and find out about local conservation efforts. Native bees are an essential part of local ecosystems and are necessary pollinators.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 使用藍牙追蹤器應用程序來定位誤放的物品、耳機和設備是很容易的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：包括我在內的很多人都容易把物品放錯地方，比如鑰匙。
耳機（如AirPods），甚至是手機。一個好的藍牙追蹤應用程序可以
幫助定位物品和設備。今天的大多數設備都內置了藍牙
並且可以很容易地找到。對於鑰匙和其他日常用品，你可以...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mv2w3k/ysk_its_easy_to_use_a_bluetooth_tracker_app_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mv2w3k/ysk_its_easy_to_use_a_bluetooth_tracker_app_to/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 05:00:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: A lot of people including me tend to misplace items like keys, headphones (like AirPods), or even phones. A good Bluetooth tracking app can help locate items and devices. Most of the devices today have Bluetooth built in and can be easily located. For keys and for other everyday items, you can use trackers like Tile or the recently announced Apple AirTag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>