<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 04:40:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如果你乘坐的飞机坠入水中，在你离开飞机之前不要给你的救生衣充气。在下沉的飞机上给你的救生衣充气会导致你漂浮并被困住。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：在为水上作业配备的飞机上进行安全演示时
空服员会告诉你，在飞机上不要给你的救生衣充气，直到
在飞机外面。这不仅是因为在飞机上这样做会
占用其他疏散人员的空间，而是因为在快速填充的情况下...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pyqcze/ysk_if_youre_ever_in_a_plane_that_crashes_into/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pyqcze/ysk_if_youre_ever_in_a_plane_that_crashes_into/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 21:35:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; During the safety demonstrations on aircraft equipped for overwater operations flight attendants will tell you to not inflate your lifevest until outside the aircraft.  This is not only because doing so in the aircraft will take up space for other evacuees, but because in a rapidly filling aircraft your lifevest can cause you to become pinned to the ceiling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你在冬天与极度寒冷的手作斗争，你的医生可能能够帮助你。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：我在成年后的大部分时间里，在任何低于10C（50F）的环境中，都与麻木/冰冷的手作斗争。
在我成年后的大部分时间里，只要环境温度低于10摄氏度（50华氏度），我的手就会麻木/冰冷。我不得不使用
我不得不在冬天使用手套和化学暖手器的组合，因为我的手仍然不能保持温暖。
因为我的手戴着普通的手套仍然不能保持温暖。我以为这只是一个...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pym44m/ysk_that_if_you_struggle_with_extremely_cold/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pym44m/ysk_that_if_you_struggle_with_extremely_cold/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 17:44:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I&amp;#39;ve struggled with numb/cold hands in quite literally any ambient temperature less than 10C (50F) for most of my adult life. I had to use a combination of mittens and chemical hand warmers for winter, because my hands still wouldn&amp;#39;t stay warm in regular gloves. I thought this was just a miserable quirk that I couldn&amp;#39;t change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it came up at a doctor&amp;#39;s appointment randomly, the doc said that this is classic Raynaud&amp;#39;s Phenomenon (previously I thought that just meant purple hands, and mine were never as purple as the pictures), and that the issue with cold is absolutely treatable! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was put on an extremely low dose of a calcium channel blocker (hopefully &lt;a href=&quot;https://emedicine.medscape.com/article/331197-treatment&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; is an okay citation) to open my blood vessels a bit, and the doc said that alternatives are available if that isn&amp;#39;t enough. So far, though, I&amp;#39;ve have huge improvements in numbness and have been able to go without gloves in fall weather, which I could not do before!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, the bottom line - if you struggle with something like this, YOU ARE NOT DOOMED TO BE MISERABLE. It&amp;#39;s worth bringing up to a medical professional!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 你的雇主可以看到你在工作电脑上的一切行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：你的雇主越大，他们的安全预算就越大，而且
他们必须保留更多的记录。
包括你在电脑上所做的一切。我在网络安全和
我在网络安全与合规部门工作，有很多人根本没有意识到这一点。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pykc5x/ysk_your_employer_can_see_everything_you_do_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pykc5x/ysk_your_employer_can_see_everything_you_do_on/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 16:34:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: The bigger your employer, the bigger their security budget and regulatory compliance requirements AKA they have to keep more records, which includes everything you do on your computer. I work in Cybersecurity &amp;amp; Compliance, and the number of people who simply don&amp;#39;t realize the extensive tooling and visibility that is maintained on &amp;quot;company-issued&amp;quot; devices is too damn high. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This might sound like common-sense, and i used to think it was, but people use &amp;quot;incognito&amp;quot; or whatever and think its private - nothing is private on a managed device. 95% of my investigations always turn up something stupid someone did on their device, and yes, thats ammo in court if you&amp;#39;re ever in litigation. nuff said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为沉默的停顿在对话中是正常的；它们并不总是意味着有问题。对我们大多数人来说，急于填补沉默是相当典型的，但学会如何适应沉默将使你的脚离开你的嘴，给你时间思考。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么YSK：沉默被一些人认为是消极的，但我们需要
但我们需要把沉默更多地看作是一种放慢速度和思考我们的反应的方式。如果我们能接受别人的沉默，就会有帮助。
如果我们能够接受别人的沉默是 "思考的时间 "而不是
"判断 "或 "不同意"。我们中的一些人倾向于喋喋不休，当我们在...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pybhf0/ysk_that_silent_pauses_are_normal_in_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pybhf0/ysk_that_silent_pauses_are_normal_in_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 05:43:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Silence is considered to be negative by some people, but we need to think of silence more as a way to slow down and think about our responses. It helps if we can accept other people&amp;#39;s silences as &amp;quot;time to think&amp;quot; instead of &amp;quot;judgement&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;disagreement.&amp;quot; Some of us tend to chatter when we&amp;#39;re nervous or whenever there&amp;#39;s a lull in the conversation, but filling the silence just clutters the conversation and interrupts whatever thoughts the speaker is putting together internally.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should also know that staying silent yourself from time to time during a conversation can give you a micro-dose of social power -- use it wisely, though, or it could be mistaken for arrogance or manipulation (because &amp;quot;the silent treatment&amp;quot; is juvenile and unproductive). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;tbc, I&amp;#39;m not suggesting long, uncomfortable, squirm-in-your-chair silences -- but pauses that are long enough to give you and others time to think before replying (something we don&amp;#39;t do enough). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many appropriate times to take a silent pause during a conversation. For example, &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Silence is quite effective when you&amp;#39;ve made a statement but someone wants to argue with you about it, especially if you didn&amp;#39;t say it to start a debate, such as a decision you&amp;#39;ve made or an opinion you hold. Your silence holds firm and solidifies your statement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Silence is also appropriate after asking someone a question, to give them time to think &amp;amp; process their answer. Consider, they may be going over several possible answers in their minds and need time to think, although we might feel impatient because we were already prepared with our question. Also, it&amp;#39;s not necessary to chatter on about the question while they&amp;#39;re thinking about it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Another useful time for silence is while listening to someone talk, which includes silencing your thoughts and mindfully listening instead of planning the next thing you want to say.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; It&amp;#39;s also respectful to be quiet for a few moments after someone has finished what they want to say about a topic, making sure they&amp;#39;re finished and that you&amp;#39;re digesting what they&amp;#39;ve said. Taking time before speaking shows that you were listening rather than waiting impatiently for your turn to speak.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 包包对小偷来说就像彩票，你不应该把它们留在你的车里。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：把背包、钱包、公文包或其他袋子放在车内，是对砸窗小偷的公开邀请。
是对砸窗盗窃者的公开邀请。你可以避免更换
你可以避免更换你的车窗、包和其他被盗的贵重物品，方法是把你的包带走或放在后备箱里。
把它放在后备箱里，就可以避免更换车窗、包和其他被盗的贵重物品--这样做只需要几秒钟。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/py6pi7/ysk_bags_are_like_lottery_tickets_for_thieves_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/py6pi7/ysk_bags_are_like_lottery_tickets_for_thieves_and/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 03:36:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Leaving backpacks, purses, briefcases, or other bags in your car is an open invitation for window-smashing thieves. You can avoid having to replace your windows, bags, and other stolen valuables by taking your bag with you or putting it in your trunk instead – the few seconds it takes to do so is worth as much as what you paid for it, if not more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To a thief, a bag in a car is full of valuable stuff at best, and a new bag to cram other stolen stuff into at worst. Even if it looks empty, it could still have a laptop, a gun, a camera, a Nintendo Switch, or any number of other expensive, pawnable things in it. If it&amp;#39;s a designer bag, the bag itself may be worth selling. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t assume it won&amp;#39;t happen to you, especially if you live in a big city.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，在大多数司法管辖区，攻击罪意味着你威胁别人，而不是真的攻击他们。]]></title><description><![CDATA[每当有一个白痴无缘无故打人的视频出现，或
吐口水或其他非法接触的视频，所有的评论都会大喊
喊出 "这是攻击行为！"

我知道我对这个问题感到困扰是非常迂腐的，但这是一个
殴打。是的，一些司法管辖区有...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/py0sv5/ysk_that_in_most_jurisdictions_the_crime_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/py0sv5/ysk_that_in_most_jurisdictions_the_crime_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 02:14:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every time there is a video of an idiot punching someone for no good reason or spitting on them or otherwise making unlawful contact, all the comments yell out: &amp;quot;That&amp;#39;s assault!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know it&amp;#39;s incredibly pedantic of me to be bothered by this, but that is a battery. Yes, some jurisdictions have different definitions, but in most places and under common law, assault means a credible threat to commit a battery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: so that you use the correct legal term when describing the behavior of the lunatics in viral videos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如果我没有路权，就不要给我让路!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道你是想做个好人，但你不可预知的驾驶行为会让其他人感到不安。
人处于危险之中。

为什么是YSK：虽然人们在应该让步的时候不让步的情况更常见。
自从搬到加州后，有好几次我在停车场等待停车的时候
当我在停车场等待停车的时候，有好几次都有人硬要...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/py6zmk/ysk_if_i_dont_have_the_right_of_way_dont_yield_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/py6zmk/ysk_if_i_dont_have_the_right_of_way_dont_yield_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 01:16:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know you are trying to be nice but your unpredictable driving can put other people at risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: While people not yielding when they should yield is much more common, several times now since moving out to California when I&amp;#39;ve been waiting to pull out from a parking lot I&amp;#39;ve had people hard brake on busy roads in order to let me &amp;quot;safely&amp;quot; make a left hand turn. The first time it happened I was taken off guard, but no one was behind the car that randomly decided to yield so it was ultimately fine. The second time on the other hand, multiple cars had to slam on their brakes to accommodate for the driver who randomly decided to stop in the middle of the road to let me turn. Now if I was edging out into the road, looking like I was going to dart in front of the incoming traffic, I could understand why people might slow down or even yield just to be safe, but on both occasions I was at a full stop and not in the main road at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once again, I know you&amp;#39;re trying to be polite but you&amp;#39;re just making the road more dangerous for other drivers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为男人很少接受赞美（来自男人或女人），而给他们一个赞美绝对可以改变他们的整个一天。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：作为一名女性，我喜欢提升其他女性的地位。我的个人目标是
我的个人目标是每天赞美10次，无论是在人前还是在网上，但我很少赞美男人。
由于过去从一个男人手中获得的创伤，我很少赞美男人，现在我有一种
现在我对他们有一种普遍的恐惧。我正在接受治疗，并努力解决这个问题。总之，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/py0fbz/ysk_that_men_very_rarely_are_on_the_receiving_end/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/py0fbz/ysk_that_men_very_rarely_are_on_the_receiving_end/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 19:43:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: as a woman, I love lifting other women up. I make it a personal goal to give 10 compliments per day either in person or online BUT I very very rarely compliment men due to past trauma from the hands of a man and now I have a general fear of them. I am in therapy and working on it. Anyway, today at the gym, a gentleman had a really cool shirt on that said “train everything” and it caught my eye. I didn’t say anything because I was scared I’d be seen as flirting or he’d see it as an excuse to flirt with ME and I didn’t want that. So I stayed silent. But, when I ran into him again at the water fountain I shoved my fears down and said &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Hey I really like your shirt!!! And it fits you so well!” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AND MY GOD YALL!!! The SMILE I got from this man! He was absolutely BEAMING. He just said “wow thank you so much!” And that was it. I couldn’t believe how incredibly happy he looked. I’ve seen that look from women before but not nearly as drastic. He looked like a starving man who was just offered a steak dinner. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It made me realize that while I am still very scared of men from my past trauma, 99% of them are just humans who deserve compliments just like women BUT… they don’t get them very often. Like it’s difficult for a cis man to compliment another man, especially on his body or attire, because it might be seen as &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;GASP&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; “gay”. And while that is an issue that also needs addressed, I think we, as women, can do our part too. Of course always stay safe and trust your gut, but let’s compliment some men together!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，大多数头盔（用于骑自行车、滑板、滑雪等）内部都有一个坚硬的泡沫，可以皱缩以吸收冲击力，但一旦皱缩，就不会再反弹了。你的头盔在经历了几次大的跌倒后，最终会停止保护你。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：这样你和你的孩子就不会死。

头盔里装的是所谓的EPS泡沫（发泡聚苯乙烯）。EPS是一种
非常轻但坚硬的泡沫，类似于发泡胶。一旦你使它变形或压碎，它就会保持这种状态。
它就会保持这种状态。

来自epsindustry.org。

> 与其他类型的填充物不同，EPS泡沫不会反弹......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pxqvzd/ysk_that_most_helmets_for_biking_skateboarding/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pxqvzd/ysk_that_most_helmets_for_biking_skateboarding/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 13:42:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: so you and your kids don&amp;#39;t die.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Helmets are filled with what&amp;#39;s called EPS foam (expanded polystyrene). EPS is a very light but stiff foam similar to styrofoam. Once you deform or crush it, it stays that way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From epsindustry.org:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike other types of padding, EPS foam does not bounce back after a compressing impact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This means it&amp;#39;s better at absorbing impact than a softer foam, which is good for protecting your head. But after an impact, that foam is crushed at that spot and no longer able to absorb any impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From off.road.cc:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to tiny impact after tiny impact over time, the EPS will gradually lose its volume making it less able to deal with the energy in the unfortunate event of an impact. Of course the more the helmet is used the more it will deteriorate, so one rule for all does not work here, but three years is a good guide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Replace your bike helmets after every big fall.
Replace your skateboard/ski/snowboard helmet after a few big falls.
Someone let me know about motorcycle helmets, I assume you wanna replace that after 1 fall.
Replace your helmets every 3 years even if you have no falls or minor falls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: Some great extra notes from the comments:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bike helmets are designs for 1 fall.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sturdier helmets like for skating or snowboarding can take a few more falls.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dropping your helmet is the same as falling on it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sources:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://epsindustry.org/other-applications/safety-devices&quot;&gt;http://epsindustry.org/other-applications/safety-devices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://off.road.cc/content/feature/when-should-you-replace-your-bicycle-helmet-1280&quot;&gt;https://off.road.cc/content/feature/when-should-you-replace-your-bicycle-helmet-1280&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 假设你工作的公司可以看到（和听到！）你在WFH时做的一切。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：这些信息可以被用来解雇你，并拒绝你的
加薪/升职。目光短浅的人力资源部门越来越多地使用这个
软件作为衡量你对公司价值的首要指标。

请参阅本篇文章的底部，了解你可以做些什么来保护自己免受...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pxtjse/ysk_assume_that_the_company_you_work_for_can_see/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pxtjse/ysk_assume_that_the_company_you_work_for_can_see/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 13:42:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; This information can be used to fire you, and to deny your raise/promotion.  Shortsighted HR departments are increasingly using this software as the leading indicator of your value to the company &lt;em&gt;above all else.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See the bottom of this post for things you can do to protect yourself from this idiocy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why I wrote this:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was shocked at the response when I mentioned this concept in a prior comment.  Many people this affects are wholly unaware.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently, someone I know was fired FOR CAUSE due to their &amp;quot;lack of engagement, and unprofessional conduct.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a little insight into what that means by way of some work buddies, and personal review of the software that was used because her boss is a narcissistic assclown who was so proud of himself that he showed me the tools that were used.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This all began because the software on her computer flagged a word in a &amp;quot;private&amp;quot; Teams chat with a colleague which started the boss down a vindictive road of parallel construction - eventually lead to her termination.  That word was &amp;quot;ass.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A quick summary:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Bossware&amp;quot; has been something companies could use for over a decade, but the bastards have integrated other Orwellian stuff like facial recognition to monitor your mood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2020/06/inside-invasive-secretive-bossware-tracking-workers&quot;&gt;Here is an in-depth article about it from EFF.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theladders.com/wp-content/uploads/02-How-Employers-Monitor-Employees.png&quot;&gt;This is a one-pager about it.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/5JiyAfT.png&quot;&gt;This is a comparison of a handful of bossware&amp;#39;s features.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theladders.com/career-advice/bossware-report-when-wfh-means-the-boss-is-watching-what-bosses-see-how-to-prevent-it&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12% of all firms have already installed it (16% at larger firms), and 8% already plan to implement it (11% at larger firms). Tracking software like this has an ominously William Gibson-esque nickname: bossware.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, bosses may use unpublicized features of their corporate email package to look out for trigger words in your emails. Or they may use dedicated bossware to check that you’re actually at your computer when you say you are.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Employers can install hidden software on your device that tracks your movements via GPS, all SMS messages and other messaging app usage, and can even record calls and Skype interactions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There is a nonzero chance that:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your webcam is taking periodic screenshots, or even video of you and your surroundings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your mic is &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; &amp;quot;hot.&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your calls are &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; recorded.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your chats and emails are &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; scraped for keywords.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your keystrokes, and mouse movements are &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; tracked.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your &amp;quot;engagement&amp;quot; is &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; monitored to the millisecond.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I emphasize the word always because software doesn&amp;#39;t sleep.  Humans don&amp;#39;t see everything at all times.  The key here is that a human is flagged for nonsensical things by the software, and that human can really pick you apart from there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Some basic stuff you can do to protec&amp;#39; ya&amp;#39; neck:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shut your computer down after work.  A device that&amp;#39;s off has very low risk of snooping during time you don&amp;#39;t even get paid for &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reconsider having personal sidechats with your coworkers on company hardware.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cover your webcam when not in use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get your own headset with a hardware mute button and leave it muted until you need to speak.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Move your mouse if you are idle during a listening task like an all hands call.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Type things frequently.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;#39;t browse anything that isn&amp;#39;t 100% work related on company hardware.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All else fails - get another job, and let your boss know why after the new contract is signed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**Edited to add something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，直视前方，远望前方可以防治晕车。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在我的成长过程中，我总是超级晕车。任何超过10分钟的车程我都会感到
恶心，超过30分钟我通常会呕吐。但一个超级有用的提示
是直视前方，这有助于平衡耳朵里的液体。
这有助于平衡你耳朵里的液体，否则会导致晕车。这也是我的经验之谈。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pxqiuy/ysk_that_staring_straight_and_far_ahead_can/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pxqiuy/ysk_that_staring_straight_and_far_ahead_can/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 10:43:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Growing up I got super car sick all the time. Any drive over 10mins I would feel nauseous and anything over 30 I would usually throw up. But a super helpful tip I learned to combat it is looking straight ahead, this helps balance the fluids in your ear that otherwise would cause car sickness. It also helps to stare at something far ahead. Since it is far it seems to move less and is less visually nauseating. However car sickness medication can do wonders as-well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: sometimes you get carsick when you normally don’t and need to not throw up. Or you get carsick often and need help. Or you forgot the medicine you normally take. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also would love to hear more tips in the comments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你想买一个智能恒温器，LED灯泡，或其他节能产品，请查看你的电力供应商的网站，YSK。他们可能有产品的回扣，可以为你节省很多钱。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：在伊利诺伊州，我们有ComEd公司为我们提供电力。在他们的
网站[https://secure.comed.com/marketplace/category/comed_smart_thermostats]
他们也有一个市场，有很多产品都有即时回扣。
现在，你可以用1美元买到Nest恒温器，而且大多数的产品都可以用。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/px6pwi/ysk_if_youre_looking_to_buy_a_smart_thermostat/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/px6pwi/ysk_if_youre_looking_to_buy_a_smart_thermostat/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 09:17:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Here in Illinois we have ComEd that supplies our electricity. On their &lt;a href=&quot;https://secure.comed.com/marketplace/category/comed_smart_thermostats&quot;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; they also have a marketplace with a bunch of products that have instant rebates. Right now you can get a Nest thermostat for $1 and most other thermostats are $100 off. You can also save quite a bit of cash if you&amp;#39;re looking to replace your light bulbs with LEDs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK的半自动驾驶规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：半挂车是一种无情的致命野兽，不尊重它可能是你做的最后一件事。
尊重它可能是你做的最后一件事。如果出了差错（确实如此），你会被抓起来。
它确实如此），而你被卷入交火中，你会死的。

规则一：半成品总是赢。总是如此。

规则2：当在高速公路上，保持你的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pxfpha/ysk_the_rules_for_driving_with_semi_trucks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pxfpha/ysk_the_rules_for_driving_with_semi_trucks/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 02:39:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: The semi truck is an unforgiving and deadly beast, and failing to pay respect to it may be the last thing you ever do. If something goes wrong (which it does), and you are caught in the crossfire, you will die. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rule #1: &lt;strong&gt;The semi always wins. Always.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rule #2: When on the freeway, keep your distance from the semi. As a rule of thumb, if you can read the license plate, you&amp;#39;re too close. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rule #3: When passing, do so as quickly as possible. If they are passing you, slow down. If you are passing them, speed up. Driving next to a semi is one of the most dangerous places you can be for multiple reasons, and therefore is a place you don&amp;#39;t want to be. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rule #4: When lane-shifting in front of the semi, make sure that you do so at a safe distance. If you shift too close, you may scare the driver, and they may swerve to avoid you. In general, if you can see both of the semi&amp;#39;s headlights in your side mirror, you&amp;#39;re at a safe distance to move. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rule #5: The semi has very large blind spots. Don&amp;#39;t be in them. They can&amp;#39;t check their blind spots very well, so a lane shift may very well shove you off the road. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rule #6: Sometimes, semis will need to take &amp;quot;Wide turns&amp;quot;, which essentially means that they can&amp;#39;t use the rightmost lane to take a right turn-they need to move one over. If you are at an intersection and have a semi next to you, don&amp;#39;t start moving as soon as the light changes-wait to see if the semi makes the first move, and confirm where they are going before making yours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK Uber Eats不再为丢失的食物退还现金。他们只向你的账户提供 "Uber现金 "积分。]]></title><description><![CDATA[YSK：通常情况下，餐馆会纠正他们的错误，给你正确的食物，从账单中扣除一些东西，或退还你的一部分钱。
食物，从账单中扣除一些东西，或者退还一部分钱。真正的
现金当然更有用，而且限制更少。

但是Uber eats现在只给小的Uber现金积分，只能用...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/px9hfr/ysk_uber_eats_no_longer_refunds_cash_for_missing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/px9hfr/ysk_uber_eats_no_longer_refunds_cash_for_missing/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 18:49:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Normally restaurants will correct their mistake by giving you the right food, taking something off the bill, or refunding a portion of your money. Real cash is of course far more useful and less restrictive. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Uber eats now only gives small Uber cash credits that can only be used on their platform. They say they can no longer refund actual cash. Be careful when ordering for groups, as you have little recourse for restaurant mistakes now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：收到的电子邮件看起来像是来自亚马逊或贝宝等合法公司，声称你的账户有问题，要求你再次登录，这就是骗局。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Why ysk: 骗子在互联网上比比皆是。我最近一直收到
电子邮件，声称我的账户被入侵，或者他们注意到我的账户有一些可疑的活动，或者这些骗子想出的其他办法。
我的账户上有一些可疑的活动，或者这些骗子想出的其他什么东西
的其他东西。如果你打开他们的电子邮件，它看起来是合法的，但它是...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/px2aze/ysk_emails_received_that_look_like_they_are_from/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/px2aze/ysk_emails_received_that_look_like_they_are_from/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 14:42:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why ysk: Scammers are plentiful on the Internet. I have recently been receiving e-mails claiming that my account has been compromised or that they have noticed some suspicious activity on my account  or whatever else these scammers come up with. If you open their e-mail it looks legitimate, but it&amp;#39;s not. There are a lot of ways you can tell that an e-mail is a scam and if you want you can click &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/how-recognize-and-avoid-phishing-scams&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to find out more about how there phishing attacks work and recognize them so that you don&amp;#39;t fall victim to these scams.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What they usually want is for you to log-in so this way they can steal your information and then they can do whatever they want with it. If they steal, for example, your log-in information for your Amazon account, they will try and see if you have a credit card attached to your account and they end up stealing it. If you want to see more on how these scammers operate, there are a lot of YouTube videos that expose these scammers, I&amp;#39;d recommend &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FO9mWvJAugQ&quot;&gt;this person&lt;/a&gt; because he explains in-depth how they operate and he even manages to hack the scammers and scare them by showing their webcam or calling them by their real name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In summary, be careful on the internet, don&amp;#39;t trust unfamiliar sources and don&amp;#39;t open suspicious e-mails. Other ways you can protect yourself online is the use of better passwords and using different passwords for every website. You can read more about how to create better passwords &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mcafee.com/blogs/enterprise/cloud-security/how-to-create-a-strong-password-you-actually-remember/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be careful out there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：有一种呼吸技巧，一些文献表明它可以激活你的副交感神经系统，它与你吃完饭后睡觉的本能有关。它可以用来减少焦虑，引发放松，并随意入睡。它被称为4-7-8。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：虽然对一些人来说，能够随意入睡可能很容易，但对另一些人（如我自己）来说，这是不可能的。
其他人（如我）来说是非常困难的。我希望那些患有慢性失眠或睡眠问题的人
我希望那些患有慢性失眠症或有入睡问题的人能够使用这个
技巧来更稳定地入睡。我还认为，这可能会证明是一个很好的方法。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwypd6/ysk_there_is_a_breathing_technique_that_some/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwypd6/ysk_there_is_a_breathing_technique_that_some/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 06:36:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: While being able to sleep at will might come easy to some people, to others (such as myself) it&amp;#39;s very difficult. It&amp;#39;s my hope that people who suffer from chronic insomnia or issues falling asleep might be able to use this technique to sleep more consistently. I also think it may prove a useful tool for people who suffer constantly from issues like anxiety, stress, and panic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To perform the technique, first expel all air from your lungs, then do a deep inhale that lasts 4 seconds. With your lungs full of air, hold your breath for 7 seconds. Finally, exhale through your mouth (through your lips, making a whooshing sound) for 8 seconds. The ratio between the time of each step is more important than counting seconds accurately, so if you have trouble holding your breath, timing like 2, 3.5, and 4 might work too, although 4-7-8 is the most common recommendation and seems to elicit the most success. If you repeat the steps 2 or 3 times, your body should enter &amp;quot;rest and digest&amp;quot; mode, which may help you fall asleep quickly if you&amp;#39;re already in good sleeping conditions (comfortable, laying down, dark and quiet) or promote relaxation if you&amp;#39;re stressed or anxious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：3的生存法则]]></title><description><![CDATA[作为一般的经验法则，你可以生存...

缺氧3分钟

在恶劣的环境中，3小时没有住所

3天没有水

3个星期没有食物

3个月没有救援

3年没有希望

为什么选择YSK：这个3原则可以帮助你记住什么是生存时的优先事项。
生存和...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwwc6b/ysk_the_rule_of_3s_for_survival/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwwc6b/ysk_the_rule_of_3s_for_survival/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 04:49:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a general rule of thumb you can survive…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 minutes without oxygen&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 hours without shelter in harsh environments &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 days without water&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 weeks without food&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 months without rescue&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 years without hope&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This rule of 3s helps you remember what are priorities in times of survival and which priorities are more important than others for a certain given time, this clearly isn’t 100% accurate but it’s a great general guide to go by and has saved many people and remembering it could save your life one day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：Chrome浏览器现在会追踪你是否处于闲置状态，以及如何禁用它。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：这是在最新版本中默认启用的一个设置。
这里的问题是，知道你没有在看某个特定的屏幕是一个
网站可以利用这个信号，对你有好处（当你不看的时候暂停视频
好的（当你不看时暂停视频），或坏的（你的工作用它来跟踪你的活动）。

如果...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwuvxl/ysk_that_the_chrome_browser_now_tracks_if_youre/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwuvxl/ysk_that_the_chrome_browser_now_tracks_if_youre/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 02:37:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: 
This is a setting that is enabled by default with the latest release. The concern here is that knowing you&amp;#39;re not looking at a particular screen is a signal that sites can use on you, for good (pausing a video when you&amp;#39;re not watching), or bad (your job using it to track your activity).  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you use Chrome or Brave, here&amp;#39;s how to disable it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;chrome://settings/content/idleDetection&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look for &amp;quot;Don’t allow sites to know when you’re actively using your device&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK您在清洗任何吸湿运动服、毛巾、运动服、阻燃或防水衣服时，应避免在洗衣中使用烘干剂或织物柔软剂。这些产品会阻塞织物的 "毛孔"，降低吸湿排汗能力。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：许多人在每次洗衣时都会使用织物柔软剂和/或烘干剂。
衣服。在清洗运动服时，这是不可取的，因为要保持运动服的
运动服处于最佳工作状态。

https://www.latimes.com/bestcovery/best-dryer-sheets]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwkw2g/ysk_you_should_avoid_using_dryer_sheets_or_fabric/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwkw2g/ysk_you_should_avoid_using_dryer_sheets_or_fabric/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 23:28:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  Many people use fabric softener and/or dryer sheets with every load of laundry.  This is not advisable when cleaning athletic wear in order to keep the athletic wear in optimal working condition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.latimes.com/bestcovery/best-dryer-sheets&quot;&gt;https://www.latimes.com/bestcovery/best-dryer-sheets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK - Reddit不能替代治疗师]]></title><description><![CDATA[希望有人早点告诉我这个。为什么是YSK：如果你有问题，就去找有适当培训的人谈谈。
如果你有问题，就去找受过适当培训的人谈，以处理你遇到的任何问题
而不是在互联网上随便找一个人。很多时候你会得到
毫无帮助或错误的建议（或者根本就没有，这只会让...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwj4k1/ysk_reddit_is_not_a_substitute_for_a_therapist/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwj4k1/ysk_reddit_is_not_a_substitute_for_a_therapist/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 17:44:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wish someone had told me this earlier. Why YSK: If you’re having issues, go talk to someone who has the proper training to deal with whatever issue you’re having, not some random person on the internet. More often than not you will get unhelpful or wrong advice (or none at all, which only makes the problem worse)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你不应该对世界持有太多僵硬的观点，以及什么是真实或不真实。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK。

与一个封闭的、应该是静态的人群互动，会导致非常僵化的
世界观和误解，使你的思想变得封闭，即使新的
信息实际上可能对你有利。

--

社会通过教育将信息传递给年轻一代...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwf508/ysk_you_shouldnt_hold_too_rigid_opinions_of_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwf508/ysk_you_shouldnt_hold_too_rigid_opinions_of_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 15:39:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interacting with a closed and supposedly static population results in very rigid world views and misconceptions that make you close minded even though the new information may actually be in your favour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;——&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Societies pass on information to younger generations through education and interactions with them. This creates a thesaurus of “common knowledge”. The problem with “common knowledge” passed down from generations is that it is often filled with misconceptions and misunderstandings. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the outcome of multiple people with varying degrees of understanding and experiences providing a take, and you as a receiver only have a partial point of view of that information, and of the person disseminating it, so it is difficult for you to understand that person’s biases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, people tend to coalesce to communities of similar thoughts and behaviour. This is called “intellectual inbreeding”, where ideas are rehashed amongst a community and over time get perverted because the community doesn’t get exposed to new information or someone willing to provide counter arguments. This is such a major problem in science that top universities often don’t accept their own graduates (PhD or not) in positions and look for candidates from other universities, though exceptions exist. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, due to the brain’s plasticity, disseminating the same ideas as our group reinforces those ideas and causes them to become very rigid and fundamental parts of our world model.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we have a very rigid world view and we encounter a person who subscribes to fundamentally different ideas, our world view gets shaken exactly because it is very rigid, and we become unable to accept the new ideas regardless of correctness because our brain interprets the new information as an attack to itself and reality. This “attach”  physically manifests as narrow-mindedness in the brain and prevents us from accepting them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What can you do about it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cultivate a process in your brain that keeps challenging the status quo and actively and honestly tries to find mistakes in it. Read books/listen to podcasts, and have discussions with people of opposing views.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keep asking, what if I am wrong, why do I have this belief, and suppose a malevolent person disseminated this idea, what could they gain from it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你不是一个孩子，并不意味着你可以掌握新的技能。如果成年人（和青少年）了解大脑如何学习新事物，他们的学习速度会比他们认为的快得多。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：成年人学习事物的速度比他们认为的要快，学习新事物和技能本身就是一个非常令人满意的过程。
学习新事物和技能本身就可以是一个非常令人满意的过程，但许多人
但许多人都希望自己能学会演奏乐器或其他技能，但却从未采取行动
因为他们觉得 "已经太晚了"....]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwfb0m/ysk_just_because_you_are_not_a_kid_doesnt_mean/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwfb0m/ysk_just_because_you_are_not_a_kid_doesnt_mean/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 14:46:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: adults can learn things faster than what they believe, and learning new things and skills can be a very satisfying process on its own, but many people wished they had learned to play an instrument or some other skill but never do something about it because they feel that “it is too late”. It isn’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, how do I do that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is this common misconception that just because you are older and the brain doesn’t “learn as fast”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this is true by some regards, kids don’t learn in the same way as adults do. Kids learn by imitating actions from their environment, they can do that because their brain has significantly more synapses(=connections between brain cells) than adults, so it’s easier for the brain to find the right pathway and reinforce it while pruning “wrong” synapses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In contrast, adults have preexisting synapses that have been reinforced for a long time and so it’s significantly harder to learn by imitation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But adults also have a significantly better world model (=understanding of the world), and significantly more developed frontal cortex (=rational thinking and control of functions and behaviour). This means that by employing pre existing knowledge and understanding you can attain a much better understanding of the skill you are trying to learn than kids. This, then means that you can explore and generate new “actions” and behaviour much better than kids because you have better understanding of what is going on under it. By doing that consciously you will be able to turn the actually “correct” and “high quality” conscious actions into subconscious actions that are second nature. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, even learning itself and creativity are skills that can be trained for (as a grad student with publications from undergrad, and a lot of original work, who has ventured into other fields in her own time because she found it interesting, I recommend the Feynman method with flashcards and extensive notes).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The brain is a very strong pattern matching and creative computer. It’s a shame that many people live with regrets of not learning to play instruments or some other skill. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some authors that I can recommend:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Kahneman (eg. “Thinking fast and slow”)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  David Eagleman (eg. “Livewired”, ”the brain”)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Robert Sapolsky (eg “Behave”, “why zebras don’t get ulcers”)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Elizier Yudkowsky (eg “Inadequate equilibria”)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Lieberman and Long (The molecule of more)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Oliver Sacks (eg “The man who mistook his wife for a hat”, “Hallucinations”, “On the river of consciousness”)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry for reposting, the title had a typo…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit:
This one has a typo as well. Jesus Christ today. Sorry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如果你得到的是学校或县城的Chromebook，如何绕过网站管理封锁。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：我们学生知道学校在网站上的限制绝对是过分的。
限制。通过浏览器管理扩展和管理封锁完全锁定了
管理区块。看在上帝的份上，有时我只是想滚动Reddit或观看Twitch
当没有其他事情发生的时候。而对于那些在学校...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pusbj0/ysk_if_youre_given_a_school_or_countybased/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pusbj0/ysk_if_youre_given_a_school_or_countybased/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 13:31:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Us students know schools go absolutely overboard on website restrictions. Completely locked down with browser management extensions and admin blocks. For gosh-sake sometimes I just wanna scroll Reddit or watch Twitch when there&amp;#39;s nothing else going on. And for those of you who a school Chromebook is the only access you have to internet, you&amp;#39;re going to want to take a break and relax sometimes. Without further delay, here&amp;#39;s how to bypass website blocks on school Chromebooks on which website &amp;quot;security&amp;quot; is managed by extensions&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1: Google search the website you want to visit. Don&amp;#39;t click the link yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2: In the top right corner you should see three vertical dots. Click that&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3: Head over to more tools and click task manager&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4: End the processes associated with your Chromebook&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;security&amp;quot; (e.g. cisco umbrella extension) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5: After that, quickly click the website you want to visit. Do this fast as the &amp;quot;security&amp;quot; processes reinstate themselves and you may have to spam &amp;#39;end process&amp;#39; multiple times for the request to go through. Refresh the page and end &amp;quot;security&amp;quot; extensions as needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once the website loads in, you should not have to spam close the &amp;quot;security&amp;quot; extensions, and most of the website features should run as normal. You should also be able to visit those websites in the future without having to complete the process above. The only exception Ive seen where consistent buffering occurs is crunchyroll and the Reddit media player.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope this helps some people :D&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: This solution only works if your school didn&amp;#39;t block task manager. If they did, you gotta resort to a dual boot process off an external drive if your processor supports windows/linux&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t exactly know the process, but I&amp;#39;m sure you could find a youtube video that shows you how to do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AMD and Intel processors support both Windows 10 and some versions of Linux.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you to &lt;a href=&quot;/u/enderwiggin42&quot;&gt;u/enderwiggin42&lt;/a&gt; for the info!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你想在敲开鸡蛋之前确保它是硬的，你可以在一个平面上旋转它。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：如果它快速旋转，这意味着内部现在是固体，你的鸡蛋
已经完成。如果它旋转得很慢和/或摇摆不定，这意味着它的一部分仍然是液体
你应该多煮一会儿。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwejx8/ysk_if_you_want_to_make_sure_your_egg_is_hard/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pwejx8/ysk_if_you_want_to_make_sure_your_egg_is_hard/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 13:31:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If it spins quickly it means that the inside is now solid and your egg is done. If it spins slowly and/or wobbles that means part of it is still liquid and you should boil it for longer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在你决定不喜欢某种水果/蔬菜之前，尝试一下传家宝或本地种植的水果/蔬菜。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：超市里销售的大多数水果和蔬菜都是大规模种植的品种，在成熟之前就被采摘，然后被运往各地。
品种，在它们成熟之前就被采摘，然后被运往全国或全世界。
然后运往全国或全世界。

常见的销售水果和蔬菜，如红色美味的苹果和胡萝卜。
是没有味道的，使很多人不喜欢...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pw3dqc/ysk_before_you_decide_you_dont_like_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pw3dqc/ysk_before_you_decide_you_dont_like_a/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 10:58:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: most fruits and vegetables sold in supermarkets are mass farmed varieties and are picked well before they’re ripe, then shipped across the country, or world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Commonly sold fruits and vegetables, such as red delicious apples and carrots, are devoid of flavor and turn lots of people off of them forever. Locally sourced varieties, which are in season, are so much better that they scarcely qualify as the same thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如果你的牙齿被打掉了，你可以按照这些重要的步骤挽救它。(重要的急救信息)]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK: 我是一名牙科学生，我注意到没有很多人知道你可以拯救你的牙齿。
我注意到，并不是很多人知道，如果你的牙齿被打掉了，你可以挽救它，而且它可以重新长出来。
活着。例如在打架或（运动）事故中。如果你不遵循这些
步骤，就会减少你的牙齿存活的机会...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pw3m1h/ysk_if_your_tooth_gets_knocked_out_you_can_save/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pw3m1h/ysk_if_your_tooth_gets_knocked_out_you_can_save/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 23:31:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I’m a dentistry student and it came to my attention that not a lot of people know you can save your tooth if it gets knocked out and it can grow back alive. For example in a fight or (sport)accident. If you don’t follow these steps it reduces the chance of survival of your tooth drastically. When it dies it becomes brown-ish and it has a short life span.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A tooth is a living part of your body. The inner part of the tooth is called the pulpa. The pulpa consists of nerves, bloodvessels, stemcells and this can die. When this happens the lifespan of the tooth is short (around &amp;lt;10 years) and will eventually require an implant or a bridge because it will fall out. When your tooth gets knocked out (or you see one getting knocked out) it is important to follow these steps:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;pick the tooth up by the crown (chewing surface). Never touch the root! These are surrounded by specialised cells which can be destroyed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inspect the tooth: is it covered in dirt? 
—&amp;gt; yes: rinse with milk or your own(!) saliva. By pouring the milk on it or spitting your saliva on it. (Clean drinkable (not tap water)) water works too. Still don’t touch or wipe the root and don’t use chemicals like soap!
If not this step can be skipped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preserve the tooth in a save environment.
There are several ways to do this:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a. (Best option) - look at the tooth. What is the front and what is the back? Place it back correctly and hold it in place with a rag (or something  soft which is similar, like toilet paper or a piece of clothing). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;b. When this is not possible because the person is either a child (because they can swallow it) unconcious, jaw is broken, or you don’t know where it belongs because several teeth are out: collect saliva of the person it belongs to (!) in a clean cup (or something similar which is clean like a cap of a waterbottle) and put it gently in there. It should be completely covered in saliva (blood doesn’t matter). Milk works too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;c. Put it in your mouth between the cheek and your teeth with your mouth closed. Don’t touch it with your tongue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contact a dentist. He needs to prepare an emergency. You need to go there asap. The dentist will clean the tooth, put it back and spalk it temporarily. This is not expensive (ask if this concerns you). After a few weeks you need to go back to see if the tooth survived. Often more than not it will survive when the above steps are done correctly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Important:
Never put back baby teeth. This might damage the gums. Not sure? Follow 3b or 3c.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only the person where the knocked out  belongs to can use his own saliva to rinse or clean it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You need to go to the dentist as soon as possible (within an hour)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：把肥皂放进公共饮水机里制造一堆泡沫并不是一个无害的恶作剧，它损坏了大多数饮水机的泵，并且需要花费大量的费用来维修。]]></title><description><![CDATA[每年，我们都会看到一些孩子或醉汉决定将肥皂扔进公共喷泉，并观看随之而来的混乱，这很有趣。
扔一点肥皂到公共喷泉里，然后看着混乱的情况发生。听起来
愚蠢而有趣，而且即兴的肥皂舞派对只是需要一点额外的水来清理，所以没有坏处，对吗？
水来清理，所以没有坏处，对吗？

喷泉使用专门的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pw27nj/ysk_putting_soap_into_a_public_water_fountain_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pw27nj/ysk_putting_soap_into_a_public_water_fountain_to/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 22:40:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every year we see posts with some kids or drunks deciding it would be fun to throw a little soap into a public fountain, and watch the chaos ensue. Sounds silly and fun, and an impromptu suds dance party will just take a little extra water to clean up so no harm, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fountains use specialized water pumps which are designed to keep lubricated even when in constant use with plain water. Unfortunately, the soap works to destroy the seals and strip the pump motors of their protective lubrication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is one major reason there are very few public water fountains anymore. One or two attacks, and most cash-strapped facilities opt to drain the fountain and let the thing rot until they can afford to dismantle it altogether.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fountains on the Lee Clarion University campus in Cleveland, Tennessee are historically prone to vandalism. One particular event in August 2010 cost the university $1,000 in materials alone to drain the fountain, clean all surfaces, chemically remove the suds and flush the pipes, not to mention add important chemicals back in to prevent algae growth and keep the water crystal clear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More recently in July 2014, a soaped fountain in Eau Claire, Wisconsin kept city workers busy for days cleaning up the mess. Crews had to clean out the whole fountain, backwash the filters, rinse, wash and repeat multiple times before all the soap was cleared out of the system. It took hours of manpower and several days before the fountain was back up and running.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.groundsguys.com/blog/2015/august/you-ve-been-soaped-now-what-/&quot;&gt;the Grounds Guys&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obligatory Why YSK: if your friends suggest damaging communal property just because they think it&amp;#39;s harmless, you may convince them to find something else is a better outlet for their energy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在美国仍然很流行的3000英里换油是一个神话，是在浪费钱。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK。我是一个5年前搬到美国的英国侨民。在每个街道
拐角处都有一个快速换油的地方，我发现几乎每个人都会在3000英里时换油。
3000英里时更换机油。

为什么这是一种浪费？

 1. 这是从60年代和70年代传来的神话，汽车发动机技术和油品
    技术...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pvrtfo/ysk_3000_mile_oil_changes_that_are_still_so/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pvrtfo/ysk_3000_mile_oil_changes_that_are_still_so/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 12:50:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK. I&amp;#39;m a British expat who moved to the USA 5 years ago. On every street corner is a quick oil change place and I found out almost everyone changes their oil at 3000 miles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why is this a waste?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a myth purported from the 60s and 70s, car engine technology and oil technology has evolved greatly since then and engines go longer between oil changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most cars in the US have engines that are used worldwide. For example, Ford engines used in cars in American are manufactured and used worldwide. Oil change intervals for these same engines are 10,000 miles +&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most cars since about 2010 will notify you when an oil change is due, based on environmental and driving conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source? I&amp;#39;m an ex Automotive filter development engineer and ex Ford development engineer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK不喜欢的东西并不意味着不喜欢它]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：经常有人问 "你喜欢X吗？"这样的问题，很多人会
自动认为你不喜欢X，当你说不喜欢。有时这只是意味着你
中立，不关心或不知道是否喜欢或不喜欢某些东西
或某人。

我认为人们应该知道，因为我们生活在一个...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pvbrsh/ysk_not_liking_something_doesnt_mean_disliking_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pvbrsh/ysk_not_liking_something_doesnt_mean_disliking_it/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 04:22:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: often people ask questions like “Do you like X?” and many people will automatically assume you dislike X when you say no. Sometimes it just means you are neutral, don’t care or don’t know enough to either like or dislike something or someone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think people should know because we live in a more and more polarized society and people more often fail to nuance that things aren’t always either this OR that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，在商店里试穿衣服时，一定要坐下来确认是否合适和舒适。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK，站着的时候很容易看到和感觉到衣服是否合适......所以我在年轻的时候认为
我年轻时曾这样认为。但是为了确保衣服合身和舒适
舒适，请确保在试穿时坐下来。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pviwo5/ysk_while_trying_on_clothes_in_a_store_make_sure/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pviwo5/ysk_while_trying_on_clothes_in_a_store_make_sure/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 01:56:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK, it&amp;#39;s easy to see and feel whether clothes fit while standing... so I used to think when I was younger. But to make sure that clothes fit and are comfortable, make sure to sit down while you are trying them on&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你不小心关闭了浏览器中的标签，你可以把它带回来。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：在我的一生中，我不小心关闭了很多标签，而且似乎人们不知道你可以直接点击："我"。
人们似乎不知道你可以直接点击。

Shift控制T

如果你是在Mac上，那就是

Shift command T

太多的人似乎接受了它永远消失的事实，并花了很多时间回到他们的网站。
回到他们的网站...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pvee8e/ysk_you_can_bring_a_tab_in_your_browser_back_if/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pvee8e/ysk_you_can_bring_a_tab_in_your_browser_back_if/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 01:56:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I have accidentaylly closed so many tabs in my lifetime and it seems quite common for people to not know that you can just hit:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shift control T&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#39;re on Mac it&amp;#39;s&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shift command T&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Too many people seem to accept it&amp;#39;s gone forever and spend a lot of time getting back to the website they were once on so hopefully this saves some people some time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK这些网站可以获得免费的教科书和解决方案手册]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：我很后悔为我所有的书支付硬拷贝，特别是在网上的一年之后。
年。在这里，你通常可以不用付一分钱就能找到它们。


图书馆创世纪

这是大多数电子书的首选网站。一些工程类的教科书
也附有解决方案手册。搜索...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pvaqms/ysk_these_websites_to_get_free_textbooks_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pvaqms/ysk_these_websites_to_get_free_textbooks_and/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 21:01:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I regret paying hard copies of all my books, especially after an online year. Here is where you can usually find them without paying a cent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Library Genesis&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the go-to site for most ebooks. Some of the engineering textbooks comes with the solution manual as well. Searching for the title + &amp;quot;solution manual&amp;quot; will give you some results. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Ch36650lut10n5 (cheggsolutions)&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A website which has textbook solutions ripped from chegg. It has quite a lot of books and free, no need to sign up or give any credentials. You can find many textbook solutions that are not on libgen or zlibrary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Zlibrary&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is another site where you can try if you can&amp;#39;t find it in Library Genesis.
You may need an account if you exceed the download limit. If you do not like to use your personal email, you can opt to use a temporary mail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Slader&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for textbook solutions for free, check Slader. You have to sign up to access materials, after that you can access many solution manuals written by teachers and professors. 
They recently installed a limit, trying to make access to answers a paid service unfortunately. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Studylib&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the name itself says it’s like a library, where you can have a large number of assignments and solutions. You can also share your notes with your friends which would help them to solve the problems. It will provide you with a solution for all the subjects. You can also upload your documents and find the solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Pdfdrive&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An online PDF search engine that lets you search, preview and download PDFs. According to the site as of right now, there are over 75 million eBooks, magazines, articles, and more that are indexed and discoverable directly on PDF Drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Sci-Hub&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great place for finding published journal/conference papers that are (usually) paywalled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;AudioBookBay&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If what you want is audiobooks then audiobookbay is the go-to place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good luck on your new semester everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：人力资源部门不是 "人类的资源"]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：你的公司把你看作是一种商品，并且有一个人力资源团队来确保
公司遵守所有的法律，他们不会因为自己的财产而被起诉。
占有。如果你向人力资源部门提出投诉，他们会立即寻求
在法律上保护自己。他们不会本能地...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pvciam/ysk_human_resources_is_not_resources_for_humans/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pvciam/ysk_human_resources_is_not_resources_for_humans/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 19:56:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Your company views you as a commodity and has an HR team to ensure  that the company stays in compliance with all laws and they do not get  sued by their possessions. If you&amp;#39;re bringing a complaint to HR they will immediately look to protect themselves legally. They will NOT instinctively look to protect you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your HR rep is on your company&amp;#39;s side. Not yours. Not ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 如果一个公司在向你收费时犯了错误，并试图用优惠券偿还你，你可能不应该接受。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：优惠券的设计是为了公司的利益，而不是为了你。你
你可能从它那里得到了一个糟糕的交易。

一些餐馆试图用优惠券来补偿向我们多收的 "错误"。
优惠券。

可能表面上看起来不错，但它不是。除了过期日期外，还有
许多巨大的限制...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pv857p/ysk_if_a_company_makes_a_mistake_in_charging_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pv857p/ysk_if_a_company_makes_a_mistake_in_charging_you/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 18:05:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Coupons are designed in the interest of the company not you. You&amp;#39;re probably getting a bad deal from it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some restaurant tried to reimburse the &amp;quot;mistake&amp;quot; in overcharging us with coupons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Might look nice on the surface but its not. Aside from expiry date, there are many huge limitations such as only being able to use one coupon each time (small amount) AFTER spending a certain amount. So basically I need to spend more at your place for your mistake? Who the hell do you think you are here?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s always a lot of &amp;quot;fine print&amp;quot; when it comes to coupons. Think of it on the lines of &amp;quot;Itchy and Scratchy money&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Get the transactions cancelled or ask them to pay in cash. Or something else! Don&amp;#39;t just lie down and let them get away with it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 那 "叫出 "某人有逻辑谬误的问题可能和你试图识别的问题一样多。识别谬误应该被用来改善你的沟通，而不是作为关闭你不喜欢的对话的工具。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK 我最近有几次试图与团体谈论有争议的
的话题，而不是讨论，只是得到了很多指责，说我是一个
我说的每一句话都被贴上了逻辑谬误的标签。
终止了对话。

尽量不要使用这些术语和...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pv537y/ysk_that_calling_out_someone_as_having_a_logical/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pv537y/ysk_that_calling_out_someone_as_having_a_logical/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 13:33:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK    I have had a few attempts recently to talk to groups about controversial topics, and instead of discussion just got a lot of accusations about being a troll and had everything I said labeled as a logical fallacy, effectively shutting down the conversation.    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Try not to use these terms and explain what you mean in plain language.   Posting “that is a Strawman argument” adds nothing.  Posting “people don’t believe X like you said, they believe various things from Y to Z, which makes your argument wrong” says what you actually mean and allows for ongoing discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have no term to describe it, but the practice of labelling every view you disagree with as a logical fallacy is definitely a rhetorical fallacy that should be avoided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如何使用尺子或卷尺进行精确到十六分之一英寸的测量]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：许多你需要用剪刀、刀或锯子切割的东西
都需要先进行精确的测量。在美国的许多行业和职业中
美国的许多行业和职业中，十六分之一英寸的精度足以被认为是精确的。

要用文字解释如何读懂一英寸是非常困难的。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/puvoxb/ysk_how_to_measure_with_an_accuracy_of_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/puvoxb/ysk_how_to_measure_with_an_accuracy_of_a/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 12:53:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Many things that you will need to cut with scissors, a knife, or a saw will need to be precisely measured first. In many trades and professions in the United States, a sixteenth of an inch is accurate enough to be considered exact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s extremely difficult to explain in text how to read a ruler or measuring tape down to the sixteenth of an inch, but &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l3Nv1mjof-I&quot;&gt;this video does an accurate job&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 如果有人给你口香糖/口香糖，你应该总是接受。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：他们可能在暗示你的呼吸是令人反感的，需要加以解决。
处理。最坏的情况是你得到一些额外的热量（或者他们
毒害你，不知道）。)]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/puq9gv/ysk_if_someone_offers_you_a_breath_mintgum_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/puq9gv/ysk_if_someone_offers_you_a_breath_mintgum_you/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 19:56:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: They may be hinting that your breath is offensive and needs to be addressed. The worst that happens is you get a few extra calories (or they poison you idk).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，苹果公司新的邮件隐私保护功能将向任何营销人员（或骗子）标记你的电子邮件地址为有效。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你使用苹果邮件应用程序并启用MPP，会发生以下情况。苹果公司首先
将邮件通过代理服务器来预装邮件内容，包括
追踪像素，然后再提供给你。即使你没有
实际打开这些邮件。

这意味着，当你打开一封电子邮件时，你...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pu7y8k/ysk_that_apples_new_mail_privacy_protection/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pu7y8k/ysk_that_apples_new_mail_privacy_protection/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 17:13:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you use the Apple Mail App and enable MPP, here’s what happens: Apple first routes emails through a proxy server to pre-load message content—including tracking pixels—before serving it to you. This happens even if you don’t actually open those emails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This means that when you open an email, you essentially access Apple&amp;#39;s version instead of the sender&amp;#39;s, disguising your IP address and time of opening to the sender.  However, when Apple initially downloads the images, it sends a signal to the sender that their email has reached a valid and active address. This has the potential to actually &lt;em&gt;increase&lt;/em&gt; the amount of unwanted emails you receive, as a scammer will know they&amp;#39;ve hit a live address and will undoubtedly make use of it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; To help you make an informed decision about your privacy. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; This is my understanding of the following article by Magan Le at Litmus &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.litmus.com/blog/apple-mail-privacy-protection-for-marketers/&quot;&gt;https://www.litmus.com/blog/apple-mail-privacy-protection-for-marketers/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为刷完牙后不应该漱口。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：在电影和电视中，人们总是在刷完牙后漱口。
他们的牙齿。但是，刷牙后漱口会把保护牙齿的好东西，如氟化物，全部冲走。
保护它们的东西，如氟化物。如果你一定要漱口，请喝一小口水
水，像漱口水一样在牙齿周围挥动，然后......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/puaq66/ysk_that_you_should_not_rinse_your_mouth_out/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/puaq66/ysk_that_you_should_not_rinse_your_mouth_out/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 15:37:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: in movies and tv people always rinse their mouth out after brushing their teeth. But rinsing your mouth after you brush rinses away all the good stuff that protects them like fluoride. If you must rinse, take a small sip of water and swish it around your teeth like mouthwash and spit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.oralanswers.com/rinse-after-brushing/&quot;&gt;https://www.oralanswers.com/rinse-after-brushing/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如何避免用你的车杀死动物。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么YSK：避免死亡、痛苦、内疚、潜在的车祸和潜在的
车辆损坏。



关于如何避免撞到动物，你需要知道的第一件事是
你需要知道的第一件事是，在动物上路之前，你就应该期待它上路。
是杀死大多数流浪动物的东西......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/puhs4j/ysk_how_to_avoid_killing_animals_with_your_car/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/puhs4j/ysk_how_to_avoid_killing_animals_with_your_car/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 12:59:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;why YSK: avoid death, suffering, guilt, a potential car accident, and potential vehicle damage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the first thing you need to know about how to avoid hitting an animal is to expect the animal to be on the road before it&amp;#39;s on the road. complacency is the thing that kills most animals that wander onto a road. COMPLACENCY is also the thing that kills most HUMANS on the road. imagine you&amp;#39;re just driving, chilling, listening to music, and suddenly there&amp;#39;s some random animal in your way and because this is such an oddity in your life your brain does not come up with a solution quickly enough. if you simulate the scenario in your mind before it happens you will be able to react accordingly, minimizing potential losses without risk to yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-if you drive at night this is relatively simple. most animal and vehicle crashes occur between the hours of 5PM and midnight. be on the lookout for animals if you drive during these times, but &lt;em&gt;especially&lt;/em&gt; if you&amp;#39;re driving while it&amp;#39;s dark out. and remember not to limit your view to what&amp;#39;s immediately in front of you. you should be aiming to look down the road 10 to 15 seconds ahead of your vehicle in order to avoid any last minute moves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;this is the thing you need to know about animals on the road: 99% of the time you encounter an animal on the road, the animal will stop in the middle of the road and/or turn around after noticing your car. the headlights confuse their dark-adjusted eyes and signal that there is imminent danger, and their brain tells them to retreat. you must anticipate this. to see this for yourself, if you look up &amp;quot;russ lepage deer&amp;quot; on google you&amp;#39;ll be directed to a video that shows a close call with an automated tesla driver and a deer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;(I would like to mention that the vehicle in this video made a lane change that I would consider too sharp for comfort, and making a split second decision to switch lanes like that is not ideal. this is not a demonstration, but it is some footage for you to get yourself acquainted with the idea of having an animal stuck in your headlights because it is a textbook encounter and should better prepare you for the situation. do not try to replicate the technique shown here. instead, read on.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;so, animals don&amp;#39;t know what&amp;#39;s on the other side of the road. they only know the area they came from. when they see your scary car, their instinct is to go back to safety. which means they&amp;#39;ll literally spin around and go back, and this will even happen if they&amp;#39;ve already safely made it to the other side of the road. all animals are guilty of this. raccoons, foxes, deer, cats, squirrels, it doesn&amp;#39;t matter. in a pinch, they will always go back to the side of the road they entered from. they will not move forward into an unknown area after realizing they&amp;#39;re in danger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;&amp;#39;the maneuver&amp;#39;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;identify animal in your field of vision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;take your foot off of the accelerator pedal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;switch lanes if possible in a controlled manner. do not act with haste. you must not make any sudden or sharp movements. if you are close to the animal, you want to switch to the lane that they came from. if you are far away or very close, do not switch lanes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;always slow down. if you are switching lanes, begin to slow down halfway into your transition from one side of the road to the other. do not brake and switch lanes at the same time. do not slam the brakes. do not brake in a way that would cause your vehicle to skid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;on switching lanes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;~8&lt;/strong&gt; seconds seconds of time to react: in the video I referenced, it is a close call. but if this was in reality, you can clearly see the deer coming a mile away. the correct choice in that instance would be to simply slow down upon spotting the deer and alerting the animal and drivers behind you that something is up by hitting your car horn. no need to switch lanes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;~&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt; seconds of time to react: in an instance where you have less time to react to the animal where it is directly in front of you, you are looking to switch lanes so that you pass the animal before it is making the active decision to turn around. the animal is also more likely to make a better decision if it can see the trajectory of your vehicle. it cannot properly see your trajectory if you are heading straight towards it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;~&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt; seconds of time to react: if you ever have a very short amount of time to react to an animal on the road unfortunately the best course of action is to slow down as much as possible without losing control of your vehicle, drive straight, and brace yourself for impact. do not attempt to change the trajectory of your vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(note that these numbers are just approximations. I&amp;#39;m not a driving expert. I am only trying to help you make the decision to switch lanes for yourself)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;tips:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;constantly check your blind spot and your left/right mirrors&lt;/strong&gt; as you are driving so you can prematurely know if you&amp;#39;re able to switch lanes on the fly if necessary. this is a helpful driving tip in general and you can avoid vehicle collisions this way as well. you may need to react quickly and not have time to check for cars on the other lane. this does not mean recklessly switch lanes without looking. it means that if you know for certain there are no cars in your way, you will be able to use the other lane to your advantage if the need arises.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;always slow down&lt;/strong&gt; if you identify an obstacle in your path (such as an animal, or another car, or a human being) there is no reason to ever not slow down. do not slam the breaks. just slow down like you normally would in a timely manner. the slower you are going, the more control you have over your vehicle. if you crash into a massive animal such as a moose or a large buck, the faster you are going the more likely you are to suffer a fatal collision. with moose, it is not much different than crashing into another vehicle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;combine tip #1 and #2.&lt;/strong&gt; just make sure that this is not done in a panic. it must be a calculated maneuver. if you make too sharp of a turn and your brakes are engaged too aggressively you could flip your car or lose control of your vehicle and spiral out of control, and kill or injure yourself and other drivers around you. and just to reiterate what I&amp;#39;ve said before, don&amp;#39;t begin to brake until you are at least halfway into your lane change. just make sure you take your foot off the accelerator before doing anything.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;do not swerve&lt;/strong&gt;. swerving is a last ditch effort and extremely dangerous. if you are going to change your trajectory to avoid an incoming collision, you must do it in a similar manner as if you were turning to switch lanes. any abrupt changes to the steering wheel at high speeds will severely and negatively impact the stability of your vehicle. this is why the previously mentioned tips are so useful. if you practice them you should not ever feel the need to swerve. animals do not usually run onto the road so spontaneously that you would need to swerve, rather we react so slowly to these situations that we may impulsively feel like swerving because we ran out of time, failed to make a decision, and panicked. on the other hand people may panic and decide to crash into an animal that they could have avoided if they were better prepared. you should expect to have around 5 seconds of time to react to an animal that has suddenly tried to cross the road, on average. 5 seconds is enough time to make a decision and execute it while on the road, provided that you were paying attention and not drifting off while manning a vehicle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;stay the speed limit while driving at night&lt;/strong&gt;. animals will not be able to react properly to anything that is going significantly faster than your average wildlife predator. if you&amp;#39;re driving in a 65mph zone, drive 65mph. it&amp;#39;s night time. you are in no rush to get home. don&amp;#39;t put animal lives in jeopardy in order to save yourself a meaningless amount of time. speed inhibits control of the vehicle. the faster you&amp;#39;re going, the longer it takes to slow down and the more vulnerable your vehicle&amp;#39;s stability is to sudden movements, and the more likely you are to get in an accident and/or run over an animal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;every time you get out of the driveway always go and personally seek out your surroundings&lt;/strong&gt; to check for animals or people around you before you get in the car, even if you live in a populated neighborhood. it is not uncommon to run over a baby duck, baby rabbit, kitten, or frog while backing out of a driveway, and they are too small for you to notice them in your mirrors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would like everyone to remind everyone to never forget how powerful a vehicle is and how weak living things are in comparison. as the years go by you get used to these machines. complacency is a killer. do not ever get used to driving a vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：关于网站https://www.doesthedogdie.com/]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：在这个网站上，你可以搜索一部电影或连续剧，看看是否有
任何对你来说可能难以观看的内容。正如其名称所示，你可以
顾名思义，你可以查看电影/电视剧中是否有狗死亡，但它也包括其他主题，如
蜘蛛、呕吐物、酷刑、强奸或癌症。该网站收集了...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pu41p9/ysk_about_the_site_httpswwwdoesthedogdiecom/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pu41p9/ysk_about_the_site_httpswwwdoesthedogdiecom/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 03:45:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: On this site you can search for a movie or series and look if there is any content that might be hard for you to watch. As the name suggests you can look if a dog dies in a movie/serie but it also covers other topics like spiders, vomit, torture, rape or cancer. The site collects information about more than 80 topics and if there is anything you dont want to see, you should know about this site to see if you can watch a movie or series.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK关于基本归因错误，以及它如何影响你如何看待世界和你周围的人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[YSK讲述了基本归因错误，这是人类倾向于
倾向于为我们自己的行为或情况辩解，因为我们知道造成这些行为或情况的环境因素
因为我们知道造成这些行为的环境因素，但却认为另一个人的行为或情况是
而认为另一个人的行为或情况是他们作为一个人的指标，而不考虑......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pu4srn/ysk_about_fundamental_attribution_error_and_how/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pu4srn/ysk_about_fundamental_attribution_error_and_how/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 03:10:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;YSK about Fundamental Attribution Error which is the tendency for humans to justify our own behaviour or situation because we know the environmental factors that have caused them, but to assume another person’s behaviour or situation is indicative of who they are as a person without consideration to environmental factors. One of the worst instances of this is victim blaming. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another example might be: Someone else who runs a red light must be reckless and stupid. If you were to run a red light, you justify the behaviour because you know your family member is having a medical emergency and you are rushing to the hospital. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: YSK about Fundamental Attribution Error because being mindful of it can give you a more positive outlook on life. We shouldn’t always assume the worst of others and should instead wonder what factors have put them in that situation or what else is contributing them to behave that way. Most people aren’t intentionally being malicious. People aren’t always as bad as we make them out to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fundamental_attribution_error&quot;&gt;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fundamental_attribution_error&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.simplypsychology.org/fundamental-attribution.html&quot;&gt;https://www.simplypsychology.org/fundamental-attribution.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK在送货司机的眼里，你的狗并不 "友好"]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：当涉及到送货司机时，狗咬人是一个非常大的问题。
仅仅说你的狗是友好的并不意味着什么，因为从本质上说，它是一个
你的狗不认识的陌生人在你的财产上行走，它的行为
在这种情况下，它的行为是无法预测的。

它有经验的司机...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptyi0a/ysk_in_the_eyes_of_a_delivery_driver_your_dog_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptyi0a/ysk_in_the_eyes_of_a_delivery_driver_your_dog_is/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 17:35:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Dog bites are a very big problem when it comes to delivery drivers, And simply saying your dog is friendly means nothing because essentially it&amp;#39;s a stranger walking on your property that your dog does not know and it&amp;#39;s behavior is not predictable in that situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It experienced driver knows how to handle a dog aggressive or not and you&amp;#39;re insistence that they are friendly and won&amp;#39;t do anything typically is what leads to drivers being bitten and we are required to report when we are bitten which could mean your dog can get put on a vicious dog list and/or put down which is something we all want to avoid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So unless you were there to hold back your dog and introduce them to a delivery driver either keep them inside or chained up to avoid any incidents so that you can get your package because it is well within the driver&amp;#39;s right to refuse the delivery if they believe a dog is dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make sure everyone&amp;#39;s safe, no one&amp;#39;s going to get hurt, and do what you can to introduce your dogs to the drivers if they&amp;#39;re going to be your regular.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你的洗碗机比你洗碗时更节能/节水。在洗碗机只装满25%的情况下，其平均用水量仍比手洗餐具少。使用洗碗机而不是手洗，可以节约水、能源和时间。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：这个小窍门可以节省你的时间和金钱，同时有助于环保。
根据你使用的洗涤剂，你甚至不需要在装盘前漂洗碗碟，这可以为你节省更多的时间。
你甚至不必在装盘前冲洗餐具，这将为你节省更多（只要确保经常清洗你的
过滤器）。)

奖励：如果你有一台能源之星洗碗机，它是...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptwcm2/ysk_your_dishwasher_is_far_more_energy_water/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptwcm2/ysk_your_dishwasher_is_far_more_energy_water/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 15:37:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This tip will save you time and money while helping the environment. Depending on the detergent you use, you don&amp;#39;t even have to rinse the dishes before loading them, which saves you even more (just make sure to clean your filter often). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bonus: if you have an Energy Star dishwasher, it is required that they use no more than 3.5 gallons per cycle (compared to the standard 5 gallons), so your water/energy savings will be even greater.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你提到时间限制，人们会对你的闲谈尝试做出更好的回应。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：许多人在发起小型谈话时感到尴尬。这也常常是
尴尬，至少最初是这样。
提到时间限制给了你们两个人一个机会，减少了压力，使你们两个人都放松下来，进入一个更容易的对话。
让你们两个人都放松下来，进入一个更容易的谈话。如果进展顺利，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptuulu/ysk_people_will_respond_much_better_to_your_small/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptuulu/ysk_people_will_respond_much_better_to_your_small/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 14:41:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Many people feel awkward when initiating small talk. It&amp;#39;s also often awkward to have someone initiate small talk with you, at least initially. Mentioning a time constraint gives both of you an out, reducing the pressure and relaxing both of you into an easier conversation. If it goes well, you can mention re-engaging later rather than running out of things to say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Example added for clarity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Hi, I&amp;#39;m on my way to work and in a bit of a hurry, but I wanted to let you know those shoes are awesome! Where did you get them?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Hey bro, I only have a minute before my next set (at the gym), but I gotta ask. What&amp;#39;s your tattoo mean?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 那就是即将到来的猛禽季节!]]></title><description><![CDATA[猛禽季节是成年鹰、猫头鹰和老鹰把今年的婴儿从它们的领地上赶走的时候。
他们的领地。

为什么是YSK：年轻的鹰、猫头鹰或猫头鹰可能会变得更加绝望，去追捕谷仓里的小猫、鸡，或在你的院子里受困。
谷仓里的小猫，鸡，或最终在你的院子里受困。

每年猛禽都有婴儿。但每只猛禽，或繁殖的一对，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptfyoz/ysk_that_its_about_to_be_raptor_season/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptfyoz/ysk_that_its_about_to_be_raptor_season/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 14:12:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Raptor Season is when adult hawks, owls, and eagles push this years babies from their territory. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: young hawks, eagles, or owls may become more desperate and go after barn kittens, chickens, or end up in your yard stranded&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each year raptors have babies. But each raptor, or breeding pair, prefer to have their own territory to hunt in. Especially as food becomes more scarce in the winter. Beginning now, and extending throughout the winter is what a lot of wildlife biologists refer to as “Raptor Season”. This is the final test basically for these babies, seeing if they can survive throughout the winter. They may be more desperate. Usually they won’t go after anything near humans (even chickens despite how many hawks have taken your chickens, only large ones can and even then they would prefer squirrel) however during this time they are more focused on not starving than safety. They may dive into cars, try to go after barn cats, try to go after chickens, or you may even find them in your yard. Raptors that become too weak to fly will quickly get parasites from prolonged time on the ground, keeping them grounded until they find help or die. Keep an extra eye out and extra caution for our winged friends as we progress more into winter!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tl;dr Raptor starvation during the winter can lead to increased exposure&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，如果你在室内，地震发生时，你不应该试图改变位置或离开建筑物。坠落物体的危险远远大于建筑物倒塌的危险。]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个常见的误解是，由于有建筑物倒塌的风险，你应该
当你感觉到摇晃时，应尝试离开建筑物。这恰恰是你
不应该这样做。

官方的指导意见是一致的。在发生地震时，做一件事
而且只做一件事。

 1. 躲避在一个大树下面。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptdv0u/ysk_that_if_you_are_indoors_and_an_earthquake/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptdv0u/ysk_that_if_you_are_indoors_and_an_earthquake/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:53:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a common misconception that, due the risk of building collapse, you should attempt to leave the building when you feel shaking. This is EXACTLY WHAT YOU SHOULD NOT DO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The official guidance is unanimous. In the event of an earthquake, do one thing and one thing ONLY:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DUCK&lt;/strong&gt; beneath a nearby sturdy object. If no sturdy desk, table, or countertop is available, duck next to an interior wall away form windows, heavy frames, shelves, and fixtures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COVER&lt;/strong&gt; your neck and head with your arms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOLD&lt;/strong&gt; on to the object you&amp;#39;re covering under until the shaking stops.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: In a major earthquake, it will be &lt;em&gt;extremely&lt;/em&gt; difficult to move around inside a building. The ground is literally sweeping violently side to side beneath your feet. It would be like trying to run on the bed of a flatbed truck while it drives over a series of speed bumps. The danger of tripping and falling is serious, and winding up on the floor with your head and neck exposed while objects may be falling down all around you is a VERY DANGEROUS situation to be in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, even if you manage to get out of the building, you will have to pass through the area immediately beneath the facade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Glass, masonry, concrete, etc...can very likely be separating from the facade of the building and falling to the street below, even if the building itself remains standing. You do NOT want to be in the area beneath the exterior of a building while the shaking is taking place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only AFTER the shaking stops should you check for injuries, put on sturdy shoes, and calmly leave the building until it can be inspected for structural damage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The USGS web page on what to do during an earthquake reads:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are INDOORS -- STAY THERE! Get under a desk or table and hang on to it (Drop, Cover, and Hold on!) or move into a hallway or against an inside wall. STAY CLEAR of windows, fireplaces, and heavy furniture or appliances. GET OUT of the kitchen, which is a dangerous place (things can fall on you). DON&amp;#39;T run downstairs or rush outside while the building is shaking or while there is danger of falling and hurting yourself or being hit by falling glass or debris.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The University of Washington advises:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DO NOT run outside or to other rooms during shaking: The area near the exterior walls of a building is the most dangerous place to be. Windows, facades and architectural details are often the first parts of the building to collapse. To stay away from this danger zone, stay inside if you are inside and outside if you are outside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK："羞愧 "的意思是 "尴尬"，而不是 "惊恐"]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：因为我已经看到这两个人被混淆了很多次，令人沮丧。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pte645/ysk_mortified_means_embarrassed_not_terrified/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pte645/ysk_mortified_means_embarrassed_not_terrified/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 22:32:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Cuz I&amp;#39;ve seen the two confused a &lt;em&gt;mortifying&lt;/em&gt; amount of times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，如果你与某人有分歧，你应该问他："有什么证据/证据能改变你的想法吗？"]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：如果他们说不，那么你说什么或做什么都不会改变他们的想法
所以尝试是没有意义的。可以说，你只是在转圈而已。

如果他们说："我不确定，但我愿意看你的任何证据/证明。
这就是一个完全有效的回应。有些人...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pt90q2/ysk_that_if_you_ever_have_a_disagreement_with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pt90q2/ysk_that_if_you_ever_have_a_disagreement_with/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 19:58:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If they say no, then nothing you can say or do will change their mind so there&amp;#39;s no point in trying. You&amp;#39;ll just be spinning your wheels so to speak. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If they say, &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m not sure, but I&amp;#39;m open to looking at whatever proof/evidence you have.&amp;quot; that&amp;#39;s a completely valid response. Some people don&amp;#39;t know what it would take to change their opinion, but if they&amp;#39;re open to the idea of seeing evidence that goes against their beliefs, then it could warrant dialogue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如果你在美国，并通过你的雇主购买医疗保险，有2/3的机会你的雇主决定了什么是承保和不承保--而不是医疗保险公司。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：如果你的一个程序被拒绝了，可能值得和以下人谈谈
谁负责人力资源部门的福利，以便在未来改变它。

在2020年，美国67%的受保工人是通过
自筹资金的计划。(链接来源)
[https://www.kff.org/report...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptb8dr/ysk_if_you_are_in_the_us_and_have_health/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ptb8dr/ysk_if_you_are_in_the_us_and_have_health/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 18:59:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:   If one of your procedures has been denied, it might be worth talking to whoever is in charge of benefits in HR to change it in the future.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2020, 67% of covered workers in the U.S. were receiving coverage through a self-funded plan. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kff.org/report-section/ehbs-2020-section-10-plan-funding/&quot;&gt;(Linked source)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Self-funded&amp;quot; means that any health premiums collected only come from that employer AND are only used on healthcare expenses for that employer. In many cases, this also allows the employer to customize elements of what they will allow to be covered and not covered. Self-funded plans can also circumvent most state-level insurance mandates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If your insurance doesn&amp;#39;t cover something like &amp;quot;transgender services&amp;quot;, that decision could be on your employer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;#39;t like the payments for your mental/behavioral health provider?  That might be something that&amp;#39;s controllable by your employer - not the insurer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your buddy went in for XYZ procedure and his was fully paid for by ABC Insurance?  If you also have an ABC Insurance card, even if you had the same procedure done on the exact same day from the exact same provider, yours might NOT be paid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And we all wonder why the U.S. Healthcare system needs an overhaul...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>