<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 01:34:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：由於廣泛的驅逐和搬遷，自我存儲是一個溢價。而且很少有任何法律保護措施來防止任意漲價。你的租金會上漲，而且是遠遠地上漲。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：搬入和搬出儲物櫃涉及到勞動力、卡車租賃等的沉沒成本。
租用等等。扔掉一半的東西，清理你的生活和你的預算
在租金上漲之前，把你的一半東西扔掉，以清理你的生活和你的預算，像俄羅斯方塊一樣把你壓垮。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o39kem/ysk_because_of_widespread_evictions_and_moves/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o39kem/ysk_because_of_widespread_evictions_and_moves/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 17:44:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Moves in and out of storage lockers involve sunk costs for labor, truck rentals, etc. Clean up your life and your budget by throwing away half your shit before the rent hikes squash you like Tetris.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：樺樹糖是木糖醇，能殺死你的狗]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們中的許多人正在努力避免使用人工甜味劑，併爲我們和我們的寵物轉向更多的天然
飲食，爲我們和我們的寵物提供更多的天然食品。聽起來像化學品的名字會讓我們認爲
的東西對我們有害，而製造商很清楚這一點，所以很多時候
他們會試圖爲他們的產品使用不那麼 "誘人 "的名字....。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o3igob/ysk_birch_sugar_is_xylitol_can_kill_your_dog/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o3igob/ysk_birch_sugar_is_xylitol_can_kill_your_dog/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 17:44:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of us are trying to avoid artificial sweeteners and move to more natural foods for us and our pets.  Chemical-sounding names can make us think that something is bad for us, and manufacturers are well aware of this, so many times they will try to use less “triggering” names for their products.  Birch sugar is one of those things.  It is a sweetener that comes from birch trees, but it is also known as xylitol.  Why YSK: Xylitol Is sugar alcohol that doesn’t play nicely with a dog’s blood sugar and causes it to drop quickly, and too much, which can lead to seizures, liver damage, and death.  And it’s in a lot of foods these days such a peanut butter and ice cream, so please be careful when giving your dogs treats.  It is also one of the most common sweeteners for sugar-free gum, and as a critical care vet tech, that was a very common toxicity I saw at my hospital.  Give your fluffy one some hugs and always read ingredient lists.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 公共廁所裏的聲音對自閉症兒童來說可能是毀滅性的，所以要注意便利貼。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：我的小兒子有自閉症，在全瓷磚的公共廁所裏彈出的聲音簡直會讓他在10分鐘內無法入睡。
我的小兒子有自閉症，全瓷磚的公共廁所發出的聲音會導致他在10分鐘內崩潰，並在他的大腦中產生非常消極的
在他的大腦中對所有公共浴室產生非常負面的聯想。自動馬桶和那些
噴氣式幹手器對我們來說是一個死刑判決。有時孩子們...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o375gm/ysk_sounds_in_a_public_restroom_can_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o375gm/ysk_sounds_in_a_public_restroom_can_be/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 16:36:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: My young son has autism and the sounds bouncing off the all tile public restrooms will literally cause a 10 minute meltdown and a very negative association in his brain to all public bathrooms. Automatic toilets and those jet engine hand dryers are a death sentence for us. Sometimes kids with autism also have a hard time predicting what might happen in some situations. So these things suddenly going off is the equivalent of you on the toilet and someone shoots a shotgun off next to your ear without you having a clue it&amp;#39;s coming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you see a post-it note on a hand dryer saying an autistic child is in there at the moment, PLEASE give us 1 minute to get out of there. It costs you 1 minute (or 0 if you like wet hands) but could set him back months of progress and limit what our family is able to get out and do. We literally have to restart at square 1 of just practicing walking by the doors and having him flip out seeing the signs. Then to walking in and straight out and so on. I will take the post-it off before we leave.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the post-it on the automatic toilet sensor...I may or may not be able to take that one. If you go into a stall and see one of these feel free to help a fellow human out by removing it. It&amp;#39;ll probably have a short note on it explaining with an apology. If I&amp;#39;m alone, I can&amp;#39;t take it off with him there and he can&amp;#39;t be left alone outside while I try.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你不需要 "清除你的思想 "來練習冥想或正念。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：根據一項研究。徘徊的心是不快樂的心
[https://wjh-www.harvard.edu/%7Edtg/KILLINGSWORTH%20&%20GILBERT%20(2010).pdf)。
我們的頭腦幾乎有47%的時間迷失在思考中，這也是導致我們不快樂的根源之一。
導致我們不快樂/抑鬱/焦慮狀態的根本原因之一。

根據一項研究表明]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o2j2w7/ysk_you_dont_have_to_clear_your_thoughts_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o2j2w7/ysk_you_dont_have_to_clear_your_thoughts_to/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 07:00:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: According to a research: &lt;a href=&quot;https://wjh-www.harvard.edu/%7Edtg/KILLINGSWORTH%20&amp;amp;%20GILBERT%20(2010&quot;&gt;A Wandering Mind Is an Unhappy Mind&lt;/a&gt;.pdf), our minds are lost in thought almost 47% of the time which is one of the root causes of our state of being unhappy/depressed/anxious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to a Mindfulness expert, Andy Puddicombe, &lt;strong&gt;meditation&lt;/strong&gt; is NOT all about stopping thoughts, getting rid of emotions or somehow controlling the mind. Instead, it&amp;#39;s more about stepping back and see thought clearly; witnessing it coming and going without any judgement but with a relaxed and focused mind. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can watch his TedTalk: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ted.com/talks/andy_puddicombe_all_it_takes_is_10_mindful_minutes?utm_campaign=tedspread&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_source=tedcomshare&quot;&gt;All it takes is 10 mindful minutes&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also can watch his &amp;quot;Guided meditation&amp;quot; on Netflix.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[當你爲一個問題聯繫技術支持時，給他們提供導致該問題的複製步驟，YSK。如果他們能夠複製這個問題，這將有助於更快地解決問題。]]></title><description><![CDATA[多年前我曾從事過技術支持工作，現在我仍然以某種身份從事這項工作。
我仍然以某種身份爲同事或家人服務。

爲什麼選擇YSK：如果有人解釋問題發生的原因，就會使
一切都會變得更容易。如果他們不這樣做，我就必須進入故障排除的狀態。
測試一切，並且...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o2ortj/ysk_that_when_you_contact_tech_support_for_an/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o2ortj/ysk_that_when_you_contact_tech_support_for_an/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 02:28:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I used to work tech support many years ago and I still kind of do in some capacity, either for coworkers or family. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If someone explains what occurred for the issue to happen, it makes everything much easier. If they don&amp;#39;t, I have to go into troubleshooting mood, testing everything, and asking a lot of questions. If I can&amp;#39;t reproduce it, I can&amp;#39;t fix it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Help your tech support help you&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK SiriusXM很可能將你的信息賣給那些汽車延保的垃圾郵件發送者]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：SiriusXM很可能將他們的客戶數據賣給了那些汽車延保名單。
保修電話名單。我是這樣知道的。

許多年前，我購買了一個二手的OEM收音機，它最初是安裝在一臺
2008年克萊斯勒Aspen，有SiriusXM的兼容性。該收音機與我的車兼容
我的車，但...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o31tvz/ysk_siriusxm_is_likely_selling_your_info_to_those/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o31tvz/ysk_siriusxm_is_likely_selling_your_info_to_those/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 23:44:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; SiriusXM is &lt;em&gt;likely&lt;/em&gt; selling their customer data to those extended car warranty call lists. Here&amp;#39;s how I know this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many years ago I purchased a used OEM radio that was originally installed in a 2008 Chrysler Aspen that had SiriusXM compatibility. The radio was compatible with my car though, like many Dodge/Chrysler/Jeep cars of the time, which was &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; a Chrysler Aspen. This was a cash sale, so the person who sold it to me knew nothing about me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since my last radio did not have satellite radio, I wanted to give it a try, so I subscribed. When you call or go online and enter the radio ID, it will confirm with you the year, make, and model that they have in their database for that radio ID. It matched what the seller said it came out of. Subscribed, activated, and everything worked fine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To this day, I continue to get calls about purchasing an extended warranty for my, you guessed it, 2008 Chrysler Aspen. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How could that be? I never actually owned one, nor have I owned anything even remotely close to that. The only person or company that ever knew I had any connection to one was SiriusXM. So that&amp;#39;s how I know they sold/shared my data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，有一些替代性的、精品式的電影流媒體服務，可能比大公司更能迎合你喜歡的電影類型。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：注意可用性可能取決於國家和地區

如果你喜歡文藝片或經典電影，在Criterion頻道有一個巨大的、定期更改的
的電影庫，價格爲100美元/年。

如果你喜歡恐怖片、邪教經典片和B級片，ARROW Player的價格爲50美元/年。
可能是一個很好的選擇...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o2xdhq/ysk_that_there_are_alternative_boutiquestyle/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o2xdhq/ysk_that_there_are_alternative_boutiquestyle/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 22:46:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: &lt;strong&gt;note availability may depend on country and region&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you like arthouse or classic movies, there is a huge and regularly altered library of films on The Criterion Channel for $100/yr.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you like horror, cult classics, and B-movies, The ARROW Player for $50/yr might be a great choice for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you like Anime, Funimation might be a good choice for $7.99/mo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not that any of these are any better or worse than Netflix, Hulu, HBO Max, etc. but the smaller ones I listed and others like them may offer different kinds of cultural enrichment and entertainment that some people may be looking for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：隨着如此龐大的嬰兒潮一代進入老年，要注意虐待老人的問題。它正在發生。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK: 照顧老人和撫養孩子一樣具有挑戰性，但
孩子們更容易被原諒（他們很可愛，而且在我們的文化中，我們更熟悉孩子而不是老人）。
在我們的文化中，我們對孩子比對老人更熟悉）。) 我們很容易對我們的老人不耐煩。
我們很容易對年邁的父母和其他老人不耐煩，當我們爲他們的行爲感到沮喪時。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o2gtfg/ysk_with_such_a_huge_boomer_generation_reaching/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o2gtfg/ysk_with_such_a_huge_boomer_generation_reaching/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 07:00:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  Caring for old folks can be as challenging as raising children, but children are easier to forgive (they&amp;#39;re cute and in our culture, we&amp;#39;re more familiar with kids than with the elderly). It&amp;#39;s easy to be impatient with our aging parents and other elderly people when we&amp;#39;re frustrated by their changes (growing dependence) and confused about the &amp;quot;right&amp;quot; way to interact with them or make choices about their care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People can become cruel or neglectful when they don&amp;#39;t understand the aging process or when they aren&amp;#39;t aware of the resources available to them as caretakers. (And unfortunately, some people are just plain cruel or neglectful by nature.) There are evil people who exploit the elderly, as well as people who neglect or hurt them. Watch out for your elderly loved ones and neighbors!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nia.nih.gov/health/elder-abuse&quot;&gt;Elder abuse&lt;/a&gt; takes many forms:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Physical abuse &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Emotional abuse&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Neglect &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Abandonment &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sexual abuse &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Financial abuse&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 坐輪椅的人站起來，甚至走一點路，並不意味着他們是在裝病。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：人們的假設可能是一個人焦慮的原因。
已經在經歷一些艱難的事情。例如，我坐過輪椅
因爲我的腿部運動和行走有問題，但可以站立。
直立就可以了。我也非常年輕，會得到非常奇怪的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o2e6yf/ysk_just_because_someone_with_a_wheelchair_stands/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o2e6yf/ysk_just_because_someone_with_a_wheelchair_stands/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 03:44:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: People making assumptions can be a cause for anxiety for someone already going through something tough. For example, I was in a wheelchair because I had trouble with movement of my legs and walking, but could stand straight up just fine. I’m also really young and would get really strange looks a lot, especially from older people, which would make me super self conscious. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are reasons other than being paralyzed that may require use of a wheelchair :) This only came to mind because I saw a post accusing someone faking their illness because they stood up from their wheelchair&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 如果你的電子郵件被黑，你需要做的不僅僅是改變你的密碼。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK: 如果你的電子郵件被黑，改變密碼並不是唯一的事情。
你應該做的。黑客會改變你賬戶內的設置，所以即使在修改密碼後
密碼更改後，他們仍然可以訪問你的電子郵件。這可能包括連接
帳戶，轉發，和自動回覆。有時這些...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o28qhk/ysk_if_your_email_gets_hacked_you_need_to_do_more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o28qhk/ysk_if_your_email_gets_hacked_you_need_to_do_more/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 01:16:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If your email gets hacked, changing the password is not the only thing you should do. Hackers will change settings inside your account so even after a password change they still can access your emails. This can include connected accounts, forwarding, and automatic replies. Sometimes these settings can be the reason why your emails go to the wrong folder or disappear. If you get hacked; Go on your email provider&amp;#39;s website to find what to look for and what to delete. Not doing this can lead to more of your accounts and information being compromised.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，你實際上可以把自己累死。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK: "漫長的工作時間每年導致數十萬人死亡。
根據世界衛生組織（WHO）的說法。第一項全球研究表明，有74.5萬人因工作時間過長而死亡。
顯示，2016年有74.5萬人因中風和心臟病而死亡。
長時間工作。(55+/周)"

來源：中國新聞網 英國廣播公司...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o243nu/ysk_that_you_actually_can_work_yourself_to_death/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o243nu/ysk_that_you_actually_can_work_yourself_to_death/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 21:43:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: &amp;quot;Long working hours are killing hundreds of thousands of people a year, according to the World Health Organization (WHO). The first global study of its kind showed 745,000 people died in 2016 from stroke and heart disease due to long hours. (55+/week)&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/news/business-57139434&quot;&gt;Source: BBC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：ADA認爲 "中 "和 "硬 "牙刷是有害的，幾乎沒有人應該使用它們。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你去藥店的牙刷貨架，你可能會被提供幾十種不同形狀和尺寸的牙刷。
不同形狀和尺寸的刷子，每一種都有自己聲稱的好處。
你有時會看到不同刷子之間的許多變化，其中之一是
刷子的硬度，一般是軟的、中的、或硬的。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o21u6r/ysk_medium_and_hard_toothbrushes_are_considered/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o21u6r/ysk_medium_and_hard_toothbrushes_are_considered/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 21:43:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you go to a pharmacy toothbrush aisle you&amp;#39;ll probably be provided with dozens of different shapes and sizes of brush, each with its own purported benefits. One of the many variations between different brushes you will sometimes see is bristle stiffness, which is generally Soft, Medium, or Hard/Firm. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This choice is presented to consumers as a seemingly benign difference based on preference, like choosing between crisscross bristles or an angled tip, but it is very much not. There is a clear consensus to exclusively use &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ada.org/en/member-center/oral-health-topics/toothbrushes&quot;&gt;soft bristled brushes&lt;/a&gt; for teeth, and no dentist will recommend that you use a medium or harder toothbrush since they can cause erosion and gum damage. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Harder bristled toothbrushes do have some very limited special-case uses, such as cleaning dentures, but manufacturers continue to resist making that distinction clear in packaging and marketing. This leads to confusing double talk where Colgate &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.colgate.com/en-us/oral-health/selecting-dental-products/soft-vs-hard-toothbrush&quot;&gt;confirms on their website&lt;/a&gt; that consumers should exclusively choose soft toothbrushes, but also markets medium firmness toothbrushes as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.colgate.com/en-gb/products/toothbrush/colgate-extra-clean-3-pack-toothbrush&quot;&gt;a standard product&lt;/a&gt; even labeling them as &amp;quot;Extra Clean,&amp;quot; implying that they work better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The industry is stuck in kind of a chicken-and-egg scenario that can cause you real harm. Some consumers want &amp;quot;firmer&amp;quot; toothbrushes based on lack of knowledge and no manufacturer wants to lose that market segment so they keep making them, but the ongoing availability of normal medium/firm brushes reinforces the misconception that they are standard choices that work better for some consumers. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Whatever other choices you are making with picking brushes you should &lt;em&gt;never&lt;/em&gt; choose a firmer bristle than soft without specific advice from your dentist, or you could damage your teeth or gums. You should think of Medium and Firm/Hard toothbrushes as specialty tools with specialty purposes and not a matter of preference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，現在的勞動力短缺可以大大有利於現在的每一個最低工資工人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：如果你在爲最低工資工作，你的工資就會大大降低。有許多地方
有這麼多地方急於尋找僱員。他們正在提高他們的
他們正在提高工資，並提供瘋狂的簽約獎金，而這些獎金並沒有提供給他們現有的員工
現有員工 當新人們被僱用時，問他們有多少錢。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o20nqi/ysk_that_the_labor_shortage_right_now_can_greatly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o20nqi/ysk_that_the_labor_shortage_right_now_can_greatly/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 19:03:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If you are working for min wage, you are greatly being underpaid. There are so many places that are desperate for employees. They are raising their wages and offering crazy sign on bonuses that they are not offering to their current employees! When new people get hired, ask how much they are making. Employers are desperate to keep their current employees and find new ones. There are tons of jobs available right now that pay over $18 an hour that will train from scratch. Start applying at night and watch them call you! Every job applied for called back and tried to schedule an interview. I gaurentee your boss has a crazy high labor budget right now. Ask them why you haven&amp;#39;t gotten a raise when so many places are offering such great incentives to work for them. We as the employees are in control much more now and I hope it stays this way.
Are you a server? Become a Bartender! Or find a place that will start you as one.
Host? Promote to server!
Fast food worker of any kind? Go apply at restaurants! Way better money for similar work BOH and FOH alike! 
Work retail? Switch to sales! If you have to deal with customers BS, and long hours, you might as well get paid way better for it! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I&amp;#39;m saying is, take advantage of these horrible companies like they&amp;#39;ve taken advantage of you. Get your job offers and go to your boss and say, I want a promotion/raise or I&amp;#39;m going to this place where they are offering both. Very few companies care about resumes right now. Go make that money!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：僱主在法律上不能強迫你自掏腰包買東西]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK？無論你以前與你的僱主簽署了什麼協議或表格
至少在加拿大卑詩省，僱主強迫僱員接受培訓是非法的。
僱員爲其工作的結果支付費用是非法的。

例子。我在一家車行工作時發生了一起小事故，當時我在車行工作。
back....]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o1ztu0/ysk_an_employer_cannot_legally_force_you_to_pay/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o1ztu0/ysk_an_employer_cannot_legally_force_you_to_pay/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 18:42:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK? Regardless of any previous deals or forms you may have signed with your employer, at least in BC Canada, it is illegal for an employer to force an employee to pay for something as a result of their work. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Example: I was in a minor accident at a car dealership I was working at a while back. It was 100% not my fault, however the managers claimed 10km/h was too fast in the lot (nobody told me the speed limit was 5km/h). The other person didn’t look before pulling out and hit the truck I was driving and therefore it was apparently my fault. They tried charging me 1/3 if the insurance deductible, which was $1,000. They also terminated me. I kept arguing that I wasn’t going to pay it and eventually found &lt;a href=&quot;https://www2.gov.bc.ca/gov/content/employment-business/employment-standards-advice/employment-standards/wages/deductions&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; and screenshot it and sent it to them. When I met with the financial people at their head office shortly after, they said my balance was $0. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t let scum bag corporations prey on young workers because they think they may not know the rules&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如果你是一個服務員/酒保，被僱主強迫支付走賬是完全違法的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：我遇到過這種情況，我看到它發生過無數次。但這是
直接是非法的。就這麼簡單。在任何情況下，經理或老闆都不可能讓你爲別人付錢。
在任何情況下，經理或老闆都不能讓你爲別人的食物買單，因爲他們決定不付錢就走了。
不付錢就走人。

根據美國司法部的規定。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o1m2t5/ysk_if_you_are_a_server_bartender_its_completely/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o1m2t5/ysk_if_you_are_a_server_bartender_its_completely/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 04:59:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I’ve had it happen to me, I’ve seen it happen countless times. But it’s straight up illegal. Simple as that. In no case is it okay for a manager or owner to make you pay for someone else’s food because they decided to walk out on you without paying. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the Department of Labor;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Where deductions for walk-outs, breakage, or cash register shortages reduce the employee’s wages below the minimum wage, such deductions are illegal. Where a tipped employee is paid $2.13 per hour in direct (or cash) wages and the employer claims the maximum tip credit of $5.12 per hour, no such deductions can be made without reducing the employee below the minimum wage (even where the employee receives more than $5.12 per hour in tips).&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately... they can still get angry and petty, and find a way to fire you if they are that shitty... but who really wants to work for those people, anyway?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t let them convince you you have any obligation to pay for a tab, ever. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/agencies/whd/fact-sheets/15-flsa-tipped-employees&quot;&gt;https://www.dol.gov/agencies/whd/fact-sheets/15-flsa-tipped-employees&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，1099關係受到IRS的嚴格監管，必須滿足非常具體的要求，工人才能成爲實際的接觸者。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK。

美國的勞動力市場充滿了故意將僱主錯誤歸類爲
作爲1099承包商。這是一種非常普遍的做法，這樣做是爲了讓僱主
可以非法地節省福利和稅收。另一個動機是，1099
承包商幾乎不受任何勞動法的約束。大多數人...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o02ti9/ysk_that_1099_relationships_are_strictly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o02ti9/ysk_that_1099_relationships_are_strictly/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 16:01:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The US labor market is filled with employers knowingly misclassifying employers as 1099 contractors. It&amp;#39;s a very common practice that is done so the employer can illegally save on benefits &amp;amp; taxes. Another motivation is that 1099 contractors are subject to almost no labor laws. Most people aren&amp;#39;t even aware of these regulations so it goes unreported.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I AM NOT A LAWYER. THIS POST IS NOT LEGAL ADVICE. CONSULT AN ATTORNEY FOR ANY QUESTIONS ABOUT YOUR SPECIFIC SITUATION.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did you know that employers can’t randomly decide you are an independent contractor? The IRS has very strict regulations governing the requirements the professional relationship must meet. Even if the “contractor” in question signs an IC agreement, the employer is still responsible for treating the contractor as a contractor. The minute they overstep, it’s tax fraud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For reference, the following are all red flags that you aren’t legally a 1099 contractor:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have a non-compete agreement. (on an tangential note, most states don&amp;#39;t even enforce non-compete agreements)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have set hours. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your employer sets your wages. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are hired on a permanent basis vs a per-project basis. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your employer provides training and expects you to follow specific operating procedures. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are micromanaged. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are required to regularly meet about your performance. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have an assigned, detailed task list.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can find more information here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.irs.gov/businesses/small-businesses-self-employed/independent-contractor-self-employed-or-employee&quot;&gt;https://www.irs.gov/businesses/small-businesses-self-employed/independent-contractor-self-employed-or-employee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t let yourself get fucked on your taxes if you’ve been misclassified. Speak to a tax professional/attorney and find out what your options are. The IRS will need to make a determination on your classification, so make sure you document all employer activities that indicate tax fraud. Most intentional misclassifications will have a lot of these red flags, making it easier to prove.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No matter how you report it to the IRS, your employer will be on the hook for half of your Social Security &amp;amp; Medicare taxes. Plus penalties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK有一個名爲Be My Eyes的應用程序，可以讓視障人士通過視頻呼叫志願者，請求提供視覺援助。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：該應用程序是免費下載的，你可以作爲志願者或視障/盲人報名參加。
視力障礙者/盲人。如果你需要視覺幫助（舉例來說
挑選正確的衣服顏色，或在購物時選擇正確的產品品牌。
而你是視障人士，你可以按一個按鈕......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o149jr/ysk_there_is_an_app_called_be_my_eyes_that_allows/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o149jr/ysk_there_is_an_app_called_be_my_eyes_that_allows/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 14:33:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: The app is free to download and you can sign up as a volunteer or a visually impaired / blind person. If you need visual help (examples given are picking the right colour of an item of clothing, or the right brand of product when shopping) and you are visually impaired, you press a button on the app. The app will call multiple volunteers (volunteers do not need to have the app open to recieve a call, they just have to be logged in) , and whoever picks up the quickest is connected by video call. The volunteer can then assist you in whatever task you need help with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thought it was a great idea and a helpful app. Currently there are over 4 million volunteers signed up, but only 310, 000 visually impaired or blind people. Thought I&amp;#39;d share in case anyone would find this useful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，你不應該對房子提出超過要價的報價。如果你是唯一的出價，你可以讓你的房地產經紀人包括一個升級條款，這樣的話，如果你是唯一的出價，你可能最終會節省數萬美元。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK。

我最近從一個人那裏聽說，他們認爲這是我所在城市市場降溫的一個跡象。
因爲他們的房子只收到一份報價。然而。
那份報價比要價高出12.5%（在這種情況下，是2萬美元）。

同樣，他們是唯一提交報價的人。

他們...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o0ky8n/ysk_that_you_shouldnt_offer_over_asking_price_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o0ky8n/ysk_that_you_shouldnt_offer_over_asking_price_on/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 21:34:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I heard from someone recently that they thought it was a sign of the market in my city cooling down, because they only got one offer on their house. However, that offer was for 12.5% (in this case, $20,000) OVER asking price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, they were the &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt; ones to submit an offer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;They literally gave away twenty thousand dollars over asking price for no reason other than the fear of someone else offering more.&lt;/strong&gt; But you can avoid all of that by simply asking your agent to add an escalation clause. With that, you can have your offer automatically go higher and higher, up to a pre-set amount, &lt;em&gt;if&lt;/em&gt; there are other higher offers on the table. Someone else bid 10k over asking but your clause goes up to 15k? Congrats, you&amp;#39;ve got the highest offer now. Turns out you&amp;#39;re the only offer on the table? Guess what, you just saved yourself five figures by &lt;em&gt;starting&lt;/em&gt; your offer at listing price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, it is of course possible that a seller can simply decide to wait and see if a higher offer comes. But that doesn&amp;#39;t automatically disqualify yours. And there are also a lot of sellers who are only ditching their homes because they&amp;#39;ve already bought another and time is a factor, so they&amp;#39;ll take a speedy sale over waiting for a bigger number. And it&amp;#39;s possible that a buyer&amp;#39;s agent will simply say they&amp;#39;re not accepting contracts with ECs. If that&amp;#39;s the case, it&amp;#39;s up to you to decide how badly you want that house.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在緊急情況發生之前，需要運行發電機。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：許多人不知道發電機在需要時經常不工作。
後不工作。你可能需要拆開化油器碗，幾乎不費吹灰之力就能清潔主噴口。
你可能需要拆開化油器碗，幾乎不費吹灰之力就能清洗初級噴射器，並在你需要它之前運行發電機。
😉。燃油可能會因爲坐起來而變壞或 "結塊"。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o0bwaz/ysk_generators_need_to_be_ran_before_emergencies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o0bwaz/ysk_generators_need_to_be_ran_before_emergencies/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 19:45:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK : Many people are not aware generators will often not work when needed after sitting up. You may need to detach the carburetor bowl and clean the primary jets nearly effortlessly,and run the generator before you will need it unexpectedly.😉.
The fuel may go bad or &amp;quot;jelly&amp;quot; due to sitting up and this prevents the fuel lines to flow or the primary jet to atomize fuel during the combustion cycle.
Allow your generator to run an entire day and gauge how much fuel is needed for 3-10 days this summer as this year a lot of .climate. activity is expected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，如果你和人們在一起，並且因爲任何原因不想喝酒；手裏拿着不含酒精的飲料（真的是任何東西）可以幫助你感到安心，並向其他人發出你不需要喝酒的信號。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：我們的社會希望人們喝酒，而人們不喝酒的原因有幾百種。
人們不喝酒。很多人只是對他們可能被叫出來或被問到爲什麼不喝酒而感到非常焦慮。
他們可能會被叫出來，或者被問到他們爲什麼不喝酒。我知道我曾經這樣做過，而且今天仍然如此。

這個小貼士幫助我度過了15年的清醒期，也幫助了我。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o0dwi5/ysk_that_if_youre_out_with_people_and_dont_want/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o0dwi5/ysk_that_if_youre_out_with_people_and_dont_want/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 16:40:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Our society expects people to drink, and there are hundreds of reasons people don’t. A lot of people simply get very anxious of the possibility they can called out or asked why they don’t drink. I know I did and still do today.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This tip has helped me through my 15 years being sober and hope this tip helps you too.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Original tip was removed from LPT as “advice”. I’ve appealed and hope this tip gets back up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 在你的車裏放一罐湯]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：在你的車裏有一罐湯可以派上用場。它可以幫助
在雪地裏、惡劣的暴風雨中等情況下，它可以發揮作用。如果你沒有現金，你也可以把它送給
如果你身上沒有現金，你也可以把它送給無家可歸的人。如果你有一天需要離開
突然離開，你至少會有一頓飯的保障。或者，如果...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nzrmyq/ysk_to_keep_a_can_of_soup_in_your_car/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nzrmyq/ysk_to_keep_a_can_of_soup_in_your_car/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 15:34:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Having a can of soup in your car can come in handy. It can be helpful in events like getting stuck in the snow, in bad storms, etc. You also can give it to homeless people if you don&amp;#39;t have cash on you. If you ever needed to leave suddenly, you would have at least one meal covered. Or, if you forget your lunch for work. I keep both a cheap plastic, microwaveable bowl and 2 cans of soup in my car usually, just in case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：《同工同酬法》（今年1月1日生效）要求科羅拉多州的所有招聘信息必須包括工資和福利。這也包括任何在科羅拉多州有效的遠程職位。如果一個公司沒有遵守這項法律，你可以舉報他們，他們將被罰款。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：所有科羅拉多州的招聘信息和美國的遠程招聘信息（即在科羅拉多州的人可以申請的職位）必須包括工資福利。
的職位）必須包括工資和福利。
信息。這很好，因爲作爲求職者，你可以瞭解到該職位的薪酬以及公司提供的福利。
職位的薪酬以及該公司提供的福利。這...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o054oh/ysk_the_equal_pay_for_equal_work_act_effective/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/o054oh/ysk_the_equal_pay_for_equal_work_act_effective/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 05:33:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: All Colorado job postings AND remote US job postings (i.e. a role that someone in Colorado could apply for) must include salary and benefits information. This is great because you, as an applicant, can find out what a the position should pay as well as what benefits the company offers. This is great for all American workers, even for ones not located in Colorado.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, many companies are not complying with this law! So if you ever see a job posting that doesn&amp;#39;t include a salary posted, and it&amp;#39;s either located in the state of colorado, or is it is a remote US position, report them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a link to file a complaint: &lt;a href=&quot;https://cdle.colorado.gov/equal-pay-for-equal-work-act-part-2&quot;&gt;https://cdle.colorado.gov/equal-pay-for-equal-work-act-part-2&lt;/a&gt;. You simply download a form from this page, fill it out, and email it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK："幾個壞蘋果 "這句話並不意味着孤立的一羣壞事。]]></title><description><![CDATA["幾個壞蘋果 "已經與 "幾個壞雞蛋 "相混淆，並被錯誤地用於
用來代替它。這兩個短語的意思並不相同。"幾個壞蛋"
是用來描述一組東西，其中有一些壞蛋
但這並不自動意味着整個...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nzpynk/ysk_the_phrase_a_few_bad_apples_does_not_mean_an/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nzpynk/ysk_the_phrase_a_few_bad_apples_does_not_mean_an/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 18:33:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;A few bad apples&amp;quot; has become confused with &lt;strong&gt;&amp;quot;a few bad&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;eggs&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;  and is incorrectly used in its place.  The two phrases DO NOT mean the  same thing. &amp;quot;A few bad eggs&amp;quot; is used to describe a group of something in  which  there are a number of bad individuals but which doesn&amp;#39;t automatically mean that  the &lt;em&gt;entire&lt;/em&gt;  group is bad *[or will become bad]. One rotten egg does not mean they will all be  rotten; it  could just be an isolated incident and the rest of the eggs will be  fine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;A few bad apples&amp;quot; describes something more nefarious, but people often leave out  the other half of the saying. The  entire phrase is &amp;quot;A few bad apples &lt;em&gt;spoil the barrel.&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt; It means that if even one apple is rotten then, unless it is removed, the rot will inevitably  spread and eat  through all of the apples. The true meaning is it is  dangerous to ignore what might be a small problem, because that problem might be caused by something more complicated, and ignoring it allows it to spread.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Using &amp;quot;a few bad apples&amp;quot; to say a problem is only due to a small, isolated group of actors downplays or overlooks the &lt;strong&gt;systemic&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;contagious&lt;/strong&gt; nature of the problem. The problem should be addressed quickly before it festers and grows into something much harder to fix.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*edit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK --- 不要忽視閃爍的發動機檢查燈。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：當發動機檢查燈閃爍時，這意味着你可能有一個更嚴重的問題需要你立即注意。
更嚴重的問題，需要你立即注意（這就是爲什麼它
閃爍）。) 你應該迅速解決這個問題，否則你有可能嚴重
損壞你的發動機。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nzaqmb/ysk_do_not_ignore_a_flashing_check_engine_light/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nzaqmb/ysk_do_not_ignore_a_flashing_check_engine_light/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 13:12:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: When the check engine light is flashing, that means you could have a more serious issue that needs your immediate attention (which is &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; it&amp;#39;s flashing). You should quickly address the problem or you risk possibly badly damaging your engine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，你可以在社會安全局的網站（美國）上看到你有權獲得的福利（除其他外）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我意識到，SSA的在線服務門戶是很少有人知道的。
瞭解。它爲你提供了大量有價值的信息。

一旦你在SSA的在線服務門戶上創建了一個賬戶
[https://www.ssa.gov/onlineservices/]，你就可以看到。

1）他們對你每年的記錄是什麼...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nzb17o/ysk_that_you_can_see_the_benefits_youre_entitled/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nzb17o/ysk_that_you_can_see_the_benefits_youre_entitled/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 07:05:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve realized that the SSA&amp;#39;s Online Service Portal is something few people know about. It provides you with a ton of valuable information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you create an account on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ssa.gov/onlineservices/&quot;&gt;SSA&amp;#39;s Online Service Portal&lt;/a&gt;, you can see:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) What they have on record for your yearly earnings for the duration of your working life (so you can confirm it&amp;#39;s accurate... and it&amp;#39;s cool to see).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) What you&amp;#39;ll collect once you turn 67 and are eligible for SSI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) What you&amp;#39;d collect should you become eligible for SSD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) What your dependents and/or spouse would receive should they become eligible for Survivor&amp;#39;s Benefits because you passed away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) If you&amp;#39;ve worked enough to even be eligible for any of those benefits. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) The estimated taxes you and your employer(s) will pay towards Social Security and Medicare in your lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;... Among other things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unrelated to the benefits this website provides, but it also allowed me to show my parents how stagnant wages have been by &lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/Lv75whI.jpg&quot;&gt;comparing their yearly earnings from when they were my age with mine&lt;/a&gt;. We&amp;#39;re in similar paying professions so it&amp;#39;s a pretty accurate depiction. It was awesome watching their faces as they came to the realization that I&amp;#39;m not completely full of shit, lol. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: You can check their records for accuracy before it comes time for you to actually need to utilize any of the benefits that are available to you. It can also help you prepare for retirement by having a good idea of how much you&amp;#39;ll be paid. And also, it&amp;#39;s super interesting (at least I think so).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fair warning... You have to be able to prove your identity and if you mess up enough, they&amp;#39;ll make you register via snail mail. Make sure you&amp;#39;re answering exactly as they want (i.e, don&amp;#39;t put your address as 123 Drive Drive if your tax return shows 123 Drive Dr).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：健康保險市場有受過培訓的工作人員，他們可以爲你的健康保險費用找到扣減項目。如果你需要使用市場，你應該打電話，讓他們指導你加入，而不是在網上進行。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：許多人認爲，通過Healthcare.gov獲得健康保險的過程與打電話和與人交談的過程相同。
保健醫療網站的過程與在市場上打電話和與人交談的過程完全相同。
市場的人一樣。有些人可能甚至不知道有電話選項的存在。
你通過電話交談的人很瞭解這個系統，而且...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nv4o2q/ysk_the_health_insurance_marketplace_has_staff/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nv4o2q/ysk_the_health_insurance_marketplace_has_staff/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 02:53:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: many people assume that the process of getting health insurance through healthcare.gov is identical to the process of calling and talking to someone at the marketplace. (Some people may not even know that a phone option exists.) But the people you talk to by phone know the system well and can ask you the right questions to ensure that you get as many deductions and credits as possible. It takes a little more time but it may be very worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I found out that because of some weird billing issue my health insurance was canceled. The health insurance company transferred me to the marketplace to dispute the problem; the woman I spoke with walked me through reapplication and showed me that as a grad student with a fairly low income I was actually due a monthly health insurance credit of more than $400. So instead of paying $112 a month I’m now paying $24 for a plan that’s actually worth about $500 a month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK你的洗碗機有一個過濾器。清潔它。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：你的洗碗機的過濾器需要定期清洗，以便它能夠
正常工作。如果你的洗碗機把舊的食物和其他垃圾留在你的
碗碟上，它可能需要清洗其過濾器。

我們一年前買了一套有洗碗機的房子，我不知道洗碗機有
甚至有...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nz65kc/ysk_that_your_dishwasher_has_a_filter_clean_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nz65kc/ysk_that_your_dishwasher_has_a_filter_clean_it/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 23:34:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Your dishwasher’s filter needs to be regularly cleaned so that it can work properly. If your dishwasher is leaving old food and other gunk on your dishes, it probably needs to have its filter cleaned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We bought a house with a dishwasher a year ago, and I had no idea dishwashers even had filters let alone ones that needed to be maintained in any way. I’m currently cleaning it for the first time, and it’s honestly worse than I expected. I sincerely hope this post is able to help some other poor, uninformed soul. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good luck!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在美國，當你在工作時，如果你覺得有迫在眉睫的死亡或受傷的威脅--你可以停止工作。]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.osha.gov/as/opa/worker/danger.html

爲什麼是YSK。

僱主們知道這一點，但很少有人會告訴員工這一點。工人在壓力下
冒着生命和傷害的危險，因爲年終審查的加薪、獎金和
需要完成的工作的時間表。我的建議是這樣的--打電話
和...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nyx4p2/ysk_in_the_us_while_you_are_working_if_you_feel/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nyx4p2/ysk_in_the_us_while_you_are_working_if_you_feel/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 15:29:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.osha.gov/as/opa/worker/danger.html&quot;&gt;https://www.osha.gov/as/opa/worker/danger.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Employers know this, but few will tell employees about it. Workers are pressured into risking life and injury because of year end review raises, bonuses, and timeline of work that needs to be completed. My recommendation is this - call and record the conversation with supervisor or the person in charge. If the person in charge starts debating your opinion, hang up and call OSHA and the Department of Labor. The reason for calling to Dept of labor is to insulate the employee from any retaliations from the employer. HR works for the employer, OSHA and the Dept of Labor works for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：運行iOS11及以上版本的iPhone（可能也包括其他品牌）有一個文件掃描工具，可以創建平面、乾淨的掃描件]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：掃描文件是許多人需要做的事情之一。
在某些時候，但往往缺乏這樣做的設備。如果你有一個iPhone，你
你可以進入筆記應用程序並創建一個筆記，點擊底部的相機圖標並選擇 "掃描文件"。
選擇 "掃描文件"。相機會自動...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nyb7vb/ysk_iphones_running_ios11_and_above_and_probably/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nyb7vb/ysk_iphones_running_ios11_and_above_and_probably/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 04:30:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Scanning documents is one of those things that many people need to do at some point but often lack the equipment to do so.  If you have an iPhone, you can go to the notes app and create a note, tap the camera icon at the bottom and select “scan documents.”  The camera will automatically detect a document, but you can also crop the scan to clean up the edges.  Voila!  You now have a flattened PDF that you can send via email, text, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK一個有執照的營養師到底能爲你做什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：我（F21）一生都與食物有着不健康的關係。
多年來，我一直想去看營養師，但我被一些恐懼所阻礙。
恐懼。我有一個先入爲主的觀念，認爲營養師只會對我的飲食習慣表示失望。
對我的飲食習慣表示失望，然後強迫我接受一種我不喜歡的飲食。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nyg06u/ysk_what_a_licensed_dietician_will_actually_do/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nyg06u/ysk_what_a_licensed_dietician_will_actually_do/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 01:13:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I (F21) have had an unhealthy relationship with food for my whole life. I had been wanting to see a dietician for years but I was held back by some fears. I had a preconceived notion that the dietician would simply express disappointment in my eating habits and then force me into a diet I wasn’t interested in. However, my experience has been the complete opposite. The dietician I see has been teaching me skills to improve my eating psychologically through things like intuitive eating skills, and not once has she ever made a comment that anything I eat is bad. In fact, she has actually been counseling me to heal a lot of my food insecurities and teaching me strategies to stop labeling the foods I enjoy as “good” or “bad,” which helps me to see food in a better light in general. I highly recommend this for anyone at all who struggles with their relationship with food, regardless of your weight, health, or anything else! There has been absolutely no dieting involved, and instead, a dietician’s job is to teach you how to understand your own body better. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NOTE: A licensed dietician is a very different (and more qualified/knowledgeable) thing than a nutritionist&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A source explaining what a licensed dietician can do, as well as the difference between dietitians and nutritionists, can be found here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/nutrition/dietitian-vs-nutritionist#dietitian&quot;&gt;https://www.healthline.com/nutrition/dietitian-vs-nutritionist#dietitian&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你現在可以看到誰在關注你了]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：一些隨機的人在跟蹤我，這總是讓我感到毛骨悚然。現在
你可以看到他們是誰，並屏蔽他們，這樣他們就可以取消對你的關注。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nx07jz/ysk_you_can_now_see_who_follows_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nx07jz/ysk_you_can_now_see_who_follows_you/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 23:35:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It always creeped me out that some random person was following me. Now you can see who they are and block them so they can unfollow you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK說，有一個叫remove.bg的網站，可以去除非透明圖像的背景，使其透明。]]></title><description><![CDATA[還有一個叫imgonline.com.ua的網站，可以把你圖片中的一種顏色變成另一種顏色。
變成另一種顏色。我一直在使用這兩個網站。(remove.bg
和imgonline.com.ua)

爲什麼是YSK：有很多非透明的圖像和圖像有
格子背景的圖像，使它們看起來...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nyaljl/ysk_that_there_is_a_website_called_removebg_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nyaljl/ysk_that_there_is_a_website_called_removebg_that/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 18:33:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is also a website called imgonline.com.ua that can turn a color in your image into another color. I use both of these websites all the time. (remove.bg and imgonline.com.ua)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: There are plenty of non-transparent images and images that have checkered backgrounds that make them look transparent and most people are looking for a tool to make these images transparent. There is a free one out there and I thought I&amp;#39;d share.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 如何檢查自己的脈搏]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：由於許多原因，這可以拯救生命，但我注意到另一件事
是這個 "Kardia "設備，它的市場定位是自制心電圖，只用兩根手指。
手指。他們宣稱可以檢測 "心動過緩、心動過速和心房顫動"。
顫動"，這聽起來很不錯。問題是，你的手指也可以....。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nxo4l7/ysk_how_to_check_your_own_pulse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nxo4l7/ysk_how_to_check_your_own_pulse/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 07:49:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This can be lifesaving for many reasons, but another thing I&amp;#39;ve noticed is this &amp;quot;Kardia&amp;quot; device that markets itself as a homemade ECG using just 2 fingers. They tout it can detect &amp;quot;bradycardia, tachycardia, and atrial fibrillation&amp;quot; which all sounds great. Thing is, so can your finger. Bradycardia is a slow heartrate, tachycardia is fast, atrial fibrillation can be felt as irregular beats (the spacing in between beats is variable and no two are the same). So to save yourself some money and to teach a potentially life saving skill, here&amp;#39;s how you do it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take your index and middle fingers (never use your thumb) and place them gently on either your radial artery, which you can find by starting at the palm side of your index finger, and tracing down in a straight line to your wrist just below your hand, or the carotid artery which is found on either side of your windpipe. You don&amp;#39;t have to press hard, just gently enough to feel the pulse. Use a clock or watch or your phone as a timer, and count for 15 seconds. Multiply whatever you get by 4 and that&amp;#39;s your heartrate. Pay attention to the rhythm as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If it&amp;#39;s within the 60-100 mark, that&amp;#39;s considered normal. Granted if you&amp;#39;re sitting on the couch and it&amp;#39;s 88 you may want to consider investigating. If it&amp;#39;s under 60 it&amp;#39;s considered bradycardia, over 100 is tachycardia. Take all this in context though, an athlete&amp;#39;s heartrate is naturally lower than a normal person&amp;#39;s, and if you just brought in groceries it&amp;#39;ll be higher than resting. I hope this helps when you just want to do a quick heart checkup!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/health/how-to-check-heart-rate&quot;&gt;https://www.healthline.com/health/how-to-check-heart-rate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：血型AB-ve是普遍的血漿捐贈者。]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，在生物課上，你可能會被告知O型血是普遍的捐贈者，AB型血是普遍的接受者。
O型血是普遍的捐贈者，AB型血是普遍的接受者。

這實際上主要是針對紅血球（RBCs）而言。我不會用細節來煩擾你。
但基本上O型血的紅細胞是無反應的，而AB型血是無反應的。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nx8xr9/ysk_blood_group_ab_ve_is_the_universal_plasma/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nx8xr9/ysk_blood_group_ab_ve_is_the_universal_plasma/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 04:42:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So in biology classes you might be taught about Blood group O being the universal donor and Blood Group AB being the universal recipient. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is actually mainly for Red Blood Cells (RBCs). I wont bore you with the details but basically Blood Group O&amp;#39;s RBCs are non reactive, vs AB being very reactive. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However AB is the universal donor of PLASMA(its plasma is less reactive). Plasma is the fluid that makes up most of your blood. AB&amp;#39;s (Especially AB negative) plasma is quite underactive and is used in making many blood products like FFP which can be used in bleeding disorder emergencies. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didnt know this until reaching medical school, and never donated being an AB. But now I donate quite often after learning of this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK : So that you still choose to donate even if you are AB&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source:
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.redcrossblood.org/donate-blood/dlp/plasma-information.html&quot;&gt;https://www.redcrossblood.org/donate-blood/dlp/plasma-information.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：即使你已經結婚，談論生育控制也很重要]]></title><description><![CDATA[YSK認爲，討論你們在性生活中是否使用避孕措施始終是很重要的。
即使你們已經結婚了。

爲什麼是YSK：我和太多的人交談過，他們說："我們沒有討論過要孩子，但是我懷孕了。
我們沒有討論過要孩子，但我卻懷孕了"。這不需要發生
這種方式。談論...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nxt5ot/ysk_talking_about_birth_control_is_important_even/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nxt5ot/ysk_talking_about_birth_control_is_important_even/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 02:04:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;YSK that it is always important to discuss whether or not you will use birth control during sex, even when you&amp;#39;re married.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I have talked to far too many people who have said things like &amp;quot;We didn&amp;#39;t talk about having kids, but I got pregnant.&amp;quot; It doesn&amp;#39;t need to happen this way. Talk about if/when you want kids before abandoning birth control. There are so many great options aside from condoms, such as IUDs and Nexplanon. You can even use the calendar method if you&amp;#39;re hesitant to use actual birth control and/or your religion prevents it. You have the power to prevent pregnancy before you are ready. Take advantage of it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：新的研究表明，臨睡前聽音樂會擾亂睡眠]]></title><description><![CDATA[背景：文章
[https://medlifestyle.news/2021/06/10/listening-to-music-near-bedtime-can-disrupt-sleep-new-research-says/]

爲什麼是YSK：該研究的作者指出，"幾乎所有人都認爲音樂可以改善
他們的睡眠，但我們發現那些聽了更多音樂的人睡得更差。" 其中
最有趣的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nx392u/ysk_listening_to_music_near_bedtime_can_disrupt/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nx392u/ysk_listening_to_music_near_bedtime_can_disrupt/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 13:14:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;context: &lt;a href=&quot;https://medlifestyle.news/2021/06/10/listening-to-music-near-bedtime-can-disrupt-sleep-new-research-says/&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: The study&amp;#39;s author states, &amp;quot;Almost everyone thought music improves their sleep, but we found those who listened to more music slept worse.&amp;quot; The most interesting thing about this study to me is that it found that instrumental music was more likely than lyrical music to disturb sleep quality. People who listened to more music before bed experienced more earworms and had lower sleep quality, according to the study. The study&amp;#39;s findings contradict the common thought that music can be utilized as an aid to help people sleep. One of the things the study&amp;#39;s author says is that the studies used to justify using music as a sleep aid were all self-reported surveys, while his research employed many more resources including gathering empirical data using polysomnography.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：有一個專門針對動物的毒物控制機構]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：有許多植物、食物和化學品對人類來說是可以的，但是
可以毒害貓、狗、馬等。

它由ASPCA管理，可以在這裏找到。
https://www.aspca.org/pet-care/animal-poison-control

此外，他們還有一個很好的工具，可以查找有毒和無毒的植物，這...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nwpo9a/ysk_there_is_a_poison_control_specifically_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nwpo9a/ysk_there_is_a_poison_control_specifically_for/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 03:57:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: there are many plants, foods, and chemicals that are ok for humans but can poison cats, dogs, horses, etc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is managed by the ASPCA and can be found here.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aspca.org/pet-care/animal-poison-control&quot;&gt;https://www.aspca.org/pet-care/animal-poison-control&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also they have a great tool for looking up toxic and non toxic plants which can be found here.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aspca.org/pet-care/animal-poison-control/toxic-and-non-toxic-plants&quot;&gt;https://www.aspca.org/pet-care/animal-poison-control/toxic-and-non-toxic-plants&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：據預測，今年夏天比去年更有利於野火的發生。請準備好一個計劃。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK。

去年，美國在7月至9月期間發生了歷史上最嚴重的4場火災。
由於難以置信的乾燥條件，7月至9月，美國出現了歷史上最嚴重的4場火災。

今年，情況更加糟糕，所以我們可以預計在加州和科羅拉多州將發生大規模火災事件
和科羅拉多州。

請花點時間想想你將做什麼，並準備好迎接...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nx1k2f/ysk_this_summer_is_predicted_to_be_even_more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nx1k2f/ysk_this_summer_is_predicted_to_be_even_more/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 02:24:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year, the United States saw its top 4 worst fires in history during July-September due to incredibly dry conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This year, it&amp;#39;s even worse, so we can expect a large fire event in California and Colorado.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please, take a moment to think about what you will do and prep for an escape if needed, and be prepared!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you saw what happened last summer and live in a fire-prone area, this post may be incredibly important to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Top Tips&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clear leaves and other debris from gutters, eaves, porches and decks. This prevents embers from igniting your home. Remove dead vegetation and other items from under your deck or porch, and within 10 feet of the house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Screen or box-in areas below patios and decks with wire mesh to prevent debris and combustible materials from accumulating. Remove flammable materials (firewood stacks, propane tanks) within 30 feet of your home’s foundation and outbuildings, including garages and sheds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If it can catch fire, don’t let it touch your house, deck or porch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wildfire can spread to tree tops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prune trees so the lowest branches are 6 to 10 feet from the ground. Keep your lawn hydrated and maintained. If it is brown, cut it down to reduce fire intensity. Dry grass and shrubs are fuel for wildfire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t let debris and lawn cuttings linger. Dispose of these items quickly to reduce fuel for fire. Inspect shingles or roof tiles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Replace or repair those that are loose or missing to prevent ember penetration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cover exterior attic vents with metal wire mesh no larger than 1/8 inch to prevent sparks from entering the home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enclose under-eave and soffit vents or screens with metal mesh to prevent ember entry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Creating an emergency plan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Assemble an emergency supply kit and place it in a safe spot. Remember to include important documents, medications and personal identification.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Develop an emergency evacuation plan and practice it with everyone in your home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plan two ways out of your neighborhood and designate a meeting place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In your community:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contact your local planning/zoning office to find out if your home is in a high wildfire risk area, and if there are specific local or county ordinances you should be following.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are part of a homeowner association, work with them to identify regulations that incorporate proven preparedness landscaping, home design and building material use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Talk to your local fire department about how to prepare, when to evacuate, and the response you and your neighbors can expect in the event of a wildfire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn about wildfire risk reduction efforts, including how land management agencies use prescribed fire to manage local landscapes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn how you can make a positive difference in your community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：情緒是本能的，是基於我們以前的經驗。通過對它們的反應，我們強化了我們的過去；然而通過對情況的反應，我們控制了我們的未來。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：情緒是對我們周圍一切事物的本能反應，根植於我們過去的經驗，甚至是幼年時的經驗。
在我們過去的經驗中，甚至在幼年時期。它們沒有真假之分。
而是簡單的存在。

當我們遇到一種情緒並對其作出反應時，我們就會強化過去的程序。
的程序。然而，通過學習...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nwxj4t/ysk_emotions_are_in_instinctive_and_based_on_our/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nwxj4t/ysk_emotions_are_in_instinctive_and_based_on_our/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 01:14:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  Emotions are instinct responses to everything around us and are rooted in our past experiences, even from early childhood. They are not true or false, but simply are.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we encounter an emotion and react to it, we reinforce the prior programming from the past. However, by learning to acknowledge why we feel this way about a given thing, we can take a moment to choose how we want to respond to the situation, not the emotion, thus taking control of our future. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A tip is to allow yourself to experience the emotion and how you feel physiologically during it. This will help you to stay level headed, acknowledge it, and not react.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：有一個新的電話詐騙案正在進行中]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：爲了保護自己不受詐騙

你應該知道，現在有一種新的電話騙局在四處流傳，以
僞裝成。"學生貸款救濟計劃"。

他們打電話的號碼是 (318) 731-6799，並在語音郵件腳本中說
說給他們回電話的號碼。(844) 877...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nw2svs/ysk_there_is_a_new_phone_scam_going_around/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nw2svs/ysk_there_is_a_new_phone_scam_going_around/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 19:30:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: to protect yourself from getting scammed&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should know that there is a new phone call scam going around under the disguise of: &amp;quot;student loan relief program&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They called from the number: (318) 731-6799, and in the voice mail script they said to call them back at the number: (844) 877-0123&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They scammers will dictate that they have good news for you and that they have selected and prequalified you for a new program of theirs, refer to the 1st paragraph.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They missed their mark with my friend cause she did not attend college.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：Plan B緊急避孕藥對體重超過155磅或體重指數超過30的人無效。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：有時人們依靠緊急避孕藥如B計劃來防止意外懷孕。
但如果你的體重超過155磅（約70公斤），或者體重指數超過30，那麼就需要使用Plan B來防止意外懷孕。
超過30，那麼Plan B可能不起作用，可能無法有效地防止懷孕。
"ella "品牌的EC對體重不超過195磅（約88公斤）的人有效。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nwn3ti/ysk_plan_b_emergency_contraception_is_not/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nwn3ti/ysk_plan_b_emergency_contraception_is_not/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 14:47:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: sometimes people rely on emergency contraception like Plan B to prevent unwanted pregnancy, but if you weigh over 155lbs (~70 kilograms) or have a BMI over 30 then Plan B might not work and may not effectively prevent pregnancy. &amp;quot;ella&amp;quot; brand EC is effective for those up to 195 lbs (~88 kilograms). If you are over 195 lbs then the traditional &amp;quot;morning after pill&amp;quot; type of emergency contraceptive cannot be relied on, and another method such as copper IUD should be considered. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/health/healthy-sex/plan-b-weight-limit&quot;&gt;more info&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As abortion access becomes more and more restricted in certain areas, it is especially important for people to be aware of ways to prevent an unwanted pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：96年前（或更早）出版的書籍或文字作品是公共領域，任何人都可以免費閱讀。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：在美國，隨着許多學生準備進行暑期閱讀，許多公司將試圖利用這些閱讀清單。
將試圖利用這些閱讀清單。如果你是一個學生的家長
如果你是學生的家長，或者你自己也是學生，請確保你不要購買分配給你的書面作品。
如果它是公共領域的，請確保你不要購買分配給你的書面作品。任何東西...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nvwvad/ysk_books_or_written_works_published_96_years_ago/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nvwvad/ysk_books_or_written_works_published_96_years_ago/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 09:59:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: As many students prepare for summer reading in the US, many companies will be trying to take advantage of these reading lists. If you&amp;#39;re a parent of a student, or a student yourself, make sure you don&amp;#39;t purchase a written work that&amp;#39;s been assigned to you if it&amp;#39;s public domain. Anything written pre-1926 (as of 2021) is available FOR FREE and does not need to be bought at a store. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are also some other isolated titles that are public domain based on either the death of the author or not registering for copyright in the proper manner, so always Google before purchasing to see if it is available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of the more popular written works that are public domain:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Great Gatsby&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Little Women&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Count of Monte Cristo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Sun Also Rises&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great Expectations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Awakening&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jane Eyre&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The House of Mirth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pride and Prejudice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Scarlet Letter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wuthering Heights&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Tale of Two Cities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sons and Lovers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crime and Punishment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frankenstein&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Turn of the Screw&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alice&amp;#39;s Adventures in Wonderland&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Picture of Dorian Gray&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dracula&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Time Machine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Adventures of Tom Sawyer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Treasure Island&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Strange Case of Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robinson Crusoe&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anne of Green Gables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Three Musketeers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;War and Peace&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Emma&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Les Miserables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Peter Pan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The War of the Worlds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Invisible Man&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Importance of Being Earnest&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Around the World in Eighty Days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sherlock Holmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are literally thousands more titles to add to this list, but here&amp;#39;s to hoping this saves someone some money this summer on books.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：露點是一個更好的測量方法，它比相對溼度更能反映出外面的潮溼 "感覺"。露點<55令人愉快，55-60是明顯的。65以上是令人不快的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：露點是空氣需要被冷卻到的溫度（在
恆壓），以達到100%的相對溼度（RH）。在這個
空氣不能以氣體形式容納更多的水。如果空氣被冷卻到
如果空氣被進一步冷卻，水蒸氣將不得不從空氣中出來。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nw2brj/ysk_dew_point_is_a_much_better_measurement_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nw2brj/ysk_dew_point_is_a_much_better_measurement_for/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 01:20:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: The dew point is the temperature the air needs to be cooled to (at constant pressure) in order to achieve a relative humidity (RH) of 100%. At this point the air cannot hold more water in the gas form. If the air were to be cooled even more, water vapor would have to come out of the atmosphere in the liquid form, usually as fog or precipitation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The higher the dew point rises, the greater the amount of moisture in the air. This directly affects how &amp;quot;comfortable&amp;quot; it will feel outside. Many times, relative humidity can be misleading. For example, a temperature of 30 and a dew point of 30 will give you a relative humidity of 100%, but a temperature of 80 and a dew point of 60 produces a relative humidity of 50%. It would feel much more &amp;quot;humid&amp;quot; on the 80 degree day with 50% relative humidity than on the 30 degree day with a 100% relative humidity. This is because of the higher dew point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you want a real judge of just how &amp;quot;dry&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;humid&amp;quot; it will feel outside, look at the dew point instead of the RH. The higher the dew point, the muggier it will feel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General comfort levels USING DEW POINT that can be expected during the summer months:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;less than or equal to 55: dry and comfortable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;between 55 and 65: becoming &amp;quot;sticky&amp;quot; with muggy evenings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;greater than or equal to 65: lots of moisture in the air, becoming oppressive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weather.gov/arx/why_dewpoint_vs_humidity&quot;&gt;https://www.weather.gov/arx/why_dewpoint_vs_humidity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：永遠不要給狗喫玉米棒子]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼ysk：狗不能消化鵝卵石，有很高的內部堵塞風險。
幾乎總是需要手術或內窺鏡檢查。

(它也是磨蝕性的，會引起問題)]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nunvs2/ysk_never_give_dogs_corn_on_the_cob/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nunvs2/ysk_never_give_dogs_corn_on_the_cob/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 16:47:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why ysk: dogs can’t digest the cob and have a high risk of internal blockages. Surgery or endoscopy is almost always needed. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(It’s also abrasive and can cause issues)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 你讓開車的人 "等一下 "並不意味着他們沒有在聽。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：作爲一家受歡迎的連鎖餐廳的經理，我無法計算有多少次人們告訴我們他們還沒有準備好，然後就開始喫非常多的東西。
人們告訴我們他們還沒有準備好點菜，然後就開始進行非常私人的談話。
私下交談。

有些事情要知道。

一旦你啓動了耳機，我們就不能把它關掉。

耳機內部有揚聲器。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nvuevh/ysk_just_because_you_told_the_person_at_the_drive/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nvuevh/ysk_just_because_you_told_the_person_at_the_drive/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 15:28:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK:
As a manager of a popular restaurant chain I cannot count the number of times people tell us they&amp;#39;re not ready to order and then proceed to have VERY private conversations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some things to know:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We cannot turn the headset off once you&amp;#39;ve activated it&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are either speakers inside the building or at least 4 people wearing headsets at all times, so literally everyone hears what you&amp;#39;re saying&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The headsets (unless you&amp;#39;re at an older place) are very sensitive, so that phone call? Yes we heard it too, also, side note, please quit screaming into them, a normal voice is fine&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We absolutely discuss everything you say, and remember the truly awkward ones, we even have names for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In summation, be ready to order, dont scream, dont have conversations you dont want overheard, and repeated (often in a funny voice) and dont be rude&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have a great day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For fun, my favorite so far is the guy we call Don Juan because he calls both his wife and girlfriend while sitting at the speaker and gets us to bag it seperately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，美國的呼叫中心僱用盲人和身體殘疾者--這些工作並不總是被外包給其他國家。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：人們對呼叫中心持批評態度，因此對呼叫中心的員工可能很無禮。
中心的員工。

編輯：呼叫中心不是銷售人員--他們不給你打電話--他們回答
他們爲各種企業接聽電話，回答客戶的問題和投訴。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nvmfwu/ysk_that_us_call_centers_hire_the_blind_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nvmfwu/ysk_that_us_call_centers_hire_the_blind_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 05:52:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: People are critical of call centers and therefore can be rude to call center employees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Call centers are not sales people - they do not call you - they answer calls for various businesses to respond to customer questions and complaints.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK - 投入資金升級你的房屋並不能直接轉化爲增加價值]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼是YSK：人們常常認爲，如果他們以15萬美元的價格買下自己的房子，並投入10萬美元進行升級。
10萬美元進行升級，他們的房子就會被估價爲25萬美元。你的房子的價值是
你的房子的價值是根據 "銷售比較法 "來評估的。
在你所在的地區，與你的房屋結構相似的房屋銷售情況（#...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nvaitm/ysk_putting_money_into_upgrading_your_home_does/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nvaitm/ysk_putting_money_into_upgrading_your_home_does/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 01:24:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: People often think that if they bought their house for $150K and put $100K into upgrades, their home will appraise for $250K. Your home’s value is appraised based on the “Sales comparison approach”, which takes recent home sales in your area of homes with similar construction to yours (# bedrooms, bathrooms, Sq. Ft....etc) and bases the value on this. Don’t dump your savings and think you can get it back with a cash out refinance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，如果你使用iCloud Drive，在文件或文件夾名稱的末尾添加".nosync "將導致它不被傳輸。]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲什麼選擇YSK：這很重要，因爲你的文檔文件夾與iCloud驅動器同步，但你有某些東西不想放在雲端（稅）。
但你有某些東西不希望放在雲端（報稅單、護照照片等）。
稅單、護照照片等）。)]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ns9wcp/ysk_that_if_you_use_icloud_drive_adding_nosync_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ns9wcp/ysk_that_if_you_use_icloud_drive_adding_nosync_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 07:57:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This is important in case your Documents folder is synced up with iCloud drive, but you have certain things that you don&amp;#39;t want in the cloud (tax returns, passport photos, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：UPS將你的個人信息，如你買的東西和你住的地方，出售給第三方。你可以選擇退出。]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.ups.com/us/en/help-center/legal-terms-conditions/privacy-notice.page?WT.svl=Footer&WT.mc_id=VAN701624#contentBlock-14

"我們可能會與我們的UPS商業夥伴和其他第三方分享物理位置數據，例如，加強定位。
夥伴和其他第三方共享物理位置數據，例如，加強基於位置的服務和開發
準確的和最新的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/num29z/ysk_ups_sells_your_personal_information_such_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/num29z/ysk_ups_sells_your_personal_information_such_as/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 23:16:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ups.com/us/en/help-center/legal-terms-conditions/privacy-notice.page?WT.svl=Footer&amp;amp;WT.mc_id=VAN701624#contentBlock-14&quot;&gt;https://www.ups.com/us/en/help-center/legal-terms-conditions/privacy-notice.page?WT.svl=Footer&amp;amp;WT.mc_id=VAN701624#contentBlock-14&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;We may share physical location data with our UPS Business Partners and other third parties to, for example, enhance location-based services and develop accurate and up-to-date maps. In addition, except as described below, unless you object, we may share other personal information with third parties who are not UPS Business Partners for those parties&amp;#39; own purposes, such as to offer products or services that may interest you.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then this nugget - &amp;quot;Information collected through third-party apps, tools, widgets and plug-ins (such as information obtained through third-party login services or relating to your use of a Face-book &amp;quot;Like&amp;quot; button) is collected directly by the providers of these features.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Because you can opt out by going here - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ups.com/ppwa/doWork?loc=en_US&quot;&gt;https://www.ups.com/ppwa/doWork?loc=en_US&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 不是要停止交通流，讓人拉出來。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果交通正在運行，你不應該完全停下來讓別人離開
駛出停車場。補充一點，不要堵住車箱。

爲什麼是YSK-

這是一個等待發生的事故。別管他們是否在左轉，另一邊是迎面而來的車輛。
來的車輛可能不會停下來，可能會導致多車相撞......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nukb9i/ysk_not_to_stop_the_flow_of_traffic_to_let/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nukb9i/ysk_not_to_stop_the_flow_of_traffic_to_let/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 20:33:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If traffic is moving you should not come to a complete stop to let someone out of a parking lot. To add to this, don’t block the box.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s an accident waiting to happen. Never mind if they’re turning left the other side of oncoming traffic may not stop and could result in a multi car crash. Just keep moving, when the road is clear they can pull out. It’s common sense not to block the box but it seems I’m seeing more and more impatient drivers everyday. You will cause a road block, and inevitably cause traffic, which just backs everything up. Please be patient and keep traffic moving.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>