<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 04:35:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK表示，母亲节（美国）是下周日，5月9日。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：如果你要邮寄东西，你需要尽快发送。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n1tqzn/ysk_that_mothers_day_us_is_next_sunday_may_9/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n1tqzn/ysk_that_mothers_day_us_is_next_sunday_may_9/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 18:00:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: if you’re going to mail something, you need to send it soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 如果你用现金支付东西，有人问你："你给了我一张X美元的钞票吗？"，这是为了挽救工作人员的工作。只要说是或不是。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：（注：我来自美国）当你把钱交给任何机构的工作人员时，他们应该要求你确认你给他们多少钱。
的时候，他们应该要求你确认你给了他们多少钱。他们最不需要的是给你6美元的零钱。
他们最不需要的就是给你6美元的零钱，因为你给了他们一张10美元的钞票。
而让你对他们大喊大叫，因为你认为你给了他们......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n1oq16/ysk_if_you_pay_for_something_in_cash_and_youre/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n1oq16/ysk_if_you_pay_for_something_in_cash_and_youre/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 09:52:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: (Note: I&amp;#39;m from the US) When you hand money to a staff member at any establishment, they should be asking you to verify how much you gave them. The last thing they need is to give you $6 in change because you gave them a $10 bill, and have you yell at them because you thought you handed them a $20 bill (and should therefore get $16 in change).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apparently at my job (I&amp;#39;m a pharmacy tech), someone in the drive-thru left a terrible review because he gave me a $10 bill to pay for a $4 medication, and I had the audacity to ask him &amp;quot;you sent me a $10 bill, correct?&amp;quot; He said it was &amp;quot;bizarre and unnecessary&amp;quot;. He gave us a 1/10 JUST for that. Don&amp;#39;t be that guy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best thing is to tell them exactly what you&amp;#39;re giving them right from the get-go. &amp;quot;Here&amp;#39;s a $20&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;ve got a dollar and 15 cents here&amp;quot; removes any doubts about what money has been exchanged, and prevents issues about money and change down the line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Someone made a good point that if you&amp;#39;re an employee, you can just state the amount of money the customer gave you, no need to ask them to verify the amount. Saying &amp;quot;out of a $20&amp;quot; is fine, and then the customer can correct you if it&amp;#39;s wrong. I do that when it&amp;#39;s a face-to-face transaction, but in this scenario, the patient was in the far drive-thru lane so I had to make sure he heard me correctly, hence why I needed to phrase it as a question&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，"etc "是 "et cetera "的简称，并且是这样发音的，而不是 "ek cetera"]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：这是一个很小但非常普遍的错误发音。
我听到电视主持人、演讲者、歌手和其他许多人这样发音。
很多时候，这种区别几乎听不出来，在非正式的讲话中，这并不重要。
么重要。但是，如果发表正式的演讲或什么...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n16and/ysk_that_etc_is_short_for_et_cetera_and_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n16and/ysk_that_etc_is_short_for_et_cetera_and_is/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 07:46:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This is a small but extremely common mispronunciation, I’ve heard it pronounced this way by television presenters, lecturers, singers, and many more. Oftentimes the distinction is barely audible, and in informal speech it wouldn’t matter. BUT if delivering a formal speech or something similar, it’s definitely worth knowing this so your pronunciation is impeccable, and so any listeners who are aware of this aren’t distracted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 你可以检查特定的密码是否在数据泄露中被暴露出来]]></title><description><![CDATA[每天都有新的数据泄露事件发生，要确保你走在它的前面很容易。
领先于它。这个网站：https://breachdirectory.tk
[https://breachdirectory.tk/]使用人工智能来监测和解析新的数据泄露事件
自动。只要输入你的电子邮件或用户名，它就会告诉你哪些...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0pr2o/ysk_that_you_can_check_whether_specific_passwords/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0pr2o/ysk_that_you_can_check_whether_specific_passwords/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 03:35:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are new data breaches occurring everyday and it&amp;#39;s pretty easy to make sure you stay ahead of it. This site: &lt;a href=&quot;https://breachdirectory.tk/&quot;&gt;https://breachdirectory.tk&lt;/a&gt; uses AI to monitor and parse new data breaches automatically. Just enter your email or username and it will tell you which of your passwords have been leaked and from where. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK? It&amp;#39;s important to make sure you are using passwords that have not been leaked before to protect yourself from account hijacking and credential stuffing attacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果一个女人在商店里紧紧地跟着你，这意味着陪伴她们的人很可能在跟踪她们。而且他们正在伸手寻求帮助。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：我在互联网上一次又一次地看到它。通常是一个女人
走到他们不认识的人面前，身后跟着一个男人。如果
如果不是我的女朋友注意到，我可能不会注意到今天发生在我身上的事情。
今天发生在我身上。我在市场上买了一杯红牛，然后有一个人跟着我。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n1hnyq/ysk_if_a_woman_is_following_you_closely_in_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n1hnyq/ysk_if_a_woman_is_following_you_closely_in_a/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 03:00:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I&amp;#39;ve seen it time and time again on the internet. Usually with a woman walking up to someone they don&amp;#39;t know, with a guy following behind her. If it weren&amp;#39;t for my girlfriend noticing I likely wouldn&amp;#39;t of noticed when it happened to me today. I was getting a Red Bull at the market, and a young girl came very close to me with who I thought was her boyfriend. I don&amp;#39;t pay much attention, and move out of their way because I figured they wanted to get to the drinks in front of me. I then walk 10 feet over to a cooler to get some salami motz rolls. And again, the girl is right by my side. It still didn&amp;#39;t click with me until my girlfriend whispered in my ear that this guy is stalking her. Apparently my girlfriend overheard him ask her how old she is, and she said &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m in High school&amp;quot; and him saying &amp;quot;Let&amp;#39;s get a coffee&amp;quot;. So I stood right there and didn&amp;#39;t say a word to either of them, until the guy ran off to the other side of the store. I watched the guy from there on, and made sure the girl wasn&amp;#39;t being followed by him afterwards and all was well. I will always notice the signs from here on out, and I hope you all will take notice too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK有一个叫 "Torch "的浏览器，它有一个内置的视频下载器，适用于网络上99%的视频。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：标题 +它是基于chrome构建的，速度相当快。我在网上没有找到很多关于它的信息
我在网上找不到很多关于它的信息，但人们似乎一致认为火炬是安全的，但可能会记录你的数据。
记录你的数据。

我只是想给他们一个机会，因为现在下载任何类型的视频
是一个巨大的痛苦的屁股。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n16xs7/ysk_theres_a_browser_called_torch_that_has_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n16xs7/ysk_theres_a_browser_called_torch_that_has_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 22:37:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Title +Its built off chrome and is pretty fast. I couldn&amp;#39;t find much on the web about it but the consensus seems to be that torch is safe, but probably records your data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;just trying to throw them a bone because downloading any sort of videos nowadays is a huge pain in the ass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你正在照顾一个患有慢性病或残疾的亲人，有一些项目可以支付你成为非熟练的护理人员的费用。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：你不应该在谋生和照顾你的亲人之间做出选择。
你所爱的人。你不需要证书或任何类型的认证就可以
成为一个不熟练的护理人员。

我的祖母在一月被诊断出患有肺癌，而我祖父的痴呆症
已经变得非常糟糕。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n13iok/ysk_if_you_are_taking_care_of_a_loved_one_who_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n13iok/ysk_if_you_are_taking_care_of_a_loved_one_who_is/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:25:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: you shouldn&amp;#39;t have to choose between making a living and taking care of your loved one. You don&amp;#39;t need credentials or any type of certification to become an unskilled caregiver.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My grandma was diagnosed with lung cancer in January, and my grandpa&amp;#39;s dementia has gotten so much worse as a result. Its come to the point where they need someone there to help out and take care of them just about 24/7. I quit my job in February so I can take care of them full time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naturally, I was worried about how I was gonna make my bills every month. I refuse to choose one or the other and I made that decision as soon as I committed to taking care of them. They went above and beyond as far as helping raise me when I was a kid. My mother struggled with drug addiction for most of her life and they took me on to raise when I was about 8 without any hesitation, even though they were both past 65 at that point. They provided me with the opportunity to be stable enough to go on and graduate high school. So honestly I feel honored to have this opportunity even if the situation is shitty. Its the least I can do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you find yourself in a similar situation, just know that there are programs that will enable you to take care of your loved ones when they need you most without the possibility of becoming homeless in the process. Im sure the programs vary from state to state, Im in Texas and the program is through Medicaid. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone should know about this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你收到来自尼尔森家族的包裹，这不是垃圾邮件。很多时候，信封里有2-5美元的现金。你可以通过寄来你所看的电视节目的记录来赚取更多的钱。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我以前被选中过，赚了一点现金。为什么是YSK？你是在
扔掉了钱!]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0rr8m/ysk_if_you_receive_a_packet_from_the_nielsen/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0rr8m/ysk_if_you_receive_a_packet_from_the_nielsen/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 06:59:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been selected before and earned a small bit of cash. Why YSK? You’re throwing away money!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，在购买文胸时，它应该适合你的最后一个钩子（给你最大的带子）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：当购买一个新的文胸时，它应该适合最后一个钩子，因为带子上的弹性会随着时间的推移而自然伸展。
因为带子中的弹性会随着时间的推移而自然伸展。你应该逐渐
逐渐将钩子移到第一个钩子上，这样你的胸罩就会继续适合你。
这样你的胸罩就能在更长的时间内继续适合你。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzavvd/ysk_that_when_buying_a_bra_it_should_fit_you_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzavvd/ysk_that_when_buying_a_bra_it_should_fit_you_on/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 04:47:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: When purchasing a new bra, it should fit on the last hook because the elastic in the band will naturally stretch over time. You should be gradually moving the hook in towards the first one as this occurs so that your bra will continue to fit you correctly for a longer span of time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你在邮箱的后面随意看到一张干纸，你的邮递员把它放在那里是有原因的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：它可以使你的承运人免于被刺伤

我是信使。

我们快到5月了，这意味着天气好，在外面闲逛。
学校在夏季关闭，以及那些可恶的魔鬼的回归。
黄家驹和黄蜂。

我相信你已经注意到了。但是，为了防止你...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0qs06/ysk_if_you_randomly_see_a_dryer_sheet_in_the_back/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0qs06/ysk_if_you_randomly_see_a_dryer_sheet_in_the_back/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 01:18:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: it could save your carrier from being stung&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Letter Carrier here. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re almost to the month of May which means nice weather, hanging out outside, school closing for the summer, and the return of those dastardly devils: Yellowjackets and Wasps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m sure you’ve noticed. But just in case you haven’t, this time of the year wasps and Yellowjackets (especially Yellowjackets) like to make nests inside of mailboxes. In a lot of places this time of the year, it’s just beginning to warm up outside, but it’s still fairly cold at night. So mailboxes provide nice, easy shelter for them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t tell you how many times, especially during this part of the year, where I’ve opened up a box to see a little nest with 3-5 Yellowjackets just chillin. If I’m really unlucky, they will have made their nest at the very back of the box so I wind up sticking my hand in not knowing they are there. We all know how temperamental these little douchebags are and merely existing in their presence is enough to piss them off. Last year alone I was stung 10 times on 10 separate occasions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getting to my point. We’ve found that they hate scented dryer sheets. If we encounter a box that is a problem for nests, we’ll often put one in there and it does the trick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So please, if you one day randomly see a dryer sheet at the back of your mailbox, just know that your carrier more than likely put it there to deter these Satanic creatures from building their home in it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK "每天 "与 "每天 "的区别]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK："每天 "意味着每24小时左右重复一次，"每天 "意味着
平凡、无聊或老套。这两个词之间的空格实际上改变了
使用正确的版本可以使你的意图更加明确
并使人们不再认为你是个白痴。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0mxr2/ysk_every_day_vs_everyday/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0mxr2/ysk_every_day_vs_everyday/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 23:50:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: &amp;quot;every day&amp;quot; means recurring every 24 hours or so and &amp;quot;everyday&amp;quot; means mundane, boring or trite. That space between the words actually changes the meaning of your sentence and using the correct version makes your intent clearer and stops people from thinking you&amp;#39;re an idiot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 在美国大多数州，法律上并不要求你在步行时进行酒精检测。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：警察可以以公共场所醉酒的罪名逮捕你，如果，也只有当。
你同意接受呼气式酒精测试，但你没有通过测试。通常情况下，警察会
通常情况下，警察会开始告诉你如何接受
通常情况下，警官会开始告诉你如何进行呼吸式酒精检测，而不会征求你的同意。如果你善意地拒绝...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0e58r/ysk_you_are_not_legally_required_to_take_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0e58r/ysk_you_are_not_legally_required_to_take_a/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 21:47:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Police officers can arrest you for public intoxication if, and only if, you consent to taking a breathalyzer test and you fail the test. Typically, the officer will just start telling you instructions about how to take the breathalyzer without ever asking for consent. If you kindly decline the test, there is little they can do, assuming you have not broken any laws.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：一辆新车会迅速贬值。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么YSK：你可能要为基本相同的汽车多付很多钱。

一辆新车和一辆使用了1或2年的二手车之间的价格差异很大。
是非常大的。因为当你买了一辆车，它就会失去价值，因为它不再是新的。
不再是新的，其次，大约在一年后，当下一个模型......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mw9wec/ysk_a_new_car_will_depreciate_in_value_rapidly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mw9wec/ysk_a_new_car_will_depreciate_in_value_rapidly/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 18:35:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;why YSK: you could be paying lots of extra money for essentially the same car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The price difference between a new car and one that is used and 1 or 2 years old is very big. Why? because when you buy a car it loses value because it&amp;#39;s no longer new, secondly just about after year when the next model releases it&amp;#39;s now  not a new car anymore and never will be. Suddenly your car has depreciated by a huge chunk it&amp;#39;s worth a LOT LESS. But by buying a used car you can skip those problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So just buy your dream car but buy one that is 1 or 2 years(or more) old.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，向食品救济站捐钱是比捐赠食物更有效的捐赠方式。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：如果你想最大限度地发挥你能为你的同胞带来的积极影响
如果你想为你的同胞带来最大的积极影响，那么捐赠现金而不是物品（尤其是食物）会更有效。
更为有效。

例如，以下是向食品店捐赠金钱而不是食物的六个理由
储藏室的六个理由。

 1. 1.金钱的储存成本比食物的储存成本低得多。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0i1cy/ysk_that_giving_money_to_food_pantries_is_a_more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0i1cy/ysk_that_giving_money_to_food_pantries_is_a_more/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 17:54:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  If you want to maximize the positive impact you can make for your fellow beings, then giving cash instead of goods (especially food,) can be much more effective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, here are six reasons for giving money instead of food to food pantries:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Money is much cheaper to store than food: less space; doesn&amp;#39;t need refrigeration; doesn&amp;#39;t require manual labor to manage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Even canned goods eventually expire. Cash doesn&amp;#39;t.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The types of food you give may not be what is needed by the recipient families. Everybody donates cans of beans. However, did you know that baby formula is one of the most needed foods? People tend to give what&amp;#39;s in their pantry, which just happens to be what they bought and haven&amp;#39;t eaten.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Food pantries get discounts on their purchases. They can make your dollars go farther in helping needy people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Food pantries have bills, too. They still pay rent, employees, transportation, utilities, just like any other operation. They can&amp;#39;t deliver their services without money to pay for those. It&amp;#39;s hard to convince the electric company to taken payment in cans of beans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Food pantries often do much more than provide food. Baby diapers, for example. Also, they will often help their recipients financially, such as utility bill assistance and housing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When giving cash, don&amp;#39;t forget to verify the legitimacy and effectiveness of the organization first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK可生物降解的塑料仍然会污染环境。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为了使可生物降解的塑料（不同于生物塑料）能够适当地分解，它们需要以特殊的方式处理。
为了使可生物降解的塑料（与生物塑料不同）正常分解，它们需要以特殊的方式进行处理。

> 这通常涉及到超过50°C的温度和适当的水分、空气和微生物的组合。
这通常涉及超过50°C的温度和适当的水分、空气和微生物的组合--这意味着这些塑料不会被分解...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0aa9f/ysk_biodegradable_plastics_can_still_pollute_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n0aa9f/ysk_biodegradable_plastics_can_still_pollute_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 10:51:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;In order for biodegradable plastics (which are different from Bioplastics) to decompose properly they need to be disposed of in a special way:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt; This typically involves temperatures of over 50°C and the right combination of moisture, air and microbes – meaning that these plastics won’t break down if left in the ocean or on domestic compost heaps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencefocus.com/science/what-does-biodegradable-plastic-degrade-into/&quot;&gt;https://www.sciencefocus.com/science/what-does-biodegradable-plastic-degrade-into/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK? You should make sure when you dispose of Biodegradable plastics that they are being disposed of properly, just putting them in the trash is a bad idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK麦当劳的冰激凌机被制造得很容易损坏]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：麦当劳的员工不是在偷懒。冰淇淋机
似乎总是发生故障的冰淇淋机被设计成了故障。它们是有目的性的
因为只要麦当劳要求维修，机器的制造商就会赚取利润。
每当麦当劳要求他们维修时......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzx36r/ysk_mcdonalds_ice_cream_machines_are_made_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzx36r/ysk_mcdonalds_ice_cream_machines_are_made_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 23:50:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; McDonald&amp;#39;s employees are not being lazy. The ice cream machines that always seem to break down are designed to malfunction. They&amp;#39;re purposefully difficult for employees to fix because the machine&amp;#39;s manufacturer makes a profit whenever McDonald&amp;#39;s calls in their repair technicians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McDonald’s franchisees can only purchase one type of ice cream machine: the Taylor ice cream machine that’s specifically designed for McDonald’s. This particular machine is very difficult to repair. When it malfunctions, the screen shows a series of cryptic error codes. The manual is long, technical, and contains little helpful information. Most “solutions” it proposes end up being “call a technician.” McDonald’s has a contract with Taylor and franchisees can only call an authorized Taylor technician. The technician has their own handbook and secret menu to operate the machine. Employees are not allowed to have this better manual; only Taylor technicians can see it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Calling in a Taylor repairman costs the franchisee hundreds of dollars an hour. Despite the fact that Taylor has worked with the McDonald’s corporation since the beginning, none of their system updates help the problem. Some of them make the error codes longer and more cryptic. McDonald’s partnership with Taylor means that the corporate heads benefit from Taylor&amp;#39;s success. 25% of Taylor’s profits come from repairs. So when the machine breaks down, Taylor makes a profit repairing it, and the McDonald&amp;#39;s corporate leaders also profit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McDonald’s and Taylor continue to prioritize maximizing profit at the expense of franchisees, employees, and customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s a video released four days ago explaining the investigative journalism behind this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/SrDEtSlqJC4&quot;&gt;The REAL reason Mcdonald’s Ice Cream Machines are Always Broken&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，如果你是一个在家的父母，你所做的工作虽然没有经济价值，但当你付钱给别人做的时候，就会有很大的货币价值。你需要人寿保险。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：想象一下，花钱请人做你每天要做的事情一整年。
平均而言，一个保姆一年可以赚取约30,000美元，而日托服务的费用约为100美元。
1万美元，但这些费用并不接近你所提供的工作和努力的货币价值。
但这些费用并没有接近你所提供的综合工作和努力的货币价值。虽然，根据...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzv2n3/ysk_that_if_you_are_a_stay_at_home_parent_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzv2n3/ysk_that_if_you_are_a_stay_at_home_parent_the/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 22:55:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Imagine paying someone to do what you do every day for an entire year. On average, a Nanny can make around $30,000 a year, and daycare can cost around $10,000 per year, but these costs don’t get close to the monetary value of the combined work and effort you provide. Although, according to the economy, your work doesn’t hold economic value, your work is incredibly valuable and will cost a lot to replace. You need about 10x the cost of your work in term life insurance to cover the costs of the value that you provide to your kids and/or to your home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，当加油机告诉你要见收银员时，你可以直接取消交易，将你的卡作为信用卡运行。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK: 如果你不知道，一些加油站的加油机在你使用借记卡后会显示 "请看
在你使用借记卡后，收银员会说 "请看"。我已经听到很多人
抱怨，说他们不想走进去，因为他们是反社会的，或者说我自己是反社会的。
因为他们是反社会的，或者我自己就是懒惰的。好吧，你是在...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mznm0s/ysk_that_when_the_gas_pump_tells_you_to_see_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mznm0s/ysk_that_when_the_gas_pump_tells_you_to_see_the/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 20:48:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK: If you do not know, some gas station pumps will say &amp;quot;please see cashier&amp;quot; after you use a debit card. I have been hearing a lot of people complaining about this saying they do not want to walk inside because they are either antisocial or I myself for instance am just lazy. Well you are in luck because I have never had to actually go inside the gas station because when that message appears simply hit the cancel button on the keypad and wait. Then reinsert your card and do not run your card as debit even though it is a debit card. There should be an instruction on how to run as credit and this is what you want to do. You may have to enter a zip code, you may not. Either way you now can pump your gas in peace without having to go inside. None of my friends or family knew this was possible and have been going inside to pay for their gas for as long as they can remember so I hope this helps someone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Someone said this is probably just a US/ North American issue! Sorry, I&amp;#39;m from a small town in Mississippi and can sometimes forget the world around me&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你认识一个有虐待行为的人，而你告诉那个虐待者的受害者你不想站在哪一边，那么你就是站在了某一边。你是在选择施暴者的一方。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么YSK：对受害者说这句话是你试图证明你的决定是正确的，或者直接以牺牲受害者的利益来使自己感觉更好。
你想证明你的决定是正确的，或者直接以受害者的利益为代价让自己感觉更好。停止吧。让你的
做出选择，处理所有当你发现你的朋友伤害了你时出现的奇怪感觉。
你的朋友伤害了其他人，而你自己却没有受到虐待......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzv3y6/ysk_if_you_know_someone_who_is_abusive_and_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzv3y6/ysk_if_you_know_someone_who_is_abusive_and_you/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 19:43:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: 
Saying that to a victim is you trying to justify your decision or make yourself feel better directly at the victim’s expense. Stop it. Make your choices, process all of the weird feelings that come up when you find out that your friend hurts other people on your own, without the abuse victim as your audience/feelingshelper. Don’t ask abuse victims for their blessing to keep your monthly “Abuser Bowling Night” going or do your processing of your feelings on their time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：拥有良好的姿势和人体工程学实际上是非常严肃的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：不良的姿势和人体工程学会导致很多令人惊讶的问题。
的问题，而且不会等到你年老的时候才出现。
了。希望很多人已经知道这一点，但如果你像我几个月前那样
几个月前，你可能认为姿势就像一些人认为的......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzg70w/ysk_having_good_posture_and_ergonomics_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzg70w/ysk_having_good_posture_and_ergonomics_is/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 09:41:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Having poor posture and ergonomics can cause a lot of surprising problems throughout your body, and it doesn&amp;#39;t wait until you&amp;#39;re elderly to show up. Hopefully a lot of people know this already, but if you&amp;#39;re like I was a few months ago, you might think of posture like some people think of diet, sort of like &amp;quot;this won&amp;#39;t affect me until I&amp;#39;m older, so I don&amp;#39;t need to worry about it yet&amp;quot; (not that that&amp;#39;s a good mindset either).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some things that can happen from poor posture are degenerated discs, upper-crossed syndrome, thoracic outlet syndrome (this can result in blot clots and aneurysms, no lie), arthritis, all kinds of pinched nerves, fatigue, and many other painful conditions that can require physical therapy, medications, and even surgery.  I couldn&amp;#39;t find an academic article about this that fits well, but here&amp;#39;s something &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/adult-health/in-depth/posture-align-yourself-for-good-health/art-20269950&quot;&gt;from the Mayo Clinic&lt;/a&gt; about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To prevent these problems, you should of course have a proper ergonomic setup for work/gaming/whatever you&amp;#39;re doing. Sitting on a yoga ball or using a standing desk is a good idea. When driving, try to adjust your seat properly. Even when standing, walking around, and relaxing on your couch try to have your shoulder blades down and together, your shoulders back, and your neck back so that your ears align with your shoulders. Also, this is slightly unrelated, but drinking enough water everyday &lt;a href=&quot;https://cospineandjoint.com/2018/11/hydration-important-spinal-health/&quot;&gt;helps keep your spinal discs healthy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not in the medical field, so anyone who knows more about this is of course welcome to correct me on stuff. I just thought I&amp;#39;d spread the word in case it can help anyone prevent their own problems. I for one didn&amp;#39;t know all this before, and now I&amp;#39;m sitting here, only in my 20s, with tingly, tired arms and a heating pad on my shoulder because I had bad ergonomics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be well everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK以此开始掌握公开演讲。公开演讲是你的恐惧，还是你的感叹？我想让你知道这一点。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：熟练的公开演讲可以提高你的自信和领导能力。
领导能力。你将需要它来管理人和领导未来的团队。

十年来，在高达1000人的人群中进行公开演讲，让我学到了很多东西。
自己和公开演讲。这里有一些要点可以帮助你。

-做到这一点。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/myaesj/ysk_this_to_begin_mastering_public_speaking_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/myaesj/ysk_this_to_begin_mastering_public_speaking_is/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 08:53:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Public speaking proficiently improves your confidence and ability to lead. You will need it to manage people and lead teams in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A decade of Public speaking to crowds up to 1000 people has taught me alot about myself and Public speaking. Here are some the points to help you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Do your prep, know your material.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Do your rehearsal without notes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Butterflys/anxiety:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have butterflys, 👍good. That feeling is great, it focuses you, adrenaline is preparing for a fight/flight. I do not feel that anymore so I actually take an energy drink immediately before an important class/presentation to simulate that hyperness (not reccomended for you), just embrace this feeling it benefits you and you will miss it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Getting sweaty/sick:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you feel nervous think about the guy in the back playing candy crush, why would you be afraid of him? He&amp;#39;s a jerk, not listening, but also not judging, just and oxygen thief.  The opposite is true as well, someone taking notes and making eye contact with you wants to hear what you have to say next and is supporting you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-The group you are speaking to is far smaller than you realize:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you get better you can command the room and have most people&amp;#39;s attention for small spans. You cannot have everyone&amp;#39;s attention for 20-30 minutes, people are just not wired that way. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Generally half of the audience isn&amp;#39;t listening, a good portion of the audience lack the mental capacity or self confidence to be judging you and listening to you at the same time.  The attentive ones you are able to make eye contact with are engaged and rooting for you, because they want to hear what&amp;#39;s next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this is some type of public speaking class where everybody is taking turns, 75% of the class you are speaking to has knots in their stomach about their own presentation and are reciting their nore cards in their head. The teacher, is a Saint and superhuman if you think they can focus on every word of 25 consecutive presentations about what someone did over summer vacation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-The person judging you most harshly is you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-You are going to crush it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在踩刹车之前，先把你的闪光灯打开]]></title><description><![CDATA[不要同时做这两件事。

为什么是YSK：这不仅可以防止你被别人追尾
的追尾，而且还能大大增加
交通的流量。对卡车司机来说，要在一瞬间停下来是非常困难的
而且，同样地，需要很长的时间来...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzd6bp/ysk_put_your_blinker_on_before_you_hit_the_brakes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mzd6bp/ysk_put_your_blinker_on_before_you_hit_the_brakes/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 03:57:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t do both simultaneously. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK: Not only will this prevent you from getting rear-ended by someone driving &amp;amp; not paying attention behind you, but it&amp;#39;ll also greatly increase the flow of traffic. It&amp;#39;s extremely difficult for truck drivers to stop on a dime and, likewise, takes a long time to crawl back up to cruising speed (because their vehicles &amp;amp; their tow loads weigh a lot more than you realize they do). Learn how your vehicle operates. You are not the only one using the road. Everyone wants to make it to their destination on time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK表示，谷歌地图将不再总是默认显示你到目的地的最快路线。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：要记住检查和选择更快的路线，这很痛苦。
谷歌地图开始默认显示排放最轻的路线，而不是最短的旅行时间。
而不是最短的旅行时间。显然，这只是在
两条路线的ETA值相近，但近10分钟是...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mz7nww/ysk_that_google_maps_will_no_longer_always_show/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mz7nww/ysk_that_google_maps_will_no_longer_always_show/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 23:44:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: it&amp;#39;s a pain having to remember to check and select the faster route.
Google maps is starting to default to displaying the route with the lightest emissions rather than the shortest travel time.
Apparently it&amp;#39;s only when the ETA for both routes is similar, but nearly 10 minutes is significant for my morning commute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：有大量的网站可以免费获得科学文章、书籍、新闻报道和期刊! 链接如下:)]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：那些科学文章的付费墙是BS。这些钱都不归属于
实际的作者和研究人员。新闻文章的付费墙也很愚蠢。
幸运的是，这并不难。特别是如果你是一个学生。
这些网站都很不错。

outline.com [https://outline.com/] - Place...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/myhvlk/ysk_there_are_tons_of_websites_to_get_scientific/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/myhvlk/ysk_there_are_tons_of_websites_to_get_scientific/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 13:45:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Those scientific article paywalls are BS. None of that goes to the actual authors and researchers. Paywalls on news articles are stupid too. Luckily, it&amp;#39;s not too hard to get around that! Especially if you&amp;#39;re a student, these sites are amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://outline.com/&quot;&gt;outline.com&lt;/a&gt; - Place &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.outline.com/&quot;&gt;www.outline.com/&lt;/a&gt; before any news article URL behind a paywall, and it&amp;#39;ll give you a non-ad-covered, annotateable, and easily shareable version!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://libgen.rs/&quot;&gt;libgen.rs&lt;/a&gt; - Library Genesis, a search engine for scientific articles, books, comics, and magazines&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sci-hub.do/&quot;&gt;sci-hub.do&lt;/a&gt; - Sci-Hub, specifically for research articles! You can stick in the URL or DOI and be taken right to the document!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://z-lib.org/&quot;&gt;z-lib.org&lt;/a&gt; - Z-library, another big search engine for books/articles!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For most of these, you don&amp;#39;t have to download the actual document unless you want to, you can read it in-browser as well! I&amp;#39;ve never had any issues with any downloads from these sites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，如果你带着年幼的孩子去露营/远足，避免给他们穿上迷彩服或中性色。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：孩子们在露营或自然郊游时经常失踪。给他们穿上
他们穿上迷彩服只会阻碍他们被找到，如果他们走失的话。
丢失。明亮的颜色更容易被找到，并使孩子在越野车和狩猎活动中更安全。
在越野车和狩猎活动中更安全。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/myof6t/ysk_if_youre_going_campinghiking_with_young/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/myof6t/ysk_if_youre_going_campinghiking_with_young/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 05:43:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Children go missing while camping or on nature outings often. Dressing them in camouflage will only hinder them from being found if they were to wind up lost. Bright colors are much easier to locate , and keeps the child safer around off road vehicles anf hunting activities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以《富爸爸，穷爸爸》一书而闻名的YSK金融大师罗伯特-清崎（Robert Kiyosaki）被参加过他的研讨会的人提起集体诉讼，加拿大广播公司（CBC）曾对他的骗局进行过曝光，他的公司Rich Global LLC于2012年申请破产。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：如果你正在阅读一本自助书籍，那么它很可能是由一个被证实的职业骗子或一个一生中唯一的成就是为了赚钱的人写的。
的人写的，或者是那些在生活中唯一的成就是写自助书的人。
写自助书籍。他们的建议、CD、DVD、研讨会、讲习班都不会对你产生
对你没有任何持久的影响。充其量，它们是安慰剂....。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mykdsy/ysk_financial_guru_robert_kiyosaki_known_best_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mykdsy/ysk_financial_guru_robert_kiyosaki_known_best_for/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 02:50:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If you are reading a self-help book, it is most likely written by a  proven professional scammer or someone who&amp;#39;s only accomplishments in  life are writing self-help books. Their advice, CDs, DVDs, seminars,  workshops will have no lasting impact on you whatsoever. At best, they  are placebos. People can be so gulable when searching for help. Do not  make the mistake of continuously looking for &amp;quot;that one self-help book&amp;quot;  that will change your life. Get better at doing searches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Research  the author&amp;#39;s background before reading a book. Question the &amp;quot;facts&amp;quot; you  are presented while reading a book. Make actions according to what  you&amp;#39;ve learned from a book, if there are any. Else, you&amp;#39;d be wasting a  lot of time reading trashy books while allowing trash into your mind and  then wonder why you&amp;#39;re feeling worse before you started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Kiyosaki&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Kiyosaki&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK-如果你听到铃声或来自封闭的电梯或井道的蜂鸣声，你应该打电话寻求帮助。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：大多数(所有)电梯在轿厢内都有一个 "报警 "按钮，作为在电话无法使用的情况下的二级警报。
如果电话不工作的话，有一个 "报警 "按钮作为辅助警报。这个按钮会在轿厢内响起，发出哔哔声，或者播放警报器
在轿厢内，偶尔也在一楼播放警报器。这可能意味着电梯
它可能意味着电梯被卡住了，而你听到它可能是里面的人的唯一办法...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mya4j7/ysk_if_you_hear_a_bell_ringing_or_a_beeping_from/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mya4j7/ysk_if_you_hear_a_bell_ringing_or_a_beeping_from/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 18:17:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Most (all?) elevators have an &amp;quot;Alarm&amp;quot; button inside the cab as a secondary alert if the phone doesn&amp;#39;t work. This will ring, beep, or play a siren on the cab and occasionally on the ground floor. It could mean that the elevator is stuck, and you hearing it could be the only way those inside could get help. Call either the security or management of the building or facility or the local fire department.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK常见的小火类型，如何扑灭它们，以及如何操作灭火器。在电视上，人们在发生小火灾时都会跑出屋外，但良好的做法可以拯救你的家。如果你有危险或火势已经蔓延，一定要拨打911。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：如何识别和扑灭小火，因为许多小火可以在蔓延之前就被预防。
因为许多小火可以在蔓延之前防止造成重大损失或伤害。以下是一些最
的火灾，以及如何扑灭它们。

A类火灾。这种类型的火是由普通的燃料源点燃的，如木材。
垃圾、布料、纸张和其他物品。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/my3dmd/ysk_common_types_of_small_fires_how_to_put_them/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/my3dmd/ysk_common_types_of_small_fires_how_to_put_them/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 12:52:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: How to recognize and put out small fires because many can be prevented from causing major damage or harm before they spread. Here are some of the most common and how to put them out: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Class A Fires: This type of fire ignites from common fuel sources, like wood, trash, fabric, paper and plastics.  Extinguish with Water or a Red Fire Extinguisher.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Class B Fires: Result from an explosion of flammable liquids or gases. Extinguish by Depleting Oxygen. Smother but never try to put water on these fires as it will make the fire grow.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Class C Fires: Result from electricity. Extinguish by removing the power source. Know where your houses main breakers are. Use a red extinguisher to suppress flames once the electricity is out.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Class K Fires: Result from grease, lard, olive oil, butter, animal fats and vegetable fats. Do NOT extinguish with water as it will spread extremely fast. Use only a Chemical Fire Extinguisher. If you do not have one do not try to put out this fire alone. These flames burn extremely hot and spread fast. Call the fire department immediately and leave the area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One more tip: Many people don’t know that fire extinguishers can’t just be left under a cabinet indefinitely without some maintenance. Look at the gauge and make sure it’s in the green square. It it’s moving out of the green or starting to rust or leak, call your local FD on a non-emergency line and ask if they service extinguishers. Some do. The one I did was happy to as the community safety is the FD’s priority. Other than that they can tell you where to go in your community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 你不应该使用食品配送应用程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在一家三明治店工作，那里有doordash和Uber Eats，但它们都是
但它们都相当相似。

为什么是YSK：在食品行业，你的利润很低，所以当一个食品配送
服务说他们将从每笔销售中抽取20-30%，这意味着你将在这笔销售中赚不到钱。
那就意味着你在那笔交易中根本赚不到钱，毕竟...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/my2w00/ysk_you_shouldnt_use_food_delivery_apps/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/my2w00/ysk_you_shouldnt_use_food_delivery_apps/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 08:53:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I work for a sandwich shop that has doordash and Uber Eats but they all are fairly similar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: In the food industry you run on a thin margin so when a food delivery service says theya re going to take 20-30% from each sale that means you will essentialy make no money on that sale after all is said an done. If you care about the restaurants you order from use their app or call in and order and pick it up yourself. The companies that run these apps do not have a sustainable business model. If you look at these companies earnings they are all fairly young campanies heavily relying on investments and are yet see significant profit. Once these companies need to start functioning without the initial investment dollars you will see the prices rise even more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TDLR: by using delivery apps you are adding an unnecessary middleman that will cost you more and make the restaurant less money, don&amp;#39;t use food delivery apps if you care about the business you are ordering from&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(If you want to read more about it this areticle breaks it down even more:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eatthecapital.com/post/why-you-shouldn-t-be-ordering-from-grubhub-or-uber-eats&quot;&gt;https://www.eatthecapital.com/post/why-you-shouldn-t-be-ordering-from-grubhub-or-uber-eats&lt;/a&gt; )&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果把你的地址刻在AirTag/Tile或其他追踪器上，你不应该把它挂在钥匙上。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：一些公司提供免费的雕刻服务，因此许多人可能会被诱惑在追踪器上写上他们的详细资料，甚至是他们的地址。
在追踪器上写上他们的详细资料，甚至是他们的地址。

这似乎是有道理的，因为追踪器可能会耗尽电池或以某种方式损坏。
损坏，但是如果这个人有你的钥匙和地址......。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx6nyy/ysk_you_should_not_get_your_address_engraved_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx6nyy/ysk_you_should_not_get_your_address_engraved_on/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 06:48:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Some companies offer free engraving so many people might be tempted to put their details on the tracker, perhaps even their address. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This might seem to make sense since the tracker could run out of battery or be damaged in some way, however if the person has your keys and address... they know where you live and could gain access to your house or vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，除了所有疯狂的费用外，食品交付应用程序还抬高了菜单价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：从字面上看，现在就去Chipotle网站。一个卷饼碗将是
$8.20. 如果你去DoorDash、Ubereats等网站，同样的卷饼碗将是
$9-11. 餐馆被迫抬高菜单价格，因为有20-30%的
送餐服务费。另一个误导性的事实是，你的那些广告...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mxwp26/ysk_that_food_delivery_apps_inflate_menu_prices/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mxwp26/ysk_that_food_delivery_apps_inflate_menu_prices/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 03:07:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Literally go on the chipotle website right now. A burrito bowl will be $8.20. If you go on DoorDash, Ubereats, etc. that same burrito bowl will be $9-11. Restaurants are FORCED to inflate menu prices because of the 20-30% delivery service fees. Another misleading fact is that those ads you see all the time for “free delivery” really mean “no delivery fee.” There are also 15-20% service fees, surge fees, and minimum cart fees. Sales taxes are also calculated differently from app to app! I usually avoid these fees by picking up the food myself or calling in my order for delivery. If I really want to splurge, I&amp;#39;ll order delivery, but because I&amp;#39;m cheap, I&amp;#39;ll use a food delivery aggregator. This &lt;a href=&quot;https://foodboss.org/&quot;&gt;aggregator&lt;/a&gt; has a website and compares Ubereats and Eatstreet. I used them for a while and saved a good amount of money. The only other option is this other &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mealme.ai/&quot;&gt;aggregator&lt;/a&gt; that compares DoorDash, Ubereats, GrubHub, Postmates, and some other ones. They messed up my first order but they gave me a promo code, so I&amp;#39;ve been using this one more since they compare more services. Whatever you choose, make sure to always tip-- the drivers definitely deserve/need it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在美国，说 "是的，先生 "或 "是的，女士 "与年龄没有关系。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK。

我知道这是另一个帖子的翻版，但我想澄清，这并不是
只是一个南方的事情。这是一个美国的事情。

这在美国很少见，但有时来自其他国家的人（尤其是在欧洲北部）。
北欧或其他只讲英语的国家的人）会被冒犯，就像
你是...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mxq14v/ysk_in_the_us_saying_yes_sir_or_yes_maam_has/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mxq14v/ysk_in_the_us_saying_yes_sir_or_yes_maam_has/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 20:38:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know this is a takeoff of another post, but I want to clarify that it&amp;#39;s not just a southern thing. It&amp;#39;s an American thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s rare in the U.S., but sometimes people from other countries (especially in Northern Europe or other only-English speaking countries) get offended, like you&amp;#39;re being too formal. It’s mostly just how we talk, but also shows respect for others. Americans say it to the 16 year old kid bagging the groceries because everyone deserves respect until they prove they don’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Believe it or not, I have a lot of experience with this (fwiw, I live in NY and have been to the south for about 10 months). I personally don&amp;#39;t ever use &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am&amp;quot; because my mom specifically used it to kiss authority figures&amp;#39; asses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve talked to lots of other people from the UK, Australia, and Scandinavia, and they have identified &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am&amp;quot; as an outdated mode of address because it wasn&amp;#39;t egalitarian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I worked customer service at a Home Depot as a late teenager and insisted on never using &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am&amp;quot; in my day-to-day life (although there was one exception that I will explain later). I found that most people, but young people especially, would always address me as &amp;quot;sir.&amp;quot; I even told some of them &amp;quot;dude, there&amp;#39;s no need to call me that; my name is Explorer as you&amp;#39;ll see on my apron,&amp;quot; but the response was &amp;quot;yes sir.&amp;quot; They disregarded my request and continued to call me &amp;quot;sir,&amp;quot; which goes to show how ingrained these words are, even in New York.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One day, I was intrigued enough with the &amp;quot;sir&amp;quot; shit that I decided to take it to the other extreme. Instead of never using &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am,&amp;quot; I used them in every sentence I would say to a customer. Sometimes, I would go full metal jacket and use the &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am sandwich;&amp;quot; for example, I would say, &amp;quot;Sir, the ant killer is in aisle 38 sir.&amp;quot; Although the idea was ludicrous and insane, believe it or not, people fucking loved it, and I was called &amp;quot;sir&amp;quot; at least 50 times that day (I started counting at some point).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, for anyone from another country who is wondering about this, in the U.S., anyone who&amp;#39;s providing a service and any stranger of any age had best be seen as an authority figure and warrants &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am&amp;quot; and the commensurate degree of deference and formality. Most people in the U.S. who say &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m not old enough to be called &amp;#39;sir/ma&amp;#39;am&amp;#39;&amp;quot; will still get a warm feeling inside from being shown that respect. In fact, if you call these people (and most others) &amp;quot;sir/ma&amp;#39;am&amp;quot; enough times, they will begin to address you in that way too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a formal nation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在沙发上放一个平坦的方形垫子，确保你的猫不会把毛发弄到家具的其他地方。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：如果他适合，他就会坐下来，你就可以少花很多时间与沙发上的棉绒滚筒相处。
绒毛辊在你的沙发上。](https://imgur.com/gallery/iiQ8ffT)]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mxpfy8/ysk_putting_a_flat_square_cushion_on_the_couch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mxpfy8/ysk_putting_a_flat_square_cushion_on_the_couch/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 19:45:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If he fits, he sits and you get to spend a lot less quality time with a lint roller on your couches. ](&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/gallery/iiQ8ffT&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/gallery/iiQ8ffT&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，脱水会使你的血压下降，这可能使你感到沮丧。这也会导致你的心脏跳动更厉害，引起焦虑。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：如果你已经容易患抑郁症或焦虑症，脱水会使其感觉更糟糕。
感觉更糟，而且很容易误事。因为你没有
因为你没有足够的血量，你的身体更难维持血流。这
导致你的身体模仿抑郁症的症状（疲劳，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx96ip/ysk_that_being_dehydrated_drops_your_blood/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx96ip/ysk_that_being_dehydrated_drops_your_blood/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 03:04:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: if you are already prone to depression or anxiety, dehydration makes it feel much worse, and it&amp;#39;s so easy to do by accident. Because you don&amp;#39;t have enough volume of blood, its harder for your body to maintain blood flow. This causes your body to mimic the symptoms of depression (fatigue, brain fog, dizziness), which can cause you to think the depressed thoughts, causing your brain to make depression chemicals. When that makes you feel shitty enough, your heart will try to fix it by beating harder, raising your blood pressure, mimicking anxiety. Additionally, it becomes harder for your blood to carry oxygen, making you breathe harder, which for me is the one that causes me to panic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn&amp;#39;t a WoW tHaNkS iM cUrEd, but for me personally makes a huge difference. For hours today my anxiety was unmanageably high for no particular reason. After an almost-breakdown I chugged 20oz of water, took a few deep breaths, and 20 minutes later felt so much better it spawned me to write this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nopanic.org.uk/dehydration-anxiety/&quot;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This message brought to you by &lt;a href=&quot;/r/hydrohomies&quot;&gt;r/hydrohomies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，在网上购物时，同一个网店可以根据你所使用的设备显示不同的价格。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：虽然听起来很疯狂，但你在网上购物时积累的数据
被网店用来确定他们认为你愿意支付的价格。
支付的价格! 你可以去同一个网站，看到不同的价格，这取决于你使用的设备。
你所使用的设备使用你的在线历史作为基础....。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx5z1v/ysk_that_when_online_shopping_the_same_online/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx5z1v/ysk_that_when_online_shopping_the_same_online/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 01:49:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: As crazy as it sounds, the data you have amassed while online shopping is being used by online stores to determine prices they think you’re willing to pay! You can go to the same site and see different prices depending on what device you are using which uses your online history as a base. You can find a lot of articles online that talk about it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before you go online shopping, you should always clear your cache and history. You may even consider downloading a VPN or using a proxy server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I came across this information because one day I was online shopping with my husband while I was at work. We both had reported different prices and exchanged pictures. There was a $20 dollar difference! I searched it up, and sure enough it is a real problem. Do you self a favor and stay informed so that you don’t spend unnecessary extra money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I can’t say all websites do it, but I know that a good amount do. Just stay weary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在南方，说 "是的，先生 "或 "是的，女士 "与年龄没有关系。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：这在南方很罕见，但有时来自其他地区的人
国家的人感到不快，好像你在说他们老。这主要是我们如何
说话的方式，但也显示了对他人的尊重。我对16岁的孩子说这句话，因为每个人都应该得到尊重。
因为每个人都应该得到尊重，直到他们证明...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx7g8d/ysk_in_the_south_saying_yes_sir_or_yes_maam_has/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx7g8d/ysk_in_the_south_saying_yes_sir_or_yes_maam_has/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 01:49:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It&amp;#39;s rare in the south, but sometimes people from other parts of the country get offended, like you&amp;#39;re calling them old. It’s mostly just how we talk, but also shows respect for others. I say it to the 16 year old kid bagging the groceries because everyone deserves respect until they prove they don’t.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 吹嘘自己从未请过病假，因为你即使生病也会去工作，并不能使你成为更好的员工。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：我经常听到人们嘲笑其他人在生病时打电话给他们。
生病时打电话出去。

他们的评论通常是这样的："我从不请假。我一定会来
即使我生病了，我也会来上班"。

这并不能使你成为更好的员工或英雄。事实上，它使你成为
恰恰相反。

它...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx4wdo/ysk_bragging_about_never_taking_a_sick_day/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx4wdo/ysk_bragging_about_never_taking_a_sick_day/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 22:56:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Often I hear folks ridiculing other for calling out of work when they are sick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The comment is usually along the lines of &amp;quot;I never call out of work. I will come to work even if I am sick.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That doesn&amp;#39;t make you a better employee or a hero. It in fact makes you the exact opposite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It shows that you&amp;#39;ve no care for your well being or the well being of others. It also shows that you&amp;#39;re willing to compromise a typically (mostly)sterile environment and possibly make others sick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay the f**k home, friendo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，如果你在车外生活，特别是带着孩子，休息站是一个很好的睡眠场所。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：它们可能有点偏僻，而且根据你居住的地方
你可能需要支付一定的费用（岔路口等），但它们是安全的空间，24/7
但它们是安全的空间，可以使用卫生间，有时还有食物。没有人会对你
睡在你的车里，而且你一般不会被注意到......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mwyjrx/ysk_that_rest_stops_are_a_great_place_to_sleep_if/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mwyjrx/ysk_that_rest_stops_are_a_great_place_to_sleep_if/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 20:38:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: They might be a little out of the way, and depending on where you live you might have to pay a fee (turnpikes, etc), but they are safe spaces with 24/7 access to bathrooms, and food sometimes. Nobody will think twice about you sleeping in your car, and you generally will not be noticed because there are different people staying there every night. It&amp;#39;s a safe place if you are working and saving up, and especially if you have small children while doing so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 充满回忆的脑袋和充满遗憾的脑袋之间的区别是你原谅自己的能力。]]></title><description><![CDATA["为什么是YSK："人们常常为他们过去所做的事情而责备自己，并且遗憾从内心开始吞噬他们。
遗憾开始从内部侵蚀他们。

他们无法超越那件事，他们的 "满脑子的遗憾"
他们的 "满脑子后悔 "使他们无法在未来成长并成为一个更好的人。

人们应该原谅...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx0dkz/ysk_difference_between_head_full_of_memories_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mx0dkz/ysk_difference_between_head_full_of_memories_and/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 19:45:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Why YSK:&amp;quot; People often blame themselves for what they did in the past and the regret starts eating them from inside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They aren&amp;#39;t able to move past that incident(s) and their &amp;quot;head full of regrets&amp;quot; makes it impossible for them to grow and become a better person in future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People should forgive themselves and try to create memories and not life long regrets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What happened, cannot be changed, they should move forward and become a better human being.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：即使你完全没有服务，如果你遇到紧急情况，仍然可以拨打911。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：除非你是在地球中心或离任何中心数百英里的地方
任何城市，附近很可能有一个运营商网络。


没有服务，你还能打911吗？

> 由于FCC的规定，网络供应商必须传输紧急呼叫（911）。
> 无论你是否使用他们的服务，都必须传输紧急呼叫（911）。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mwf4au/ysk_even_if_you_have_no_service_at_all_still_call/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mwf4au/ysk_even_if_you_have_no_service_at_all_still_call/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 04:37:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Unless you are in the center of the earth or hundreds of miles off from any city, there is most likely a carrier network nearby.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Can you still call 911 without service?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to the FCC, network providers must transmit an emergency call (911) regardless of whether you use their service or not. This means if your provider doesnt have coverage in that area, your phone will show that it has no service. ... As long as it has battery power and can reach a signal, the phone can connect to 911.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.puretalkusa.com/blog/article?p=how-to-use-your-cell-phone-in-these-3-emergencies&quot;&gt;PureTalk USA via Google&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see so many damn people saying “and if you have no service” when being told to call 911. It’s unlikely it’ll happen, but this could very well save your life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK说，如果你关心蜜蜂，你就不应该在早春时节修剪或杀死草坪上的蒲公英。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：据专家介绍，在早春，蒲公英可以是一个重要的食物来源。
在经历了漫长的冬季后，蒲公英可以成为蜜蜂的重要食物来源，因为它们要靠自己的储备来生活。春天可以
春天对蜜蜂来说是一个困难时期，因为它们在10摄氏度/50华氏度时开始活跃，这通常是在许多授粉的花朵绽放之前。
通常在许多授粉的花朵开花之前....。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mwerxp/ysk_that_if_you_care_about_the_bees_you_shouldnt/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mwerxp/ysk_that_if_you_care_about_the_bees_you_shouldnt/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 23:00:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: According to experts, in early spring dandelions can be a crucial food source for the bees after a long winter of living off their reserves. Spring can be a difficult time for the bees as they become active at 10C/50F, which is usually well before many pollinating flowers have bloomed. Dandelions grow early in the season in large numbers, and quickly generate lots of pollen for the bees to collect. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theweathernetwork.com/ca/news/article/heres-why-you-shouldnt-mow-dandelions-spring-lawn-care-benefits-and-save-bees&quot;&gt;https://www.theweathernetwork.com/ca/news/article/heres-why-you-shouldnt-mow-dandelions-spring-lawn-care-benefits-and-save-bees&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，房地产商的 "费用"--即销售价格的百分比佣金结构已经过时，不应继续使用。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：销售价格的佣金收费结构只适用于20-30年前的房地产价格低得多的时候。
在房地产价格低得多、与工资关系更密切的时候
与工资密切相关。今天使用相同的价格结构（例如销售或购买价格的3-7%）完全没有意义。
价格的3-7%）是没有任何意义的，不要让...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mw9z7a/ysk_that_the_realtors_fee_aka_the_of_sales_price/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mw9z7a/ysk_that_the_realtors_fee_aka_the_of_sales_price/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 22:24:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Sales price commission fee structures were only applicable 20-30 years ago when the price of real estate was much, much lower and more closely related to salary. Using the same pricing structure today (e.g. 3-7% of sale or purchase price) does not make any sense whatsoever - and do not let a realtor convince you that it does!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most realtors today agree on lump sum payments for their services, and agreeing with your realtor on some pre-set price that has nothing to do with the value of your home is completely fine. There are still a few realtors that will prey on naive customers. The total cost of paying your realtor shouldn&amp;#39;t be more than what a paralegal or (at best) lawyer would charge in your area for a similar amount of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since we&amp;#39;ve had a crazy upward spiral in real estate prices recently, I&amp;#39;m seeing a lot of naive old people who agree with outrageous commission structure some realtors offer. No realtor is worth that much money, and don&amp;#39;t let them convince your grandparents that they are!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：呼吸法--度过恐慌期的简单方法]]></title><description><![CDATA[呼吸练习的作用是根据你的呼吸深度和节奏来调整你的神经系统。
呼吸深度和节奏。这使得它们对高警觉性类型的情况非常有用
恐慌症发作和焦虑症发作等情况非常有用。

治疗惊恐发作的呼吸法

 * 从你的鼻子吸气4秒钟。
 * 保持你的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mw2v7v/ysk_the_breath_method_simple_way_to_get_through_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mw2v7v/ysk_the_breath_method_simple_way_to_get_through_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 16:10:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Breathing exercises work by adjusting your nervous system according to your breathing depth &amp;amp; pace. Which makes them ultra useful for high-alertness type of situations like panic attacks and anxiety attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Breath Method for Panic Attacks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inhale from your nose for 4 seconds,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold your breath for 4 seconds,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exhale from your mouth for 6 seconds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And repeat this pattern for as long as you want. Focus on your bodily sensations, and affirm yourself in your mind that it&amp;#39;ll all be fine - because it really will!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Panic Attacks are the worst, but this might help you - as it did me and my friends &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So yeah. I&amp;#39;m aware of this exercise because of a breathing exercises app, and here&amp;#39;s the screenshot of the exercise (in case you have visual memory, or just save it on your phone): &lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/kNa4GdV.png&quot;&gt;Panic Button breathing exercise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: People have been asking me about the app, the app&amp;#39;s name is &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;Huma Breath&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;quot; - I use it on Apple but it should be available for Android too. There are other exercises for anxiety, sleep, energy etc too, recommend it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Btw, if you ever feel down or want to talk to someone, please feel free to PM me!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：'很多'不是一个词。它是'很多'。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：这是最常见的错别字之一，人们通过模仿来学习拼写某些东西。
因此，这种癌症错别字传播得越多
就会有更多的人继续把它弄错。请加入我的努力，让全世界都知道
世界知道 "a lot "是两个词，而不是一个。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvuuuq/ysk_alot_is_not_a_word_its_a_lot/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvuuuq/ysk_alot_is_not_a_word_its_a_lot/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 10:51:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This is one of the most common misspellings and people learn to spell certain things by example, therefore the more this cancer typo is spread around the more people will continue to get it wrong. Join me in my efforts to let the world know that &amp;#39;a lot&amp;#39; is two words, not one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，在夏季来临之际，让你的狗游泳要非常小心，蓝绿藻是有毒的，往往对狗是致命的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：蓝绿藻，或称蓝细菌，在适当的环境下，几乎可以在任何淡水体中生长。
在适当的情况下，蓝绿藻或蓝细菌几乎可以在任何淡水中生长。17个州报告了蓝绿藻
相关的死亡事件，在2019年。你不能确定任何藻类是否有毒，所以
如果你打算靠近水，特别是停滞的水体...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvvz07/ysk_be_very_careful_letting_your_dog_swim_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvvz07/ysk_be_very_careful_letting_your_dog_swim_as/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 07:02:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  Blue green algae, or cyanobacteria can grow in nearly any body of fresh water under the right circumstances. Seventeen states reported blue green algae related deaths in 2019. You cannot be sure that any algae is or isn&amp;#39;t toxic, so if you plan on being near water especially stagnant bodies during warm weather take precautions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keep your dog leashed near bodies of water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Try not to let them drink any.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you notice any foam or films on the surface of the water it&amp;#39;s best not to let them swim or play in it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This toxin can be fatal very quickly and by the time your pet displays symptoms it&amp;#39;s often too late. There is no antidote, so look before you leap!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你去一家餐馆，银器上有水渍，这并不意味着银器很脏。]]></title><description><![CDATA[所有这一切都意味着滚动银器的人（可能甚至不是你的
的人（很可能甚至不是你的服务员）懒得去擦拭它。

为什么YSK：没有必要要求新的银器，尤其是当你的服务员
是很糟糕的。银器是干净的! 它只是在经过清洗后湿漉漉地放了一会儿
通过清洗]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvtoh7/ysk_if_you_go_to_a_restaurant_and_there_are_water/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvtoh7/ysk_if_you_go_to_a_restaurant_and_there_are_water/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 05:51:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;All it means is the person who rolled the silverware (likely not even your server) was too lazy to polish it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: it’s unnecessary to ask for new silverware, especially if your server is slammed. The silverware is clean! It just sat out wet for a bit after going through the wash&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：母亲节是5月9日（还有18天）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：如果你打算在网上订购东西，这是一个好时机。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvubbt/ysk_mothers_day_is_may_9th_in_18_days/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvubbt/ysk_mothers_day_is_may_9th_in_18_days/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 05:01:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It&amp;#39;s a good time to order things online if you intend to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，淫羊藿是大量破坏性和非法交易的对象。询问供应商的来源可能会有帮助。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：因为多肉植物是比较独特的植物品种之一，它们已经成为 "偷猎 "的目标。
它们已经成为 "偷猎 "的目标。许多人认为他们在帮助
许多人认为他们在购买这些植物时是在帮助保护这些物种，但如果助长非法供应，就会无意中伤害它们。
助于非法供应。可以找到更多信息...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvn7ix/ysk_that_succulents_are_the_subject_of_a_great/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mvn7ix/ysk_that_succulents_are_the_subject_of_a_great/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 21:47:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: because succulents are one of the more unique varieties of plants out there, they&amp;#39;ve become a target for &amp;quot;poaching.&amp;quot; Many people think they&amp;#39;re helping preserve the species when they purchase them, but can inadvertently hurt them if contributing to illegal supply. Some more info can be found in this piece by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KirP2ef1lJ0&quot;&gt;Cheddar&lt;/a&gt;. Ultimately, it&amp;#39;s OK to have succulents! But if we want them to stay around, it&amp;#39;s good to spread info on best-buying habits. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a post on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/interestingasfuck&quot;&gt;r/interestingasfuck&lt;/a&gt; that showed off a living rock cactus, which is a common victim of illegal trade. Made me think I should share the video I had recently seen on it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK拯救蜜蜂组织更关注原生蜜蜂而不是蜜蜂]]></title><description><![CDATA[蜜蜂没有消亡的危险；许多本地蜜蜂都濒临灭绝或受到威胁。
受到威胁。我在网上看到很多带有 "拯救蜜蜂 "标题的帖子
我在网上看到很多带有 "拯救蜜蜂 "标题的帖子，都是以蜜蜂和养蜂为主题。

为什么YSK：很多人对蜜蜂而不是本地蜜蜂感兴趣。
蜜蜂。努力帮助...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mv8dcp/ysk_save_the_bees_focuses_more_on_native_bees/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mv8dcp/ysk_save_the_bees_focuses_more_on_native_bees/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 13:42:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Honeybees are in no danger of dying out; lots of native bees are endangered or threatened. A lot of post I&amp;#39;ve seen online with &amp;#39;save the bee&amp;#39; captions have been focusing on honeybees and beekeeping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Lots of people are taking an interest in honeybees rather than native bees. Efforts to help honeybees often end up hurting native bee populations. If you&amp;#39;re able, plant native plants and wildflowers, go pesticide free, buy/build nesting houses, and find out about local conservation efforts. Native bees are an essential part of local ecosystems and are necessary pollinators.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 使用蓝牙追踪器应用程序来定位误放的物品、耳机和设备是很容易的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：包括我在内的很多人都容易把物品放错地方，比如钥匙。
耳机（如AirPods），甚至是手机。一个好的蓝牙追踪应用程序可以
帮助定位物品和设备。今天的大多数设备都内置了蓝牙
并且可以很容易地找到。对于钥匙和其他日常用品，你可以...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mv2w3k/ysk_its_easy_to_use_a_bluetooth_tracker_app_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/mv2w3k/ysk_its_easy_to_use_a_bluetooth_tracker_app_to/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 05:00:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: A lot of people including me tend to misplace items like keys, headphones (like AirPods), or even phones. A good Bluetooth tracking app can help locate items and devices. Most of the devices today have Bluetooth built in and can be easily located. For keys and for other everyday items, you can use trackers like Tile or the recently announced Apple AirTag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>