<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 04:41:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK表示，美国医院被要求从1月1日起遵守价格透明规则，你可以举报你的医院不遵守规则。]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 在此报告一家医院的不合规行为
> [https://cms.gov1.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_b2fAQwrDLIC7Iyx]

为什么是YSK：PatientRightsAdvocate.org估计，只有不到6%的医院...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pf9gns/ysk_that_us_hospitals_were_required_to_comply/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pf9gns/ysk_that_us_hospitals_were_required_to_comply/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 18:47:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Report a hospital for non-compliance &lt;a href=&quot;https://cms.gov1.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_b2fAQwrDLIC7Iyx&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: PatientRightsAdvocate.org estimates &lt;a href=&quot;https://static1.squarespace.com/static/60065b8fc8cd610112ab89a7/t/60f1c225e1a54c0e42272fbf/1626456614723/PatientRightsAdvocate.org+Semi-Annual+Hospital+Compliance+Report.pdf&quot;&gt;that less than 6% of hospitals are compliant&lt;/a&gt;. You can report your hospital for non-compliance  to the Centers for Medicare &amp;amp; Medicaid Services &lt;a href=&quot;https://cms.gov1.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_b2fAQwrDLIC7Iyx&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, they can be fined for each day they are noncompliant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cms.gov/hospital-price-transparency/hospitals&quot;&gt;To be compliant, a hospital must make &lt;strong&gt;all&lt;/strong&gt; of the following information publicly available on their website&lt;/a&gt; (they can&amp;#39;t require you to email them for the information, or require an account, password, or fee):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.)  Single &lt;strong&gt;machine-readable digital file&lt;/strong&gt; containing the following standard charges for all items and services provided by the hospital: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;gross charges&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;discounted cash prices &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;payer-specific negotiated charges&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;de-identified minimum and maximum negotiated charges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.) Display of at least 300 “shoppable services” (or as many as the hospital provides if less than 300) that a health care consumer can schedule in advance. &lt;strong&gt;Must contain plain language descriptions of the services&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;group them with ancillary services&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can find more information at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cms.gov/hospital-price-transparency&quot;&gt;https://www.cms.gov/hospital-price-transparency&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 你的早期依恋风格会显著影响你在成年后应对压力和调节情绪的方式。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：因为它可以帮助阐明一些可能的原因，让你感受到。
思考或以特定方式行事的可能原因。像这样的解释可能是相当有力的
因为它可以让你意识到塑造你的环境，特别是如果你是那种
特别是如果你是那种认为自己的...的人。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pf3m48/ysk_your_early_attachment_style_can_significantly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pf3m48/ysk_your_early_attachment_style_can_significantly/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 13:42:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Because it can help shed light on some possible reasons why you feel, think or behave in a particular way. An explanation like this can be quite powerful in that it can make you aware of the circumstances that shape who you become, especially if you’re the kind of person who thinks their character is all their fault. It’s also valuable for parents to know how their interactions with their kids can become neurally embedded and affect the children’s later life. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;None of this is about assigning blame to parents or rejecting personal responsibility. It’s also not something I read in a self-help book or some such. Attachment theory has been backed by a lot of research in psychology and has inspired some of the most forward-thinking studies in neuroscience, too. Below I’ll sum up some findings from two decades of research by psychologist Mario Miculincer - and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/profile/Mario-Mikulincer/publication/285623488_The_Attachment_Behavioral_System_In_Adulthood_Activation_Psychodynamics_And_Interpersonal_Processes/links/573d709808ae298602e5a533/The-Attachment-Behavioral-System-In-Adulthood-Activation-Psychodynamics-And-Interpersonal-Processes.pdf&quot;&gt;here’s a link&lt;/a&gt; with an in-depth (100 pages) report on his research.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OK, here we go:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Firstly, according to attachment theory, children of sensitive parents develop secure attachment. They learn to be okay with negative feelings, ask others for help, and trust their own ability to deal with stress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By contrast, children of unresponsive caregivers can become insecurely attached. They get anxious and upset by the smallest sign of separation from their attachment figure. Harsh or dismissive parenting can lead to avoidant infants who suppress their emotions and deal with stress alone. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interactions with early attachment figures become neurally encoded and can be subconsciously activated later in life, especially in stressful and intimate situations.  For example, as adults, anxious people often develop low self-esteem and are easily overwhelmed by negative emotions. They also tend to exaggerate threats and doubt their ability to deal with them. Such people often exhibit a desperate need for safety and seek to “merge” with their partners. They can also become suspicious, jealous or angry without objective cause.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Avoidant people want distance and control. They detach from strong emotions (both positive and negative), and avoid conflicts and intimacy. Their self-reliance means that they see themselves as strong and independent, but this can mean that their close relationships remain superficial, distant and unsatisfying. And while being emotionally numb can help avoidant people during ordinary challenges, in the midst of a crisis, their defences can crumble and leave them extremely vulnerable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你使用多流回收，请不要粉碎铝罐。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：与塑料不同，铝是可以无限循环利用的，但如果最终被填埋，它就不能被回收。
但如果它最终被填埋，就不能被回收。

在单流回收中，你有一个路边的回收箱，粉碎的铝很难被自动分拣机正确分拣。
在单流回收中，你有一个路边的回收箱，破碎的铝很难被自动分拣机正确分拣，并可能最终进入垃圾箱。
在单流回收中，你有一个路边的回收箱，破碎的铝很难被自动分拣机正确分拣，并可能最终进入垃圾堆。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/peroe7/ysk_if_you_use_multistream_recycling_do_not_crush/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/peroe7/ysk_if_you_use_multistream_recycling_do_not_crush/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 03:44:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Unlike plastic, Aluminum is infinitely recyclable, but it can&amp;#39;t be recycled if it ends up in a landfill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Single-Stream recycling, where you have 1 curbside recycling bin, crushed aluminum is more difficult to be properly sorted by the automated sorting machines and can end up in the landfill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have multi-stream recycling, where you have to sort out the various materials into separate bins, then it is ok to crush aluminum cans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit 1: Brain mixed up single and multi-stream. Single stream is 1 curbside bin. Title should read &amp;quot;If you use Single-Stream recycling, DO NOT crush aluminum cans.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit 2: Links for those wanting proof. &lt;a href=&quot;https://lifehacker.com/dont-crush-cans-before-recycling-them-1833374490&quot;&gt;Lifehacker&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rd.com/article/dont-crush-aluminum-cans-before-recycling/&quot;&gt;Readers Digest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ysk: 在雌性狗/猫进入第一个发情周期前对其进行绝育（修复），不仅仅是为了防止怀孕。它可以拯救你的宠物的生命。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：我的狗在她的乳腺中患上了癌症，原因是她没有接受荷尔蒙的影响。
在她年轻的时候给她做了绝育手术。给她做绝育手术可以防止她
得癌症。没有人愿意失去他们的宠物或让他们处于痛苦之中。修复
你的狗/猫的好处远远多于负面后果。如果我愿意...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pejczv/ysk_spaying_fixing_a_female_dogcat_before_going/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pejczv/ysk_spaying_fixing_a_female_dogcat_before_going/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 03:29:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: My dog has Cancer in her Mammary Glands due to hormones from not Spaying her- when she was young. Spaying her could have prevented her from getting cancer. No one wants to lose their pets or have them in pain. Fixing your dog/cat has way more benefits than negative consequences. If I would have known, it would have saved me a lot of money and time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fixing your female dog/cat before their first heat cycle can prevent illnesses and help them live a healthier life. Spaying helps prevent uterline infections and tumors (which can be malignant or cancerous) in 50% of dogs and 90%. It also helps them not have to go into heat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Dogs will have their first heat cycle between 4 months and 2 years with the average of 6 months. Cats are roughly around 6-9 months. I am not advocating for spaying/neutering at the earliest possible date (8 weeks  old)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为Tik Tok的 "Oh no, Oh no, Oh no no no no "这首歌最初是Aerosmith的歌曲（记得Walking In the Sand），而且很好听！这首歌的歌词是："Oh no, Oh no, Oh no no"。你可以听一下这首原唱，以净化自己的病态，即Tik Tok的混音。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：很多人对Tik Tok的翻唱感到厌烦，而听原唱会让他们觉得很舒服。
聆听原版歌曲会让他们感觉更好

史密斯飞船。Remember Walking in the sand [https://youtu.be/POLYGEfhQBc]

编辑：从评论中可以看出，即使是Aerosmith的也是翻唱的同名歌曲
标题的Shangri...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pemaqd/ysk_that_the_tik_tok_oh_no_oh_no_oh_no_no_no_no/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pemaqd/ysk_that_the_tik_tok_oh_no_oh_no_oh_no_no_no_no/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 22:32:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: A lot of the people are sick of this Tik Tok remix and listening to the original song will make them feel better!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/POLYGEfhQBc&quot;&gt;Aerosmith: Remember Walking in the sand&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: From the comments even Aerosmith’s is a cover for the song with the same title by Shangri-Las. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/V5YxtweUxrA&quot;&gt;https://youtu.be/V5YxtweUxrA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你不相信普遍接受的医疗做法，你可以通过AMA（反对医疗建议）出院来要求出院。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么YSK：如果你不相信任何一个医生，那么你最好回家去
在家做你认为最好的治疗，并为别人打开一张病床。
给别人。如果你认为医院是在让你或你所爱的人
死亡，那么为什么要浪费你的时间和增加医疗费用呢......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pei7rt/ysk_if_you_dont_believe_in_commonly_accepted/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pei7rt/ysk_if_you_dont_believe_in_commonly_accepted/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 19:08:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If you don’t trust any of the doctors, then you might as well go home and do whatever treatments you think are best at home and open a hospital bed up for someone else. If you believe the hospital is letting you or your loved one die, then why waste your time and rack up medical bills sitting in the hospital?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just get an AMA discharge
 and go home to your herbal treatments and whatever other treatments you think are better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC2664598/&quot;&gt;More info on AMA discharges here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，在阳光下将柠檬或酸橙汁弄到皮肤上可能会导致严重烧伤，称为植物性皮炎。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：这些烧伤，也被称为 "玛格丽特烧伤"，主要影响那些皮肤白皙的人。
皮肤白皙的人和对阳光敏感的人--特别是从事食品服务的人。
你不仅仅会被柠檬和酸橙烧伤（尽管它们似乎是
最常见的罪魁祸首）。) 植物性皮炎也是由...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/peh1ok/ysk_that_getting_lemon_or_lime_juice_on_your_skin/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/peh1ok/ysk_that_getting_lemon_or_lime_juice_on_your_skin/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 17:50:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: These burns, also called &amp;quot;margarita burns&amp;quot;, mostly affect those with fair skin, and people sensitive to the sun - especially those in food service. You can get burned by more than just lemons and limes (though they seem to be the most common culprits). Phytophotodermatitis is also caused by carrots, celery, parsley, dill, bergamot, fig, any citrus, and essential oils containing any of these things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://health.clevelandclinic.org/lime-juice-and-sunshine-can-make-for-painful-unexpected-sunburn/&quot;&gt;https://health.clevelandclinic.org/lime-juice-and-sunshine-can-make-for-painful-unexpected-sunburn/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK说BRI（Bob Ross Inc）从他的儿子Steve Ross那里偷走了Bob Ross的名字，并且不让Bob的儿子用自己的姓作画。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK

这部新的Netflix特别节目讲述了科瓦尔斯基家族如何从自己的儿子那里偷走了 "罗斯 "的一切。
从他自己的儿子那里。该公司只使用鲍勃-罗斯的名字来赚钱。

编辑：我还应该说，该特别节目指出，BRI伪造了罗斯的
签名的画。他们还起诉了，并让鲍勃的所有...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pegzfr/ysk_that_bri_bob_ross_inc_stole_the_bob_ross_name/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pegzfr/ysk_that_bri_bob_ross_inc_stole_the_bob_ross_name/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 13:42:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new Netflix special tells how the Kowalski family stole everything &amp;#39;Ross&amp;#39; from his own son. The company only uses the Bob Ross name to make money.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I should also say, that the special notes that BRI has forged the Ross signature on paintings. They also sued, and had all of Bob&amp;#39;s paintings taken from the family home. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;BOYCOTTBRI&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为好市多不收取额外费用来安装和拖走通过他们购买的一些电器]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK: 我刚刚从Costco买了一台新的洗碗机，因为我知道
安装和运走服务都包括在价格里。最重要的是。
我买的这台洗碗机在好市多比家得宝的同型号产品便宜了250美元。
同型号的洗碗机，好市多比家得宝便宜250美元（考虑到这是美国的劳动节促销活动，我也不知道）。这是我最满意的地方。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pe5gkz/ysk_that_costco_doesnt_charge_extra_to_install/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pe5gkz/ysk_that_costco_doesnt_charge_extra_to_install/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:42:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I just bought a new dishwasher from Costco after I learned that installation and haul away services were included in the price. On top of that, the dishwasher I got was almost $250 cheaper at Costco than Home Depot for the same model (YMMV given it was a Labor Day sale in the USA). The install/haul services range from $150-175 at Lowe’s or Home Depot, whereas a Costco membership is only $60 (lasts for a year).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 你的抗菌洗手液使情况变得更糟]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK

为什么你应该知道。抗菌洗手液不仅是不必要的（肥皂和洗手液），而且也是不可取的。
水就可以了），而且它们还在积极促成抗生素
耐药性的细菌，并且实际上使市政层面的水净化变得更加困难。
更加困难。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pe10dx/ysk_your_antibacterial_hand_soap_is_making_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pe10dx/ysk_your_antibacterial_hand_soap_is_making_the/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 20:33:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why you should know: Antibacterial hand soaps are not only unnecessary (soap and water works well enough) but they’re actively contributing to antibiotic resistant bacteria and actually making water purification at the municipal level much harder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：有一些免费的大学课程，你可以在网上学习]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：在这段时间里，很多人可能会有更多的休息时间，或者他们想要
继续接受教育，但这通常要花费很多钱。虽然你
虽然你可以使用YouTube查找特定的主题，但有一个结构化的课程也是不错的。
结构化的课程。我具体谈论的课程是这样的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pdm585/ysk_there_are_free_college_courses_you_can_take/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pdm585/ysk_there_are_free_college_courses_you_can_take/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 07:29:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: During this time a lot of people might have more downtime or they want to continue there education but that usually cost a lot of money. While you could use YouTube to look up specific topics, it can be nice to have a structured course. The classes I am specifically talking about is this one edx.org which has classes from colleges like Stanford and Harvard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，先生们，如果你的睾丸有疼痛感，请立即进行检查。如果是坏消息，越早发现越好，或者可以像我一样省去几个月的焦虑。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK......我的右睾丸轻微疼痛了一年多才去看医生。
去看医生。我没有去看医生，因为如果我听到 "C "字，我就会毫无准备。
我没有去看医生，因为如果我听到 "C "字，我就没有准备，如果我没有大声听到它，它就不是真的（听起来很傻，我知道）。
我知道）。)

最终，大约两个月前，在它出现在我的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pdncay/ysk_gentlemen_if_you_have_ache_or_pain_in_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pdncay/ysk_gentlemen_if_you_have_ache_or_pain_in_your/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:55:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK... I had a slight ache in my right testicle for over a year before I went to my doctor. I didn&amp;#39;t go to the doctor because if I heard the &amp;quot;C&amp;quot; word, I was unprepared and if I didn&amp;#39;t hear it out loud, it wasn&amp;#39;t real (sounds silly, I know) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eventually, about 2 months ago, after it being on my mind for so long and depression had set it, I had had enough and visited my doctor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He examined me, it took 20 seconds(which wasn&amp;#39;t that bad) and he said that he couldn&amp;#39;t feel any abnormalities but said we&amp;#39;d do an ultrasound to be sure...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was scheduled for a week later. It was the longest week of my life. I was sure that, that&amp;#39;s it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the ultrasound time came along on a Friday. The technician wasn&amp;#39;t as nice as my doctor and basically scaned me with a straight face and said that the radiologist will be in touch with my doctor on Monday. So another horrible long weekend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My doctor contacted me with my results after what seemed like months. Turns out that I have &amp;quot;varicocele&amp;quot; which is a varicose vein in my testicle. It&amp;#39;s can cause infertility but I have my family now so I don&amp;#39;t really care about that.Thr relief was overwhelming, It actually broke down in tears!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could have saved myself a lot of anxiety if I had just gotten checked out over a year ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gentlemen if it doesn&amp;#39;t feel right, get it checked!! If it&amp;#39;s bad news, the earlier it&amp;#39;s found the better... Or it could be something like my situation. X&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：铁路交叉口和停车场的吊杆障碍物被设计成可以在紧急情况下开过去的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：我之前看到一个帖子，有人被卡在了铁道口的障碍物之间
障碍物之间，他们让自己的车被撞了。这很悲惨，因为如果
他们只要对这些障碍物的设计有一点了解，他们就会没事。
就不会有事了。

臂膀的设计是为了通过....。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pdh45l/ysk_boom_barriers_at_railway_crossings_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pdh45l/ysk_boom_barriers_at_railway_crossings_and/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 22:37:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I saw a post earlier where someone got stuck in between the barriers at a railway crossing, and they let their car get hit. This is tragic, because if they&amp;#39;d only known a little about the design of these barriers they would have been okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The arms are &lt;em&gt;designed&lt;/em&gt; to be driven through. They&amp;#39;re typically made of easily broken wood or flexible plastic, and are considered a consumable part as this happens (by accident or on purpose) all the time. Some are made of metal, but with a breakaway joint at the base so that they can be reused in areas where they&amp;#39;re broken especially often. Counterweighted designs will automatically lift and stay up if broken. Some of the best designs can even log the event for security and electronically self reset!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In all cases, all damage to your vehicle will range from none to cosmetic scratches. I can imagine a freak scenario where you could end up with a cracked windshield, but that&amp;#39;s still better than getting hit by a train or being trapped in a parking structure in a fire. It costs a maximum of a couple hundred bucks to fix one of these arms, but in a real emergency you shouldn&amp;#39;t be worried about that and hopefully wouldn&amp;#39;t be charged for it. Expect steep fines if you do it to avoid paying for parking or to beat a train though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some video sources (no injuries or anything):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AM00gZ1PP2U&quot;&gt;Demo of a couple breakaway designs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GJklQZ8y9XI&quot;&gt;Van vs heavy duty aluminum reusable arm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GheJGLkKMs0&quot;&gt;Florida man demonstrates his technique&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_yBTmGMG-Wc&quot;&gt;A guy breaks one by hand and falls down&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Related mini YSK: This is NOT TRUE for height clearance bars, many can cause severe damage stopping your vehicle from hitting whatever they&amp;#39;re protecting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK Reddit的黑暗主题可以变得更黑暗]]></title><description><![CDATA[我刚刚进入设置，发现你可以将深色主题改为
称为 "午夜 "的更深的黑色。

为什么选择YSK：对比度很惊人]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pdfszo/ysk_reddits_dark_theme_can_go_darker/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pdfszo/ysk_reddits_dark_theme_can_go_darker/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 21:32:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just went into settings and found out you can change the dark theme to a darker black called, “midnight”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: The contrast is amazing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，如果你经常吸食大麻而不再做梦，那是因为你的快速眼动睡眠减少了! 点击查看更多信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK。

使用杂草（特别是delta 9-thc）可以减少快速眼动睡眠。(资料来源1
[https://academic.oup.com/sleep/article/43/Supplement_1/A62/5846891], 来源2
[https://ascpt.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/cpt1976196782]）如果你
仍然每天做着生动的梦，那么恭喜你，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pd9o4g/ysk_that_if_you_smoke_weed_regularly_and_are_no/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pd9o4g/ysk_that_if_you_smoke_weed_regularly_and_are_no/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 20:17:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weed use (specifically delta 9-thc) can reduce REM sleep. (&lt;a href=&quot;https://academic.oup.com/sleep/article/43/Supplement_1/A62/5846891&quot;&gt;Source 1&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://ascpt.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/cpt1976196782&quot;&gt;Source 2&lt;/a&gt;) if you are still having vivid dreams every day, then congratulations, your REM sleep is probably fine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason this is important is because the lack of REM sleep is associated with decreased learning ability and decreased memory consolidation. (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0960982217313295&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has also been studied that cannabis use among REM-sleep deprived rats shows that they become more aggressive. (&lt;a href=&quot;https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/BF00426483&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might be able to circumvent this to some extent if you go to bed completely sober, but I&amp;#39;m not sure if doing that allows for full REM cycles again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In summary: Smoking delta-9 THC (weed), especially before bed, can reduce your time in REM sleep. This causes you to have worse memory, and makes it harder to learn new things and new habits. This is stuff that weed by itself already makes harder for a lot of people, so it&amp;#39;s even worse when combined with lack of REM sleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: by the way, this isn&amp;#39;t to say that you should never smoke weed before bed or for nightmares or anything like that. I&amp;#39;m just trying to inform more people because I&amp;#39;ve been experiencing REM-sleep deprivation for years now and had no idea until now that it had any effects other than just blocking dreams. And now that I&amp;#39;ve been trying to dream more I feel like I am getting more restful sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：想检查你的Windows笔记本电池健康/容量？不需要安装其他软件，Windows的内置功能就可以做到这一切。]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 1. 点击开始按钮，开始输入Powershell。当它出现的时候，右键
    点击它并选择以管理员身份运行。

 2. 当提示符打开时，粘贴以下命令并点击回车。
    
    > powercfg /batteryreport /output "C:\battery-report.html" 。

 3. 转到您的C盘文件夹...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pdev6d/ysk_want_to_check_your_windows_laptop_battery/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pdev6d/ysk_want_to_check_your_windows_laptop_battery/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 19:54:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Click the start button and start typing Powershell. When it comes up, right click it and choose to run as administrator.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the prompt opens up, paste the below command and hit enter:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;powercfg /batteryreport /output “C:\battery-report.html”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Go to your C drive folder and click the battery report file. Within the file search for two important bits:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  “DESIGN CAPACITY”: This is how much the battery is supposed to be able to hold&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  “FULL CHARGE CAPACITY”: This is how much charge the battery is actually holding now on average&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; There is no magical percentage that you should change your battery, but this should give you a good overall picture of how your battery is doing so you can make a more informed decision about whether you really need to replace your battery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如果有人因打架或受伤而没有反应，不要立即移动他们，并试图迫使他们站起来！这可能会造成严重的永久性伤害。这可能会造成严重和永久性的损害。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：我确信这是相当普遍的知识，只是我在这里看到了太多的视频。
在reddit上看到了太多的视频，一些可怜的家伙被弹出的灯光
一些可怜的家伙被关上了灯，然后就像柱子一样僵硬，只有3号小妞或其他什么人跑过来，开始摇晃昏迷的人。
旁边的3号或其他什么人跑过来，开始摇晃失去知觉的人，并大喊大叫......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pdat0g/ysk_if_someone_is_left_unresponsive_due_to_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pdat0g/ysk_if_someone_is_left_unresponsive_due_to_a/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 17:56:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I&amp;#39;m sure this is fairly common knowledge, it&amp;#39;s just that I have seen one too many videos here on reddit of some poor fella getting his lights flicked off and being left stiff as a post, only to have side chick #3 or whatever run up and start shaking the unconscious person and screaming &amp;quot;WAKE UP&amp;quot; or something along those lines. While sometimes this is enough to snap whomever back to reality, if the afflicted is suffering from a head or spinal injury, unnecessary movement can result in a life of rehabilitation or worse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK葡萄、葡萄干、洋葱和大蒜都对狗有很大毒性。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：如果你喂错了东西，你的动物会死。

我的朋友给他的狗喂葡萄，因为我知道葡萄有毒，所以我吓坏了
我吓坏了，打电话给兽医，他们说喂它一些双氧水，让它
呕吐。幸运的是，这在他喂完葡萄后立即发生了，但可能...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pd8w29/ysk_grapes_raisins_onions_and_garlic_are_all_very/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pd8w29/ysk_grapes_raisins_onions_and_garlic_are_all_very/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:12:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Your animal can die if you feed them the wrong thing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My friend fed his dog grapes and since I knew grapes were toxic, I freaked out and called the vet and they said feed him some hydrogen peroxide to get him to vomit. Luckily this happened immediately after he fed them, but could have been a disaster had he waited an hour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：维生素D的缺乏会让你感到相当低落，空虚更抑郁而不自知。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：我发现我有维生素D缺乏症（很可能是因为
我一直在室内），在服用维生素D的几天后
几天后，我觉得自己更快乐了，与以前相比不再空虚了。
我相信我不是唯一有这种情况的人......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pd7zth/ysk_that_a_vitamin_d_deficiency_can_make_you_feel/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pd7zth/ysk_that_a_vitamin_d_deficiency_can_make_you_feel/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 12:34:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Well I found out that I had a vitamin d deficiency(most likely because I’ve been indoors all the time) and a few days after taking my vitamin d supplements, I just felt much more happier, less empty compared to before and I’m sure I’m not the only one with this experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/health/depression-and-vitamin-d&quot;&gt;https://www.healthline.com/health/depression-and-vitamin-d&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你养育了你的猫或狗，从第一天起你就是它们的中心，它们一生的性情在很大程度上取决于你在它们出生后的头几周内给予它们多少爱，或缺乏爱。]]></title><description><![CDATA[2020年4月，我发现一只一周大的小猫在我的下水道里独自哭泣。
在一场大雨中独自哭泣。她当时在大约2英寸的雨水中。
雨水中，而我拒绝让她淹死。我给她喂奶，鼓励她
我给她喂奶，刺激她上厕所，教她自己洗澡和使用猫砂盆--如何......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pd6lrg/ysk_if_you_have_raisedhandreared_your_cat_or_dog/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pd6lrg/ysk_if_you_have_raisedhandreared_your_cat_or_dog/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 11:02:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;In April of 2020, I discovered a week- old kitten crying alone in my storm drain, in the middle of a heavy downpour. She was in about 2 inches of rainwater, and I refused to leave her to drown. I bottlefed her and stimulated potty breaks, taught her to bathe herself and use the litter box - how to be a cat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a baby, I’d keep “Rei “ close always. All the kisses and pets, naps together, followed by long nights awake to feed her and potty. She was/is my heart. She knows nothing but loVe and affection. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She’s A little over a year old now - she’s sweet to all the faces that stop by regularly, and has a sweet habit of looking for/giving physical affection/touch more often than you’d ever expect from a cat. With strangers/friends alike, the most with me. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: If You show them love from start, that’s all they’ll ever know. It’s a beautiful thing. Same goes for the opposite, if you neglect them or go without showing them affection, they’re more likely to grow up reclusively and antisocial.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你在一家大商店网上购物，你的购物车是巨大的。先买一两件东西，然后再买其他的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：很多商店都会在你的包裹里放一张优惠券（可享受25%以上的优惠）。
折扣），当你从他们的商店购买一件东西时。这可以确保
你会再次去那里购物。

如果你已经打算在那里花很多钱，这个最初的
优惠券可以真正减轻对你的打击。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pcyc48/ysk_if_youre_online_shopping_from_a_big_store_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pcyc48/ysk_if_youre_online_shopping_from_a_big_store_and/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:44:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: A LOT of stores will put a coupon in your package (for upwards of 25% off your next purchase) when you buy one thing from their store. This ensures you shop there again. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you were already planning on spending a lot of money there this initial coupon could really soften the blow on your wallet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你可以在出售丙烷罐的地方回收这些罐子。用记号笔写上 "RECYCLE"，放在笼子旁边。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：每个商店的员工，如果你问他们，都会说 "我们只接受
换"。

今天我花了1个小时来回收一个蓝犀牛丙烷罐，它是由房子的前主人留下的。
我今天花了1个小时来回收一个蓝犀牛丙烷罐，这是房子的前主人留下的。第一个地方，尽管在蓝犀牛网站上被列为
尽管在蓝犀牛网站上被列为接受回收的地方，但他们说 "我们......"。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pcvmec/ysk_you_can_recycle_propane_tanks_at_places_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pcvmec/ysk_you_can_recycle_propane_tanks_at_places_that/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 23:07:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Every store employee, if you ask them, will say &amp;quot;we only take exchanges.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It took me 1 hour today to recycle a Blue Rhino propane tank that was left by the previous owner of the house. First place, despite being listed on the Blue Rhino website as a place that takes recycling, said &amp;quot;we only do exchanges.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What they mean is, &amp;quot;I don&amp;#39;t know anything about recycling them and I don&amp;#39;t want to be bothered, go away.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I went to a hardware store (thinking that maybe it was a gas station specific thing) and the employees all said the same thing. I called Blue Rhino up and had their customer service tell the employees how to do recycling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best part? When I went to the cage - there were two canisters next to it. The guy had previously told me it was &amp;quot;against store policy to have canisters outside of cages.&amp;quot; (They are for theft protection, if they explode, all that metal becomes shrapnel, it ain&amp;#39;t for safety).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suggest just skipping telling the employees and just doing it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如何让管家的工作更轻松]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是一名管家。有相当多的时候（没有我担心的那么多，感谢上帝），人们做的事情使我们的工作变得困难。
上帝）人们做的事情使我们的工作变得困难甚至是危险。
无论他们是否有意为之。我知道这是一项被遗忘的工作
人们不会想到要帮助我们，但我们都会非常...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pcif8l/ysk_how_to_make_housekeepers_jobs_easier/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pcif8l/ysk_how_to_make_housekeepers_jobs_easier/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 09:23:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m a housekeeper. And a fair amount of times (not as much as I&amp;#39;d feared, thank god) people do things that just make our job difficult or even dangerous, whether they mean to or not. I know it&amp;#39;s a job that&amp;#39;s kind of forgotten about and people don&amp;#39;t think about helping us out but we&amp;#39;d all greatly appreciate it :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strip your bed after you&amp;#39;re done with it. It&amp;#39;s instinct to try and make the bed but please don&amp;#39;t. Just take all the blankets and pillow cases off and throw them in a pile somewhere.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;#39;t leave trash. Seriously. You aren&amp;#39;t a child ffs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Control your blood. People bleed like, SO much in hotel rooms. That is a biohazard and we have to go way out of our way to follow procedure. Throw your bloody tissues in the garbage. Try not to get blood on sheets or carpet, and if you do (it happens) please tell a staff member ASAP so we can be prepared to treat it and so it doesn&amp;#39;t stain. Same goes for any bodily fluid. We aren&amp;#39;t judging you if your kid pees the bed, we just need to know so we can treat it. If you get injured, we have first aid kits all over and will gladly patch you up.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;#39;t leave your soaking wet towels just laying around. Hang them up to dry, please.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you smoke weed in the room, leave some for us. We can smell it, we want some, and you&amp;#39;re a tease. We&amp;#39;ll also &amp;quot;forget&amp;quot; who was in that room and won&amp;#39;t charge you for damages a good amount of the time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Try not to use two beds in a double bedded room if you only need one. It&amp;#39;s twice the work. I do get the desire to jump from one to the other though, so I&amp;#39;m not too mad when I see it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;(this one doesn&amp;#39;t actually help us, it just helps you) If you put a bag over your smoke detector cause you&amp;#39;re smoking in your room, congrats, you&amp;#39;re a dumbass who just snitched on yourself. Your cigarette won&amp;#39;t set off the alarms and we can&amp;#39;t smell it half the time. But if we see a bag on your detector, we&amp;#39;re charging you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You know what? Kick your kids out. Just make them sleep in the halls. We hate rooms with kids.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tip. We&amp;#39;re wage workers. We don&amp;#39;t get paid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;But OP,&amp;quot; I hear you say, &amp;quot;that&amp;#39;s all common sense!&amp;quot;. To which I raise you: no the fuck it isn&amp;#39;t, apparently. If I clean 10 rooms, like 7 of them will have people who were dicks staying there. Consider us, please. Our job sucks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Our job kinda sucks and making it easier is a super Chad thing to do. Also, it might save you money, because if you piss us off we will advocate for the hotel to charge you more for any damages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：巨魔试图通过复制/粘贴几个月前的帖子的评论来使他们的Reddit账户合法化，这样他们就有了历史。如果你看到它，请报告（例子在正文中）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK: 嘲弄是一种宣传形式，用于混淆和切断公民讨论，以便无法达成共识（人类的自然愿望）。
讨论，从而无法达成共识（人类的自然愿望）。
人的自然愿望）。)

这里有一个...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pch6h6/ysk_trolls_try_to_legitimize_their_reddit_accts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pch6h6/ysk_trolls_try_to_legitimize_their_reddit_accts/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 09:23:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Trolling is a form of propaganda used to confuse and cut off civil discussion so that no consensus is achieved (the natural desire of human beings).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/n08nbd/zookeepers_of_reddit_whats_the_lowdown_dirty/gw5uef8?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web2x&amp;amp;context=3&quot;&gt;Here is a post&lt;/a&gt; I made 4 months ago with the original comment made by &lt;a href=&quot;/u/drotothedruid&quot;&gt;/u/drotothedruid&lt;/a&gt; linked. I read all comments in my post, and so today when I noticed a familiar comment, it had set alarm bells.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/n08nbd/zookeepers_of_reddit_whats_the_lowdown_dirty/hait62p?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web2x&amp;amp;context=3&quot;&gt;Here is the troll account&lt;/a&gt; copy/paste comment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And just in case the troll decides to wipe the account, &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/Rsb5FMX&quot;&gt;here are screenshots&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I wonder is if Reddit is aware and will scrub troll accounts like these?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如何快速、轻松地评估一项研究的样本量是否 "太小"，并说服他人]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：我已经看到了内容丰富的（编辑：国家/世界人口）研究
涉及超过100个甚至1000个参与者，却被毫无根据的说法所否定
样本量太小，不能代表人口。

让我们假设我们在讨论一项经同行评审的研究，声称79%的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pcbrvp/ysk_how_to_quickly_and_easily_evaluate_whether_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pcbrvp/ysk_how_to_quickly_and_easily_evaluate_whether_a/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 01:41:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I&amp;#39;ve seen informative (edit: country/world population) studies involving over 100 or even 1000 participants dismissed with the unbacked claim that the sample size is too small to be representative of the population.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let us suppose we are discussing a peer-reviewed study claiming 79% of the US population believes &amp;#39;blorp&amp;#39;, and the sample-size is 427 randomly-selected participants. Let us next suppose that someone replies 427 is too small to say anything about the US population.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, open a &amp;#39;margin-of-error&amp;#39; calculator such as: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.calculator.net/sample-size-calculator.html&quot;&gt;https://www.calculator.net/sample-size-calculator.html&lt;/a&gt; (2nd section of the page) and plug in the following values:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Confidence level: 99% (This can be increased or decreased.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sample Size: 427&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Population proportion: 79%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Population: 332,677,777&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see the inputs and output here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.calculator.net/sample-size-calculator.html?type=2&amp;amp;cl2=99&amp;amp;ss2=427&amp;amp;pc2=79&amp;amp;ps2=332677777&amp;amp;x=74&amp;amp;y=24#findci&quot;&gt;https://www.calculator.net/sample-size-calculator.html?type=2&amp;amp;cl2=99&amp;amp;ss2=427&amp;amp;pc2=79&amp;amp;ps2=332677777&amp;amp;x=74&amp;amp;y=24#findci&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This results in &amp;#39;margin of error&amp;#39; 5.09%, which means there is a 99% chance the actual value is between (79% - 5.09%) and (79% + 5.09%)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;= approximately between 74% and 84%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can now phrase your reply this way, along with the calculation link (test your link after commenting and edit if needed) :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a sample-size of 427, a population of 332,677,777, and a finding of 79%, there is a 99% chance the actual value is between 74% and 84%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.calculator.net/sample-size-calculator.html?type=2&amp;amp;cl2=99&amp;amp;ss2=427&amp;amp;pc2=79&amp;amp;ps2=332677777&amp;amp;x=74&amp;amp;y=24#findci&quot;&gt;https://www.calculator.net/sample-size-calculator.html?type=2&amp;amp;cl2=99&amp;amp;ss2=427&amp;amp;pc2=79&amp;amp;ps2=332677777&amp;amp;x=74&amp;amp;y=24#findci&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Citation showing the math being done by the calculator: &lt;a href=&quot;http://crab.rutgers.edu/%7Egoertzel/marginsoferror.htm&quot;&gt;Guide to Computing Margins of Error for Percentages and Means&lt;/a&gt; (Rutgers University)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feedback encouraged!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK OpenStreetMap是谷歌/苹果地图的免费和开放的替代品。]]></title><description><![CDATA[像谷歌地图和维基百科一样，人们必须编辑兴趣点。随着越来越多的
越来越多的人使用它，数据变得更加准确。

与专有产品不同，这些数据是任何人都可以免费使用的。唯一需要注意的是
是没有官方的移动应用程序（我个人使用有机地图）。

为什么选择YSK: 随着越来越多的人开始使用YSK，它将成为一个新的平台。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pbmlih/ysk_openstreetmap_is_a_free_and_open_alternative/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pbmlih/ysk_openstreetmap_is_a_free_and_open_alternative/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 15:35:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like Google Maps and Wikipedia, people have to edit points of interests. As more people use it, the data becomes more accurate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unlike proprietary products, the data is free to use by anyone. The only caveat is that there&amp;#39;s no official mobile app (I personally use Organic Maps).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK: With more people contributing, you help to create an open Internet where the data isn&amp;#39;t sold to the highest bidder. Imagine if Wikipedia was riddled with ads or paywalls or tracked your usage.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.openstreetmap.org/&quot;&gt;Official website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你想知道一家（大型上市）公司发生了什么，请阅读他们的年度10-K表格报告。市场营销和股东沟通可以被扭曲，使事情看起来比实际情况要好，但10-K表格是法律要求的，有不扭曲的财务和风险分析。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：公司的沟通是由营销和公众形象问题决定的，这是众所周知的。
形象的关注。不仅是实际的广告，甚至是股东信也可以
描绘出一幅美好的画面，以鼓励投资或作为非正式的宣传材料。
材料，过分强调进展顺利的事情，而埋没了......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pbqha8/ysk_if_you_want_to_know_whats_going_on_in_a_large/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pbqha8/ysk_if_you_want_to_know_whats_going_on_in_a_large/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 04:29:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Company communication is notorious to be shaped by marketing and public image concerns. Not only actual advertising, but even shareholder letters can paint a rosy picture to encourage investment or act as informal promotional material, over-emphasizing things that went well and burying things that didn&amp;#39;t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, under US law, every large (over $10M in assets) publicly traded company must file an annual financial and risk analysis report called a &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Form_10-K&quot;&gt;Form 10-K&lt;/a&gt; to the Securities Exchange Commission. This report must, by law, have an honest and undistorted statement of financial performance, risk analysis, executive compensation, major corporate decisions, and other relevant information. Since it is filed to the government, rather than to the general public, corporations are far more careful about ensuring what they say is truthful and representative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether or not you are a shareholder, a consumer, or just a concerned citizen, Form 10-K may expose inner dealings that a corporation might otherwise prefer to keep under wraps. For example, a quote from EA&amp;#39;s Form 10-k report from 2017 states: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;em&gt;Negative player sentiment about our business practices also can lead to investigations from regulatory agencies and consumer groups, as well as litigation, which, regardless of their outcome, may be costly, damaging to our reputation and harm our business.&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为对毒藤的 "免疫 "是一个神话。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：为了避免任何潜在的不愉快的经历，希望能够防止
任何无意中对自己或他人造成的伤害。

灵感来自我在r/IsItBullshit看到的一个帖子
[https://www.reddit.com/r/IsItBullshit/]中看到的一个帖子，我对其进行了评论，并决定它
值得提升信号，因为它令人惊讶......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pbg2z0/ysk_that_immunity_to_poison_ivy_is_a_myth/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pbg2z0/ysk_that_immunity_to_poison_ivy_is_a_myth/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 03:28:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: To avoid any potentially unpleasant experiences and hopefully prevent any unintentional harm coming to yourself or others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inspired by a post I saw in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/IsItBullshit/&quot;&gt;r/IsItBullshit&lt;/a&gt; that I commented on and decided it is worth signal boosting because its surprising how widespread of a rumor this is. Pretty much copy and pasted my comment from that thread, removing some profanity. Also, to be clear, I&amp;#39;m just trying to be informative! I&amp;#39;m not trying to call anybody out, just dispel an oft perpetuated rumor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The &amp;quot;active&amp;quot; ingredient in Poison Ivy that causes the rash is Urushiol, it is a hapten molecule which means sticks to your cells (in this case, skin cells), causing your immune cells (CD8+ killer T cells) to recognize your own cells as foreign and attack, leading to a type IV hypersensitivity reaction.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is a fundamental aspect of adaptive immune response and if you don&amp;#39;t experience type IV reactions at all, you probably have a greater immune problem.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;If you doubt me, that&amp;#39;s fine, but I advise you to actually look it up because pretty much any medical resource will tell you the same thing. It is not the same type of allergy as we commonly associate with seasonal or food allergies. Repeated exposure to poison ivy sensitizes you to it precisely because the reaction is mediated by the adaptive immune response, which has &amp;quot;memory&amp;quot; and reacts more intensely each time you are re-exposed to a given compound or microbe.&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many compounds are like this. For example, the resin used for 3D printing does the same thing, though I&amp;#39;m not quite sure what it is exactly in the resin that is responsible for this. Each subsequent exposure results in a more dramatic effect. &lt;strong&gt;The reality is that the people who say they aren&amp;#39;t allergic just haven&amp;#39;t been exposed to it very much and/or are careful enough around it to avoid exposure altogether.&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;#39;ve never had a reaction before, but that doesn&amp;#39;t mean I&amp;#39;m going to go frolicking through patches of poison ivy butt naked. My dad was &amp;quot;immune&amp;quot; until about a decade ago when he got a horrible reaction while doing yardwork, nearly had to go to the ER because he unknowingly spread it all over his body. Tolerance can be genetically inherited, but as you age, various factors (something to do with changes in various protein and immune marker expression) can cause you to lose that tolerance even without exposure, similar to how some people &amp;quot;randomly&amp;quot; develop a seafood allergy.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, the 15% figure often touted online is also false if you are talking about total immunity. You may be &amp;quot;tolerant&amp;quot; of it but that doesn&amp;#39;t mean you won&amp;#39;t eventually have some reaction. I&amp;#39;m not gonna beat up anybody for spreading this rumor, but it *is* potentially harmful disinformation and people should know the truth so they don&amp;#39;t end up hurting themselves or others unintentionally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully this post saves somebody from an avoidable rash and teaches people to be a bit more cautious around poison ivy, even if you are tolerant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Citations:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;source 1: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK562228/&quot;&gt;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK562228/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;source 2: &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Urushiol&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Urushiol&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;source 3: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/health/poison-ivy-immunity#:%7E:text=The%20bottom%20line,to%20the%20effects%20of%20urushiol&quot;&gt;https://www.healthline.com/health/poison-ivy-immunity#:~:text=The%20bottom%20line,to%20the%20effects%20of%20urushiol&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;source 4:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.livescience.com/35712-heathy-geezer-poison-ivy.html&quot;&gt;https://www.livescience.com/35712-heathy-geezer-poison-ivy.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK在Wally World使用洗手液的必要性]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：我看到有很多男人（和男孩）从浴室的小便池和隔间出来，却没有停下来洗手。
和隔间里出来，却没有停下来洗手，这意味着我们都在接触他们的
这意味着我们都在接触他们的垃圾（或更糟），因为他们在处理产品，触摸手推车和柜台等。任何
男性注意到同样的不卫生现象吗？- 是的，它无处不在......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pbgj8t/ysk_the_necessity_of_using_hand_sanitizer_at/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pbgj8t/ysk_the_necessity_of_using_hand_sanitizer_at/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 22:59:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: By the amount of men (and boys) I see coming out of bathroom urinals and stalls and not stopping to wash their hands, means we&amp;#39;re all touching their junk (or worse) as they handle products, touch carts and counters, etc. Any males notice the same lack of hygiene? - and yes, it&amp;#39;s everywhere - not just at your box store.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[像沃尔玛这样的商店会在不降价的情况下将商品清仓。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：许多人没有意识到，当他们进入一家商店的清仓区时，他们没有意识到。
许多人没有意识到，当进入像沃尔玛这样的商店时，他们会添加一个黄色的贴纸，其中没有提到以前的价格。
价格。这通常是为了让人相信价格已经降低，但实际上
他们只是想在不降价的情况下更快地卖掉它们。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pbk82b/ysk_stores_like_walmart_will_put_items_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pbk82b/ysk_stores_like_walmart_will_put_items_on/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 22:15:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Many people don&amp;#39;t realize when going into the clearance section of a store like Walmart, they add a yellow sticker that doesn&amp;#39;t mention a previous price. This is often to make a person believe the price is reduced but in fact they just want to sell them faster without reducing first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK的男性性病测试只需要在杯子里撒尿。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么YSK大多数人没有意识到，男性的性病检查不再需要将切口推入尿道。
刀具被推入尿道。这种耻辱感吓跑了很多男性，使他们不敢接受检测。
但这已不再是常规做法。因此，如果你担心你可能有
感染了性病，不要犹豫，去做检查吧!]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pbar45/ysk_std_tests_for_men_only_require_peeing_in_a_cup/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pbar45/ysk_std_tests_for_men_only_require_peeing_in_a_cup/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 14:17:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK most people don&amp;#39;t realize that std tests for males no longer require a cutip to be pushed into the urethra. This stigma scares away a lot of men from getting tested but it is no longer the norm. So if you&amp;#39;re worried you may have an std don&amp;#39;t hesitate to go get tested!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，皮肤填充剂比你认为的要持久得多。它们不会分解，而是在脸上移动。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK

面部填充物，或称皮肤填充物，在过去的几年里已经变得非常流行。
在过去的几年里，年仅十几岁的人就开始做这种手术，有时会造成严重后果。
带来可怕的后果。

专业人士以 "手术是暂时的 "这一承诺来吸引客户。
暂时性的，这意味着无论你做什么]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pax8u3/ysk_that_derma_fillers_are_a_lot_more_permanent/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pax8u3/ysk_that_derma_fillers_are_a_lot_more_permanent/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 23:14:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Facial fillers, or derma fillers, have become immensely popular in the past years with people as young as teenagers getting the procedures done, sometimes with dire consequences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Professionals lure in clients with the promise that the procedures are temporary, meaning that whatever you pump into your face will be absorbed or broken down over time and you&amp;#39;ll be back to your normal self without issue or any aftermath.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MRI scans of people who&amp;#39;ve had derma fillers injected show that the fillers aren&amp;#39;t being broken down by the body and are showing up on scans up to ten years later. Since there is nothing tethering them in place they, like all other liquids, end up moving around. This is most easily seen in people who frequently get derma fillers where their face starts rounding up, they get a shelve on their top lip or a build up under the eyes (tear trough fillers).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MRI scans show that, for example, lip filler isn&amp;#39;t breaking down but rather moving upwards towards the nose and downwards to the chin. This gives the illusion that the filler has broken down and people go back to get another injection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a good and scientific breakdown of this I highly recommend checking out the Victorian Cosmetic Institute on YT where DR. Gavin Chan goes over the above in detail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/yoF_Ez27-L0&quot;&gt;https://youtu.be/yoF_Ez27-L0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[哺乳期内可以怀孕的YSK]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：虽然妇女的月经周期更有可能在孩子断奶时恢复
断奶时，妇女的月经周期更有可能恢复，但仍有可能在给孩子喂奶的时候被敲醒。
在给孩子喂奶的时候仍然有可能怀孕。

就像这里所说的[https://www.llli.org/breastfeeding-info/fertility/]。
母乳喂养（尤其是纯母乳喂养）可以是一个...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pamiah/ysk_that_you_can_get_pregnant_while_breastfeeding/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pamiah/ysk_that_you_can_get_pregnant_while_breastfeeding/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 19:18:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: While a woman&amp;#39;s menstrual cycle is more likely to return when the kid is being weaned, it&amp;#39;s still possible to get knocked up while giving milk au&amp;#39; naturel to your child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like stated &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.llli.org/breastfeeding-info/fertility/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, Breastfeeding (especially exclusively) can be a pretty good form of birth control, but it&amp;#39;s not foolproof. So if you want to wait with having another kid remember: don&amp;#39;t be a fool, go wrap that tool!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你在遛狗的时候，绳子有张力，你可能是遛狗的方式不正确。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：狗链是一种通讯设备，是向狗发出某种运动信号的手段。
给狗。

只有当你需要向你的狗传达一个提示/动作时，才应该使用绳子上的张力。
行动（例如，走近点，向左转，坐下，坐下）。一旦信号
一旦通过绳索发出信号，就应将其关闭...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pap2mj/ysk_if_you_are_walking_your_dog_with_tension_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pap2mj/ysk_if_you_are_walking_your_dog_with_tension_in/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:26:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: A leash is a communication device as means to signal a certain movement to the dog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tension on the line should only be used if you need to communicate a cue / action to your dog (e.g., come closer, turn left, sit, down). Once the signal through the leash is made it should be turned of (slack line)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People have just grown accustomed to a constant pull on the leash, which in my view is an extremely unpleasant way to walk. I think people underestimate how much dogs are capable of, and a walk can be a very pleasant experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contrary to popular belief dogs dont naturally learn how to walk with you (unless you are consistent and clear in your training) so while people still believe their dogs will eventually grow out of it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A leash is a communication device as means to signal a certain movement to the dog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tension on the line should only be used if you need to communicate a cue / action to your dog (e.g., come closer, turn left, sit, down). Once the signal through the leash is made it should be turned of (slack line)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People have just grown accustomed to a constant pull on the leash, which in my view is an extremely unpleasant way to walk. I think people underestimate how much dogs are capable of, and a walk can be a very pleasant experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contrary to popular belief dogs dont naturally learn how to walk with you (unless you are consistent and clear in your training) so while people still believe their dogs will eventually grow out of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 一个简单的风扇是阻止蚊子的最有效方法之一。密歇根州立大学的昆虫学家发现，风扇产生的风会大大减少蚊子，他们建议我们在后院使用这种方法来保护自己和宠物。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK: 蚊子是非常恼人的，人们想尽各种办法来阻止它们。
驱赶它们。这一招其实很有效。

只要在外面附近放一两个风扇，蚊子就会远离。
因为它们无法对抗风扇产生的风。它真的很有效...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pae7zk/ysk_a_simple_fan_is_one_of_the_most_effective/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pae7zk/ysk_a_simple_fan_is_one_of_the_most_effective/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 03:42:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  Mosquitos are very irritating and people try all kinds of tricks to keep them away.  This one actually works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just place a fan or two nearby outside and the mosquitos will mostly stay away as they can&amp;#39;t fight the wind generated from the fan.  It works really well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://lifehacker.com/keep-mosquitoes-away-with-a-fan-813282325&quot;&gt;https://lifehacker.com/keep-mosquitoes-away-with-a-fan-813282325&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，烘干机的绒毛是非常易燃的，比纸或甚至棉球更容易点燃。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK。

我经常使用普通的烘干机绒毛作为起火器，来捕捉我的火石和钢鞭的火花。
和钢的火花。它是唯一精细的、蓬松的、易燃的东西之一。
足够可靠地从一个简单的火花中点燃，而不需要实际的火焰。

每次装载后都要清洁你的棉绒网。清洁...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/paa0vv/ysk_that_dryer_lint_is_extremely_flammable/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/paa0vv/ysk_that_dryer_lint_is_extremely_flammable/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 02:01:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I regularly use plain dryer lint as a fire starter to catch sparks from my flint and steel while camping. Its one of the only things fine, fluffy, and flammable enough to reliably ignite from a simple spark, without needing an actual flame.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clean your lint screen after every load. Clean your lint trap, and dryer vent line once a year. If you notice your dryer taking longer to dry clothes, but it still gets hot, you likely have a buildup of highly flammable lint in the system somewhere that is having tons of hot air pumped through it every load of laundry. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You do NOT want to have your dryer ignite 45 minutes into an hour long cycle, long after you&amp;#39;ve forgotten about it. By the time you notice it might be too late to control the fire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为拔掉智齿通常是不必要的，这与你的牙医可能说的不同。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK。

16至19岁的人根据牙医的建议拔掉智齿是非常普遍的。
根据牙医的建议拔掉智齿是很常见的，但通常情况下，这种可能有风险的手术实际上并不需要。
但通常情况下，这种可能有风险的程序实际上根本不需要。

牙科，特别是在美国和加拿大，是一个巨大的赚钱...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pa5d01/ysk_that_wisdom_teeth_removals_are_often_not/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pa5d01/ysk_that_wisdom_teeth_removals_are_often_not/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 21:47:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s very common for people aged 16 to 19 years old to get their wisdom teeth removed according to their dentist&amp;#39;s recommendation, but often, this possibly risky procedure isn&amp;#39;t actually required at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dentistry, especially in the US and Canada, is a huge money-making industry. Unnecessary dental procedures are by far the most common and most costly of all dental scams. According to a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.smilecaredental.ca/blog/dentist-scams-and-unnecessary-dental-treatment&quot;&gt;reputable Canadian dentist&lt;/a&gt;, &amp;quot;Any person who learns how to avoid unnecessary dental procedures will save more than 50% on dental costs over their lifetime!&amp;quot;... which is very concerning when you think about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My former dental office would constantly tell me that I required dental x-rays, denying that I had recently had them taken. Each time this would happen, I would get out my phone, take a look at the date I recorded for the last time I had them taken, look at the official American Dental Association recommendations, and prove to them that they&amp;#39;re just trying to scam me. It&amp;#39;s a shame that most people would take the dental office&amp;#39;s word and get exposed to unnecessary radiation while simultaneously wasting their money/dental insurance coverage for something they don&amp;#39;t need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, back to the wisdom teeth removal part...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, that same dental office now says that I will need wisdom teeth removal surgery. Since I couldn&amp;#39;t really trust my dentist in the first place, I wanted a second opinion on this recommendation. I went to my former orthodontist, who just so happens to be one of the most reputable in my city, where I got my braces from when I was younger. She just laughed, saying that my wisdom teeth do not need removing whatsoever, confirming my skepticism with my dentist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The orthodontist also explained that dentists, especially in Canada and the US, will try to pressure you into a wisdom teeth removal surgery that you don&amp;#39;t really need since they get a sort of &amp;quot;referral bonus&amp;quot; from the dental surgeon each time one of their patients is referred to get a surgery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think about how terrible and uncalled for this is... the risks involved with anesthesia, the cost of the procedure for the patients, the risk of a failed procedure, the stress it puts on the patients, and the list goes on. All of this so that dentists can make some extra $.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do your research before your next dental appointment. Sources used: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.utdentists.com/news/story.htm?id=5388dc51-2195-48a8-a0af-29da4eda8f97&quot;&gt;UTDentists&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/wisdom-teeth/expert-answers/wisdom-teeth-removal/faq-20058558&quot;&gt;Mayo Clinic&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.smilecaredental.ca/blog/dentist-scams-and-unnecessary-dental-treatment&quot;&gt;Smile Care Dental&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK在喝咖啡或小睡之间，实际上最好是先喝咖啡再小睡。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：使你感到疲倦或筋疲力尽的原因是你大脑中的一种分子
在你的大脑中被称为腺苷，是大脑活动的副产品。当它与你的大脑受体结合时
与你的大脑受体结合时，它减缓了神经元之间的交流。睡眠
是身体和大脑重新充电和清理的方式。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pa10c5/ysk_between_a_coffee_or_a_nap_its_actually_best/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/pa10c5/ysk_between_a_coffee_or_a_nap_its_actually_best/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 16:54:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: What&amp;#39;s responsible for making you feel tired or exhausted is a molecule in your brain known as adenosine, a byproduct of brain activity.  When it bonds to your brain receptors, it slows down the communication between neurons.  Sleep is the body and brain&amp;#39;s way of recharging and cleaning out adenosine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Caffeine just so happens to bond to the same receptors that adenosine does.  However, unlike adenosine, neuron communication is not hindered.  This is why caffeine seemingly gives you brain energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For coffee to begin to affect you, it needs at least 20 minutes from the moment of consumption to when it finally hits your brain.  A quick 20 to 30 minute nap is also still significant enough to clean out some of the adenosine in your brain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a Coffee Nap, as it&amp;#39;s referred to, both of the beneficial processes occur at once.  Adenosine is cleaned up from the brain, while the caffeine from coffee replaces the adenosine&amp;#39;s spot on your brain receptors.  Thus, when you wake up, you&amp;#39;re way more energized and alert than if you had chosen to do one of the two activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Science Studies Supporting This:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/8936399/&quot;&gt;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/8936399/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/9401427/&quot;&gt;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/9401427/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1388245703002554&quot;&gt;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1388245703002554&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/8026448/&quot;&gt;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/8026448/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Explanation on Coffee Naps - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/nutrition/coffee-nap#what-it-is&quot;&gt;https://www.healthline.com/nutrition/coffee-nap#what-it-is&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK大多数电子产品商店提供免费的电子产品回收。你永远不应该扔掉你的旧电子产品。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是ysk。扔掉废旧电子产品对环境极为不利。
大多数回收中心对接受电子产品收费。像Microcenter
和百思买(Best Buy)等商店会免费接收你的破损技术。这意味着像
电池、电脑、屏幕、电缆等。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p9mess/ysk_most_electronics_stores_offer_free/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p9mess/ysk_most_electronics_stores_offer_free/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 15:51:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why ysk: Throwing away used electronics is extremely bad for the environment. Most recycling centers charge for accepting electronics. Stores like Microcenter and Best Buy will take your broken tech for free. That means things like batteries, computers, screens, cables etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你在安卓系统上注册订阅，请用Google play支付。]]></title><description><![CDATA[当你在安卓设备上注册一个订阅服务时，很多时候
你可以选择用Google Play支付。

为什么是YSK：当你想取消订阅时，你可以通过Google play取消它，而且不会终止。
你可以通过Google Play取消订阅，直到你必须再次付款的那一天，它才会结束订阅。
再次。它允许你...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p7pwkc/ysk_if_you_sign_up_for_a_subscription_on_android/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p7pwkc/ysk_if_you_sign_up_for_a_subscription_on_android/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 06:57:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you sign up for a subscription service on an Android device, often times you get the option to pay with Google play.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: When you want to cancel cancel subscription, you can cancel it through Google play and it won&amp;#39;t end the subscription until the day you have to pay again. It allows you to bypass the rule some apps have in place that ends your benefits as soon as you cancel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK洗完澡后，特别是在热的情况下，你的四肢会比平时重得多，这并不是因为它们 "吸收 "了水分。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么YSK：避免措手不及可以防止事故和伤害。你已经
你在浴缸里盯着手机太久了，当你终于
当你决定站起来走出去时，你的肌肉还不适应腿部更大的重量。
你的肌肉不习惯你的腿的更大重量，你有可能滑倒并受伤......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p9lx2t/ysk_after_a_bath_especially_if_hot_your_limbs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p9lx2t/ysk_after_a_bath_especially_if_hot_your_limbs/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 01:37:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: avoid being caught off-guard can prevent accidents and injuries.
You&amp;#39;ve been in your tub for a bit too long staring at your phone, and when you finally decide to stand up and get out, your muscles are not used to the greater weight of your legs, and you can potentially slip and hurt yourself. Same with the arms.
The reason is not because your skin somehow gets soaked in water and weights more, like I thought for a long time.
The reason is because the water&amp;#39;s heats dilates your blood vessels, and more blood can circulate in your limbs. This helps alleviate sore muscles and such because the blood can heal them much quicker with increased access.
Be aware that the increased blood flow will come mainly from your brain and heart, which in turn makes your weaker and slower, therefore much more prone to accidents.
Always make sure to assess the weight and hold to some firm surface when you&amp;#39;re standing up.
Cheers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你在美国，而且你有一个残疾儿童，Shriners将免费为你的孩子治疗。他们将承担100%的医疗费用、预约期间的酒店住宿、前往预约地点的汽油费、前往预约地点的车费以及住院期间所需的食物。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：如果你在经济上有困难，你可能觉得你没有
希望为你的孩子提供他们需要的医疗服务，特别是如果你太穷，买不起保险，但收入太高，没有资格获得医疗补助。
特别是如果你太穷，买不起保险，但收入太高，没有资格享受医疗补助。Shriners
会提供帮助。

我最近发布了一张我的孩子和他的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p9nmh5/ysk_if_you_are_in_the_usa_and_you_have_a_child/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p9nmh5/ysk_if_you_are_in_the_usa_and_you_have_a_child/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:45:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: if you are struggling financially, you might feel like you have no hopes to get your child the medical care they need, especially if you are too poor to afford insurance but make too much to qualify for Medicaid. The Shriners will help. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently posted a photo of my child and his prosthetics (it ended up being deleted but here’s the pic: &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/jd3WxAB&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/a/jd3WxAB&lt;/a&gt; ) I was asked countless times how we afforded 5 pairs of prosthetics for our child who is only 5 years old and honestly? We have not paid one dime for his team of specialists. When he was first born, we were dirt poor. We were just a couple kids who suddenly had a disabled child and it was terrifying. Thankfully we had a pediatrician who wrote a referral to the Shriners and our sons entire future opened up. We lived 6 hours from the closest hospital but they had volunteers (known as Shriners) pick us up and take us to the doctor appointment and then drive us home the same day. If you keep your receipts for the food you buy on the way, they will reimburse you. If you live too far to make a trip in on day, they will pay for your hotel. They really just want to help children and that’s why you should know about them!!! Now that my husband and I are more well off, we don’t request assistance for anything but the actual medical bills. They pay 100%, even if you don’t have insurance. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope this helps someone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：学习障碍与学习困难的意思不一样!]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：这样我们就能了解到神经分化的差异。
人们可以利用这一点来获得他们或他们可能认识的其他人的帮助。
可能认识的人需要的帮助。

我的资料来源如下。轻度、中度、重度学习障碍
差异 |...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p9idd3/ysk_learning_disabilities_do_not_mean_the_same/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p9idd3/ysk_learning_disabilities_do_not_mean_the_same/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 20:58:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: So that we can learn about the differences in neuro-divergent conditions and people can use this to get help that they or someone else they might know needs based on this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My sources are as follows:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthyplace.com/neurodevelopmental-disorders/intellectual-disability/mild-moderate-severe-intellectual-disability-differences&quot;&gt;Mild, Moderate, Severe Learning Disability Differences | HealthyPlace&lt;/a&gt; ;   &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.readandspell.com/types-of-learning-difficulties#what-is-a-learning-difficulty?&quot;&gt;5 Types of learning difficulties and how to help (readandspell.com)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learning disabilities (aka Intellectual disabilities)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason learning disabilities are referred to as also intellectual disabilities is because IQ is a component in diagnosis (you can&amp;#39;t have an IQ of 90+ to have one), as well as the ability to learn and apply  conceptual, social, and practical life skills. Below is a table where I explain the criteria for the four different levels of learning disabilities someone can have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Type of Learning/Intellectual disabiltity&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Diagnostic criteria&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Mild Intellectual disability&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;IQ 50 to 70; Slower than typical in all developmental areas; No unusual physical characteristics; Able to learn practical life skills; Attains reading and math skills up to grade levels 3 to 6; Able to blend in socially; Functions in daily life&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Moderate Intellectual disability&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;IQ 35 to 49; Noticeable developmental delays (i.e. speech, motor skills); May have physical signs of impairment (i.e. thick tongue); Can communicate in basic, simple ways; Able to learn basic health and safety skills; Can complete self-care activities; Can travel alone to nearby, familiar places&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Severe Intellectual disability&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;IQ 20 to 34; Considerable delays in development; Understands speech, but little ability to communicate; Able to learn daily routines; May learn very simple self-care; Needs direct supervision in social situations&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Profound Intellectual disability&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;IQ less than 20; Significant developmental delays in all areas; Obvious physical and congenital abnormalities; Requires close supervision; Requires attendant to help in self-care activities; May respond to physical and social activities; Not capable of independent living&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learning difficulties&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A learning difficulty is a condition that can cause an individual to experience problems in a traditional classroom learning context. It may interfere with literacy skills development and math/maths and can also affect memory, ability to focus and organizational skills. No two individuals with a learning difficulty are exactly alike and many conditions, such as dyslexia, attention deficit hyperactive disorder, dyscalculia, and dysgraphia, exist on a wide-spectrum. To be diagnosed, you must have specific issues that do not correlate with what would be expected of your overall IQ. See my table below to learn about the most common learning difficulties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Types of learning difficulties&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Definitions&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Dyslexia&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Individuals who struggle with dyslexia can have issues with reading, writing or spelling or any combination of them.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Dyscalculia&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Individuals who struggle with dyscalculia have difficulty with processing numbers, whether that be basic arithmetic, deciding the approach to take on a mathematical problem, sequencing numbers and understanding spatial reasoning.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Dysgraphia&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Individuals who struggle with dysgraphia have a hard time with writing and may produce text that is illegible&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;ADHD&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;There are three types of ADHD (ADHD-Primarily Inattentive; ADHD-Primarily Hyperactive/Impulsive; and ADHD-Combined Presentation).&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Dyspraxia&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;A motor-skills difficulty that can affect a learner’s ability to write by hand, and may impact on planning skills&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t know how useful this could be for anyone, but as someone with dyscalculia, Asperger&amp;#39;s (Autism) and ADHD-Combined Presentation, I get really frustrated when people call my difficulties by the wrong name!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：喝母乳会感染艾滋病毒]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：所以最近我看到这个帖子
[https://www.reddit.com/r/Unexpected/comments/p9cuuc/shes_got_some_milk/?utm_source=share&utm_medium=ios_app&utm_name=iossmf]
我很震惊，一个女人居然在喝陌生人的母乳。
大多数评论都是来自理所当然的厌恶的人，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p9ina3/ysk_you_can_contract_hiv_by_drinking_breast_milk/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p9ina3/ysk_you_can_contract_hiv_by_drinking_breast_milk/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 20:33:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: So recently I saw &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Unexpected/comments/p9cuuc/shes_got_some_milk/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=ios_app&amp;amp;utm_name=iossmf&quot;&gt;this post&lt;/a&gt; and was horrified that a woman was actually drinking a strangers breast milk. Most of the comments were from rightfully disgusted people, but some people were actually saying they wouldn’t mind getting sprayed with a strangers breast milk! HIV can be spread through breast milk and I’m shocked at how many people in those comments seemed oblivious to this fact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：卡车公司总是要对坠落物负责。]]></title><description><![CDATA["对落物不负责任 "不是法律上的免责声明，而是一种
它是阻止受害方行使其起诉权的一种不诚实的方式。

你不能单方面赔偿自己对公众造成的损害；潜在的受损害方必须免除你的责任。
潜在的受损方必须自愿免除你的责任，作为对...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p9icx8/ysk_truck_companies_are_always_responsible_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p9icx8/ysk_truck_companies_are_always_responsible_for/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 19:42:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Not responsible for falling objects&amp;quot; is not a legal disclaimer, it&amp;#39;s a dishonest way of deterring injured parties from exercising their right to sue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can&amp;#39;t unilaterally indemnify yourself for damages to the public; a potential damaged party has to relieve you voluntarily as consideration for some reciprocal transaction. There are ways to create implicit consent, but no private party has the ability to give or withhold consent to a stranger&amp;#39;s use of a public roadway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Too many people allow themselves to be misled and intimidated into waiving their legal rights. The ony person who can tell you what your rights are is your lawyer. Not the police, not some asshole with a sign, not opposing counsel, and definitely not me. So if you suffer damages and a conflict arises, call a lawyer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：抗抑郁药在少数情况下会导致永久性勃起功能障碍或其他性功能障碍。]]></title><description><![CDATA[特别是SSRI类型的抗抑郁药可以引起PSSD，即永久性的性功能障碍。
的副作用（包括男性和女性）。它们也可能有长期的副作用。
所以，如果你在停药后几个月都有影响，不要惊慌失措。
因为它们仍然可能消失。但是要去看泌尿科医生或...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p9412f/ysk_antidepressants_can_in_rare_cases_cause/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p9412f/ysk_antidepressants_can_in_rare_cases_cause/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 10:53:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Specifically antidepressants that are SSRI type can cause PSSD, permanent sexual side effects (for both men and women). They can also have long-lasting side effects, so don&amp;#39;t freak out if you have had effects for months after stopping, because they could still go away. But do see a urologist or endocrinologist, or other specialized doctor, who you know knows about PSSD. That way they can help figure out what is wrong with you and what the next steps are. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, YSK: that doctors and psychiatrists are specialists in their own field. Most psychiatrists do &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; specialize in therapy. What this means is there may be therapy options for your disorder which you may be unaware of. For instance many psychiatrists (as opposed to psychologists) will prescribe SSRIs for OCD, and not ask whether the patient is doing exposure therapy (which is the golden standard for OCD treatment). This is to no fault of their own; it is just outside of their speciality which is to know about &lt;em&gt;medication&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Talk over your different health options with a doctor or second opinion if you believe you are being prescribed medication that does not fit your needs. However NEVER stop a medication without medical supervision, that can be extremely dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://rxisk.org/post-ssri-sexual-dysfunction-pssd/&quot;&gt;https://rxisk.org/post-ssri-sexual-dysfunction-pssd/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/28778697/&quot;&gt;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/28778697/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I realized as soon as I wrote this that I should have clarified in the title that PSSD can be both men &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; women (and all genders). Sorry folks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，为什么新闻机构拒绝在标题中使用 "强奸 "或 "谋杀 "的术语，因为这可能会导致法律纠纷。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：当新闻中说有人 "强迫______与他们发生性关系 "或 "据称在交通事故中杀害了______"时，人们似乎会不合理地愤怒。
"强迫___与他们发生性关系 "或 "据称在交通事故中杀害了___"或其他什么的时候，人们似乎会无端地愤怒。
事件 "或其他什么。这是因为使用 "强奸 "或 "谋杀 "这样的字眼相当于公开指控。
相当于公开指控。如果被告后来被发现没有...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p92z4o/ysk_the_reason_why_news_organisations_refuse_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p92z4o/ysk_the_reason_why_news_organisations_refuse_to/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 05:14:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: People seem to get unreasonably angry when the news says someone &amp;quot;forced ___ to have sex with them&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;allegedly killed ___ in a traffic incident&amp;quot; or whatnot. This is because using the words &amp;quot;raped&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;murdered&amp;quot; is tantamount to a public accusation. If the accused is later found not guilty in court, then they could sue the news organisation for libel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is why after someone is found guilty, then you start seeing those words on the news, because they are now legally judged to have committed that offence, and it&amp;#39;s not libel to state the fact anymore. But using those words before they&amp;#39;re found guilty is legally risky.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 在药房购买的东西将在你的银行对账单上显示为ATM提款。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK: 我在一家大银行的反欺诈部门工作，我每天都会接到很多电话。
我每天都会接到很多人的电话，报告自动取款机上的欺诈性交易，这些交易的金额是随机的。
通常不能从ATM机上提取的随机金额。在法律上，药房不能说他们是一个
药房，所以所做的交易不会显示为药房。节省...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p91w18/ysk_purchases_made_at_dispensaries_will_show_up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p91w18/ysk_purchases_made_at_dispensaries_will_show_up/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 01:12:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I work in the fraud department at a major bank and I get SO MANY calls daily from people reporting fraudulent ATM transactions with random amounts you normally can&amp;#39;t withdraw from an ATM. 
Legally, dispensaries cannot say they are a dispensary so transactions made will not show as such. 
Save yourself the hassle of filing a claim and having to get a new card by remembering this the next time you make a purchase at your favorite spot or when you see a transaction at an ATM pop up that you may not recognize and you&amp;#39;ve shopped at a dispensary recently :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK你可以把新鲜的面包冷冻起来，需要时用烤箱或空气炸锅重新加热。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK。

当你购买新鲜面包时，往往有太多的面包，特别是如果你住在
独自一人。如果你把面包放在室温下，它很快就会变坏（主要是指
主要是指质地和味道）。)

如果你把它放在冰箱里，许多个月后你可以把它拿出来，重新加热。
就会有酥脆的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p8uu51/ysk_you_can_freeze_fresh_bread_and_reheat_it_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p8uu51/ysk_you_can_freeze_fresh_bread_and_reheat_it_in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 18:31:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you buy fresh bread there is often too much of it, especially if you live alone. If you leave the bread at room temperature it will soon go bad (mostly talking about texture and taste).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you put it in a freezer, you can take it out after many months, reheat it, and have crispy slices that are still soft on the inside with most of the taste and texture preserved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你可以用奶酪切片机在面包上涂抹冷黄油]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK:冷黄油在面包上涂抹均匀是件很麻烦的事，而且通常都会破损。
但切黄油可以得到均匀的片状物，你可以把它们放在面包上。
覆盖在面包上，所以你不需要涂抹黄油，只需要把黄油片放在面包上。

对不起，英语不是我的第一语言]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p7r0qq/ysk_you_can_use_cheese_slicer_to_apply_cold/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/p7r0qq/ysk_you_can_use_cheese_slicer_to_apply_cold/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 17:16:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:Cold butter is pain in the butt to spread evenly on bread,and usually the bread breaks, but slicing butter gets you even slices that you can place over the bread, so you dont need to spread the butter,just put the butter slices&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry english not my first language&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>