<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 19:20:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如何在最后一刻攥紧你的作业，专业拖延者指南]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么YSK：你的作业很快就要完成了，这将有助于你按时完成作业或获得成绩。
或获得成绩。

这不是关于长期拖延的问题。如果你能停止，就尽快停止。
这些技巧只在一个铰链中起作用，过度使用它们会给你带来麻烦，因为它们每次都会变得
每次都不太有效。

3个技巧+...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/np5qt5/ysk_how_to_clutch_your_assignments_last_min/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/np5qt5/ysk_how_to_clutch_your_assignments_last_min/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 20:10:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;why YSK: you have an assignment due very soon this will help you finish them on time or get the grade. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;this isn&amp;#39;t about long-term procrastination. if you can stop, stop asap. these tips only work in a hinge and overusing them will get you in trouble as they get less effective every time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 tips + consumables&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;don&amp;#39;t panic. you panic, you cant work. you think of the large pile of homework ahead of you, the three essays and exams. I don&amp;#39;t care if you have it due in 5 mins. if you panic you won&amp;#39;t start working until much later. also, most emotions can lead to panic, so try and suppress them. this isn&amp;#39;t about finishing your homework in a healthy way, but about not handing it in late.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;decide the compromise right now. if it&amp;#39;s a test, the content you studied the most before is gonna have to go. if it&amp;#39;s a project, skip on the least marked criteria. have an action plan that gets you somewhere on the deadline then fix the compromises. fixing something, even if it&amp;#39;s trash is a lot easier than working on a blank slate because it gives you the illusion that you&amp;#39;re almost there. but understand you can also make a compromise in time. if you put this in mind, however, it leads to more procrastination. you make the compromise at the end. maybe skip the class before it&amp;#39;s due. pull an allnighter. make an excuse for why it&amp;#39;s late, its gonna get scummy and degrading but gain, this about clutching the grade.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;don&amp;#39;t compromise sleep. you lose sleep and you lose your sanity. don&amp;#39;t get me wrong, all-nighters are okay in the case of a single project which you can rest afterward, but an all-nighter takes time to regenerate from, ruining your sleep schedule. this doesn&amp;#39;t work in the areas of stress where you need to procrastinate such as finals. you will trick yourself into thinking it&amp;#39;s an easy compromise, it&amp;#39;s not. in long periods of time, it will destroy your sanity, you will panic, and everything will fall apart. unless you have the next 2 days to regenerate, make sure you get 5 hours minimum every day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;last but not least and most importantly, use consumables wisely. I&amp;#39;m referring to coffee, that music that gets you hyped, alarms, maybe a drink or food that you associate with a clutch night. they are very powerful. the first time you drink coffee, its effect is insane. when I first listened to a hype song, I felt like on my way to Valhalla finishing the homework. they&amp;#39;re incredibly useful and are your secret weapons. if you over procrastinate and use them all the time, they start to feel normal. associate them with clutch situations and only use them then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;now go finish the assignment NOW you&amp;#39;ve wasted too much time reading&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你对溺水的心理想象可能是错误的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[嗨，r/YouShouldKnow [/r/YouShouldKnow]! 我做了5年的救生员。
最终以我的方式管理我所在城市最大的水上设施，在任何时候都有20多名救生员在我手下工作。
20多名救生员在任何时候都在我手下工作。随着阵亡将士纪念日
即将到来（我的组织的夏季季节的开始）和...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nnj14f/ysk_your_mental_imagery_of_drownings_is_probably/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nnj14f/ysk_your_mental_imagery_of_drownings_is_probably/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 12:07:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi, &lt;a href=&quot;/r/YouShouldKnow&quot;&gt;r/YouShouldKnow&lt;/a&gt;! I was a lifeguard for 5 years, eventually working my way up to running my city’s biggest aquatic facility with 20+ lifeguards on staff working under me at any given time. With Memorial Day coming up (the start of the summer season for my organization) and plenty of people looking to hit the beach or pool after missing out last year, there’s going to be lots of inexperienced swimmers back in the water… many of whom haven’t swam for at least two years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I ask people what they think a drowning victim looks like, they usually describe to me &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HWgONcX5VhQ&quot;&gt;something that looks like this&lt;/a&gt; - someone shouting for help, raising their arms high, and making a lot of noise as they splash in the water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a dramatic and somewhat inaccurate representation invented by Hollywood. Real active drownings tend to be much, much quieter events. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a video with sound of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=beNheoRRdKk&amp;amp;t=10s&quot;&gt;a girl who is actively drowning&lt;/a&gt; before a lifeguard rescues her - notice how little sound she makes, and how little time it takes for her head to sink underwater. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Active drowning is a state of panic in which someone is struggling to keep their head above water. A person who is actively drowning will instinctively do whatever they can to keep their head above water and will try to take in as much air as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: An actively drowning person won’t have the time nor breath to call for air, because every fiber of their being is focused on trying to keep their lungs full. I have seen many parents think their kids were completely fine when in reality, their kids were distressed or actively drowning less than five feet behind them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than trying to listen for sounds of drowning, keep on the lookout for people who are: struggling to keep their head above water and/or making big sweeping motions in an attempt to move water under them. If there is little to no pattern for how long their head is above water vs below water, there’s a good chance they’re actively drowning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s another video (also with sound) of &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/nANNAtq8Bpw?t=5&quot;&gt;a child actively drowning&lt;/a&gt; - again, I want to point your attention to how little sound the victim makes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What if I see someone who is drowning?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So say you’re a drowning-spotting expert now. You’re hanging out at the beach/pool, you&amp;#39;re soaking some sun, and you successfully spot someone drowning - what do you do now?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For many people their first instinct is to dash into the water and help the victim - particularly if they are a child and/or relative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is this the part where I tell you that it’s a bad idea? Well… maybe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In shallow water, it’s totally fine to mosey on over and pick up a child that’s struggling. If it’s deep water, then it’s a different story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please listen to what I’m about to say, because I cannot stress this enough - if you spot someone actively drowning in deep water, do not just jump in to try to save them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A person who is actively drowning is literally not thinking. They are acting out of pure instinct to push whatever objects they can underneath their body to stay above water, whether it be driftwood, floaties, or another human being.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have seen parents jump into 12-feet deep water trying to save their struggling child, only to become a victim themselves when their child inevitably push the parent’s head underwater to try to stay afloat. PEOPLE WHO ARE ACTIVELY DROWNING WILL ALSO DROWN YOU.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me say that again - PEOPLE WHO ARE ACTIVELY DROWNING WILL ALSO DROWN YOU.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me let you in on a secret - you know the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.americanlifeguard.net/Images/40ComfortGuard.jpg&quot;&gt;ring buoys&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://marydonahue.org/facultyfiles.deanza.edu/images/donahuemary//sheperdscrookonwall.jpg&quot;&gt;shepherds hook&lt;/a&gt; you see hanging on the pool fence? Those are there for you. Many lifeguards aren’t even trained to use them, because it’s far quicker and easier for us to use ourselves and our rescue tubes to do rescues. Health codes in basically every US state, however, require pools to have them, because basically anyone can use them to help someone who is actively drowning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So to get back to the question - what should you do if someone in front of you is actively drowning in deep water?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First off, if any lifeguards are nearby, direct their attention to the drowning person. Waving one arm over your head and pointing to the victim with your other arm while looking straight at a lifeguard is usually sufficient, and shouting “active drowning” will definitely grab the attention of any competent lifeguards on duty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But what if there are no lifeguards? Maybe I’m at a river, or a private beach, or it’s a “swim at my own risk” area.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The answer is that you should first make sure that you’re safely anchored to the shore - usually by holding onto a pole/tree with a hand, or by lying flat on the ground. Failing to anchor yourself could result in the victim pulling you into the water! Once safely anchored, you should extend anything you can to them for them to pull themselves to shore. Either the ring buoy or the shepherds hook that I mentioned above, a beach towel, your shirt, a tree branch - anything that the victim can grab onto and pull themselves on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What if they’re too far away, or I don’t have anything I can use to safely pull them in?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re unable to locate a rope or long object that you can extend to the victim, then you’ll need to do two things - a.) try to throw buoyant objects for them to make use of (like beach balls, life jackets, or floaties), and b.) call 911 (or your local emergency number). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll say it again - it is not safe for you to attempt to help someone who is actively drowning in deep water if you don’t have any available tools to assist you. If you are unable to help someone who is actively drowning, then you should call your local emergency services as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a brief period of time, active drowning victims will tire themselves out. At this point in time, they will likely lose consciousness and go limp. If someone in front of you is actively drowning in deep water, and you don’t have any tools you can use to bring them to shore safely, it is much safer for you to wait for them to “go passive” before bringing them in than it is for you to assist them while they’re still conscious. You can help someone who is unconscious, but you can’t help someone if you’re unconscious yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s cold, it’s heartbreaking, and it’s painful to type these words, but it’s also how you can guarantee that one drowning person doesn’t turn into two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But don’t let me end this on a downer - here are some tips to help keep you and your loved ones safe!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stay within arm’s reach of your group, and especially keep track of beginner/poor/non-swimmers. If you’re a parent, it is your duty to keep watch of your children. Lifeguards are not there to babysit - they’re there to enforce rules and respond to emergencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Take a break at least once an hour to rest and rehydrate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whenever you enter a waterfront, pool, or aquatic facility, try to spot any ring buoys, shepherd hooks, or other safety equipment that you can run to if an emergency occurs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Take it slow - stay in shallow areas until you’re confident that you’re able to tackle deeper areas safely. Do not pressure friends or family to enter areas they feel uncomfortable to enter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please listen to your lifeguards, if present - I promise you, we make our patrons’ safety our utmost priority… even if it means we have to be killjoys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please do whatever you can to have a fun and safe time out in the water!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer - I am not a medical professional nor am I liable for any injuries that may occur as a result of you following this advice. Please exercise your best judgement when in an emergency. When in doubt, call 911.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：苹果公司在健康应用程序中有更漂亮的报警铃声]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：我们中的大多数人都使用时钟应用程序作为早晨的闹钟，其蹩脚的铃声选项只会吓醒我们，让我们讨厌这种声音。
铃声选项只会把我们吓醒，让我们讨厌这种声音。
但我最近发现，在健康应用程序（iPhone自带）中，有一个睡眠部分，你可以设置你的睡眠时间表，并选择你的睡眠时间。
但我最近发现，在健康应用程序（iPhone自带）中，有一个睡眠部分，你可以设置你的睡眠时间表，并选择...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nm0vaz/ysk_apple_has_much_nicer_alarm_ringtones_in_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nm0vaz/ysk_apple_has_much_nicer_alarm_ringtones_in_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 09:34:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Most of us use the clock app for our morning alarms, with crappy ringtone options that only scare us awake and make us hate the sound, but I recently found that in the health app (which comes with the iPhone) there is a sleep section where you can set your sleeping schedule, and choose from some amazing alarm sounds like Helios and first light, that are meant for waking up to. They start slow and have some really calming tunes that could be from a video game soundtrack. I 100% recommend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK你的VHS磁带和家庭电影的寿命很短，需要转移来保存它们]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：VHS磁带并不意味着可以永远持续下去，每过一天就意味着你的珍贵记忆永远消失一天。
你的宝贵记忆就会永远消失。旧的VHS磁带和
家庭电影面临着被霉变、老化和带状物破坏的危险。
变质。世界各地都有公司会对旧录像带和家庭电影进行处理。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nn75g5/ysk_your_vhs_tapes_and_home_movies_have_a_short/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nn75g5/ysk_your_vhs_tapes_and_home_movies_have_a_short/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 22:55:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK :  VHS tapes were not meant to last forever and every day that goes by is one day closer to your precious memories being lost forever. Old VHS tapes and home movies are in danger of being destroyed by mold, age and ribbon deterioration. There are companies all over the world that will transfer your VHS tapes to a more long term options. Even if you find the ribbons have mold or damage there are companies that can repair and transfer your movies. It&amp;#39;s much cheaper transferring tapes in good condition than it is to transfer moldy or damaged tapes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 癫痫治疗]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：每当你看到有人癫痫发作时，周围的人都在惊慌失措。
时，你必须告诉他们都不要靠近，因为拥挤会使人惊慌失措，使人难以呼吸。
使患者惊慌失措并使其难以呼吸。接下来，你让他们躺在自己的
这样他们就能呼吸并排出泡沫，因为这可能会...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nmr2h5/ysk_seizure_treatment/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nmr2h5/ysk_seizure_treatment/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 18:20:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Whenever you see someone having a seizure whilst there are people around them panicking, you have to tell them all to stay clear as crowding will make the person panic and make it hard to breathe. Next, you lay them on their side so they can breathe and get rid of foam because that can obstruct breathing. Finally, calmly comfort them and help them breathe whilst the seizure runs its course. On average a seizure lasts between 30-2:30 seconds but if the seizure persists for over 5 minutes seek immediate medical attention as this circumstance can be a serious problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：与输入数据建立人工智能系统有关的验证码请求不一定知道所有的正确答案。你可以给它提供不正确的答案，虽然你会失败几次，但它最终会让你通过，因为它不知道所有的图像是山/自行车/汽车等。]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是对最近YSK讨论CAPTCHA请求的回应，该请求被用于
帮助建立人工智能系统。

为什么是YSK：因为，如果你不想参与给一些免费的劳动
构建人工智能的服务，我想这是你的权利。
你有权拒绝。

这可能...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nmsc8c/ysk_captcha_requests_linked_to_feeding_data_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nmsc8c/ysk_captcha_requests_linked_to_feeding_data_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 14:50:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is in response to a recent YSK discussing CAPTCHA requests that are used to help build out AI systems.      &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Because, if you do not want to participate in giving free labor to some service to build an AI to be used for who knows what purpose, I imagine it is your right to refuse.      &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This may sound like extra work, because it is, but you can get rather quick at it after doing it a few times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：一般的住宅烤箱很少是准确的。一个售后的炉内温度计是必要的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：你的烤箱面板上的温标是印在一块金属上的
在一条生产线上，并不真正准确。烘烤和烹饪的核心
温度是有原因的。你的失败的日本乳酪蛋糕或过熟的松饼但
但中间没有熟透的松饼可能并不完全是你的错。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nmqvkj/ysk_that_the_average_residential_oven_is_rarely/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nmqvkj/ysk_that_the_average_residential_oven_is_rarely/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 12:03:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: your oven face plate temperature scale is printed on a piece of metal in a production line that&amp;#39;s not really accurate. Baking and cooking have core temps for a reason. Your flopped Japanese cheesecake or overcooked muffins but undercooked in the middle may not be entirely your fault.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 为了避免感到被问题所害，你应该采用英雄心态。游戏教得非常好，而且有研究支持。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在最近举行的全球人机交互会议（CHI）上，一位人工智能
研究人员介绍了一个新的免费应用程序[http://betwixt.life/]，作为心理健康创新的下一个浪潮。
心理健康创新的下一波浪潮，它被描述为游戏 "生命线 "和 "林中之王 "的交叉产物。
生命线》和《指环王》的交叉。

它背后的想法显然是来自...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nm85br/ysk_to_avoid_feeling_victimized_by_problems_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nm85br/ysk_to_avoid_feeling_victimized_by_problems_you/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 15:56:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the recent global conference on human-computer interaction (CHI), an AI researcher presented &lt;a href=&quot;http://betwixt.life/&quot;&gt;a new free app&lt;/a&gt; as the next wave in mental health innovation and it was described as a cross between the game Lifeline and Lord of the Rings. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea behind it apparently came from research in narrative identity, which found that the people who improved most from therapy and achieved sustained better health, were able to adopt a hero mindset. Basically, they managed to see themselves as characters in an epic story overcoming obstacles along their journey. This subtle mind shift allowed them to reframe their problems as challenges that are part and parcel of the hero’s journey, that can be figured out and that provide opportunities for growth. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adopting a hero mindset increases your sense of agency in the face of struggle, allowing you to change your perspective and feel empowered to tackle the problems life throws at you. If you manage to see yourself as the hero of an epic story (even a little bit), you won’t feel victimised by the setbacks along the way, because your willingness to confront obstacles is precisely what defines you as a hero in the first place. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously I’m not saying you should engage in wishful thinking. This is just a subtle, simple mental shift to think about your life that’s been shown to link with bigger and more lasting improvements in therapy. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SOURCES:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AI researcher’s paper on the future of mental health chatbots: &lt;a href=&quot;http://francisconunes.me/RealizingAIinHealthcareWS/papers/Harmon2021.pdf&quot;&gt;http://francisconunes.me/RealizingAIinHealthcareWS/papers/Harmon2021.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The app (it’s free) based on this research: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.betwixt.life/&quot;&gt;https://www.betwixt.life/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Narrative identity research mentioned in the post: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/269603657_Narrative_Identity&quot;&gt;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/269603657_Narrative_Identity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你的宠物吃了有潜在危险的东西，你可以联系YSK的动物毒物控制号码。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：当涉及到意外中毒时，时间可能是非常关键的。你
你可以与ASPCA毒物控制中心的成员联系，他们可以指导你做任何必要的事情，或者你需要把你的宠物送到兽医那里。
你可以做任何必要的事情，或者如果你需要带你的宠物去看兽医。I
不幸的是，昨天在我的狗得病后，我不得不利用这个方法。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nl0bar/ysk_that_there_is_an_animal_poison_control_number/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nl0bar/ysk_that_there_is_an_animal_poison_control_number/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 21:24:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Time can be very critical when it comes to an accidental poisoning. You are connected to a member of the ASPCA Poison Control who can walk you through any necessary things you can do or if you need to take your pet to the vet. I unfortunately had to utilize this yesterday after my dog got into  a slow release fertilizer (it smells sweet by comparison to normal fertilizer) and as I was taking him to the vet, I was able to call them and they were able to see if there were any specific reactions that could happen as well as assuring me that the active chemicals were not life threatening&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aspca.org/pet-care/animal-poison-control&quot;&gt;The number is  (888) 426-4435.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 你的图书馆不仅仅有书]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：最近的这个评论
[https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/nkwaqy/whats_a_free_resource_available_to_everyone_that/gzf3x0l?utm_source=share&utm_medium=web2x&context=3]
激励我去我的图书馆。除了 "书"（和一个性感的图书管理员），我的主要图书馆还有一些课程，如艺术课程。
我的主要图书馆有一些课程，如艺术...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nlep8l/ysk_your_library_has_more_than_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nlep8l/ysk_your_library_has_more_than_books/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 15:42:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/nkwaqy/whats_a_free_resource_available_to_everyone_that/gzf3x0l?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web2x&amp;amp;context=3&quot;&gt;This recent comment&lt;/a&gt; inspired me to go to my library.  Besides &amp;quot;books&amp;quot; (and one hottie librarian), my main library has classes such as art classes, laser cutting and computer courses; you can check out (location-dependent) sports equipment like tennis rackets and kayaks, kitchen appliances, CDs/DVDs, use 3-D printers, even telescopes.  If there&amp;#39;s something you can&amp;#39;t find, they might be able to order it for you.  [this is in the US and very location-dependent]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在食品标签上，列出的第一种成分以重量计含量最大，列出的最后一种成分以重量计含量最小。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK。

例如，下面是达能的达能底部水果的成分表
酸奶
[https://www.danoneawayfromhome.com/food-service-products/brand-dannon-fruit-on-the-bottom-strawberry-5-3oz/]。

> 牛奶、糖、覆盆子果泥、水、变性食品淀粉、含有少于
>1%的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nkpsr7/ysk_on_food_labels_the_first_ingredient_listed_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nkpsr7/ysk_on_food_labels_the_first_ingredient_listed_is/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 04:29:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, here&amp;#39;s the ingredients list for Danone&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.danoneawayfromhome.com/food-service-products/brand-dannon-fruit-on-the-bottom-strawberry-5-3oz/&quot;&gt;Dannon Fruit on the Bottom Yogurt&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Milk,  Sugar, Raspberry Puree, Water, Modified Food Starch, Contains Less Than  1% Of Kosher Gelatin, Pectin, Vegetable Juice Concentrate (For Color),  Natural Flavor, Calcium Citrate, Vitamin D3, Sodium Citrate, Malic Acid&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As  you can see, &amp;quot;Sugar&amp;quot; comes before &amp;quot;Raspberry Puree&amp;quot;. This means that  there&amp;#39;s more sugar than fruit, and there&amp;#39;s more fruit than natural flavors, and so on...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is especially useful when you want to know how much of an unhealthy ingredient is present in the product. So even when you think  something (like yogurt) might be healthy enough (because you might think that it&amp;#39;s basically &amp;quot;just milk with fruits&amp;quot;), you can just check the food label to see if the product actually is healthy enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bonus tip: When it comes to processed/packaged/canned foods, the less ingredients are on the food label, the healthier the product!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，当使用那些限制你每月只能阅读几篇免费文章的网站时，你可以将文章复制粘贴到一个隐身标签中，以绕过付费墙。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：某些网站，如《纽约时报》，限制用户每月只能阅读3-5篇免费文章，并要求订阅更多文章。
而需要订阅才能阅读更多。通过复制和粘贴链接
到一个隐身标签，你就可以绕过这一点，并可以阅读无限量的
文章。不过，如果你可以的话，最好还是订阅以支持...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nl0k35/ysk_that_when_using_websites_that_limit_you_to_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nl0k35/ysk_that_when_using_websites_that_limit_you_to_a/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 23:34:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Certain sites like the NYTimes limit users to 3-5 free articles a month, and require a subscription to read more. By copying and pasting the link into an incognito tab, you bypass this and can read an unlimited amount of articles. Still, if you can, it&amp;#39;s better to subscribe to support the journalism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，"减少"、"再利用"、"再循环 "这句话是有原因的。不买可回收的东西或重复使用它们比回收更重要。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：回收费用很高，而且有时产品最终会被填埋。
总之
[https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/jun/21/us-plastic-recycling-landfills]。
少买垃圾或自己重复使用东西比回收更有利于环境。
回收。

重复使用一个产品也比...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nkxmsk/ysk_that_the_phrase_reduce_reuse_recycle_is_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nkxmsk/ysk_that_the_phrase_reduce_reuse_recycle_is_in/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 21:43:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Recycling is expensive, and sometimes the product &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/jun/21/us-plastic-recycling-landfills&quot;&gt;ends up in a landfill anyway&lt;/a&gt;. Buying less junk or reusing things yourself are better for the environment than recycling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reusing a product is also better than recycling. Sell or give away old furniture. Use old jelly jars to store leftovers. Refill soap dispensers. Reusing products means buying new stuff less often.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如果你在工作中提前两周通知，即使他们要求你在这两周结束前离开，他们通常也必须支付你工资。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：如果你在发出通知的同一天被送走，你的老板可能会
你的老板可能希望你没有意识到你被拖欠了这笔工资。

如果雇主在他们的合同或雇员手册中规定了通知的要求
手册，那么大多数州（美国）的法律都要求他们支付这两个星期的工资。
周，甚至...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nj76du/ysk_if_you_give_two_weeks_notice_at_work_they/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nj76du/ysk_if_you_give_two_weeks_notice_at_work_they/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 19:06:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: if you get sent away on the same day as giving notice, your boss might be hoping you don’t realize you are owed this pay. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If an employer includes a requirement for notice in their contract or employee handbook then the law in most states (US) require they pay out for those two weeks even if they tell you not to come in to work. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An angry manager, or a job that considers a resigning employee a security risk, does not have to allow the employee to work for two weeks, but must pay them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 你不应该对玩游戏或阅读幻想感到内疚。它们可以教会你一种有价值的心态转变，这种转变得到了研究的支持，并被用于改善心理健康的新工具中]]></title><description><![CDATA[在最近的全球人机交互会议（CHI）上，一位人工智能
研究人员提出了一个新的免费应用程序[http://betwixt.life/]，作为下一波的
心理健康创新的下一个浪潮，它被描述为游戏 "生命线 "和 "指环王 "之间的交叉。
生命线》和《指环王》的交叉。

它背后的想法显然是来自...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nkrlgq/ysk_you_shouldnt_feel_guilty_about_playing_games/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nkrlgq/ysk_you_shouldnt_feel_guilty_about_playing_games/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 18:20:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the recent global conference on human-computer interaction (CHI), an AI researcher presented &lt;a href=&quot;http://betwixt.life/&quot;&gt;a new free app&lt;/a&gt; as the next wave in mental health innovation and it was described as a cross between the game Lifeline and Lord of the Rings. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea behind it apparently came from research in narrative identity, which found that the people who improved most from therapy and achieved sustained better health, were able to adopt a heroic mindset. Basically, they saw themselves more like the heroes of an epic story, overcoming obstacles along the way, and this allowed them to reframe problems as challenges and growth opportunities. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s easy to (be made to) feel guilty for “escaping” your real life through fantasy and video games, but these escapes can also teach you a valuable mindset and help you cope better when you come back to the real world. Game mindset = Growth mindset &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SOURCES:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AI researcher’s paper on the future of mental health chatbots: &lt;a href=&quot;http://francisconunes.me/RealizingAIinHealthcareWS/papers/Harmon2021.pdf&quot;&gt;http://francisconunes.me/RealizingAIinHealthcareWS/papers/Harmon2021.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The app (it’s free) presented at the conference: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.betwixt.life/&quot;&gt;https://www.betwixt.life/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Narrative identity research mentioned in the post: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/269603657_Narrative_Identity&quot;&gt;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/269603657_Narrative_Identity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 蝉不会咬你，它们甚至没有嘴。]]></title><description><![CDATA[蝉不吃东西，它们只在幼虫阶段消耗食物。当它们长大
长成我们所说的蝉时，它们的身体甚至没有 "嘴"。当它们
当它们耗尽能量时，它们会发出最后的死亡叫声，然后死去。所以不要
害怕，它们真的不会咬你 它们确实有一个...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nkm3s5/ysk_cicadas_cant_bite_you_they_dont_even_have/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nkm3s5/ysk_cicadas_cant_bite_you_they_dont_even_have/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 12:47:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cicadas don&amp;#39;t eat; they only consume food in their larval stage. When they grow up into what we call &lt;em&gt;cicadas&lt;/em&gt;, their body does not even have a &amp;quot;mouth&amp;quot;. When they run out of energy, they do some final death cries and drop dead. So don&amp;#39;t be afraid, they literally &lt;em&gt;can&amp;#39;t&lt;/em&gt; bite you! They do have a proboscis for drinking, though. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I heard there is a mass emergence of cicadas in the United States right now and it&amp;#39;s freaking people out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你为Doordash、Uber Eats、Grubhub开车，你应该修改你的保险政策。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：很多人不知道，如果你为这些应用程序提供服务，如果你的应用程序在使用过程中发生事故，你的保险公司不会为你提供赔偿。
如果在你的应用程序运行时发生事故，你的保险公司不会赔偿你。
运行时发生的事故，你的保险公司不会赔偿你。

此外，虽然像Doordash或Grubhub这样的公司有他们自己的责任
保险，但许多司机没有意识到的是，这...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nk163d/ysk_that_if_you_drive_for_doordash_uber_eats/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nk163d/ysk_that_if_you_drive_for_doordash_uber_eats/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 06:50:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  A lot of people don&amp;#39;t know that if you deliver for these apps, your insurance company will not cover you if an accident occurs while your app is running.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, while companies like Doordash or Grubhub have their own liability insurance, what many drivers don&amp;#39;t realize, is that this does not benefit YOU in any way. This only covers damage you cause to another party - bodily injury, property damage, etc.   Whatever damage you incur on the job - even if it was 100% the other guy&amp;#39;s fault - has to come out of your own pocket.  As far as you are concerned, you are uninsured in that moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;((Just came back to make an edit.  The liability insurance policy is going to vary between what company you use - Postmates is going to differ from Grubhub which will differ from Doordash))&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So even though you have to provide some proof of insurance in order to sign up for these apps, that is not because they want to see that you have coverage while you&amp;#39;re driving FOR them.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some insurance companies have what&amp;#39;s called &amp;quot;Rideshare gap.&amp;quot; What this means is that you have coverage for when you are waiting for an order.  Once you have an order, and have the delivery items in your possession, the app&amp;#39;s insurance kicks in (again, this only covers other people).  This means you have insurance coverage during the &amp;quot;gap&amp;quot; between orders, but you, personally, have ZERO coverage during an active delivery.  If you choose Rideshare Gap as an add-on to your policy, it&amp;#39;s another $5-15 a month, which is basically a &amp;quot;better than nothing&amp;quot; option, but not the best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some people have found that their insurance company didn&amp;#39;t provide any kind of coverage, and as a result they had to change insurance providers.  In some cases, they have been involved in an accident and decided to omit the fact that their app was on.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this omission is insurance fraud.   Many car insurance companies will actually contact these  delivery apps, and if they find out that you were signed in to the app during the accident - even if it was a straight up hit and run that you caught on camera - they will not cover you.  Moreover, you may be hit with a felony insurance fraud charge, as you did not disclose that you were working during the accident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thing is, both your insurance company, AND the delivery app you work for, have your social security number, they have your license plate, they have a lot of the some personal information about you.  You might as well not lie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moral of the story&lt;/strong&gt;:  if you use any rideshare or delivery apps, make sure you are covered with some sort of Rideshare policy.  If you are not covered, DON&amp;#39;T LIE if you are in an accident.  Just eat the cost and learn whatever lesson you need to learn.  At that point, you&amp;#39;re better off learning the lesson of a totaled car, than learning the lesson of felony insurance fraud charges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 大多数冰箱/冰柜可以安全地侧向运输]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：我知道有很多人抱怨说他们在做完这个之后把冰箱弄坏了。
我知道有很多人抱怨他们这样做后把冰箱弄坏了，甚至有更多的人在搬家时选择留下/卖掉他们的冰箱。
更多的人在搬家时选择留下/卖掉他们的冰箱，因为它的运输是多么的麻烦。
运输的麻烦。了解冰箱/冰柜的工作原理可以为你省钱...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/njsj9t/ysk_most_fridgesfreezers_are_safe_to_transport_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/njsj9t/ysk_most_fridgesfreezers_are_safe_to_transport_on/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 12:46:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I know a lot of people who have complained about how they broke their fridge after they did this, and know even more people who choose to just leave behind/sell their fridge when they move because of what a hassle it is to transport. Knowing how a fridge/freezer works will save you money and time, and prevent you from breaking it yourself on accident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The concern comes from an issue that was common in older fridges/freezers. When tilted past a 45 degree angle, the oil in the compressor had a tendency to spill out into the cooling tubes and clog them, preventing coolant from filling the fridge completely. This used to be the end of a fridge&amp;#39;s life and meant a hefty bill for a new one. Over time though, oils were treated so they wouldn&amp;#39;t congeal around foreign particles, which prevented blocking. Additionally, more stringent, coiled cooling tubes were made with better materials like fiberglass and unique polymers that became an industry standard because they would give and compress to push things through the pipe. These two features have worked in tandem to prevent blockage, but their efforts won&amp;#39;t stop people who ruin their fridges on accident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because coolant tubes are usually quite small and oil is fairly viscous, it takes some time for the oil to move through the tubes. What usually kills a fridge/freezer after transport is turning it on before the oil has had a chance to settle in the compressor. If you run it without oil, the machine simply won&amp;#39;t function outside of forcing pressure into the oil-filled coolant tubes, which only pushes the oil further up the pipe and compresses it into an actual blockage. It&amp;#39;s a waste of a good fridge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The solution, of course, is to let the oil settle. In most fridges/freezers, the oil will settle back into the compressor after sitting upright for 24-48 hours regardless of how long it was on it&amp;#39;s side. At bare minimum, give it the same amount of time upright as it was in transport. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope this helped!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: Grammar&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：吸烟（和吸食）会显著增加男性的勃起功能障碍风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[香烟中的化学物质导致血液循环不良，使男人患勃起功能障碍的机会增加一倍。
获得勃起功能障碍的机会增加一倍。因为尼古丁会收缩血管，所以吸食
也会导致勃起功能障碍。

为什么是YSK：许多人都在谈论吸烟的未来癌症风险。但是
但是，有大量的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/njlxej/ysk_smoking_and_vaping_significantly_increases/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/njlxej/ysk_smoking_and_vaping_significantly_increases/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 05:00:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The chemicals in cigarettes cause poor circulation, doubling a man&amp;#39;s chances of getting erectile dysfunction. Because nicotine constricts blood vessels, vaping it can also cause erectile dysfunction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Many people talk about the future risks of cancer with smoking. But there are a ton of other, often more immediate, risks including erectile dysfunction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/health/erectile-dysfunction/impotence-and-smoking&quot;&gt;https://www.healthline.com/health/erectile-dysfunction/impotence-and-smoking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.manual.co/health-centre/erectile-dysfunction/smoking&quot;&gt;https://www.manual.co/health-centre/erectile-dysfunction/smoking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I want to add that many states and countries have FREE smoking cessation programs. So it isn&amp;#39;t something that needs to be done alone, even if you can&amp;#39;t pay for help (although paid help can often be covered by insurance as well).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 纪录片可能具有极大的误导性。]]></title><description><![CDATA[有一个 "有趣的 "帖子说，如果一个和尚在特定的姿势/动作方面没有通过 "测试"，他必须在3年内接受 "重新测试"。
如果他没有通过对某一特定姿势/动作的 "测试"，就必须在三年内 "重新测试"。



这是一个极端夸张的说法。纪录片中的很多信息
与此相关的许多信息都被大大夸大了，或者是完全错误的。



为什么YSK：以...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/njdb5l/ysk_documentaries_can_be_extremely_misleading/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/njdb5l/ysk_documentaries_can_be_extremely_misleading/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 21:48:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s an &amp;quot;interestingasf*ck&amp;quot; post stating a Monk had to be &amp;quot;retested&amp;quot; in 3 years if he failed his &amp;quot;test&amp;quot; regarding a particular stance/moves. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s an extreme exaggeration. A lot of the information in the documentary relating to it was greatly exaggerated or just plain wrong. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Taking documentaries as the end all will leave you with a much poorer understanding of the reality of the world. This could be your health or being insulting incorrect about someone&amp;#39;s culture. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to see why the Shaolin Monk documentary is extremely exaggerated, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jHUewEWi9SE&amp;amp;t=38s&quot;&gt;watch this YouTuber who has video/picture evidence of his time being there who reviews the documentary himself&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK的哭声实际上让你更快乐!]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：哭泣会释放费洛蒙，这是一种自动的情绪调节剂! 永远不要
害怕哭泣!]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nj2o5z/ysk_crying_actually_makes_you_happier/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nj2o5z/ysk_crying_actually_makes_you_happier/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 10:58:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: crying releases pheromones which serves as an auto mood-lifter! Never be afraid to cry!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为甜叶菊和豚草是同一家族的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：甜叶菊可以让对豚草过敏的人产生与豚草相同类型（或更严重）的过敏反应。
更糟糕）的过敏反应。
https://www.marconews.com/story/life/2018/10/08/ask-pharmacist-allergic-connection-between-stevia-and-ragweed/1525152002/]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/niynqn/ysk_that_stevia_and_ragweed_are_from_the_same/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/niynqn/ysk_that_stevia_and_ragweed_are_from_the_same/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 08:57:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Stevia can give people with Ragweed allergies the same type of (or worse) allergic reaction as Ragweed.
 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marconews.com/story/life/2018/10/08/ask-pharmacist-allergic-connection-between-stevia-and-ragweed/1525152002/&quot;&gt;https://www.marconews.com/story/life/2018/10/08/ask-pharmacist-allergic-connection-between-stevia-and-ragweed/1525152002/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 眼镜内臂上的三组数字是以毫米为单位的：镜片宽度、鼻梁宽度和太阳穴长度。根据你的脸型和特征来调整尺寸。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK？

太窄的框架会使你的脸看起来更宽，而太宽的框架则会使你的脸看起来更窄。
太宽会使你的脸看起来更窄。这是找到一副合适的眼镜最重要的因素之一。
这是找到一副合适的眼镜的最重要因素之一。找到一个合适的镜框
比你的脸稍微宽一点--不超过一个手指。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/niuwil/ysk_the_three_sets_numbers_on_the_inside_arm_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/niuwil/ysk_the_three_sets_numbers_on_the_inside_arm_of/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 03:58:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;h1&gt;WHY YSK:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A frame that is too narrow will make your face look wider, while a frame that is too wide will make your face look narrower. This is one of the most important factors in finding a pair of glasses that fits well. Find a frame that is slightly wider than your face — no more than a finger width between the temple and your face. Any wider is a sign your frames are too wide. (This measurement is not printed on the temple of your glasses. To find it, take your measuring tape and measure horizontally across the front of your frames, including any hinges or design features that stick out on the sides.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The numbers, from left to right are for:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;LENS WIDTH&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To determine which lens size is right for you, know that a small lens width is 50mm or less, medium is between 51mm and 54mm and large is any lens wider than 55mm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your eyes should be centered within your lenses. Eyeglass frames that are too wide will make your eyes appear too close together, while narrow frames will give your eyes a wide-set look.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;TEMPLE LENGTH&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Temple length is the measurement in millimeters of the “arms” of the frame. This measurement does not vary as much as the others. 135mm, 140mm, 145mm, and 150mm are the most common options. The temple should fit horizontally and evenly along your face and fit comfortably along the outside of your ear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;BRIDGE WIDTH&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The distance between two lenses equals a frame&amp;#39;s bridge width. The bridge should sit comfortably flush against your nose. If you have close-set eyes or want a narrow bridge, this number should be lower. If you have wide-set eyes or want a wide bridge, this number should be higher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The location of your nose can help determine which frame style works best for you. If your nose is higher on your face, an eyeglass style where the bridge is even with the frame’s brow line will look best. If your nose is situated a bit lower on your face, a frame with a lower bridge and curved brow line will better suit your features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 自我反省实际上会使你的心理健康状况恶化，如果你不注意如何做的话。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：自我反省被认为是自我发展的关键之一。
心理健康和改善治疗的关键之一。然而，研究表明
[http://selfcontrol.psych.lsa.umich.edu/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/1-s2.0-S0065260116300338-main-2.pdf]
如果你用错误的方式，它实际上可以...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nikcds/ysk_selfreflection_can_actually_make_your_mental/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nikcds/ysk_selfreflection_can_actually_make_your_mental/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 00:42:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK&lt;/strong&gt;: Self-reflection is considered one of the keys to self-development, mental well-being and improvement in therapy. However, &lt;a href=&quot;http://selfcontrol.psych.lsa.umich.edu/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/1-s2.0-S0065260116300338-main-2.pdf&quot;&gt;research shows&lt;/a&gt; that if you do it the wrong way, it can actually make your problems worse. The wrong way, it turns out, is when you get too immersed in whatever is upsetting you by reflecting on it. To make self-reflection actually work, you need to learn to self-distance while doing it - i.e. take a mental step back from the problem. For example, you can imagine that you are looking at the situation from afar, or through someone else’s eyes; or you can write about it by referring to yourself in the third person (‘he’, ‘she’, ‘they’).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The studies show that this can reduce your negative emotions, and help you achieve closure and greater clarity. There’s also a free iOS app (not sure if it’s on Android, too) based on this research that uses roleplaying and guided journaling to make this type of self-reflection easier to do on the go and turn into a habit:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.apple.com/gb/app/betwixt-the-story-of-you/id1540472983&quot;&gt;https://apps.apple.com/gb/app/betwixt-the-story-of-you/id1540472983&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 如果你使用多于一罐的油漆，你应该先把它们混合在一起。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你需要覆盖一个大的表面，并且要使用多个罐子，你应该事先将它们混合在一起，而不是用一个罐子打开另一个罐子。
应该在使用前将它们混合在一起，而不是使用一个后再打开另一个。
因为你可以看到彼此之间的细微差别。
这样做可以使油漆工作看起来更均匀。

为什么是YSK：尽管...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nio494/ysk_if_youre_using_more_than_one_tin_of_paint_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nio494/ysk_if_youre_using_more_than_one_tin_of_paint_you/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 22:59:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re needing to cover a large surface and going to use multiple tins you should mix them together before hand rather than using one and opening another as you’ll be able to see the slight differences next to one another and doing this makes the paint job look more uniform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Even though you will be buying the same colour of paint there is always slight variation between every tin of paint that make it more obvious where the start of a new tin of paint has began.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为 "强大的低音 "和类似的术语只是一个营销噱头。让高端和低音更响亮只是一种廉价的方法，以产生人们认为好的声音。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：你的耳机应该很好地表现你的音乐，而不是改变它。更不用说
更不用说你可以通过避免使用这样的品牌来获得更好的声音。
营销。经常在网站上检查耳机的声音特征，如Rtings和
soundguys。细节也是非常重要的]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nifwwv/ysk_that_powerful_bass_and_terms_alike_are_just_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nifwwv/ysk_that_powerful_bass_and_terms_alike_are_just_a/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 12:27:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK : Your headphones should represent your music well, not alter it. Not to mention that you could get better sound by just avoiding brands with such marketing. 
Always check headphones sound signature on websites like rtings and soundguys. Detail is also very important&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：当亚马逊、银行等大公司说他们支持 "小企业 "时，他们指的是员工人数不超过250-1500人的企业（取决于行业）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：广告经常试图通过展示小型家庭企业和家庭拥有/经营的企业的图像来改变你对大公司的看法。
试图改变你对大公司的看法，展示小企业、家庭企业和家庭拥有/经营的企业的形象。
但当他们声称他们参与了 "小企业 "时，他们通常使用的是 "小企业 "的定义。
但当他们宣称参与 "小企业 "时，他们通常使用的定义是......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ni9dvv/ysk_when_huge_companies_like_amazon_banks_and_etc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ni9dvv/ysk_when_huge_companies_like_amazon_banks_and_etc/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 07:03:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Advertisements will often try to change your view of large companies by showing imagery of tiny, home businesses, and family owned/operated business that they are supposedly helping but when they make claims of their involvement with &amp;quot;small businesses&amp;quot; they&amp;#39;re usually using the definitions the U.S. Small Business Association (SBA) uses&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecfr.gov/cgi-bin/text-idx?SID=0ff5f0839abff4eec707b4478ed733c6&amp;amp;mc=true&amp;amp;node=pt13.1.121&amp;amp;rgn=div5#se13.1.121_1101&quot;&gt;uses&lt;/a&gt; which allows for companies that employ between 250 and 1500 employees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 汽车保修诈骗电话是为了收集敏感信息。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：你应该知道这些，以保护自己免受骗局的影响，如果你容易受骗的话。
易受其影响，如果你不是，你应该知道，这样你就可以帮助使其成为一个
不可行的骗局。

步骤1.) 欺骗一个来自目标地区的号码，阅读你的脚本，关于他们的
延长保修期

第2步：) 收集车辆的品牌和型号。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nhus2x/ysk_the_car_warranty_scam_calls_are_about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nhus2x/ysk_the_car_warranty_scam_calls_are_about/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 17:11:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: You Should know this to defend yourself from the scam if you&amp;#39;re susceptible to it, if you&amp;#39;re not you should know so you can help make it an unviable scam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 1.) Spoof a number from the targets area, read your script about their extended warranty&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 2.) Collect Make of vehicle and target zip code&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 3.) Call ACTUAL sales department of specified Make of vehicle and merge the calls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 4.) Listen in as target feeds sensitive information to the sales department.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doesn&amp;#39;t matter which make/model/year you say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you can do&lt;/strong&gt;: Feed the warranty scammer fake/false information, this is make/model/zip so prepare a fake zip. As soon as they transfer you to the actual sales office for the make of &amp;quot;your&amp;quot; vehicle inform them of how this scam works. It needs to be just annoying enough for vehicle manufacturers so they change their phone practices so this scam no longer works. This whole process should take ~2 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: So far I&amp;#39;ve gotten to Honda and Toyota sales departments. I tried to do Chevy but the scammer un-merged the call while I was explaining to the Chevy rep what was going on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK的睡眠不是一种可有可无的奢侈生活方式。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：睡眠问题专家马修-沃克说，睡眠是一种
不容商量的生物必需品。

但有些人并不关心他们的睡眠时间，这不仅影响到他们的职业生活，也影响到个人生活。
他们的职业生活，也影响到个人生活。

如果你不知道它如何影响我们的日常...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nhlefq/ysk_sleep_is_not_an_optional_lifestyle_luxury/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nhlefq/ysk_sleep_is_not_an_optional_lifestyle_luxury/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 10:47:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  Matthew Walker, an expert on the subject of sleep, said that sleep is a non-negotiable biological necessity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But some people don&amp;#39;t care about their sleeping schedule which not only affects their professional life but personal life as well. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don&amp;#39;t know how it affects our day-to-day activities and productivity, or hamper our biological cycle, then take some time and read some articles and watch some videos written and made by some experts. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have a look at this short video: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ted.com/talks/matt_walker_hacking_your_memory_with_sleep?utm_campaign=tedspread&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_source=tedcomshare&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full video:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ted.com/talks/matt_walker_sleep_is_your_superpower?utm_campaign=tedspread&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_source=tedcomshare&quot;&gt;Sleep is your superpower&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：许多大学都有向公众出售的剩余部门，可以成为廉价家具的一个好来源。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK: 装修一个新的地方可能很昂贵，而且大学总是有
的东西要扔掉。有时甚至是很酷的复古物品。在我当地的大学盈余。
我已经看到了从基本的办公用品、文件柜、显示器、书桌。
到钢琴和奇怪的旧实验室设备。这是一个废话，和...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nhaxni/ysk_many_universities_have_surplus_department/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nhaxni/ysk_many_universities_have_surplus_department/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 21:48:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Furnishing a new place can be expensive, and Universities always have stuff to get rid of. Sometimes even cool vintage stuff. At my local U surplus, I&amp;#39;ve seen everything from basic office supplies, file cabinets, monitors, desks, to pianos and weird old lab equipment. It&amp;#39;s a crap-shoot, and places may or may not be open at the moment, but take a look. You might find something great.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，在移动或储存之前，需要将垫圈排空。一个简单的方法是用车间吸尘器吸住后面的黑色软管，让它把水吸出来。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么YSK：洗衣机在存放或移动前不排水，不仅会使洗衣机更重。
它更重，而且会导致水在水箱内滞留和发霉。即使是
储存中的一点点水分都会破坏你的整个世界。你所要做的是
就是把车间真空管放在水箱的黑色排水管上。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nh05u7/ysk_that_washers_need_to_be_drained_before_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nh05u7/ysk_that_washers_need_to_be_drained_before_you/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 18:05:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Not draining a washer before it is stored or moved will not only make it heavier, but it will cause water to stagnate and mold inside the tank. Even a little bit of moisture in storage can wreck your whole world. All you have to do is put a shop vac hose on the black drainage hose on the back of the washer make a tight seal with your hand or tape and let it suck the moisture out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你的信用分数究竟是如何计算的？]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：有很多关于你应该和不应该做什么的错误指导在四处流传。
和不应该做的事。

这篇文章将重点讨论FICO分数，因为它是最多的一种信用分数。
因为它是当今使用最多的信用分数。那么，什么是FICO分数？首先，FICO是指
Fair Isaac Corporation....]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ngklcz/ysk_how_your_credit_score_is_actually_calculated/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ngklcz/ysk_how_your_credit_score_is_actually_calculated/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 08:55:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: There is a lot of bad guidance floating around about what you should and should not do with regards to credit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This post will focus on the FICO Score since it is the most prolific type of credit score used today. So, what is a FICO score?  First, FICO stands for the Fair Isaac Corporation. The FICO score was created in 1989 as a standardized way for lenders to interpret your credit report and determine whether or not to give you a loan.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How is a FICO score different than a credit report? A FICO score is simply a summarized version of your credit report. Your credit report lists all your credit history, but it doesn’t keep track of everything forever. Good credit is maintained for 10 years and bad credit is tracked for 7. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s on your credit report? If you have a credit card, auto loan, or mortgage all of that will be included. Why does your score matter? A quick caveat, if you follow Dave Ramsey’s philosophy, be aware an undeterminable score (AKA a score of 0) is very different from having a bad score. Dave cites 6-12 months after you close your last account to reach an undeterminable score, but I was not able to verify this number with a third party. If that’s what you want to do, that’s perfectly fine, but your credit score will potentially affect you until it reaches “zero”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some areas your score will affect: Better terms when you get a loan, lower insurance premiums, the ability to rent in some apartment complexes, potentially new jobs who require a credit check on new employees. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your FICO score is composed of five categories: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Payment history (35% of your scores) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amounts owed (30% of your scores) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Length of credit history (15% of your scores) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New credit (10% of your scores) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Credit mix (10% of your scores) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you get your credit score? There are lots of free and paid ways to get your score, but the easiest is probably through your credit card company of choice. Personally, with AMEX I can check my credit score whenever I want through their website. To get your actual credit report the three big credit bureaus: Experian, Equifax, and TransUnion offer your credit report (different from your credit score) once each year for free as mandated by federal law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, it’s a myth that checking your credit score will lower it. The reason why is because there are two different types of ways credit is checked: 1) Soft check occurs anytime you check your own score or when a lender checks your score to preapprove you 2) A hard credit check occurs when a lender checks your credit to determine if you met their lending criteria such as applying for a mortgage or new credit card, this would lower your credit score slightly &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What can you do to improve your FICO score? 1) Always pay in full and on time 2) Keep your credit utilization rate low, one way to reduce your credit utilization rate is to increase your credit limits. So long as you pay everything off every month you should be able to request a credit limit increase every 9 months 3) Keep your credit cards open for a long time 4) Only open new lines of credit when you need to, such as when applying for a mortgage &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some links you might find helpful!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FICO Score Website &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ficoscore.com/home&quot;&gt;https://www.ficoscore.com/home&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Free Credit Report &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.annualcreditreport.com/index.action&quot;&gt;https://www.annualcreditreport.com/index.action&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experian &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.experian.com/&quot;&gt;https://www.experian.com/&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Equifax &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.equifax.com/personal/&quot;&gt;https://www.equifax.com/personal/&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TransUnion &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.transunion.com/&quot;&gt;https://www.transunion.com/&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And here is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/8vtnh5kYxj8&quot;&gt;video&lt;/a&gt; that goes a little more in depth than this post if you&amp;#39;re interested in learning more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK "臭名昭著 "是指以坏的理由出名。"知名 "是指以好的理由而闻名。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK。

除非你说的是克里斯托弗-华莱士，如果你说某人是
"臭名昭著"，这意味着他们因某些众所周知的错误或应受谴责的行为而闻名。
应受谴责的行为。没有人愿意侮辱一个他们想抬高的人。
相反，如果你想赞美某人，就用 "赞誉"，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ngni7j/ysk_notorious_means_famous_for_a_bad_reason/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ngni7j/ysk_notorious_means_famous_for_a_bad_reason/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 03:48:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unless you&amp;#39;re talking Christopher Wallace, if you say that someone is &amp;quot;notorious&amp;quot; that implies that what they&amp;#39;re known for is some well-known fault or reprehensible action. Nobody wants to insult someone they meant to lift up. Instead, if you want to compliment someone, use &amp;quot;acclaimed&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;celebrated&amp;quot;, or just plain &amp;quot;famous&amp;quot; (&lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; &amp;quot;infamous&amp;quot;). If you would put it on the outside of confectionery, it&amp;#39;s acclaimed. If you hear a news anchor use it to describe a serial killer, it&amp;#39;s notorious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Someone might be &lt;strong&gt;acclaimed&lt;/strong&gt; for making people smile and baking people pies but &lt;strong&gt;notorious&lt;/strong&gt; for &lt;em&gt;making&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;people smile&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;baking people-pies&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s a &lt;strong&gt;big&lt;/strong&gt; difference, and &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;you should know&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;it&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now you do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 你可以通过按住空格键和移动你的拇指来轻松控制iPhone上的文字光标。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：当试图编辑Reddit上的帖子，或者试图在手机浏览器上修复一个链接中的错字时
时，会很痛苦，因为你无法真正看到光标。
光标，而且当你放开光标时，它就会卡在奇怪的地方。按住
在iPhone键盘上按住空格键，然后移动你的拇指，这样就可以...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nfuzgs/ysk_you_can_easily_control_the_text_cursor_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nfuzgs/ysk_you_can_easily_control_the_text_cursor_on/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 09:19:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: When trying to edit posts on Reddit, or trying to fix a typo in a link on your mobile web browser, it can be a pain since you can’t really see the cursor and when you let go of the cursor it snaps to odd places. Holding down spacebar on the iPhone keyboard and moving your thumb around gives you full control of the cursor. I personally didn’t know this. Ever since Apple removed the magnifying glass when highlighting text, it has been a serious pain to navigate text.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你为《阿凡达》最后的Airbender太短而难过，那么你可以看别的东西。]]></title><description><![CDATA[不，我不是在谈论Korra。我说的是那个被低估的节目。
龙的传人。这个节目有许多与《阿凡达》相同的编剧和配音演员。
阿凡达》，并且有一个惊人的情节和动画风格。它在Netflix上，我不知道为什么它没有被推广。
我不知道为什么它没有得到更好的推广。

为什么是YSK：人们在...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nfuqlf/ysk_if_you_are_sad_that_avatar_the_last_airbender/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nfuqlf/ysk_if_you_are_sad_that_avatar_the_last_airbender/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 05:55:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;And no, I am not talking about &lt;em&gt;Korra&lt;/em&gt;. I am talking about the underclaimed show, &lt;em&gt;The Dragon Prince&lt;/em&gt;. This show has many of the same writers and voice actors as &lt;em&gt;Avatar&lt;/em&gt;, and has an amazing plot and animation style. It is on Netflix and I have no idea why it isn&amp;#39;t promoted better.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: People are obsessed with &lt;em&gt;Avatar&lt;/em&gt;, and yet for some reason many of them don&amp;#39;t know about &lt;em&gt;The Dragon Prince&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你囤积汽油，它变坏的速度比你想象的快得多。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：人们开始惊慌失措，囤积汽油，但如果真的出现短缺，这可能对他们没有什么好处。
但如果真的出现短缺，这可能对他们没有什么好处。

虽然它根据成分（E15比E10坏得快）和
储存方式的不同而有所差异，但与乙醇混合的汽油
[https://www.jdpower.com/cars/shopping...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nan4dg/ysk_that_if_youre_hoarding_gas_it_goes_bad_much/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nan4dg/ysk_that_if_youre_hoarding_gas_it_goes_bad_much/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 04:04:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: people are starting to freak out and hoard gas, but it probably won&amp;#39;t do them much good if a shortage really does develop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While it varies a little based on composition (E15  goes bad faster than E10) and how you store it, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jdpower.com/cars/shopping-guides/how-long-can-gas-sit-in-a-car-before-it-goes-bad&quot;&gt;gas blended with ethanol&lt;/a&gt; (which is almost all gas) has a very short shelf life of less than three months. Ethanol is hydrophilic, so water will be introduced to your gas; at the same time as the compound itself oxidizes and degrades, creating non combustible residue. Even ethanol free premium only keeps for three to six months or so in the best possible conditions. A fuel stabilizer can extend that up to a year or more, but it reduces the octane rating of your gas and will generally &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/chsGBhB5g7o&quot;&gt;make your car run worse&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your car will &lt;em&gt;probably&lt;/em&gt; still run on old gas, but it won&amp;#39;t run well, and if you use enough of it, you are likely to damage injectors, or clog up a fuel filter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s plenty of gas, folks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK - 当你打电话给你的公用事业公司或移动/互联网供应商时，电话那头的代理可能和你一样讨厌这家公司。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK--在我20多岁的时候，我曾在这些行业工作过很多次，我说
大约95%的员工讨厌他们的工作和公司，这完全是因为他们对待员工的方式。
他们对待员工的方式。这些公司倾向于欺骗客户和员工。
客户和他们的员工。

虽然你可能会感到沮丧...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nfavm4/ysk_when_you_ring_your_utilities_company_or/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nfavm4/ysk_when_you_ring_your_utilities_company_or/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 17:23:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK - Having worked in these industries a lot during my twenties I&amp;#39;d say about 95% of the employees hated their job and the company purely because of the way they tend to treat their employees. These companies tend to screw over the customers and their staff. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although you might be frustrated try to keep your composure with the person on the end of the phone as you&amp;#39;re more likely to get what you need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，如果你有来自非营利性医院的医疗债务，如果你的收入说你无法支付，你可以大幅减少或完全注销账单。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：不管债务有多老，也不管它是否被送去催收。
催收。如果你在账单产生时有保险，这也不重要。
产生时是否有保险也无关紧要。只要非营利性医院拥有这笔债务，而且它没有被卖掉
那么你就有资格获得财政援助，如果你无力支付......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nf2icd/ysk_that_if_you_have_medical_debt_from_a_non/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nf2icd/ysk_that_if_you_have_medical_debt_from_a_non/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 08:33:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It does not matter how old the debt is or if it was sent to collections. It doesn&amp;#39;t even matter if you had insurance when the bill was created. As long as the non profit hospital owns the debt and it wasn&amp;#39;t sold off then you&amp;#39;ll be eligible for financial assistance if you can&amp;#39;t afford to pay the debt at all. Don&amp;#39;t let them run you in circles. They will lie, they will tell you false info even if they&amp;#39;re not supposed to. The billing might claim &amp;quot;oh, we can&amp;#39;t do anything about it. The account was sent to &amp;quot;x&amp;quot; collection company. We can&amp;#39;t change anything anymore since we don&amp;#39;t have it, you have to speak with them.&amp;quot; If your bill is as little as 2 years old, the collections agency will tell you &amp;quot;there&amp;#39;s nothing we can do. The bill has aged out already. You can&amp;#39;t do payment plans on 2, 3, 4 year old bills. The most I can do is give you a discount but it has to be paid in lump sum.&amp;quot; This is a lie, and they will continue to lie and play dumb. My conversation with collections went something like &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Hi, I have a problem. I was eligible for free care at the hospital back in 2019 but the hospital never provided me with any information like they were supposed to (in my state, there is a law that says hospitals MUST provide patients with info on financial assistance) I only just recently got &amp;quot;x&amp;quot; health care and, had the hospital told me like they were required to, I would&amp;#39;ve had no bill&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;I don&amp;#39;t understand what you want me to do? Theres nothing you can do &lt;em&gt;my name&lt;/em&gt; these bills are 2, 3, years old. They&amp;#39;ve aged out already. And you have 22 accounts,  TWENTY TWO. I don&amp;#39;t mean to be rude but why would you wait so long to try and fix it?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;I did try and fix it before it was sent to collections but they gave me incorrect info. They told me my only options were a payment plan or pay in full. The hospital also never gave me financial assistance info like they&amp;#39;re supposed to&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;em&gt;my name&lt;/em&gt; you&amp;#39;re an adult, you&amp;#39;re supposed to find that info on your own. If you wanted to set up a payment plan or something then you should&amp;#39;ve dealt with this in a timely manner before it was sent to collections. Its aged out, you can&amp;#39;t do that anymore&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After arguing with billing and collections for 5 hours, someone finally connected me with a financial assistance counselor. She apologized profusely for the lies I was told and said the debt doesnt age out and the debt can still be dealt with. Apparently this is something she&amp;#39;s contacted Upper management about many times. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t let them lie to you and try to play stupid. Look up your states laws and never back down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：对于一个成功的关系，它不仅仅是妥协。最重要的是，在每次妥协之后，你应该仍然喜欢自己和对方。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：大家都在说，关系需要妥协。健康的
关系应该建立在支持和理解的基础上，因此
妥协的目的应该是为了改善彼此和关系。承认
错误和性格弱点是困难的，但会导致性格的改变。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nf0sbo/ysk_for_a_successful_relationship_its_not_just/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nf0sbo/ysk_for_a_successful_relationship_its_not_just/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 07:51:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Everyone is saying that relationships require compromises. Healthy relationships should be based on support and understanding, therefore compromises should aim to better each other and the relationship. Admitting mistakes and character weaknesses is difficult but leads to character growth. However, changing one&amp;#39;s self to fit a relationship to the point where you don&amp;#39;t like or recognise yourself is not healthy and will not lead to a long lasting relationship. Love yourself, love each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：带有金属刷毛的烧烤刷是致命的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：小铁丝碎片可能会断裂并被摄入，而这些小碎片会对你的身体造成严重的伤害，需要进行紧急手术。
这些小碎片会对你的身体造成重大损害，并需要进行紧急手术
需要对穿孔的器官进行紧急手术。今年夏天，请确保你的家人安全，并使用塑料（或
木头，正如其他人所指出的）烧烤刷。

文章...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/neyc8s/ysk_bbq_brushes_with_metal_bristles_are_deadly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/neyc8s/ysk_bbq_brushes_with_metal_bristles_are_deadly/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 04:53:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: The small wire pieces can break off and be ingested, and those little shards can cause significant damage to your body, and require emergency surgery for perforated organs. Keep your family safe this summer and use a plastic (or wood, as others have pointed out) BBQ brush.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Article 1: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/manitoba/wire-barbecue-brushes-health-canada-review-1.4205997&quot;&gt;https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/manitoba/wire-barbecue-brushes-health-canada-review-1.4205997&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Article 2: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/manitoba/bbq-wire-brushes-new-standard-1.5456886&quot;&gt;https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/manitoba/bbq-wire-brushes-new-standard-1.5456886&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Article 3: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.consumerreports.org/food-safety/wire-grill-brush-danger/&quot;&gt;https://www.consumerreports.org/food-safety/wire-grill-brush-danger/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你正在考虑为精神问题寻求专业帮助，但不确定你是否感觉 "足够糟糕"，一定要这样做。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：我知道有很多人考虑过这个问题，其中一个最常见的问题是，他们认为自己并不感到难过。
阻碍他们的最常见的事情是认为他们感觉不够糟糕
以至于没有权利寻求和接受帮助。认识到这一点很重要
你的想法和感受是真实的，而事实上，有些人...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/neh0yl/ysk_if_youre_considering_seeking_professional/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/neh0yl/ysk_if_youre_considering_seeking_professional/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 15:55:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I know a lot of people who have considered this, and one of the most common things that held them back was the thought that they weren&amp;#39;t feeling bad enough to have the right to seek and receive help. It&amp;#39;s important to recognize your thoughts and feelings as real, and the fact that some people might feel worse does not mean you don&amp;#39;t have the right to talk to someone about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I am lucky enough to live in a country where you can get a certain amount of hours for free. I am aware of the fact that in some countries it is not available at a reasonable price, which is pretty fucked up if you ask me. My point is just that if there are no other (financial) factors that hold you back, you should go for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你每天坐在椅子上几个小时，提高扶手（如果可以调整），使其促进你的肩膀保持平衡，背部挺直。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：这将有助于防止你懒洋洋地靠在一个臂架上寻求支持
并在整体上促进更健康的休息姿势。

参考资料。

https://www.physiomed.co.uk/uploads/guide/file/22/Physiomed_Sitting_Guide_-_Working_at_a_Desk_Digital.pdf]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nawktg/ysk_if_you_sit_at_a_chair_for_hours_a_day_raise/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nawktg/ysk_if_you_sit_at_a_chair_for_hours_a_day_raise/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 14:55:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: this will help prevent you from slouching to one arm rest for support and overall promote a more healthy resting posture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reference:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.physiomed.co.uk/uploads/guide/file/22/Physiomed_Sitting_Guide_-_Working_at_a_Desk_Digital.pdf&quot;&gt;https://www.physiomed.co.uk/uploads/guide/file/22/Physiomed_Sitting_Guide_-_Working_at_a_Desk_Digital.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为经常洗车对你的车辆很重要]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：道路上的灰尘和污垢会在你想不到的地方堆积起来。
你不会想到的地方。另外，住在有雪/冰的地区的人
的人，要处理他们各自的市政府或县政府为维护道路而在道路上撒的盐。
他们各自的市政府或县政府为了维护道路而在道路上撒盐。至少去洗一次车...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ne1ag7/ysk_that_getting_frequent_car_washes_is_important/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ne1ag7/ysk_that_getting_frequent_car_washes_is_important/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 01:49:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: The amount of dirt and grime that comes from the road builds up in places you wouldn’t think of. Plus people who live in areas that have snow/ice on the roads deal with the salt that their respective municipalities or counties put on the roads to maintain them. Get a car wash at least once a month regardless of the weather, and take the time to clean the undercarriage every 6 months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：40%的大学生沉迷于智能手机，严重损害了他们的睡眠]]></title><description><![CDATA[背景：文章
[https://medlifestyle.news/2021/05/16/40-of-university-students-found-to-be-addicted-to-their-smartphone-study-says/]

为什么是YSK：最近发表的多项研究显示，不仅是
在普通人群中 "智能手机上瘾 "的增加，特别是
在...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ndzskv/ysk_40_of_university_students_are_addicted_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ndzskv/ysk_40_of_university_students_are_addicted_to/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 01:49:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Context: &lt;a href=&quot;https://medlifestyle.news/2021/05/16/40-of-university-students-found-to-be-addicted-to-their-smartphone-study-says/&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Multiple studies have recently been published showing not only the  increase in &amp;#39;smartphone addiction&amp;#39; amongst the general population,  specifically within the teenage and young adult age groups, but also showing a very particularly link between smartphone use and poor sleep  quality. We know that poor sleep quality has been linked to dementia, obesity, and lower cognitive function.  Smartphones have not been around long enough for researchers to be able to study the multi-decade effects that they may have, which is why it&amp;#39;s important that we stay cautious and aware of how long we are spending  on our devices and understand the known detriments that they can cause.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：只给你的狗浇水降温可能会使事情变得更糟。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：这可以减轻毛皮的重量，并形成一层隔热层，可以
增加体温。如果你打算给你的狗浇水，请
也使用风扇/通风来利用蒸发冷却。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ndqev9/ysk_only_pouring_water_on_your_dog_to_cool_them/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ndqev9/ysk_only_pouring_water_on_your_dog_to_cool_them/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 22:56:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This can weigh down the fur and create a layer of insulation that can increase body temperature.  If you are going to pour water on your dog please also use fans/ventilation to utilize evaporative cooling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK在冰沙中放置生的蔬菜，如春卷/麦芽菜和胡萝卜，可以让人以较少的体积吃到更多的蔬菜。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：很多人都不愿意吃蔬菜，而将蔬菜混合在冰沙中可以在同样的时间内吃到更多的蔬菜。
而在冰沙中混合蔬菜，可以在相同的体积中吃到更多的蔬菜。
蔬菜冰沙的体积。用香蕉作为冰沙中蔬菜的粘性粘合剂。
蔬菜在冰沙中。















有些人像我一样可以吃...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n84p90/ysk_placing_raw_vegetables_such_as_spring/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n84p90/ysk_placing_raw_vegetables_such_as_spring/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 07:31:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Many people can not bring themselves to eat vegetables, while mixing them within a smoothie would allow more vegetables to be eaten in the same volume as a non vegetable smoothie. Use banana as a sticky binder for the vegetables within the smoothie. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some like me can eat spring mix alone without dressing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：阴天别忘了涂抹防晒霜]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：大多数云层最多只能阻挡50%的紫外线，因此，太阳光线仍然可以
仍能在你不知道的情况下，设法损害你的皮肤。每年有8000名美国人死于
每年有8000名美国人死于黑色素瘤，尽量不要成为其中的一员。

来源[https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3364536/]]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/natqa9/ysk_dont_forget_to_apply_sunscreen_on_cloudy_days/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/natqa9/ysk_dont_forget_to_apply_sunscreen_on_cloudy_days/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 03:49:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; Most clouds can at most block 50% of UV rays and thus sun rays can still, unbeknownst to you, manage to damage your skin. 8000 Americans lose their life to melanoma annually, try not to be one of them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3364536/&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你可以通过下载这些全面的音频课程来免费学习一种语言!]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK。

我最近从Living Language购买了一个意大利语课程。它有三个
工作簿，以便在音频课程中跟读。音频课程是通过CD提供的。
通过CD提供，但网站也说如果你愿意，可以下载内容。
愿意。直到今天，我才意识到，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n9c333/ysk_you_can_learn_a_language_for_free_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/n9c333/ysk_you_can_learn_a_language_for_free_by/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 02:00:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently purchased a course in Italian from Living Language. It comes with 3 workbooks to follow along with during the audio lessons. The audio lessons are provided via CD, but the website also states you can download the content if you prefer. What I didn&amp;#39;t realize until today is that the downloadable content is just posted to their website and you do not need a referral or access code to download it! So there you have it. I paid for an Italian course, but you should all know you can access their downloads (of any available language) for free by visiting the Living Language website, selecting &amp;quot;Support&amp;quot; and then &amp;quot;Downloads&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*For best results, use the &amp;quot;Complete Edition&amp;quot; rather than &amp;quot;Basics&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: Linking for easy access, hope that is okay: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.livinglanguage.com/faq/downloads&quot;&gt;https://www.livinglanguage.com/faq/downloads&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and they also have free literature which I didn&amp;#39;t know either! &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.livinglanguage.com/additional&quot;&gt;https://www.livinglanguage.com/additional&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK用过的披萨盒几乎无法回收利用]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：根据圣何塞市的说法
[https://sanjoserecycles.org/guide/pizza-boxes/]，"油腻的比萨饼盒
污染了清洁的回收物，对回收业来说是很昂贵的：据估计，污染的代价是
据估计，污染每年给回收商带来7亿美元的损失，因为
损坏的机器，成本...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nas163/ysk_used_pizza_boxes_are_almost_never_recyclable/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nas163/ysk_used_pizza_boxes_are_almost_never_recyclable/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:41:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: According to &lt;a href=&quot;https://sanjoserecycles.org/guide/pizza-boxes/&quot;&gt;the City of San José&lt;/a&gt;, &amp;quot;&lt;em&gt;Greasy pizza boxes contaminate clean recycling and are expensive for the recycling industry: it’s estimated that contamination costs recyclers $700 million per year, because of damaged machinery, the cost of disposing of non-recyclable materials and wasted time.&lt;/em&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, even if your pizza box has recycle logos on it, it&amp;#39;s probably not,  because those logos are &lt;em&gt;marketing&lt;/em&gt;, not informational. A clean pristine pizza box &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; recyclable and that&amp;#39;s why they they label it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your municipality has a &amp;quot;green bin&amp;quot;, a bin for compost and organic waste, that might be the place to discard pizza boxes. As is the case for many assumed-recycleable items, check the website to see where your waste-collectors want it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：最近在商店里流行的怪味洗手液使用的是乙醇而不是异丙醇。如果你想避免难闻的气味，请看一下 "活性成分 "部分，确认它不包括乙醇。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：每个人都讨厌廉价饮酒的味道，但当你把消毒剂涂在手上时，通常已经太晚了。
但当你把消毒剂放在手上时，通常已经太晚了。在你购买或使用一瓶洗手液之前，快速检查一下
在你购买或使用一瓶洗手液之前，快速检查一下，将使你免于被涂抹的糟糕经历。
在接下来的15分钟内闻到水晶宫的味道的糟糕经历。恐怕...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nchvkj/ysk_the_weird_smelling_hand_sanitizer_that_has/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/nchvkj/ysk_the_weird_smelling_hand_sanitizer_that_has/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 22:34:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Everyone hates the smell of cheap drinking alcohol, but it&amp;#39;s usually too late by the time you&amp;#39;ve put the sanitizer on your hands. A quick check before you buy or use a bottle of hand sanitizer will save you the bad experience of smelling Crystal Palace for the next 15 minutes.
I&amp;#39;m afraid I can&amp;#39;t help with that weird goopy consistency that some brands have. You&amp;#39;re on your own for that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>