<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 04:40:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 在用于结婚礼物的支票上只写一个名字]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：这使得新婚夫妇在存入一张写有两个名字的支票时更加困难。
特别是如果你把他们的名字写成同名同姓的话。
姓。不是每个人都会随同伴侣的姓氏，即使打算随同伴侣的姓氏，他们的姓氏也不会在支票上出现。
他们的姓氏在法律上也会有一段时间不会被改变。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qjp67k/ysk_to_only_put_one_name_on_a_cheque_that_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qjp67k/ysk_to_only_put_one_name_on_a_cheque_that_is/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 14:45:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It makes it a lot more difficult for the newlyweds to deposit a cheque with two names on it - especially if you have addressed them as having the same last name. Not everybody assumes their partner’s last name, and even if intend to, their last name won’t be legally changed for a while.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为灭火器会过期。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：大多数人没有意识到这一点，而且这种情况很少发生，但如果灭火器已经过期，它可能在你需要的时候发生故障。
过时，它可能会在你需要它时发生故障。这显然可能是
这显然是非常危险的。你可以在附着在灭火器顶部的标签上找到日期。
的标签上找到日期。

"虽然它们没有真正的 "到期日"，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qjalo0/ysk_that_fire_extinguishers_expire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qjalo0/ysk_that_fire_extinguishers_expire/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 23:57:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Most people don’t realize this and it’s rare but if the extinguisher is out of date, it can malfunction when you need it. That can obviously be extremely dangerous. You can find the date on the tag attached to the top of the unit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Although they don&amp;#39;t have a true &amp;quot;expiration date,&amp;quot; traditional fire extinguishers generally have a 10-12 year life expectancy. Disposable fire extinguishers should be replaced every 12 years. Rechargeable fire extinguishers should be taken to an experienced fire equipment company and recharged every 10 years.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://support.firstalert.com/s/article/How-long-do-fire-extinguishers-last&quot;&gt;https://support.firstalert.com/s/article/How-long-do-fire-extinguishers-last&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Word中的YSK数字和绘图可以通过将其嵌入到一个表格中来更容易地进行操作。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：它节省了大量的时间和精力（以及精神崩溃）。我已经看到
太多的备忘录了，不可能什么都不说。

例如，我想在一个Word文档中加入一个数字。我所做的是

1）创建一个2x1的表格。

2）在第一行中复制我的情节。

3) 将我的标题放在最下面一行。

4)使...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qizkf6/ysk_figures_and_plots_in_word_can_be_easier/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qizkf6/ysk_figures_and_plots_in_word_can_be_easier/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 15:42:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It saves a lot of time and effort (and mental breakdowns). I&amp;#39;ve seen too many memes to not say anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, I want to include a figure in a Word document. What I do is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Create a 2x1 table,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Copy my plot in the first row,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Include my caption in the bottom row,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Make the table borders invisible, and Tada!, you&amp;#39;ve got a beautiful plot, with a caption, which can be easily manipulated around the page!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s also scalable. You can create an adjacent column to have legends and arrows pointing to elements in the picture, or even have 2 graphs with 2 distinct captions along the same row.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，你在reddit上发布的所有内容都被第三方（pushshift）所储存，所以在reddit上删除并不能完全消除你的数字足迹。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK。

他们所做的是非法的（违反GDPR第17条），但除非有人起诉
他们会继续这样做。有一些线程，用户试图
要求退出，但人们已经等了几个月都没有用。
开发商是无法联系到的。因此，建议你注意一下...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qiwwap/ysk_that_everything_you_post_on_reddit_is_being/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qiwwap/ysk_that_everything_you_post_on_reddit_is_being/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 09:42:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What they are doing is illegal (against Art. 17 GDPR) but unless someone sues them they&amp;#39;re gonna keep doing it. There have been threads where users try to request to opt out, but ppl have been waiting for months to no avail, and the dev is impossible to reach. So word of advice, watch what you say online, all the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：有毒的万圣节糖果的恐慌神话]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：没有证据表明有陌生人以这种方式杀害或永久伤害儿童的案例。
已经被证实。通常，这个故事出现在媒体上，当一个年轻的孩子
万圣节后突然死亡。

在极少数情况下，成年家庭成员散布这个故事，试图掩盖
掩盖谋杀或意外...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qirqcs/ysk_the_poisoned_halloween_candy_scare_myth/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qirqcs/ysk_the_poisoned_halloween_candy_scare_myth/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 03:41:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: No cases of strangers killing or permanently injuring children this way have been proven. Commonly, the story appears in the media when a young child dies suddenly after Halloween.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In rare cases, adult family members have spread this story in an effort to cover up murder or accidental deaths. In other incidents, a child who has been told about poisoned candy places a dangerous object or substance in a pile of candy and pretends that it was the work of a stranger. This behavior is called the copycat effect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, always take caution and inspect but know that it is not as big of a threat as media might make it each year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Poisoned_candy_myths&quot;&gt;Wiki Info&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbc.ca/news/health/halloween-candy-tampering-urban-legend-truth-1.5341734&quot;&gt;4 cases of tampering reported between 2008 and 2019, but none resulted in injury or death, CFIA says (Canada)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/30/health/halloween-candy-panic-conversation-wellness/index.html&quot;&gt;CNN article 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，如果你不喜欢一个网站的官方网站，几乎总是有一个第三方的应用程序可用。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：官方应用程序是为了赚钱而设计的，可能充满了广告或
其他令人沮丧的问题。第三方应用程序通常没有广告，界面更干净，而且
更高级的功能。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhz2b8/ysk_that_if_you_dislike_the_official_site_for_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhz2b8/ysk_that_if_you_dislike_the_official_site_for_a/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 13:04:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Official apps are designed to make money, and may be full of ads or other frustrations. Third party apps often have no ads, cleaner interfaces, and more advanced features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，有大量的公开课程可以帮助你选择学位或进行一般的学习。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：获得学位是你一生中做出的最严肃的决定之一
而确定一门课程是否适合你可能是很困难的。为了帮助你
为了帮助你做出决定，有一些免费的在线资源，你可以实际看到你要参加的那种
介绍性的讲座。

例如，你可以搜索麻省理工学院的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qi9wt8/ysk_that_there_are_plenty_of_open_courses_to_help/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qi9wt8/ysk_that_there_are_plenty_of_open_courses_to_help/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 12:35:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Getting a degree is one of the most serious decisions you make in life and determining if a course is right for you can be difficult. To help you decide, there are free online resources where you can actually see the kind of introductory lectures you&amp;#39;d take.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;eg. you can search the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCEBb1b_L6zDS3xTUrIALZOw&quot;&gt;MIT OpenCourseWare&lt;/a&gt; by subject (they have playlists) or a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/reddit.com/comments/cktxy/reddit_lets_compile_a_list_of_the_best_online/&quot;&gt;whole list of other channels and websites&lt;/a&gt; compiled by reddit (even if 10 years ago, haven&amp;#39;t tried them all but the 5 I checked works fine).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 你的TPM 1.2芯片很有可能通过简单的更新升级到TPM 2.0。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK: 因为许多人在试图安装Windows 11时，会收到 "不支持的PC "警告，因为他们的TPM是1.2而不是2.0。
Windows 11，因为它有TPM 1.2而不是2.0。然而，一些OEM厂商提供了工具
提供升级TPM 2.0的工具。

首先，对于那些不知道整个事情是什么的人。
https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/enable-tpm-2...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhwl3d/ysk_theres_a_fair_chance_your_tpm_12_chip_can_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhwl3d/ysk_theres_a_fair_chance_your_tpm_12_chip_can_be/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 10:44:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Because many people get &amp;quot;Unsupported PC&amp;quot; warning when trying to install Windows 11 for having TPM 1.2 instead of 2.0. Some OEM&amp;#39;s however, provides tools for a TPM 2.0 upgrade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, for those who don&amp;#39;t know what&amp;#39;s the entire thing: &lt;a href=&quot;https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/enable-tpm-2-0-on-your-pc-1fd5a332-360d-4f46-a1e7-ae6b0c90645c&quot;&gt;https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/enable-tpm-2-0-on-your-pc-1fd5a332-360d-4f46-a1e7-ae6b0c90645c&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MS&amp;#39; justification as why it&amp;#39;s required: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tg9QUrnVFho&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tg9QUrnVFho&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And for those wondering what is TPM: &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trusted_Platform_Module&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trusted_Platform_Module&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL:DR if you want to install Windows 11 officially, you need TPM 2.0 support. There&amp;#39;s ways to bypass this, but MS says they won&amp;#39;t guarantee that you&amp;#39;ll get updates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s a chance, however, that your OEM is providing means to upgrade it to 2.0. As an example&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HP: &lt;a href=&quot;https://support.hp.com/au-en/document/c05381064&quot;&gt;https://support.hp.com/au-en/document/c05381064&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dell: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dell.com/support/kbdoc/tr-tr/000184894/how-to-successfully-update-the-tpm-firmware-on-your-dell-computer?lang=en&quot;&gt;https://www.dell.com/support/kbdoc/tr-tr/000184894/how-to-successfully-update-the-tpm-firmware-on-your-dell-computer?lang=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should be able to find your own OEM&amp;#39;s instructions on Google&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在电脑或任何类型的电子产品附近吸烟会产生后果]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK。

献给那些做出错误决定而染上尼古丁瘾的吸烟者朋友们。
是的，如果它靠近你的电脑，它可以而且会损坏它。

我注意到从我的电脑上传来了一种奇怪的声音，因为已经有将近一年的时间了。
我决定是时候这样做了，而且它可能......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhsznv/ysk_vaping_near_a_computer_or_any_kind_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhsznv/ysk_vaping_near_a_computer_or_any_kind_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 21:41:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To my fellow vapers who made the poor decision to pick up a nicotine addiction, yes, It can and will damage your PC if it gets near it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I noticed a weird sound coming from my pc, given it&amp;#39;s been almost a year since I&amp;#39;ve cleaned the thing, I decided it was time to do so and that it might be the cause of the issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I noticed a weird sticky substance around my CPU and GPU fans. At first I thought It was just because I haven&amp;#39;t cleaned it in so long. So I used a Q-tip and wiped it off a bit, or at least tried. It was stubborn. I later looked at it wondering what it was, and I smelled it. Smelled like pineapple. My favorite flavor at the time (haven&amp;#39;t touched a vape in three months :))&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only can it build up like what happened to me, but with research I found that many of the common ingredients in E-liquid are conductive, would could cause permanent damage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I never smoked and I&amp;#39;m just a teenager who made stupid decisions, but in stressful times I was going through 3 packs of cigs worth of nicotine in a day. Majority of those days was spent at my computer doing my online classes. my friend came over one day and she said my whole room smelled like the pineapple vape i was using. she&amp;#39;s used mine before and could instantly detect the smell, that&amp;#39;s how much i was using it. I cant imagine have badly it could be for someone who used/uses for a much longer time on their computer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This also applies to cigarettes, smoking and vaping THC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Side note 1: Nicotine isn&amp;#39;t cool and just because you discovered a gas station that doesn&amp;#39;t check ID&amp;#39;s isn&amp;#39;t an excuse to keep vaping and kick the habit,(most ppl here are gonna be 21 anyways but my point still stands) I was getting cheap fake disposables before from sketchy ppl and made the excuse of &amp;quot;i can keep doing it since it is legit and won&amp;#39;t hurt me as much and I&amp;#39;m safer from these people&amp;quot;. I don&amp;#39;t have the luxury of an older sibling like most of my friends, and when I discovered this gas station my usage went through the roof, and i made the mistake of telling people and now some friends beg me to go over there for them, especially girls because they don&amp;#39;t want to meet up with people. Not needing to pump nicotine in your system at least every few hours is nice, healthier, cheaper, less worrying, and if you&amp;#39;re like me you don&amp;#39;t have to worry about parents or getting pulled over. notice how this side note is almost as long as the post? Because the whole post wouldn&amp;#39;t be needed if people didn&amp;#39;t struggle like me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Side note 2: Please open your computer every few months and clean it out and look for any build up, this goes to everybody, not just vapers/smokers. But if you are a vaper/smoker you should definitely do it more often if you use in the same room as your computer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR : Don&amp;#39;t vape near your pc in an enclosed space, will build up and can cause issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你可以在谷歌广告设置中关闭赌博和酒精广告。]]></title><description><![CDATA[原因：澳大利亚马上就要到赛马季节了，我们中的一些人可能已经厌倦了看到越来越多的赌博广告。
看到越来越多的赌博广告而感到厌烦。或者是你想戒掉
赌博或喝酒。很高兴知道，你可以去谷歌广告设置
并将其关闭。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhjh9r/ysk_that_you_can_turn_off_gambling_and_alcohol/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhjh9r/ysk_that_you_can_turn_off_gambling_and_alcohol/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 19:44:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why ysk:
It&amp;#39;s gonna be horse racing season in Australia soon and some of us may be sick of seeing an increase of gambling ads. Or maybe you want to quit gambling or drinking. It&amp;#39;s good to know that you can go to google ads settings and turn it off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你的硬盘/SSD可以预测它何时会失效，而且很容易检查这个数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：它很简单，可以帮助你避免硬盘故障。

存储设备通过一种称为SMART的技术预测它们何时会出现故障。对于
硬盘，它可以预测75%的故障。

在Windows 7时代，当SMART预测到故障时，电脑会告诉你。
失败。电脑会说："你的硬盘坏了。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhein4/ysk_your_hard_drivessd_can_predict_when_its_going/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhein4/ysk_your_hard_drivessd_can_predict_when_its_going/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 11:06:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It’s simple and helps you avoid hard drive failure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Storage devices predict when they will fail with a technology called SMART. For hard drives, it predicts 75% of all failures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back in the Windows 7 era, computers would tell you when SMART predicted a failure. The computer would say a SMART failure is predicted when booting up, Windows 7 would give you errors every few minutes saying your hard drive is going to fail, and you couldn’t even install Windows 7 onto a failing drive unless you turned off the SMART check.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, for some reason, windows 10 has none of that. My hard drive was predicting a failure for 6 months before I caught it, because I was testing a diagnostic utility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, if you want to check, Download CrystalDiskInfo. It will say OK, Caution, or Bad. If it’s Caution, it means there are errors, (bad sectors), but the hard drive or SSD has reallocated them. This is still an indication of a bad drive. If it’s Bad, it means it’s , well, bad. Discontinue use of this drive. SSDs will have percentages instead. These are usually accurate, and measure the amount of life left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was running on a HDD with hundreds of bad sectors before I caught it. Before I pulled it, it had almost 1000. That drive was likely to crash at any moment. Luckily, I was able to catch it and copy off all the data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/S.M.A.R.T&quot;&gt;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/S.M.A.R.T&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：任何人都可以将堕胎药邮寄给他们。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：你不需要一个诊所。你可以安全地照顾好自己，并且
匿名的方式，这里有一个链接
[https://nwhn.org/safe-online-delivered-how-to-get-the-abortion-pill-by-mail/]
请公开地、经常地分享这一点。药片可以一直服用到怀孕第10周
怀孕的第10周。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhddco/ysk_anyone_can_have_an_abortion_pill_mailed_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qhddco/ysk_anyone_can_have_an_abortion_pill_mailed_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 03:34:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: You don’t need a clinic. You can take care of yourself safely and anonymously &lt;a href=&quot;https://nwhn.org/safe-online-delivered-how-to-get-the-abortion-pill-by-mail/&quot;&gt;HERES A LINK&lt;/a&gt; Please share this openly and often. The pill can be taken up until the 10th week of pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK关于邮局为没有地址的人提供的 "普通快递"。它是免费的，不需要申请。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么YSK：最小的邮政信箱是70美元/3个月。预付70美元。我的情况是
我的情况是，给我的谷仓是用来给青少年上免费课的，内容是如何从汽车上拆下发动机并安装新的发动机。
从汽车上拆下发动机并安装新的发动机，它的地址属于旁边的房子。
旁边的房子，而谷仓本身实际上需要自己的地址......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qh1va2/ysk_about_the_post_offices_general_delivery_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qh1va2/ysk_about_the_post_offices_general_delivery_for/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:49:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: the smallest P.O. Box is $70/3 months. $70 upfront. My situation is that the barn that was given to me to teach a free class to teenagers on how to remove engines from cars and install new ones, it&amp;#39;s address belongs to the house next to it, and the barn itself actually needs its own address because people live in the house. The properties are separate but share the same address.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go to your local post office, ask for general delivery instructions, and they will tell you how to receive mail to that post office. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My city only has one post office, so to format the address on my envelopes, it&amp;#39;s simply:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Name&lt;br/&gt;
General Delivery&lt;br/&gt;
City, State Zip  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, don&amp;#39;t forget to put in a change of address to whatever they format the post office gives you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: address format&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK烹饪和烘焙的区别]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：在烹饪方面，有无限的空间来试验不同的
的成分和比例。然而，当你在烘烤
面包/蛋糕等，配方的功能是酵母、面粉、糖和热量之间的化学反应。
面粉、糖和热量之间的化学反应。配比需要准确遵循，以创造出一个好的产品。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qh02wu/ysk_the_differences_between_cooking_and_baking/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qh02wu/ysk_the_differences_between_cooking_and_baking/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 17:48:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: with cooking, there&amp;#39;s infinite room to experiment with different ingredients and ratios in your recipes. However, when you&amp;#39;re baking bread/cake/etc. the recipe functions as a chemical reaction between the yeast, flour, sugar, and heat. The ratios need to be followed accurate to create a good final product. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You cook with your heart, you bake with a recipe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你是一个破产的大学生，不想为你所需的教科书支付巨额的费用，那么YSK这些网站]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：我很后悔为我所有的书支付硬拷贝，特别是在网上的一年之后。
年。这里是你通常可以找到它们的地方。


图书馆创世纪

这是大多数电子书的首选网站。一些工程类的教科书
也附有解决方案手册。搜索标题+"解决方案...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qgr59x/ysk_these_websites_if_you_are_a_broke_college/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qgr59x/ysk_these_websites_if_you_are_a_broke_college/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 09:41:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I regret paying hard copies of all my books, especially after an online year. Here is where you can usually find them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Library Genesis&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the go-to site for most ebooks. Some of the engineering textbooks comes with the solution manual as well. Searching for the title + &amp;quot;solution manual&amp;quot; will give you some results. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Ch36650lut10n5 (cheggsolutions)&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A website which has textbook solutions ripped from chegg. It has quite a lot of books and free, no need to sign up or give any credentials. You can find many textbook solutions that are not on libgen or zlibrary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Zlibrary&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is another site where you can try if you can&amp;#39;t find it in Library Genesis.
You may need an account if you exceed the download limit. If you do not like to use your personal email, you can opt to use a temporary mail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Slader&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for textbook solutions for free, check Slader. You have to sign up to access materials, after that you can access many solution manuals written by teachers and professors. 
They recently installed a limit, trying to make access to answers a paid service unfortunately. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Studylib&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the name itself says it’s like a library, where you can have a large number of assignments and solutions. You can also share your notes with your friends which would help them to solve the problems. It will provide you with a solution for all the subjects. You can also upload your documents and find the solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Pdfdrive&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An online PDF search engine that lets you search, preview and download PDFs. According to the site as of right now, there are over 75 million eBooks, magazines, articles, and more that are indexed and discoverable directly on PDF Drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Sci-Hub&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great place for finding published journal/conference papers that are (usually) paywalled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;AudioBookBay&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If what you want is audiobooks then audiobookbay is the go-to place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good luck on your new semester everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为饮食失调是最容易导致死亡的精神疾病]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：饮食失调往往没有像其他精神疾病那样被认真对待
但它们应该得到重视。现在，我们都非常清楚精神健康问题导致的自杀危险。
但抑郁症和类似的情况还不是最致命的精神疾病，而是由精神健康问题导致的自杀。
甚至不是最致命的精神疾病。身体羞辱和...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qgoc3c/ysk_that_eating_disorders_are_the_mental_illness/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qgoc3c/ysk_that_eating_disorders_are_the_mental_illness/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 07:23:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Eating disorders are often not taken as seriously as other mental illnesses but they should be.
By now we are all very aware of the dangers of suicide caused by mental health problems, but depression and similar conditions aren’t even the most deadly of mental illnesses. Body shaming and the pressure to be thin has very serious risks for vulnerable people in society. Be mindful of what you say about food and weight around vulnerable people and if you suffer from an eating disorder please know that you matter and please seek help.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK的长度为你的手、前臂和至少一个手指。当附近没有尺子时，它对测量东西会很有用。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：如果你发现自己需要知道一个物体的大致尺寸，但身边却没有尺子或卷尺。
如果你发现自己需要知道一个物体的大致尺寸，但你身边没有尺子或测量带，能够用你的身体来测量它
用你的身体来测量，就会变得非常有用。

我正在寻找一个新的沙发，在商店里发现了一个很棒的沙发，价格也很便宜。
价格。唯一的问题是...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qgjqp0/ysk_the_length_of_your_hand_forearm_and_at_least/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qgjqp0/ysk_the_length_of_your_hand_forearm_and_at_least/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 05:43:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: if you ever find yourself needing to know the approximate size of an object but have no ruler or measurer tape near you, being able to measure it with your body becomes extremely useful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was looking for a new couch and found an awesome one at the store for a great price. The only problem is that I didn&amp;#39;t know if it was slim enough to go through my front door. Fortunately I know that my open hand is about 20cm wide, and coincidentally knew that my front door is 90cm wide. Got it wrong by 3cm but the couch fitted alright.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another useful thing to learn is being able to measure larger distances by steps, but that&amp;#39;s a skill I have not yet mastered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK大多数州都有当前道路状况的在线地图，因此你可以安全地计划冬季旅行。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：道路状况是不断变化的，在同一路段上可能有很大的不同。
因此，拥有一张最新的路况地图是非常重要的。
对于制定冬季的安全旅行计划非常有用。美国国家海洋和大气管理局（NOAA）已经编制了一份清单，其中包括
有道路状况地图的州的名单...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qg6orj/ysk_most_states_have_online_maps_of_current_road/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qg6orj/ysk_most_states_have_online_maps_of_current_road/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 20:35:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Road conditions are constantly changing and can vary considerably over the same stretch of road, so having an up to date map of conditions is very useful for making safe travel plans in winter. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weather.gov/cys/unitedstatesroadconditions&quot;&gt;NOAA has compiled a list of states that have road condition maps available.&lt;/a&gt; Safe travels!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：沃尔玛对其会计系统进行了审计，并悄悄地将工资支票寄到前员工的非常旧的地址上。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：我上次在那里工作是在2014-2015年。我只在那里工作了6个月
就收到了一张13美元的支票，寄到我6年前最后使用的地址。我知道这
我知道这对我来说不是一个重要的数额，但我听说在那里工作时间较长的员工的工资在200美元左右。
但我听说在那里工作时间较长的员工的奖金在200美元左右。我希望这个词能被...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qg9x0z/ysk_walmart_conducted_an_audit_of_their/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qg9x0z/ysk_walmart_conducted_an_audit_of_their/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 17:46:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I last worked there from 2014-2015. I only worked there for 6 months and got a $13 check sent to the address I last used 6 years ago. I know it wasn&amp;#39;t a significant amount of money to me but I&amp;#39;ve heard it being in the $200 range for employees who worked there longer. I&amp;#39;d like the word to be spread so former associates can get the money they are entitled to if they have moved since they last worked at walmart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：当有人说 "什么？"时，很可能不是因为他们没有听到，而是因为他们没有理解你的意思，或者他们需要时间来制定一个回应。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：大多数时候，当有人说 "什么？"时，你会简单地重复一下
自己。这通常会失败，他们就会再次说 "什么？"。

与其只是重复自己，不如放慢速度，说得更清楚。
然后用不同的词再说一遍。这将给他们时间来...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qg51ph/ysk_when_someone_says_what_its_most_likely_not/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qg51ph/ysk_when_someone_says_what_its_most_likely_not/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 14:45:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Most of the time, when someone says “What?”, you will simply repeat yourself. This will usually fail, and they will just say “What?” again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of just repeating yourself, you should slow down, speak more clearly, and say it again but using different words. This will give them time to process your question/statement and formulate a response.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Example 1 (This actually happened to me):&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy (speaking quickly): So did you stay at Ben’s?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me (thinking something about a Mercedes Benz): … What?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy (same speed): Did you stay at Ben’s?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me: … … Sorry, what?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy (probably frustrated): Did you stay at Ben’s?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me (finally getting it): Oh… yeah, I did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Example 2 (How it should have gone):&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy (speaking quickly): So did you stay at Ben’s?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me (thinking something about a Mercedes Benz): … What?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy (slower): Did you stay over at Ben’s place last night?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me: Yeah, I did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：沃尔玛.com为了与亚马逊竞争，允许第三方骗子使用他们的网站进行销售。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：人们通常认为，如果他们在沃尔玛的网站上购买，就是从零售商那里购买。
他们就是从零售商那里购买的。

这不一定是真的。第三方卖家被允许在其网站上销售。
他们中的一些人是骗子，出售有问题的产品，或者只是拿消费者的钱给他们。
消费者的钱并给他们...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qfzbhw/ysk_walmart_com_in_an_attempt_to_compete_with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qfzbhw/ysk_walmart_com_in_an_attempt_to_compete_with/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 08:39:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: People often expect that if they&amp;#39;re buying from Walmart&amp;#39;s website, they&amp;#39;re buying from a retailer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not necessarily true. 3rd party sellers are allowed to sell on their website, and some of them are scammers who sell faulty products, or simply take the consumer&amp;#39;s money and give them nothing. Reviews are sometimes skewed using fake reviews and bot reviews. You&amp;#39;ll know when you&amp;#39;ve got enough real reviews on a seller. The point you should take home here is that buying from walmart .com is not buying from a retailer at all. It&amp;#39;s a marketplace full of individual sellers, and some of them don&amp;#39;t have any qualms scamming you -which they will if you let them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Streamlined for efficiency&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如果你在帖子上头版后删除了它，人们仍然可以阅读它。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：因为你认为你可以发布任何东西，并在之后简单地删除它。
实际上有一个小故障，在显示 "删除 "信息之前，会加载大约半秒钟的文本。
显示 "删除 "信息。即使你退缩并再次点击，它也会
在加载 "删除 "信息之前继续显示文本....。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qfrxao/ysk_if_you_delete_a_post_after_it_makes_it_to_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qfrxao/ysk_if_you_delete_a_post_after_it_makes_it_to_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 23:40:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: In case you think you can post anything and simply remove it after, there is actually a glitch that loads the text for about half a second before displaying the “deleted” message. Even if you back out and click again it will keep displaying the text before loading the “deleted” message. This means anyone can actually screencap your “deleted” message.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你的安卓手机在输入15个错误的PIN码后，会自动设置重置]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：这种设置适合于可能有敏感信息的商业电话，但不一定适合个人电话，因为个人电话一般都有敏感信息。
敏感信息，但不一定适用于个人电话，因为个人电话通常被扔在口袋或钱包里。
扔在口袋或钱包里。身体部位或物体接触到屏幕可以
触发它，导致它开机并接受 "输入"。快速和...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qfhk5p/ysk_your_android_phone_comes_set_to_reset_itself/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qfhk5p/ysk_your_android_phone_comes_set_to_reset_itself/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 17:32:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:  This setting is good for business phones which may have sensitive information on them, but not necessarily for personal phones which are typically tossed in a pocket or purse. Body parts or objects touching the screen can trigger it, causing it to come on and accept &amp;quot;input&amp;quot;. Quickly and suddenly you could find yourself looking at the initial setup screen. Pictures, messages, contacts, etc. - all could be lost completely if not backed up, and require a lengthy restore if they are backed up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Settings, Lock Screen, Secure Lock Settings (requires PIN), you can turn off &amp;quot;Auto factory reset&amp;quot; if you wish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：研究发现，随着时间的推移，你经常喝酒的次数越多，你患乳腺癌的机会就越高。如果你是一个女人，你每周喝3杯，你的几率比完全不喝酒的女人高15%。而每多喝一次/周，这种风险估计会上升10%。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么YSK：每个人都喜欢ta-tas
https://www.webmd.com/breast-cancer/guide/link-between-breast-cancer-and-alcohol]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qf6zfz/ysk_studies_have_found_that_the_more_you_drink/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qf6zfz/ysk_studies_have_found_that_the_more_you_drink/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 03:39:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: everyone loves ta-tas &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.webmd.com/breast-cancer/guide/link-between-breast-cancer-and-alcohol&quot;&gt;https://www.webmd.com/breast-cancer/guide/link-between-breast-cancer-and-alcohol&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你的盒子里有Funko pop数字，你可以在Funko应用程序上扫描它们，根据各网站的互联网销售情况对它们进行估值。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：流行人物是广泛的收藏品，限量版或拱形的
不再生产的数字可以价值数百甚至数千。我发现
我发现了一个应用程序，你扫描盒子底部的条形码，发现我拥有的一个公仔价值200美元，它不是限量版或...
我发现我拥有的一个价值200美元，它不是限量版或...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qf5dyu/ysk_if_you_have_funko_pop_figures_in_the_box_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qf5dyu/ysk_if_you_have_funko_pop_figures_in_the_box_you/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 02:42:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Pop figures are widely collectable with limited edition or vaulted figures no longer in production can be worth hundreds If not thousands. I found out about the app where you scan the barcode at the bottom of the box and found out one I own is worth $200, it&amp;#39;s not limited edition or anything it&amp;#39;s just older (2015-2018) around then which has stopped production on so that figure is worth alot more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was shocked when I saw my collection was worth triple what I spent only 4-5 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：要避免所谓的健康食品，其中菊苣根在成分清单上的位置很高。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：因为它是一种廉价的纤维添加剂，会导致气体和其他症状。
胃肠道不适的症状。

有一种叫做菊粉的纤维，在低到中等量的情况下是一种
是一种良好的益生菌和可溶性纤维的来源。然而，大量使用时，它可以
导致气体、腹胀和腹痛。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qetzbp/ysk_to_avoid_supposedly_healthy_foods_with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qetzbp/ysk_to_avoid_supposedly_healthy_foods_with/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 21:47:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Because it&amp;#39;s a cheap fiber additive that causes gas and other symptoms of gastrointestinal discomfort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a type of fiber called inulin, which in low to moderate amounts is a good prebiotic and source of soluble fiber. However, in large amounts it can cause gas, bloating, and abdominal pain. Chicory root is one of the most common sources of inulin because it&amp;#39;s cheap, abundant, and in powder form can be added to almost anything to boost that food&amp;#39;s total fiber numbers without significantly impacting taste or texture. Everything from cereals to granola bars to fiber gummies and beyond has it these days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chicory root at near the bottom of the ingredients list doesn&amp;#39;t worry me. But, when it&amp;#39;s towards the top, I avoid it. Also, don&amp;#39;t assume because you bought a product once and it didn&amp;#39;t have chicory root that it never will. Food manufacturers change up the ingredients subtly all the time and it&amp;#39;s not at all uncommon for me to check a box of cereal I&amp;#39;ve been eating for a long time and suddenly notice it now has it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，当你在使用VPN时被要求在谷歌上验证是否为人类时，这是他们试图故意惹恼你，以便你关闭VPN。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么YSK这样做？因为隐私]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qer7kz/ysk_that_when_you_get_asked_to_verify_being_human/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qer7kz/ysk_that_when_you_get_asked_to_verify_being_human/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 14:14:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK this? Because privacy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK说，不是所有的虐待都是身体上的，如果有人在情感上一直让你感到难过，那仍然是100%的虐待，同样糟糕。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么YSK：精神虐待使成千上万的人陷入抑郁和自杀，没有人值得这样做。
没有人值得这样。

如果你和一个从未接触过你的人纠缠在一起，但他们却在贬低你，伤害你的精神状态，这仍然是100%的虐待。
贬低你并伤害你的精神状态，这仍然是100%的虐待。如果有人
让你不断质疑自己，并且...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qeqkyc/ysk_that_not_all_abuse_is_physical_and_if_someone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qeqkyc/ysk_that_not_all_abuse_is_physical_and_if_someone/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 12:34:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Mental.Abuse drives thousands of people to depression and suicide and nobody deserves that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#39;re struggling with someone that has never touched you but they are degrading you and harming your mental state, that&amp;#39;s still 100% abuse. If someone makes you question yourself constantly and forces you to ask yourself constantly why it&amp;#39;s your fault? That&amp;#39;s 100% abuse. You&amp;#39;re not an asshole,.you&amp;#39;re not a bad person you just need another human that will appreciate you for you. If you need or want to talk to someone that can understand, message me or ANYONE in your life that you know loves you. Trust me, if can save your sanity, maybe even your life. You don&amp;#39;t need to feel bad for being alive. There is hope and love for your out there, don&amp;#39;t let yourself be taken down this way. You deserve better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：亚马逊因销售过期和无用的一氧化碳检测器而臭名昭著。阅读评论，知道要找什么。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么YSK：一氧化碳探测器平均在7年后过期。

过期的探测器会在一氧化碳含量达到致命程度时无法报警，而且
也会在荒唐的时候对没有危险的东西发出警报。这
这就产生了一个次要的危险，因为它造成了 "狼来了的男孩"......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qeg5ro/ysk_amazon_is_notorious_for_selling_expired_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qeg5ro/ysk_amazon_is_notorious_for_selling_expired_and/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 00:34:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK : Carbon Monoxide detectors expire, on average, after 7 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expired detectors will fail to alarm when carbon monoxide levels are deadly, and will also go off at ridiculous times for something that is no danger. This creates a secondary danger as it creates the &amp;quot;boy who cries wolf&amp;quot; effect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amazon is notorious of selling very expired carbon monoxide detectors that will waste your money, your time, and not save your life in the event of high levels of carbon monoxide in your home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s is a great example of something to NEVER buy, that is shown as the top recommended on Amazon, sold by Amazon:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B002GP7CZS/ref=cm_sw_em_r_mt_dp_dl_GK3039N6GJWWJGX8WWSS?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;psc=1&quot;&gt;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B002GP7CZS/ref=cm_sw_em_r_mt_dp_dl_GK3039N6GJWWJGX8WWSS?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;psc=1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Always check the manufacture date on the back of a carbon monoxide detector. Replace after 7 years&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你不得不迅速离开一个房间，一定要告诉对方你要去洗手间。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：有许多原因使你可能需要快速离开一个房间，而且
你总是可以用 "自然召唤 "作为理由。如果你身处的环境是
他们不希望你去洗手间，那么在那里可能就不安全了。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qec8ko/ysk_if_you_ever_have_to_quickly_leave_a_room/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qec8ko/ysk_if_you_ever_have_to_quickly_leave_a_room/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 23:38:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: There are many reasons why you might need to quickly leave a room, and you can always use &amp;quot;nature calls&amp;quot; as a reason. If you&amp;#39;re in a situation where they don&amp;#39;t want you to go to the bathroom, it might not be safe to be there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，如果你要离开家几个小时，你的宠物可能会喜欢低音量的冷色调器乐。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：当宠物被单独留在家中时，它们的生活可能会变得单调，而音乐是使它们的生活更加愉快的最佳方式之一。
音乐是让它们生活得更愉快的最好方法之一 我的猫咪喜欢lofi chillhop &
旧视频游戏曲目的翻唱，例如]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qecptt/ysk_that_if_you_are_going_to_be_away_from_home/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qecptt/ysk_that_if_you_are_going_to_be_away_from_home/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 22:34:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Pet&amp;#39;s lives can get monotonous when left home alone and music is one of the best ways to make their lives more enjoyable! My cats love lofi chillhop &amp;amp; remixes of old video game tracks, for example&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK的有机水果和蔬菜都有化学残留物，只是没有合成杀虫剂的残留。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：有机产品可能包括与传统产品相同的化学成分。
含有相同的化学物质（但比例不一）。
需要冲洗以避免摄入。

在美国，有机产品也可能有化学残留物，但区别在于
有机产品只能...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qe4l09/ysk_organic_fruits_and_veggies_have_chemical/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qe4l09/ysk_organic_fruits_and_veggies_have_chemical/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 16:25:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Organic produce can include the same chemical compounds as conventional produce sprayed with synthetic pesticides (but at more variable rates), and needs to be rinsed to avoid ingesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the US, organic produce can also have chemical residue, but the difference is organics can only be treated with certain classes of chemicals. Most traditional pesticides are synthetically produced chemical compounds, and these aren&amp;#39;t allowed to be applied to organic crops. Organic crops can have the same chemical compounds applied, if they&amp;#39;re not produced synthetically, but are produced by a bacteria that &amp;#39;poops&amp;#39; out the same chemical (along with many additional chemical compounds). These safe, beneficial bacteria are sprayed on the plants or soil. The chemical compound is exactly the same, but because it&amp;#39;s a biological pesticide, it&amp;#39;s okay to apply. Chemical products like pesticides are regulated much, much more heavily than other products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chemical applications have to follow a lot of rules, for example,  they usually can&amp;#39;t be applied after flowering, and since the fruit develops from a pollinated flower, it&amp;#39;s really the leaves and stems that take the chemical load, not the fruit. And vegetables that grow underground like potatoes and onions don&amp;#39;t get exposed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a PhD in an agricultural plant genetics, and have worked in the biological agriculture industry (but don&amp;#39;t anymore). Personally, I don&amp;#39;t worry too much about organic, and believe it&amp;#39;s better to buy local (from a conventional or organic farmer). If the produce has been picked more quickly, it will have a better nutritional profile (higher nutrient and micronutrient levels, greater diversity of flavonoids like carotenoids and anthocyanins, and other antioxidants). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to buy organic, focus on leafy greens and international fruit, especially bananas -- where organic means a better quality of work and life for the workers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 有时候，你的卫生间会需要一次以上的冲水。这也没关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：这主要是与公共厕所有关，尽管我相信你的
我相信你的室友也会同意。如果你把大便或卫生纸漂浮在公共厕所里
如果你把大便或卫生纸漂浮在公共厕所里，人们往往会感到恶心，不想使用那个厕所。
另外，如果你在一个多档位的厕所里拉了一坨特别臭的大便......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qe62lg/ysk_sometimes_your_bathroom_session_will_require/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qe62lg/ysk_sometimes_your_bathroom_session_will_require/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 16:25:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: This is mostly pertaining to public toilets, though I&amp;#39;m sure your housemates will approve as well. If you leave poop or toilet paper floating in a public toilet people tend to get grossed out and not want to use that toilet. Also, if you&amp;#39;re having a particularly smelly poop in a multi-stall bathroom, it&amp;#39;s okay to have periodic courtesy flushes so your stank isn&amp;#39;t just sitting there under you. Plus, who wants to be the nasty dude at work who leaves gross toilets? Bathroom etiquette goes a long way&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 又到了一年中检查轮胎压力的时候了。更冷的空气会占据更少的体积。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：天气寒冷，压力低。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qdtd07/ysk_its_that_time_of_year_again_to_check_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qdtd07/ysk_its_that_time_of_year_again_to_check_your/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 01:49:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: weather cold, pressure low.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如果你在美国的公共服务部门工作，你可能有资格获得过去不符合条件的付款抵扣联邦贷款的豁免。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：这是一个有限的机会，通过美国的公共服务工作者提供。
这是由美国教育部提供给公共服务工作者的有限机会，很少有媒体报道，并且要求你在10月31日前提交PSLF（公共服务贷款豁免）表格。
2021年10月31日之前提交PSLF（公共服务贷款豁免）表格。由于你
由于你可以获得早在2007年10月的付款信用，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qdp5hp/ysk_if_you_work_in_public_service_in_the_us_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qdp5hp/ysk_if_you_work_in_public_service_in_the_us_you/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 00:42:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; This is a limited opportunity offered to public service workers through the US Dept of Education, has received very little press, and requires you to submit a PSLF (Public Service Loan Forgiveness) form by &lt;strong&gt;Oct 31, 2021&lt;/strong&gt;. Since you can get credits for payments as far back as October 2007, this could potentially eliminate your debt or get you significantly closer to forgiveness. You can find out more information, how to apply, and if you would qualify at &lt;a href=&quot;https://studentaid.gov/announcements-events/pslf-limited-waiver&quot;&gt;https://studentaid.gov/announcements-events/pslf-limited-waiver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are you a public service worker?&lt;/strong&gt;
If you are employed by any federal government agency full time, you count as a public service worker. But that&amp;#39;s not all! You are also considered one if you work full time for a state government, local government, tribal government, the US military, or a not-for-profit organization. You also may qualify if you work in education, public health, law enforcement, emergency management, elder or disability care, or at a library. The website linked above provides more specific information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do not work for the federal government or in finance or with student loans, so I cannot provide advice or any guarantees. I just figured I should share this because I literally found out about this yesterday, the deadline is October 31st, and the form was easy to complete and submit, at least in my case. Hope this helps someone in these rough times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你早上起床有困难，可以试着打开窗帘睡觉。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：获得良好的睡眠对每天的健康生活至关重要。作为
作为一个几年来睡眠质量很差的人，这个小建议对我的帮助很大。
极大的帮助。

在我的大学时代，我睡在一个没有窗户的房间里。漆黑一片。我
每天早上6点醒来，感觉就像我被一个...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qds8sb/ysk_if_you_have_trouble_getting_out_of_bed_in_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qds8sb/ysk_if_you_have_trouble_getting_out_of_bed_in_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 00:42:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Getting good sleep is essential for a healthy day to day life. As someone who slept terribly for a few years, this small tip helped me out immensely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During my college years, i slept in a room with no windows. Pitch black. I&amp;#39;d wake up at 6am every morning feeling like i had been hit by a truck and it would take me pretty much half of the morning to get my brain going. After that, i moved and had a bedroom with one window over my bed. Out of lazyness, i started sleeping with the curtains open and over time noticed i slept better, woke up fresher and not feeling as heavy as before. I looked it up and basically what happens is that the gradual increase in the level of light in the room will stop the melatonin production in your brain, essentially making you less sleepy over time, even while you are still asleep, so you don&amp;#39;t jump from deep sleep state to awake. This will help you get out of bed easier and up and running much faster. Here&amp;#39;s a short article on how to sleep better: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.sciencefocus.com/the-human-body/how-to-get-the-perfect-nights-sleep/amp/&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.sciencefocus.com/the-human-body/how-to-get-the-perfect-nights-sleep/amp/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope someone finds this useful. For me it was a game changer. Everyone&amp;#39;s sleep is different, so give it a try, you&amp;#39;ve got nothing to lose :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你现在应该检查你的借记卡/信用卡账单，看看是否有标题为 "POS DEBIT GOOGLE[随机人名]"的费用，大约为12.99-13.01美元。这是一个新的骗局，我昨天才注意到。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK。

昨天随机查看了我的借记卡账单，发现有一笔奇怪的费用。
因为我很少使用我的借记卡。我取消了这张卡并得到了
退款，但当我进一步调查时，这似乎是一个新的骗局，可能是一些数据泄露。
可能是一些数据泄露，因为我和一些人...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qdn2h0/ysk_you_should_check_your_debitcredit_card/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qdn2h0/ysk_you_should_check_your_debitcredit_card/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 20:00:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Checked my debit card statement randomly yesterday, noticed a strange charge, since I hardly ever use my debit card. Cancelled the card and am getting refunded, but when I looked into it more, it looks like this is a new scam going around, possibly some data breach, since myself and a few other comments I&amp;#39;ve read rarely/never use their cards for any physical purchases. See more info here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/personalfinance/comments/q2eyyv/got_a_random_charge_under_pos_google_debit/&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/personalfinance/comments/q2eyyv/got_a_random_charge_under_pos_google_debit/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/personalfinance/comments/pgmvw7/google_charged_me_two_1299_charges_and_i_dont/&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/personalfinance/comments/pgmvw7/google_charged_me_two_1299_charges_and_i_dont/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.callercenter.com/650-253-0000.html&quot;&gt;https://www.callercenter.com/650-253-0000.html&lt;/a&gt; (this is the phone number listed in the info of the debit card charge, it&amp;#39;s for google apparently, but most of the responses on that site are people complaining of similar fraudulent charges on their cards)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你把自己看作是你所讲的关于自己的故事的人物、英雄或作者，YSK。它可以解释很多关于你的内心生活。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么YSK：你总是在不经意间讲述一些关于你自己的不成文的故事。
它指导你如何应对压力--无论你把它们看作是威胁还是挑战，是挣扎还是生活中的障碍。
它们是威胁还是挑战，是挣扎还是障碍，都是生活的一部分。在
心理学上，这被称为叙事...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qdi1y3/ysk_if_you_see_yourself_as_a_character_hero_or/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qdi1y3/ysk_if_you_see_yourself_as_a_character_hero_or/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 17:02:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK: There’s always some unwritten story you tell about yourself without being aware of it, and it guides how you respond to stressors - whether you see them as threats or challenges, struggles or obstacles that are part of life. In psychology, this is called &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/269603657_Narrative_Identity&quot;&gt;narrative identity&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;A character&lt;/strong&gt; is someone who thinks that stuff happens to them, that their successes or failures result from external factors beyond their control.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;A hero&lt;/strong&gt; is someone who isn’t afraid to go to battle to overcome the curveballs life throws at them.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;An author&lt;/strong&gt; embraces everything that happens to them and takes responsibility for creating something beautiful and meaningful out of their experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s more about this concept in &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@Ellie_/3be15461d9bd&quot;&gt;this article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在美国的高速公路上开车时，左边的车道是用来通行的!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我和其他许多人一样，没有被教过如何在高速公路和多车道上开车。
我的驾驶教练没有教我如何在高速公路和多车道的道路上正确驾驶。我学会了正确的方法
后来是由我父亲教的。

许多人把左边的车道称为 "快车道"，因为他们认为如果他们的速度超过了限速，他们就会
他们认为如果他们的速度超过了限速，他们就...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qd853j/ysk_when_driving_on_a_highway_in_america_the_left/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qd853j/ysk_when_driving_on_a_highway_in_america_the_left/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 06:29:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I, like I&amp;#39;m sure many other people, was not taught how to drive on highways and multi-lane roads correctly by my driving instructor. I learned the correct way later on by my dad. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people call the left lane the &amp;quot;fast lane&amp;quot; because they assume if they are going faster than the speed limit they are in the correct Lane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is just not true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The left lane is for passing folks in the right lane and when you&amp;#39;ve cleared them and have space, MOVE OVER TO THE RIGHT LANE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There will ALWAYS be someone moving faster than you, don&amp;#39;t try to &amp;quot;help them control their driving speed.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: driving on highways incorrectly causes traffic which causes accidents. Everyone has somewhere they&amp;#39;d rather be so why not make it easier for everyone by making the roads better to drive on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: true it&amp;#39;s not &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; for passing, check w your states laws&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你应该知道，测谎仪不是测谎仪。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：这只是一个延续的神话，我认为人们应该知道。
虽然我很喜欢这个事实，即它使警察在对付真正的罪犯时有优势，但它也可能被滥用来吓唬无辜的人。
它也可能被滥用来吓唬无辜的人，试图迫使他们招供。
供认。此外，它还被一些公司和政府使用...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qd64p4/ysk_you_should_know_that_polygraph_machines_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qd64p4/ysk_you_should_know_that_polygraph_machines_are/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 03:41:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: It is just a perpetuated myth that I think people should know about. While I do like the fact that it gives police an edge against real criminals, it could also be abused to frighten innocent individuals in an attempt to force a confession. Also, it is used by some companies and government organizations when they are hiring, which makes absolutely no sense since they are far less than accurate and they know that. Even the inventor of the original polygraph machine said it wasn&amp;#39;t a lie detector and would be vocal about how it&amp;#39;s bullshit. It only has around a 40% success rate when it comes to &amp;quot;spotting lies&amp;quot;. It has an even lower success rate when you take into account people with anxiety, or people on drugs. Additionally, pathological liars and psychopaths usually pass polygraphs with flying colors. And people can be trained to pass the polygraph, you can alter results just by thinking stressful thoughts and clenching your butthole (seriously). Police know that it&amp;#39;s BS and tend to stick to using it as an interrogation tool, but fuck that shit if a company tries to get you to take a polygraph to apply for a job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK - 你可以在车里给自己做海姆利克急救法。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：人们经常在开车时吃东西，而在开车时发生窒息的情况是正确的。
在驾驶汽车时发生窒息，就像在州际公路上以70英里的速度行驶时发现摩托车头盔里有一只蜘蛛一样。
在州际公路上以70英里的速度行驶时，发现摩托车头盔里有一只蜘蛛。

如果你在开车时开始窒息，请立即靠边停车，并在你的座位上挂上安全带。
你的座位上尝试计划...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qceeq9/ysk_you_can_give_yourself_the_heimlich_maneuver/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qceeq9/ysk_you_can_give_yourself_the_heimlich_maneuver/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 13:44:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: People often eat while driving, and experiencing choking while you&amp;#39;re driving a car is right up there with discovering a spider in your motorcycle helmet while doing 70 on the interstate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the event that you begin choking while driving, pull over immediately and in your seat try Plan A.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make a fist (it&amp;#39;s best to do this with your non-dominant hand but it doesn&amp;#39;t really matter). Put the thumb of your fist against your stomach, below your ribs and above your belly button. Grab your fist firmly with the other hand and jam it AS HARD AS YOU CAN up and under your ribcage with a fast punching movement. You&amp;#39;re literally trying to suckerpunch yourself. It doesn&amp;#39;t matter if it hurts. If it works you&amp;#39;ll have plenty of time to complain. If it doesn&amp;#39;t, it won&amp;#39;t bother you for long. So lean into it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this doesn&amp;#39;t work within fifteen seconds (or your arm gets too tired). Stand up, open your car door, and lean over your car door. Same idea (this is commonly done with a chair), quick thrusts until the object clears from your throat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of people are taught the chair technique, but almost nobody knows that you can use a car door with the same training and results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay safe out there kids.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 心理健康应用程序可能是污名化和肤浅的，而人工智能并不能使事情变得更好。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我刚刚读了一篇文章
[https://hazelgale.medium.com/mental-health-tech-is-broken-were-betting-on-games-to-fix-it-e1c413890a25]
这篇文章让我感到震惊，似乎有什么重要的东西要与你分享。

为什么是YSK。

所以，事实证明，只有少数人（不到20%）活...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qcoxa1/ysk_mental_health_apps_can_be_stigmatising_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qcoxa1/ysk_mental_health_apps_can_be_stigmatising_and/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 13:30:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just read &lt;a href=&quot;https://hazelgale.medium.com/mental-health-tech-is-broken-were-betting-on-games-to-fix-it-e1c413890a25&quot;&gt;an article&lt;/a&gt; that stunned me and it seemed like something important to share with you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, it turns out that only a small minority of people (less than 20%) live with positive levels of mental health, and over 80% of us will likely experience clinical symptoms at some point in our lives. Mental healthcare is broken pretty much everywhere and many of us will count on digital solutions for help. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, there are a lot of problems with those, and you should be aware of them so you can make well-informed decisions about how you take care of your wellbeing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To cite just two examples from the article:&lt;br/&gt;
One, AI therapists/chatbots are nowhere close to mimicking human conversations that make you feel connected, heard and seen. They are machine-like, shallow and often insensitive. “For example, one chatbot, when told “I am depressed,” responded dismissively: ‘Maybe the weather is affecting you’.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two, mental health apps can create self-stigma. “Users who are experiencing low-level symptoms of a disorder may feel labeled by an app that assumes that they have a clinical diagnosis. Self-stigma from this labeling can be harmful, lowering self-esteem and self-efficacy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://hazelgale.medium.com/mental-health-tech-is-broken-were-betting-on-games-to-fix-it-e1c413890a25&quot;&gt;Here’s&lt;/a&gt; the full article.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK："女士 "是对女性的一种婚姻中立的尊称，与对男性的 "先生 "使用完全相同。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：你应该知道这一点，这样你就可以在正式场合称呼女性时选择适当的术语。
你应该知道这一点，这样你就可以在正式场合称呼妇女时选择适当的术语，并避免误解这个术语的含义。I
我经常看到很多关于这个术语的混淆和误解。

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ms。

"小姐"、"夫人 "和 "女士 "都是...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qcbond/ysk_ms_is_a_marriageneutral_honorific_for_women/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qcbond/ysk_ms_is_a_marriageneutral_honorific_for_women/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 22:33:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: You should know this so you can select the appropriate term to use when addressing women in formal contexts, and to avoid misinterpreting this term. I often see a lot of confusion and misconceptions about this term. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ms&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ms&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Miss,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Mrs.&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Ms.&amp;quot; are all abbreviations of &amp;quot;Mistress.&amp;quot; Originally, all three abbreviations were in common use and used interchangeably, but over time &amp;quot;Miss&amp;quot; came to mean an unmarried woman, &amp;quot;Mrs.&amp;quot; a married woman, and &amp;quot;Ms.&amp;quot; fell out of favor. This forced women to be addressed according to their marital status, while &amp;quot;Mr.&amp;quot; (short for Mister) remained marriage-neutral. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently, &amp;quot;Ms.&amp;quot; (pronounced &amp;quot;mizz&amp;quot;) has been revived as a marriage neutral honorific for women and it has become increasingly popular. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few misconceptions I&amp;#39;ve noticed: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;People think &amp;quot;Ms.&amp;quot; means a woman is divorced or widowed (it does not- though divorced women might be more likely to use it)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;People think &amp;quot;Ms.&amp;quot; is short for &amp;quot;miss&amp;quot; and means the same thing (it does not- Miss means an unmarried woman, Ms. is marriage-neutral).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;People think &amp;quot;Ms.&amp;quot; is pronounced the same as &amp;quot;miss.&amp;quot; (some regional accents pronounce &amp;quot;miss&amp;quot; as &amp;quot;mizz&amp;quot; so in those places they are pronounced similarly, but for places where &amp;quot;miss&amp;quot; is pronounced with an s sound they are pronounced differently). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So  in conclusion, if you&amp;#39;re not sure if a woman is married (or you want to just skip the whole marriage issue altogether) you can use the honorific Ms. Use it exactly how you would use &amp;quot;Mr.&amp;quot; for men. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bonus YSK: a common gender-neural honorific for non-binary people is &amp;quot;Mx.&amp;quot; (pronounced like &amp;quot;mix&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;meks&amp;quot;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如果你通过经销商购买了维修保修，如果你要换车或该车被撞毁，你可以得到退款]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么YSK......如果你最终换掉了通过经销商购买的车辆，或者如果你将车辆彻底报废，维修保证可以被退还。
如果你通过经销商购买的车辆最终被换掉，或者如果你的车辆因交通事故而被清空，那么维修保单可以退还。
事故。可能会导致有利的退款。

我最近换了一辆仍有延长保养保修期的suv。
我最近换了一辆suv，它仍然有一个延长的维护保修期，是通过一个经销商购买的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qc60ln/ysk_if_you_purchased_a_maintenance_warranty/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qc60ln/ysk_if_you_purchased_a_maintenance_warranty/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 20:22:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK… maintenance warranties can be refunded if you end up trading in a vehicle purchased through a dealer, or if you total out a vehicle from an accident. Possibly resulting in a favorable refund. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently traded in an suv that still had an extended maintenance warranty purchased through a major named dealer. As we were signing paperwork for the a new vehicle, I asked if there was a refund option from the traded in vehicle, the finance guy was hesitant and didn’t answer my question directly. I let it slide, until we were about to leave. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find the finance manager and asked the same question. And again….. was greeted with hesitation. He eventually steers me to the proper process to receive a refund, but the hinkyness to it was all to shady as they made me feel I was stealing from them. Which I wasn’t, I’m rightfully getting my money back. The dealers are pocketing an exorbitant amount of money that people have no clue about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 自我意识，"21世纪的元任务"]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK。
心理学家和研究员塔莎-尤里奇博士将自我意识称为 "21世纪的元任务"。
21世纪的元任务"。这是一种能够清楚地看到自己的能力，了解自己是谁，以及自己如何适应这个世界。
你是谁以及你如何适应这个世界。研究表明，自我意识是一个
幸福的强大因素。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qbycnp/ysk_selfawareness_the_metaskill_of_the_21st/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qbycnp/ysk_selfawareness_the_metaskill_of_the_21st/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 15:58:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK:&lt;br/&gt;
Psychologist and researcher Dr. Tasha Eurich calls self-awareness “the metaskill of the 21st century”. It’s the ability to see yourself clearly, understand who you are and how you fit in the world. Studies show that self-awareness is a powerful factor underlying happiness, good relationships, effective parenthood, job performance, leadership, creativity, confidence and a lot more.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@Ellie_/self-awareness-the-metaskill-of-the-21st-century-2334d840d8fa&quot;&gt;Here’s an article&lt;/a&gt; explaining more of the research and some ways to put it into practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，如果你的飞机在水中着陆，要忍住立即给你的救生衣充气的冲动。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：如果飞机在水面上紧急降落，请抵制立即给救生衣充气的冲动。
在水面上紧急着陆。救生衣的浮力可能使
如果水涌入机舱，你就很难在机舱内跑动。所以要游到一个
出口，然后给你的救生衣充气以保持漂浮状态。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qbwivz/ysk_that_if_your_plane_makes_a_water_landing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qbwivz/ysk_that_if_your_plane_makes_a_water_landing/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 11:00:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Resist the impulse to inflate your life jacket immediately if a plane is making an emergency landing on water. The buoyancy of the jacket could make it harder for you to run inside the cabin if water rushes in.
So swim to an exit, then inflate your jacket to stay afloat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK的百分比是多少。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在讨论百分比时，"点 "的概念告诉你 "多 "和 "少 "这两个词的实际含义。
"多 "和 "少 "的实际含义--"点 "在这些情况下意味着
加法而不是乘法。

例如，如果你正在就一个项目的特许权使用费进行谈判，而开头的
出价是利润的10%，....]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qbsib8/ysk_what_percentage_points_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qbsib8/ysk_what_percentage_points_are/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 06:55:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The notion of &amp;quot;points&amp;quot; when discussing percentages tells you what the words &amp;quot;more&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;less&amp;quot; actually mean -- the word &amp;quot;points&amp;quot; in these cases means addition instead of multiplication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, if you are negotiating for royalties on a project, and the opening offer is for 10% of the profits. Asking for 5% more is very different than asking for 5 percentage points more! Asking for five percentage points more than 10% means 10%+5%=15%, whereas 5% more then 10% means 10% + (10% x 5%) = 10.5%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Without the notion of percentage points, discussing percentages is ambiguous. This will definitely come up when refinancing your house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As another example, a home loan might be 3% per year. If you are renegotiating the loan for lower monthly payments, they may mention increasing the percentage by some number, like 1.5 percentage points. That means your new interest rate will be 3% + 1.5% = 4.5%. This sounds small, but really your interest rate just went up by 50%!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，"10%的80%的增长并不意味着什么东西现在是90%。它已经被增加了10%的80%，所以现在是18%。]]></title><description><![CDATA[很多人似乎误解了百分比的工作原理，所以我在这里给予
一个小小的解释。

例如，如果你有一个基本的10%的机会，而你的
机会增加了50%，现在是15%，而不是60。

为什么是YSK：学习百分比从来都不是一件坏事，而...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qbdkqn/ysk_that_an_80_increase_of_10_does_not_mean/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qbdkqn/ysk_that_an_80_increase_of_10_does_not_mean/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 17:02:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lot of people seem to misunderstand how percentages work, so i’m here to give a little explanation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example if you have a base 10% chance of something happening, and your chances are increased by 50%, they are now 15%, not 60. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: it’s never a bad thing to learn about percentages and how they work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 美国男性的平均身高是5英尺9英寸。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：对于那些强调自己身高的男孩，让我告诉你
这并不是什么大问题，你可能非常接近平均水平。也有
但那些人通常是年轻的人，他们正在过着自己的生活，还没有定下来，他们要求6英尺以上。
但那些人通常是年轻的人，他们正在过自己的生活，还没有安定下来，随着年龄的增长，这种情况要少得多......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qb75bh/ysk_the_average_height_for_men_in_the_us_is_59/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qb75bh/ysk_the_average_height_for_men_in_the_us_is_59/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 13:04:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: For the boys out there stressing on their height let me tell you that it&amp;#39;s not a big deal and you are probably pretty close to average. There are people asking for 6&amp;#39;+ but those are usually younger people who are living their lives and not settling down yet, it&amp;#39;s much less common as you get older and see more people looking for serious relationships. Also most people really don&amp;#39;t care about your height so don&amp;#39;t let the relative few that do bother you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And 5&amp;#39;9 is still pretty tall, you can reach most high shelves and the tops of the fridge. And for my guys in the lower range let me tell you, have a taller partner  is pretty cool cause you get to either be the little spoon or the jet pack while cuddling and both are a good time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t let your height be something that hold you back or keeps you down because it&amp;#39;s not a big deal, and honestly as a 5&amp;#39;10-5&amp;#39;11 guy (depends on the time of day) the world just seems more comfortable if your a bit shorter. So accept it and let your confidence grow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Firefox插件Bypass Paywall Clean允许你绕过纽约时报等网站的付费墙。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK。

对于那些不想注册像《纽约时报》那样的订阅的人来说
以阅读他们的文章，我刚刚找到一个解决方案。绕过付费墙清洁
的magnolia1234让你阅读。我只用了1天，但到目前为止，它是
很棒，而且超级简单]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qayisg/ysk_the_firefox_addon_bypass_paywall_clean_allows/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/qayisg/ysk_the_firefox_addon_bypass_paywall_clean_allows/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 01:52:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To anyone who doesn&amp;#39;t want to sign up for something like a NY Times subscription in order to read their articles, I just found a solution. Bypass Paywall Clean by magnolia1234 lets you read it. I&amp;#39;ve only used it for 1 day, but so far it&amp;#39;s been awesome and super easy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>