<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 04:40:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK木糖醇被更频繁地用作糖的替代品，对大多数宠物来说是非常有毒的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：任何标有无糖或无添加糖的东西，只要是甜的，就很可能含有木糖醇或其他类似的甜味剂产品。
它很可能含有木糖醇或其他类似的甜味剂产品（木糖醇也可以被称为木糖醇）。
也可称为桦树糖）。) 这些甜味剂在极少量的情况下会导致动物死亡
导致血糖突然极度下降，从而诱发癫痫发作和...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ovausl/ysk_xylitol_is_being_used_more_frequently_as_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ovausl/ysk_xylitol_is_being_used_more_frequently_as_a/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 21:41:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Anything labeled sugar free or no added sugar, that is sweet, most likely has xylitol or some other equivalent sweetener product in it (xylitol can also be called birch sugar). These kill animals in tiny amounts by causing a sudden extreme drop in blood sugar which induces seizures and liver damage ultimately leading to death in most cases. Look out for it in foods you may share with your pets (although technically they shouldn&amp;#39;t really have processed people food at all!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你服用药片形式的药物有困难，向前倾斜可以帮助你]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：许多人（包括我自己）都有服药困难。
特别是当它们以大药丸的形式出现时。这可能会导致
当涉及到服用处方药时，病人的依从性会下降。哈佛大学
健康出版社
[https://www.health.harvard.edu/blog/two-tricks...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ov5svc/ysk_if_you_have_difficulty_taking_medication_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ov5svc/ysk_if_you_have_difficulty_taking_medication_in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 19:58:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: many people (myself included) have difficulty taking medicines, especially when they come in a large pill form. This can lead to a decrease in patient compliance when it comes to taking one&amp;#39;s prescribed medication. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.health.harvard.edu/blog/two-tricks-make-easier-swallow-pills-201411137515&quot;&gt;Harvard Health Publishing&lt;/a&gt; highlights two helpful techniques: the pop-bottle method (creating a seal while drinking) and the lean-forward method (tilting your chin to your chest while swallowing). The study showed 89% of people reported an easier time swallowing pills when tilting their head forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK不要为你生活中的人屏蔽那些让你担心或不安的事情。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK。

很多人都不愿意告诉他们的亲人（伙伴、家人、朋友等）他们生活中的坏事。
等），因为我们不想让他们承受更多的坏消息或更多的担忧。
更多的坏消息或更多的忧虑。当你与这些人如此接近时，你
你觉得你知道他们所有的担忧和关切...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ov9p73/ysk_not_to_shield_the_people_in_your_life_from/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ov9p73/ysk_not_to_shield_the_people_in_your_life_from/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 19:33:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of people struggle to tell their loved ones (partners, family, friends, etc.) about the bad things in their life because we don’t want to burden them with more bad news or more worries. When you’re so close to these people, you feel like you know all their worries and concerns already and you‘d feel guilty adding negativity on top of that. This type of thinking is so common, and incredibly unhealthy. Our loved ones are the exact people we should confide in to share our feelings and insecurities because our loved ones are going to be the ones most likely to help us get through them &lt;em&gt;without us breaking down or worsening our mental health&lt;/em&gt;. Togetherness. Improves. Mental. Health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use the people in your life who are there for you. You don’t have to ask them for money or advice. Use them to unburden yourself of the feelings you hide or things you feel you have to face alone. You’re not alone. You have people who love you and sometimes just talking with these people openly about your feelings is all the love you need. It doesn’t make you less strong or less independent. Talking about your feelings makes you stronger, I promise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope this sentiment can help someone a little 💙&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK - 堵塞所需的出口通道（出口）是非法的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK - 企业不能以任何理由阻挡所需的出口通道。

建筑物的设计是为了满足居住者的需求，而出口的设置是为了以最小的旅行距离处理这些居住者。
处理那些旅行距离最少的居住者。

如果被封锁的门上方有出口标志，请联系当地消防部门。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ov8bcu/ysk_it_is_illegal_to_block_required_means_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ov8bcu/ysk_it_is_illegal_to_block_required_means_of/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 17:44:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK - Businesses cannot block required means of egress for ANY reason. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buildings are designed to accommodate an occupant load with exits placed to handle those occupants with the least amount of travel distance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there is an exit sign above the blocked door, contact the local fire marshals office. This is a life safety issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They can block entry to corral folks but they CANNOT block exits. It’s against the law.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：可冲水湿巾对你的管道系统没有好处/安全。这100%是个谎言。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是水管工，是的，这是真的。

对消费者来说，不幸的是，营销人员擅长的是他们与律师和销售人员共同拥有的一项技能
与律师和销售人员共享的技能；撒谎。

事实证明，对于诸如 "可冲洗湿巾 "这样的包装上的声明，实际上没有任何监管。
擦拭布"（它们被大胆地宣传和展示为这样）或 "世界上最好的擦拭布 "等包装上的宣称没有任何监管。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ov1b8o/ysk_flushable_wipes_are_not_goodsafe_for_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ov1b8o/ysk_flushable_wipes_are_not_goodsafe_for_your/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 06:48:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plumber here, yes it&amp;#39;s true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately for consumers, marketers specialize in the one skill they share with lawyers and salespeople; lying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turns out there&amp;#39;s actually no regulation on claims on package such as &amp;quot;Flushable Wipes&amp;quot; (Hell they&amp;#39;re boldly advertised and displayed as such) or &amp;quot;World&amp;#39;s Best Dildo&amp;quot; for that matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why ysk: Wipes (or excessive TP, paper towels)... really anything &lt;strong&gt;except&lt;/strong&gt; turds, moderate TP or severely eviscerated food waste via garburator... should NOT be flushed down any drains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rule most people I encounter prescribe is &amp;quot;out of sight out of mind&amp;quot;... which is a toxic mentality... often literally. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your toilet drains real slow, that&amp;#39;s more than often the reason.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Call a plumber to come snake your drain and immediately stop flushing wipes and other crap besides poop and TP.  Provided your plumbing doesn&amp;#39;t suck, you should almost never get clogs or slow draining in a modern plumbing system. If it does suck, getting your piping redone correctly up to your main stack can drastically improve that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if it doesn&amp;#39;t clog your drains it makes it&amp;#39;s way to the water treatment plant and can often clog and impede their pipes and equipment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, do what old age homes do in their lobby bathrooms: put little trashcans with secure lids with a bag under the sink or some out of the way location and change it often.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or just get a bidet. Give your brown eyed monster the proper bath it needs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 前列腺刺激可以是一种健康和愉悦的活动，每个男人都可以享受，无论其性取向如何。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：大多数男人一生都没有经历过男人可以拥有的最好的性体验之一
的性体验，只是因为对性行为的污名化。
这样做。

我第一次在Reddit上发现前列腺刺激是在大约十年前，也就是我20岁出头的时候。
20s. 有人写下了他们的故事，说他们有心灵上的创伤。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ouu874/ysk_prostate_stimulation_can_be_a_healthy_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ouu874/ysk_prostate_stimulation_can_be_a_healthy_and/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 23:41:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: most men go their whole lives not experiencing what is one of the best sexual experiences a man can have, simply because of the stigma attached to doing so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I first discovered prostate stimulation on Reddit about a decade ago in my early 20s. Someone had written their story of having mind blowing orgasms and I decided I would try it for myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I found that it felt great by myself, but I carried some pointless guilt and embarrassment for many years. It wasn&amp;#39;t until I accepted that I can enjoy it as a straight male that I really discovered how pleasurable prostate stimulation can be. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It wasnt until this discovery that I brought it up with my wife. Once I did, we began experimenting a bit more with toys specifically made for it. Butt plugs, vibrators, wands. I can honestly say it has produced some of the best sexual experiences I have ever had. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is even possible to orgasm from prostate stimulation alone, though I&amp;#39;ve never experienced it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you are even a little curious, do some research and try it out. Use your fingers or a toy meant for such things. Be safe, relax and enjoy. You may just find that you can be more comfortable with yourself when you begin breaking down stigmas such as this. I have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，最常见的自闭症疗法--应用行为分析（ABA）是由奥莱-伊瓦尔-洛瓦斯（Ole Ivar Lovaas）创立的，他也是帮助开创同性恋转换疗法的人。它们基于相同的原则。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：很多善意的自闭症儿童家长都被宣传ABA疗法的信息所淹没。
的信息，但它实际上是建立在虐待的原则之上的。
虐待。有证据表明，约有一半的自闭症患者在接受ABA治疗后会出现创伤后遗症。
经历了创伤后应激障碍，而这一过程是建立在......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/out0wt/ysk_that_the_most_common_therapy_for_autism/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/out0wt/ysk_that_the_most_common_therapy_for_autism/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 22:38:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: a lot of well-meaning parents of autistic children are inundated with information promoting ABA therapy, but it is actually founded on principles of abuse. There is evidence that about half of autistic people who go through ABA experience PTSD as a result of the process, which is founded on the concept of desensitizing autistic kids to make them appear “normal” (source linked at the end).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The foundation of ABA is that autistic kids must be “shaped” into people, and “non-autistic” behaviors are rewarded with treats, similar to dog training. This model of operant conditioning does two things:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;it only impacts behavior, and not communication—ironic, considering autism is a disability of communication, and thus ignores the root of what autistic people need accommodations with. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;it teaches kids that all that matters is the needs of those around them, and not their own. By being punished or ignored for expressing their own needs, they are discouraged from having autonomy and learn that any attempts at self-advocacy are unacceptable. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some programs also still use shock-therapy, which has been denounced by the UN as torture. (Side note: if you haven’t heard of the Judge Rotenberg Center, please look it up. It’s appalling.) But even “modern” ABA centers use the same foundation, which can still have harmful consequences. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Much more safe and effective therapies are occupational therapy and speech and language therapy, which are tailored to individuals and are intended to promote autonomy and connect patients to necessary accommodations. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Resources to learn more, because I barely covered it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.emerald.com/insight/content/doi/10.1108/AIA-08-2017-0016/full/html&quot;&gt;https://www.emerald.com/insight/content/doi/10.1108/AIA-08-2017-0016/full/html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/23311908.2019.1641258&quot;&gt;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/23311908.2019.1641258&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://catalystjournal.org/index.php/catalyst/article/view/29579&quot;&gt;https://catalystjournal.org/index.php/catalyst/article/view/29579&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://tania.co.za/non-speaking-autistics-thoughts-on-aba/&quot;&gt;https://tania.co.za/non-speaking-autistics-thoughts-on-aba/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://neuroclastic.com/2019/03/28/invisible-abuse-aba-and-the-things-only-autistic-people-can-see/&quot;&gt;https://neuroclastic.com/2019/03/28/invisible-abuse-aba-and-the-things-only-autistic-people-can-see/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=94sy4YrUGRk&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=94sy4YrUGRk&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://awnnetwork.org/my-thoughts-on-aba/&quot;&gt;https://awnnetwork.org/my-thoughts-on-aba/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://therapistndc.org/therapy/applied-behavior-analysis-aba/&quot;&gt;https://therapistndc.org/therapy/applied-behavior-analysis-aba/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：减少、再利用、再循环实际上是按重要性排序的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：减少你的消费是迄今为止最有效的三个方法。
而你应该重复使用你不能减少的东西!

在购买新的物品之前，你应该从你现有的物品中获得最大的使用价值。
或者你应该考虑从朋友那里借来上述物品，如果你不需要的话
不需要这个...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ouskjl/ysk_reduce_reuse_recycle_are_actually_in_order_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ouskjl/ysk_reduce_reuse_recycle_are_actually_in_order_of/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 21:44:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Reducing what you consume is by far the most effective of the three, and you should be reusing what you can&amp;#39;t reduce!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before buying an item new, you should get the most use out of the item you currently have, or you should consider borrowing said item from a friend if you don&amp;#39;t need this item daily/permanently. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What most people do not know is that &lt;strong&gt;recycling&lt;/strong&gt; falls third on the list because it is the &lt;strong&gt;least effective.&lt;/strong&gt; This is why we shouldn&amp;#39;t be recycling until we have tried reducing/reusing. Recycling should really be a last resort.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：个人/健身教练不需要有执照。]]></title><description><![CDATA[与理发师和按摩师不同的是，健身/个人教练不需要获得州政府的执照。
与理发师和按摩师不同，健身/私人教练不需要获得州政府的执业许可证。大多数培训师所做的是获得一个
"认证"，这只是一本教科书/测试。为什么选择YSK：与一个没有受过教育的教练合作
是危险的，而且弊大于利。只是...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oumox4/ysk_personalfitness_trainers_are_not_required_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oumox4/ysk_personalfitness_trainers_are_not_required_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 18:30:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike barbers and massage therapists, fitness/personal trainers are not required to get a state license to practice. What most trainers do is get a &amp;quot;Certification&amp;quot;, which is just a textbook/test. Why YSK: Working with a trainer that is uneducated is dangerous and does more harm and good. Just because someone is &amp;quot;Certified&amp;quot; means they were able to study and pass a test. Even if the certification is accredited, that just means that an accrediting agency (for profit) makes sure the tests are legitimate (for example: that they are proctored, that the company doesn&amp;#39;t lie about the cost, etc), not so much that the CONTENT is legitimate. Also, personal training is expensive. To pay someone so much money per hour that may not be qualified or educated seems silly. Make sure that you find a trainer that went to a hands-on program for personal training, one that is accredited as an education establishment (diploma), not just a &amp;quot;certification&amp;quot;. Or at least someone who did an apprenticeship/has hands-on experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，虽然蛋白质通常与健身和运动有很大关系，但根据哈佛大学等知名人士的说法，成年人每天每磅体重仍应摄入约0.3-0.5克的蛋白质（以下链接）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：蛋白质是肌肉生长的必要营养物质，是的，但它是
关于所有组织的生长。它为肌肉、器官、皮肤、血液、抗体等提供了构建模块。
皮肤、血液、抗体和更多。我们的社会将蛋白质与运动紧密联系起来
我们的社会将蛋白质与运动联系在一起，常常给人留下 "嗯，我不是...... "的印象。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ou8vhs/ysk_that_while_protein_is_often_heavily/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ou8vhs/ysk_that_while_protein_is_often_heavily/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 12:33:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: protein is an essential nutrient for muscle growth, yeah, but it’s about &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; tissue growth. It provides the building blocks for muscle, organs, skin, blood, antibodies and more. The heavy connection our society gives protein to exercising often leaves the impression of “well, I’m not working out, I don’t need it that much” and that’s so far from the truth. It’s essential for your body to repair and maintain itself in a MULTITUDE of ways! It’s no miracle cure all, but you may need a little more in your life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, I am no nutritionist, scientist, family medicine practitioner or personal trainer, so please consult a specialist when it comes to your individual intake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Link:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.health.harvard.edu/blog/how-much-protein-do-you-need-every-day-201506188096&quot;&gt;https://www.health.harvard.edu/blog/how-much-protein-do-you-need-every-day-201506188096&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK不要对你的机械师撒谎]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：像医生一样，机械师只是想帮助你解决你的问题。我们大多数人
我们中的大多数人都是好人，都在努力谋生。如果你让你的表弟
乔-杰克试图用米奇老鼠的东西。请让机械师知道。这将
告诉他们 "是的，有一个白痴搞乱了...... "要好得多。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oudtr6/ysk_to_not_lie_to_your_mechanic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oudtr6/ysk_to_not_lie_to_your_mechanic/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 11:30:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: like Doctors, mechanics just want to help you with your problem. Most of us are good people who are trying to make a living. If you had your cousin Joe Jack try to mickey mouse something. Please let the mechanic know. It would be much better to tell them “Yeah some idiot messed around with it and took wires before you” than for us to spend countless of hours and resources trying to figure out what the issue is. Plus it might be cheaper since we’ll know where to start.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK是 "我不在乎"，而不是 "我可以不在乎"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK，太多网上和现实中的人错误地使用这个短语来表达
表达他们对某件事情的关心程度，而没有意识到说后一句 "我可以不关心 "实际上是指 "我可以不关心"。
我可以不在乎 "实际上意味着 "我有更多的空间去不在乎，这意味着我
实际上是有点在乎"，请停止这种说法，朋友们。它伤害了我]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ou98pc/ysk_that_its_i_couldnt_care_less_and_not_i_could/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ou98pc/ysk_that_its_i_couldnt_care_less_and_not_i_could/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 02:13:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK,
Too many people online and irl incorrectly use this phrase to express how little care they have for something, not realising that saying the latter “I could care less” actually means ‘I have more room to care less which means I actually care a bit” 
please stop it friends. It hurts me&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：大多数女性不能仅从插入中获得高潮。这并不意味着你让她达到高潮就不是一个男人了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：能够给你的伴侣带来更好的性快感是一件好事。
对你们两个人来说都是一件好事。

指法、嘴巴、性玩具等等。看看什么对她最有效。如果有的话。
它使你更像一个男人，考虑她的需要和愿望，而不是只关注
只专注于...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ou76ji/ysk_most_women_cannot_orgasm_from_penetration/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ou76ji/ysk_most_women_cannot_orgasm_from_penetration/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 23:43:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Being able to give your partner better sexual pleasures can be a great thing for the both of you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fingering, mouth, sex toys,  and so on. See what works best for her. If anything, it makes you more of a man to think about what she needs and desires instead of only focusing on yourself. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nbcnews.com/better/lifestyle/orgasm-gap-why-it-exists-what-women-can-do-about-ncna983311&quot;&gt;https://www.nbcnews.com/better/lifestyle/orgasm-gap-why-it-exists-what-women-can-do-about-ncna983311&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://metro.co.uk/2017/09/02/how-many-times-do-women-need-to-explain-that-penetration-isnt-everything-before-everyone-gets-it-6896506/&quot;&gt;https://metro.co.uk/2017/09/02/how-many-times-do-women-need-to-explain-that-penetration-isnt-everything-before-everyone-gets-it-6896506/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many women are afraid of bruising men&amp;#39;s ego&amp;#39;s, them taking it violently, etc. So they take mediocre or even bad sex over telling them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The penis to a lot of women is secondary, while the foreplay tends to be the main event. Not saying that the penis isn&amp;#39;t important, but it&amp;#39;s just not as important as some men believe that it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I did not mean &amp;quot;letting her&amp;quot; as a bad thing. I&amp;#39;m a woman by the way. I just mean that &amp;quot;some&amp;quot; (not all men), think of having a woman having orgasms or doing extra stuff for her is extra work/a chore for &amp;quot;some&amp;quot; of them. Like, it&amp;#39;s not something that they worry about as long as they get theirs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK说，虽然胰岛素的成本总是以疯狂的价格出现在新闻中，但你可以通过社区卫生中心以每瓶2-25美元的价格获得它。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：一项名为340b药品折扣计划的政府计划要求
药品公司以相同的价格向社区卫生中心出售药品。
卖给医疗补助。

没有收入限制，你只需要预约就可以了。
与当地社区中心的医生预约......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ou39q8/ysk_that_while_the_cost_of_insulin_is_always_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ou39q8/ysk_that_while_the_cost_of_insulin_is_always_in/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 20:39:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: A government program called the 340b Drug Discount Program requires drug companies to sell drugs to community health centers at the same prices they sell to Medicaid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are no income restrictions and you just need to schedule an appointment with a doctor at the local community center once a year in order to get a prescription. My wife will pick up ~10 vials of humalog each visit for like $25 total. The link below has details on how to find a community center near you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cheapinsulin.org/340b&quot;&gt;https://cheapinsulin.org/340b&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你说得越少越好。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：你有更少的机会出错，有更多的机会倾听。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ou48kz/ysk_the_less_you_say_the_better/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ou48kz/ysk_the_less_you_say_the_better/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 20:39:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; You have less chances to be wrong, more chances to listen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK："100家公司是71%的排放源 "的统计数字经常被误解，这些排放中的很大一部分来自个人]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：为了更好地了解公司和个人对气候变化的影响，避免被统计数据误导。
为了更好地了解公司和个人对气候变化的影响，避免被统计数据误导。

TL;DR: 统计数据只关注化石燃料公司，包括其产品的排放。
他们的产品的排放，即你的汽车使用的燃料。

编辑：为了澄清我的意图：...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/otzy5f/ysk_the_100_companies_are_source_of_71_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/otzy5f/ysk_the_100_companies_are_source_of_71_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 17:45:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/strong&gt; To better understand the impact of companies and private individuals on climate change and avoid being misled by statistics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL;DR:&lt;/strong&gt; The statistic only looks at fossil fuel companies and includes the emissions from their products, i.e. the fuel your car uses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit to clarify my intent:&lt;/strong&gt; This post is not meant to defend the negative impact of oil companies or similar on the climate and environment. It is meant to disarm the argument that individual action is futile because of the large impact of companies by showing how one specific statistic is commonly misinterpreted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In light of the many recent extreme wheather events around the world people have cited this number to deflect calls to take action against climate change away from individuals onto companies. While companies must be held accountable every one of us has the ability and needs to contribute to lessen the effects of climate change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 71 % number shows up in the „&lt;em&gt;CDP Carbon Majors Report 2017&lt;/em&gt;“ by the Carbon Disclosure Project, a non-profit that discloses information on environmental impact [1]. The report was published on July 10th 2017 [2] and The Guardian wrote an article titled „&lt;em&gt;Just 100 companies responsible for 71% of global emissions, study says&lt;/em&gt;“ the same day [3]. I believe this to be the souce of the above claim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Carbon Majors Report specifically aims at fossil fuel investors [4, p. 2] and the 100 companies in question are the 100 largest producers of fossil fuels. They look at fossil fuel emissions as the sum of two things [5, p. 3] :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All fossil fuels a company uses in the &lt;strong&gt;extraction and production of fossil fuels&lt;/strong&gt; (Scope 1 emissions)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Emissions from the „&lt;strong&gt;use of sold products&lt;/strong&gt;“, meaning the emissions from the use of the manufactured fossil fuels. This typically represents &amp;gt; 90 % of all emissions of a company. (Scope 3 Category 11 emissions)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since this is all about fossil fuel companies the „use of sold products“ includes the fuel your car burns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 71 % number refers to the sum of CO2 emissions of those companies between 1988 and 2015 listed in the „Past accountability“ section of the report [4, p. 8]. This is meant to display the significant contribution of just a few companies, but cannot easily be compared to other emission statistics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One response to people citing this number here on reddit is that it only refers to &lt;strong&gt;industrial emissions&lt;/strong&gt;. This is true, but it is important to look up how the report defines industrial emissions before comparing this to other statistics. According to the accompanying methodology report industrial greenhouse gas emissions include &lt;strong&gt;all man-made greenhouse gasses except carbon dioxide relating to land-use change, and methane deriving from farming, landfills, and other non-industrial sources.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The full report (16 pages) can be &lt;a href=&quot;https://6fefcbb86e61af1b2fc4-c70d8ead6ced550b4d987d7c03fcdd1d.ssl.cf3.rackcdn.com/cms/reports/documents/000/002/327/original/Carbon-Majors-Report-2017.pdf?1501833772&quot;&gt;read here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The methodology report (11 pages) can be &lt;a href=&quot;https://b8f65cb373b1b7b15feb-c70d8ead6ced550b4d987d7c03fcdd1d.ssl.cf3.rackcdn.com/comfy/cms/files/files/000/000/979/original/Carbon-Majors-Database-2017-Method.pdf&quot;&gt;read here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dataset including all numbers and company names (1 excel file in a zip folder) can be &lt;a href=&quot;https://b8f65cb373b1b7b15feb-c70d8ead6ced550b4d987d7c03fcdd1d.ssl.cf3.rackcdn.com/comfy/cms/files/files/000/000/978/original/Carbon-Majors-Database-2017-Datasets.zip&quot;&gt;downloaded here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;References&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[1] &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdp.net/en/info/about-us&quot;&gt;https://www.cdp.net/en/info/about-us&lt;/a&gt;, accessed 29.07.2021, 16:36 CEST&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[2] &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cdp.net/en/articles/media/new-report-shows-just-100-companies-are-source-of-over-70-of-emissions&quot;&gt;https://www.cdp.net/en/articles/media/new-report-shows-just-100-companies-are-source-of-over-70-of-emissions&lt;/a&gt;, accessed 29.07.2021, 16:39 CEST&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[3] &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/sustainable-business/2017/jul/10/100-fossil-fuel-companies-investors-responsible-71-global-emissions-cdp-study-climate-change&quot;&gt;https://www.theguardian.com/sustainable-business/2017/jul/10/100-fossil-fuel-companies-investors-responsible-71-global-emissions-cdp-study-climate-change&lt;/a&gt;, accessed 29.07.2021, 16:40 CEST&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[4] Griffin, P. (2017). &lt;em&gt;The Carbon Majors Database, CDP Carbon Majors Report 2017.&lt;/em&gt; CDP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[5] Griffin, P., Heede, R., van der Vlugt, I. (2017). &lt;em&gt;The Carbon Majors Database, Methodology Report 2017.&lt;/em&gt; CDP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，在你的求职信中滥用 "已证明的历史 "这一短语是不专业的，让人觉得你在使用一个模板]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：因为你可能想成为一个成功的申请者!

我对专业职位和研究生院的申请者都进行面试。
这也是我最讨厌的问题之一。我不是一个人，所以我可以保证
我不是一个人，所以我可以向你保证，这个错误会让你在别人眼里显得不专业......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oto92l/ysk_that_misusing_the_phrase_demonstrated_history/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oto92l/ysk_that_misusing_the_phrase_demonstrated_history/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 08:02:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: because you probably want to be a successful applicant!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I interview applicants both for professional positions and for graduate school, and this has to be one of my biggest pet peeves.  I&amp;#39;m not alone, so I can assure you that this mistake will make you seem unprofessional in the eyes of many prospective employers.  What shocks me most is that I see it in about half of the applications/resumes I receive nowadays, and these are from highly educated people!  So, I feel the need to give some advice here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short: the phrase &amp;quot;demonstrated history of X&amp;quot; has a very specific meaning.  It&amp;#39;s used to communicate that you&amp;#39;ve accomplished something special and that you have the results to show for it.  You want to use it when talking about your achievements - it&amp;#39;s a bragging phrase.  You don&amp;#39;t want to use it when you&amp;#39;re stating simple facts about your work history, because those speak for themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, you don&amp;#39;t need to tell your prospective employer that you have a &amp;quot;demonstrated history of working in finance.&amp;quot;  That&amp;#39;s abundantly clear from your resume, and it isn&amp;#39;t impressive.  Working in finance isn&amp;#39;t some kind of accomplishment in and of itself; the guy who showed up for the first day of work and slapped his boss has a demonstrated history of working in finance, too.  That just means you showed up to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, what you &lt;em&gt;might&lt;/em&gt; want to tell your prospective employer is that you have a &amp;quot;demonstrated history of effectively leading multidisciplinary teams,&amp;quot; or a &amp;quot;demonstrated history of improving customer retention rates.&amp;quot;  You&amp;#39;re talking about specific things you&amp;#39;ve done well in your career.  Don&amp;#39;t tell them you have a &amp;quot;demonstrated history of working as a landscape designer&amp;quot;; tell them you have a &amp;quot;demonstrated history of designing unique landscape features for clients with diverse landscaping needs.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this still doesn&amp;#39;t make sense, then just don&amp;#39;t ever put the words &amp;quot;demonstrated&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;history&amp;quot; next to each other in a sentence and you&amp;#39;ll be fine!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为防晒霜会使皮肤上的尖锐物脱落]]></title><description><![CDATA[我小时候经常在我的整个手臂上画画，我记得我很难过，因为我的 "艺术 "在田径场上被抹掉了。
我的 "艺术 "在野战日被涂掉了。

为什么是Ysk：这可能对那些有一天会被醉酒的朋友在脸上画上小弟弟而醒来的人有用。
醉酒的朋友在你的脸上画了一个小弟弟。

编辑：人们评论说所有的乳液都会这样，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ot6r46/ysk_that_sunscreen_takes_sharpie_off_skin/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ot6r46/ysk_that_sunscreen_takes_sharpie_off_skin/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 06:47:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;i used to draw on my ENTIRE arm as a kid, and i remember being DEVASTATED that all my “art” smeared off at field day. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;why ysk: this may be useful for those of you who will someday wake up with a dick sharpied on your face by a drunk friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit: people are commenting that all lotion does this, but i’m referring to spray sunscreen. melts it off almost entirely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 健身房的 "免费客人通行证 "几乎都有令人讨厌的附加条件]]></title><description><![CDATA[来源于 我在多个健身房工作了大约4年，而且一生都在去各种健身房。
我的一生都在去各种健身房。

"免费客人通行证 "更多时候是健身房收集线索的一种方式。
然后打扰你的生活，试图让你注册/购买
个人培训/...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/otj7is/ysk_free_guest_passes_at_gyms_almost_always_have/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/otj7is/ysk_free_guest_passes_at_gyms_almost_always_have/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 01:38:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Source: I have worked at multiple gyms over a period of about 4 years and have also been going to various gyms my whole life. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Free guest pass” is more often than not a way for the gym to collect leads , then bother the ever-loving F out of you trying to get you to sign up/buy personal training/ etc. You will most likely be required to go on a tour and hear a sales pitch before you can even try out the gym. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, once your free trial is over, expect them to continue reaching out to you. Forever. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: You can avoid a major headache by not using these, or at the very least you’ll know what’s coming. IMO, you’re better off paying whatever their one-day fee is, and trying it out that way before signing up, or using a friend’s guest privileges (different than “guest pass”).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为Head and Shoulders洗发水可以清除成人痤疮。]]></title><description><![CDATA[YSK : 含有吡硫翁锌的去头皮屑洗发水对顽固的成人痤疮非常有效。
顽固的成人痤疮。 去头皮屑痤疮疗法
[https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4120804/]]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/otaf8c/ysk_that_head_and_shoulders_shampoo_clears_up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/otaf8c/ysk_that_head_and_shoulders_shampoo_clears_up/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 18:30:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK : Anti-dandruff shampoos with pyrithione zinc are very effective against persistent adult acne. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4120804/&quot;&gt;anti dandruff acne remedy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，无论是否有 "退后 "或 "不负责任 "的标志/贴纸，泥头车仍需对从其车上掉下的碎片造成的损害负责。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：卡车公司会在他们的卡车上贴上 "后退300英尺"（距离不同）或 "公司不负责赔偿 "的标志/贴纸。
后退300英尺"（距离不同）或 "公司对损害不负责任"，作为
以此来防止人们对他们的保险索赔。
挡风玻璃、大灯、油漆损坏等。然而，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ot2yf8/ysk_that_dump_trucks_are_still_liable_for_damage/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ot2yf8/ysk_that_dump_trucks_are_still_liable_for_damage/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 06:56:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Trucking companies will put signs/stickers on their trucks saying “Stay Back 300 Feet” (the distance varies) or “Company Not Responsible For Damage” as a way to prevent people from making insurance claims against them for chipped/cracked windshields, headlights, paint damage, etc. However, they actually &lt;em&gt;are&lt;/em&gt; liable, because they’re required to properly secure their load, no matter what it is. So if a clump of dirt, for example, falls off of the bed sides or the truck hits a bump and a rock comes out of the bed, and it hits your car, they are liable for the repairs to your car. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Advice I was given by a LEO was to get the information from the truck and report it to my insurance, and let them fight the trucking company. The information you’d need includes the company name, truck license plate number or truck number (companies with multiple trucks will generally put a number somewhere on the side of the hood, or a rear corner of the cab; it’s usually a two or three digit number), what road you were on and where on that road it happened, direction of travel for both of you, and what it was that caused the damage (if you’re able to tell.) If you can’t tell what exactly it was that hit your vehicle, don’t lie and say it was something, because if you say it was a rock, but the truck was hauling mulch, they can use that to contest your claim. Also, if you can’t safely read or find a license plate (most states don’t have rear plates for trucks that size), a description of the truck. This isn’t a comprehensive list of details that you should compile, as always, the more information you have the better off you’ll be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be clear: this only includes things that fall off of or out of the trucks. It does not include things that may have been kicked up off the road. For example, if a truck hits a rock on the road, and that causes it to fly up and hit your windshield, that’s considered a road hazard, and they &lt;em&gt;aren’t&lt;/em&gt; liable for that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK有99.99%的机会，你的车在你不知道的情况下安装了GPS追踪器和点火切断开关。(不，这不是你的手机或导航包）。)]]></title><description><![CDATA[几天前，我的一个朋友（一个吉普车经销商的销售员）告诉我，他们
在他们出售的每辆车上都安装了GPS追踪装置和点火开关
他们在出售的每辆车（二手车和新车）上都安装了GPS追踪装置和点火开关，这样贷款人就可以追踪你的车辆，如果你错过了付款，就会使它失效。
错过一次付款。我开始在网上做一些调查，并...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/osz449/ysk_theres_a_9999_chance_that_your_car_has_a_gps/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/osz449/ysk_theres_a_9999_chance_that_your_car_has_a_gps/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 02:35:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few days ago a friend of mine (a salesman at a Jeep dealership) told me they install GPS tracking devices and ignition cutoff switches in every vehicle they sell (used and new) so that lenders can track your vehicle and disable it if you miss a payment. I started doing some digging online and calling some other dealerships and they confirmed the information. We&amp;#39;re not talking about &amp;quot;Buy Here Pay Here&amp;quot; car lots.. I&amp;#39;m talking about l&lt;em&gt;egitimate dealerships.&lt;/em&gt; And technically, you consent to it since it&amp;#39;s hidden in the fine print of all those contracts that you sign at the time of purchase. And you most likely paid an extra couple hundred dollars for them to install it! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: The really interesting part is even if you pay for your car in full at the time of purchase, you still have the GPS and ignition cutoffs pre-installed. But &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; can&amp;#39;t use them. &lt;em&gt;You&lt;/em&gt; don&amp;#39;t have access to these services, even though it&amp;#39;s always actively running (as long as your battery is hooked up). &lt;em&gt;You&lt;/em&gt; aren&amp;#39;t notified if someone accesses that information without your knowledge. The dealership (and whoever else) could access this information any time they want for any reason they want because &lt;em&gt;you can&amp;#39;t confirm if/when it&amp;#39;s happening because you don&amp;#39;t have access to it.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I paid for my Jeep in full at the time of purchase and I can confirm the Jeep dealership installed a GPS tracker and ignition cutoff in my vehicle as well. I cut the wires, spliced everything back together and called the dealership that sold it to me. I asked them to give me access to the tracking and ignition cut off services, all the records and documents relating to these devices, and a list of anyone whose ever viewed or pinged my location with their reason for doing so. I was told &amp;quot;we can&amp;#39;t do that&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m not sure where that information would be.&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These GPS trackers theoretically could be placed anywhere. But 95% of the time they&amp;#39;re located under the steering wheel by the OBD port and/or fuse box. You&amp;#39;ll need to remove the plastic panel from below your steering wheel to see the device(s) but it&amp;#39;s pretty easy - there will be 3 or 4 screws at the bottom of the plastic panel (just above the gas/brake pedal). After you remove the panel search YouTube for some videos of people removing the GPS trackers and proceed to cut them off your vehicle. It will be a black box that looks different from the rest, most likely spliced to your OBD port. Note: Be sure to read the terms of your lease/loan (if you have one) to make sure you&amp;#39;re not violating your contract by removing these devices. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have no idea how this is legal for them to do and seriously, FUCK the dealerships who install these and sneak it past customers. Read the fine print like a hawk, question everything, and if you have one of these installed, I suggest removing it and running it TF over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(For context, I&amp;#39;m in the USA)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：不是每个人都能流利地使用你说的语言，如果他们说一些愚蠢的事情；嘲笑他们是你可能做的最糟糕的事情。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：一个不流利的演讲者最害怕的是说一些
不合适的东西，或者不小心说了一些可笑的东西。

我个人在学习英语的过程中，有很多时候我说了很多
我个人在学习英语的过程中，有很多时候说了一些看起来很正常的话，而流利的人可能会把这些话理解为是一种暗示。
暗示，或有...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/osupur/ysk_not_everyone_is_fluent_in_the_language_youre/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/osupur/ysk_not_everyone_is_fluent_in_the_language_youre/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 22:37:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: The biggest fear a non-fluent speaker has is saying something inappropriate or something ridiculous by accident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I personally, while learning English have had a lot of moments where I’ve said something seemingly normal that a fluent speaker could interpret as being an innuendo, or have asked store clerks if pork products are halal because I did not know what the word “pork” meant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These things are obviously embarrassing when pointed out, which is a kind thing to do because it helps me learn, but way too often have people taken it too far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course i can see the humor in this and I always do laugh with them, but man does it hurt when they straight up ridicule you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was scared to speak English because I didn’t want to say silly things, and it took me a long time to become confident &lt;em&gt;enough&lt;/em&gt; in my english.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am now learning another language, which is similarly difficult and I’ve started experiencing this again. Which reminded me of the pain I felt learning English. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please be considerate to non-fluent speakers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：通过结账进行的慈善捐款帮助大公司逃税。]]></title><description><![CDATA[每天在快餐店、杂货店和大型商店，在结账时他们会要求你
捐赠零钱给当地或全国的慈善机构。

这些公司会收集所有的捐款，并把它们交给慈善机构。
慈善机构。这些捐款来自公司，而不是来自消费者。通过这样做，它成为一个主要的
税款写...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/osecwh/ysk_donations_for_charity_done_via_checkouts_help/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/osecwh/ysk_donations_for_charity_done_via_checkouts_help/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 20:37:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everyday at fast food, grocery and major stores, during checkout they will ask you to donate change, to a local or nation wide charity. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These companies will then collect all the donations and give them to the charity. From the company, not the consumer. By doing this, it becomes a major tax write off in the USA, making them have to pay less overall tax. Those tax dollars help improve general life in the country, including roads and education. Don&amp;#39;t give major companies a way to cheat on taxes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you wish to give to a charity, please give directly. The more middlemen, the less money will actually be used for the things that need it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Even through the money you give goes towards a charity, the company can write it off and avoid paying taxes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK："没有X的证据 "与 "没有X的证据 "是不一样的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：它将帮助你得出正确和符合逻辑的结论，并进行思考
批判性地思考。

例如，当你的医生说他没有看到任何癌症的迹象时，它
这实际上意味着，在他的观察中，没有癌症的证据，而不是说
有证据表明你没有患癌症。你...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/osn0zm/ysk_theres_evidence_of_no_x_is_not_the_same_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/osn0zm/ysk_theres_evidence_of_no_x_is_not_the_same_as/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 18:52:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: it will help you take the correct and logical conclusions and to think critically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, when your doctor says that he didn&amp;#39;t see any signs of cancer, it actually means that in his observation, there&amp;#39;s no evidence of cancer, not that there&amp;#39;s evidence that you don&amp;#39;t have cancer. You could then follow this information with other data such as what&amp;#39;s the probability of developing cancer if someone is told the same thing by their doctor, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK："可冲洗 "湿巾不能很好地分解，会堵塞管道，这可能导致数千美元的专业管道费用。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：公司显然有动力宣传其产品的最佳品质。
他们的产品。虽然可冲水湿巾与传统湿巾相比，更容易分解和
虽然可冲水湿巾与传统湿巾相比更容易分解，但它们并不像传统湿巾那样有效。
正如许多人所认为的那样。你应该非常警惕地把它们冲下去......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oso4qt/ysk_flushable_wipes_do_not_break_down_well_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oso4qt/ysk_flushable_wipes_do_not_break_down_well_and/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 17:46:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Companies are obviously incentivized to advertise the best qualities of their products. While flushable wipes are more likely to break down and decompose compared to traditional wipes, they are not as efficient as doing so as many people believe. You should very wary of flushing them down your drains to avoid expensive repair bills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source for more information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.greenamerica.org/blog/are-flushable-wipes-really-flushable&quot;&gt;https://www.greenamerica.org/blog/are-flushable-wipes-really-flushable&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你在开车时多花点时间，收银员往往会因此而惹上麻烦。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：大多数驾驶座里面都有计时器。根据商店的情况，它们
为了 "提高生产力"，它们往往是不合理的，也是不可能维持的。

在现实中，这意味着那些阅读菜单的顾客，没有快速拉开距离，或者一般在店内花费超过90秒（总共）。
足够的时间，或通常在店内花费超过90秒（总共）。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/osf2wz/ysk_if_you_take_extra_time_in_a_drive_thru_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/osf2wz/ysk_if_you_take_extra_time_in_a_drive_thru_the/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 06:59:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Most drive thrus have timers inside. Depending on the store, they are often unreasonable and impossible to maintain, to &amp;quot;promote more productivity&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In reality, this means that customers who read the menu, don&amp;#39;t pull away fast enough, or generally spend more than 90 seconds (total) in the drive thru, can be a cause of a lot of stress on cashiers. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As anyone who&amp;#39;s worked customer service can tell you, managers often make life much harder. This standard was a huge problem when I worked a drive thru a few years ago. Threats of being written up or fired over a car that took two minutes to leave the store from the time it pulled to the speaker is ridiculous, but sadly also a daily occurrence. And the poor customer who just needed to read the menu has no idea that maybe &lt;em&gt;they&lt;/em&gt; were the straw that broke the camel&amp;#39;s back and lost that person their job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What you can do: if you don&amp;#39;t know what you want, go inside if you&amp;#39;re able. They&amp;#39;ll be trying to get your food almost as quickly, but they won&amp;#39;t get in trouble. You&amp;#39;ll also have a much easier time making special requests or instructions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you really can&amp;#39;t go inside, look it up. Figure out what you want before arriving. Streamlining the process will come back around when all the employees love you for making their jobs easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And, please, don&amp;#39;t verbally abuse the cashiers like every other customer. You&amp;#39;re not above them. If you want to be treated like royalty, fast food isn&amp;#39;t the place the do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: A lot of the comments seem to be about this similar point. No, none of this is the customer&amp;#39;s responsibility. Yes, it&amp;#39;s a horribly flawed system. Still, that doesn&amp;#39;t stop that cashier from learning what an anxiety attack is at their first job&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如果你可以选择用固定电话而不是移动设备拨打紧急服务电话]]></title><description><![CDATA[用座机拨打紧急服务电话，可以让他们准确地确定你的位置，而不是让他们确定你的位置。
准确的位置，而不是让他们找出你的确切位置
和可能的错误。

为什么是YSK：当涉及到紧急情况时，每一秒都很重要，可能是
紧急情况下，每一秒都很重要，可以成为生命与安全之间的区别...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oq8hbr/ysk_if_you_have_the_option_call_emergency/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oq8hbr/ysk_if_you_have_the_option_call_emergency/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 05:53:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Calling emergency services on a landline allows them to triangulate your position accurately rather than them having to work out exactly where you are and potentialy getting it wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: when it comes to emergency situations every second matters and can be the difference between life and death.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：对于一个新的大麻消费者来说，食用1毫克和10毫克的THC可谓是一种非常不同的体验。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：我最近听到了很多关于人们在第一次使用大麻时服用食用剂的故事。
的故事，许多人并不清楚他们应该服用多少毫克四氢大麻。
许多人不清楚他们应该服用多少毫克四氢大麻酚，尽管包装上的说明很清楚。
包装上的说明。所以我想这是我对大麻的RTFM。

对于人们来说...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/os8tpi/ysk_having_a_1_mg_vs_a_10_mg_thc_edible_can_be_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/os8tpi/ysk_having_a_1_mg_vs_a_10_mg_thc_edible_can_be_a/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 01:47:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: I&amp;#39;ve heard a lot of stories recently about people who take an edible for their first time using cannabis, and many people aren&amp;#39;t acutely aware of how many MG of THC they should take, despite the instructions being clear on the package. So I guess this is my RTFM for cannabis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For people who have never had cannabis (or who haven’t had it in recent months), you might want to try taking only 1 MG of THC. For example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1 MG: Some people will feel mild euphoria, some will feel nothing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2 - 3 MG: Some people will feel euphoria and psychedelic effects, some will feel very little&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 - 5 MG: Many people will feel euphoria and psychedelic effects, some people might feel overwhelmed or anxious&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5 - 10 MG: Most people will feel strong euphoria and psychedelic effects, many people will feel overwhelmed or anxious&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Start low and go slow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s better to take too little than to take too much. If you take too much you can experience mild to severe anxiety, panic attacks, and other unpleasant feelings. In some cases, people have a very bad experience that can cause lasting trauma.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Know your dose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking 1 MG of THC on a Friday night, with a buddy to keep you company, is a great idea for your first time consuming cannabis. If you don’t experience any effects, take 2 MG the next time. Then 3 MG the next time. Give your body a full 24 hours to process the experience before trying again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, after you’ve gotten to understand how to reach a place of mild euphoria, excitement, or relaxation (depending on the product you take), you can try more if you want a stronger effect—or not!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s fine if you want to blast off to the moon and take more, but I&amp;#39;m mainly just writing this for people who might not know how big a difference 1 MG vs. 10 MG can be for a cannabis newbie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Safe travels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.leafly.com/news/cannabis-101/cannabis-edibles-dosage-guide-chart&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，可以用水和小苏打去除皮肤上的染发剂污渍]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：没有人愿意在脸上或手臂上沾上染发剂的污渍后去工作或外出。
脸上、胳膊上等等。如果你是那种把头发染成深色的人
如果你是那种把头发染成深色的人，有时这些污渍会在你的皮肤上停留好几天。特别是
不方便工作或外出。用一块湿抹布，放一点...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/orfsq7/ysk_that_you_can_remove_hairdye_stains_from_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/orfsq7/ysk_that_you_can_remove_hairdye_stains_from_your/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 21:53:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: No one wants to go to work or go out after getting hairdye stains on your face, arms, etc. If you&amp;#39;re one of those people who dye your hair dark of crazy colors, sometimes those stains can stay on your skin for days. Especially inconvenient for work or outings. Use a wet rag, put a little bit of baking soda on it, and gently wipe the stains off. Scrubbing with baking soda may really hurt your skin so be sure not to scrub too hard. Baking soda is a very good absorbent. It works well for absorbing the hairdye color.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你在天空中看到明亮而快速的东西--比如一颗巨大的流星--那可能是一个火球。你可以向美国流星协会报告。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：美国流星协会汇总报告，并与NASA分享数据
与NASA分享。追踪陨石和火球是研究太空、太阳系和宇宙的一个重要部分。
空间、我们的太阳系和宇宙研究的重要部分。

这里是报告火球的链接，火球就是他们所说的大...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ort6ky/ysk_if_you_saw_something_bright_and_fast_in_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ort6ky/ysk_if_you_saw_something_bright_and_fast_in_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 10:13:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: The American Meteor Society aggregates reports, and shares the data with NASA. Tracking meteorites and fireballs is an important part of the study of space, our solar system, and the universe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://fireball.amsmeteors.org/members/imo/report_intro/&quot;&gt;Here is the link to report a fireball, which is what they call a large meteor&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在你的生活中拥有两部手机是很重要的。一个用于个人，一个用于商务]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：在不断增长的技术世界中，公司希望你在工作中使用你的个人电话（例如称为BYOD（自带电话））。
你的个人电话用于工作（例如，称之为BYOD（自带设备）），问题是，企业对你的工作要求很高。
设备），问题是公司希望保护他们的知识产权。
问题是企业想保护他们的知识产权，而这两件事是相互对立的。最...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/orq2he/ysk_it_is_important_to_have_2_cell_phones_in_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/orq2he/ysk_it_is_important_to_have_2_cell_phones_in_your/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 10:13:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: in the ever increasing world of technology companies expect you to use your personal phone for work (for example calling it BYOD (Bring your own device)), the problem is corporations want to protect their intellectual property and these two things butt up against each other. The most popular thing companies want you to do is download a 2 factor authentication app for your work resources. Also companies expect you to add your corporate email to your personal phone. These two things are just privacy disasters waiting to happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I administer a small exchange (Microsoft Outlook/Office email service) server and while I disable as much of it as I can the amount of personal information companies can take from your personal device without you knowing is quite scary. I also manage another solution that pulls a lot of information as well that it certainly should not. On top of that almost every organization has the ability to remotely wipe with no notification on your device (most common is through you adding your work email to your phone it gives them that authority), if you are not doing backups or even if you are you could be left with a lot of lost information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It might be annoying to have 2 phones but its also to help save your sanity. When you have a work mobile phone and a personal when you are on vacation or after hours you can leave/turn off your &amp;quot;work&amp;quot; phone and take some much needed rest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My rule is simple: My personal phone is for Reddit, to text/call friends &amp;amp; family, and all the normal stuff. My work phone is just that, it has my company email and company required apps and thats it. If work wiped my work phone then in the end nothing much is lost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a perfect world companies should be providing mobile devices to all employees expected to need to do anything with said device, but the small increase in an extra mobile plan each month will pay off for you in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK对蚊虫叮咬进行加热，可以立即缓解瘙痒的感觉。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我很少看到这种方法作为一种补救措施显示出来，所以我想我应该分享。你只是想
将受影响的区域暴露在热气中。我发现最好的方法是使用一个
我发现最好的方法是用吹风机调到高电平，并简单地让它在每个咬痕上停留尽可能长的时间。
尽可能长，最好是15秒左右。在这个过程中，该区域会发痒。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/orr1yl/ysk_applying_heat_to_mosquito_bites_will/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/orr1yl/ysk_applying_heat_to_mosquito_bites_will/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 07:37:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I rarely see this method shown as a remedy so I thought I’d share. You just want to expose the affected areas to heat. I’ve found the best way is to use a hairdryer set on high and simply leaving it over each bite for as long as possible, ideally around 15 seconds. The area will itch during the process for a few seconds and then immediately go away. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alternatively you can heat up a spoon over a stovetop and apply it directly to the skin. Just make sure it’s hot but not too hot that it’ll burn you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: mosquito bites can be really annoying and scratching the area can make itching worse and even cause infection. This method is safe, simple, uses equipment nearly everyone has and can be done in minutes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As far as why it works, it has to do with heat breaking down heparin, which is found in mosquito saliva. It prevents clotting which makes it easier to suck blood. Unfortunately it also causes inflammation and itching. Heat destroys heparin and the foreign proteins, stopping the autoimmune response.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 你可以在给别人打电话时隐藏你的号码]]></title><description><![CDATA[拨打*67，然后将你拨打的电话号码显示为限制号码。

为什么选择YSK：我个人在建筑行业工作，最近才发现这个功能。
我用它来拨打工作电话，在一天结束后，我没有人
打回我的电话。这为我节省了许多 "请不要......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/orn9gc/ysk_you_can_hide_your_number_when_calling_people/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/orn9gc/ysk_you_can_hide_your_number_when_calling_people/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 07:05:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dial *67 then the phone number your calling to come up as a restricted number. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Personally I work in construction and just recently discovered this and I use it to make calls for work and at the end of the day I dont have people calling my phone back. This saves me so many &amp;quot;please don&amp;#39;t call my personal phone at 2 am&amp;quot; incidents&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use it when I have to call sketchy numbers too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feel free to expand on this with what you use it for&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: to clarify the company i work for has a separate 24 hr emergency services line and some confuse that with personal phone
(I&amp;#39;m still newish to reddit hope this post is ok)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如果生的水果和蔬菜使你的喉咙发痒，你可能有口腔过敏综合症。你可以把大多数水果和蔬菜放在微波炉里加热10秒钟，然后重新冷却，以解决这个问题。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：口腔过敏综合征是最常见的食物过敏，你或你认识的人可能有这种情况。
你或你认识的人可能有这种情况。你可以通过杀死你提供的食物上的花粉来帮助他们。
你提供的食物。

我感到惊讶的是，许多朋友因为吃了香蕉、西瓜、李子等食物而喉咙发痒，但他们并没有放弃。
香蕉、西瓜、李子等引起的喉咙发痒，却不知道口服......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oobcjo/ysk_if_raw_fruits_and_vegetables_make_your_throat/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oobcjo/ysk_if_raw_fruits_and_vegetables_make_your_throat/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 04:54:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Oral allergy syndrome is the most common food allergy and you, or someone you know, may have it. You can help them out by killing the pollen on the food you serve. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been surprised that numerous friends who had their throat itch from bananas, watermelon plums etc. weren&amp;#39;t aware of oral allergy syndrome.  Also known as &amp;quot;food pollen syndrome&amp;quot; it relates to foods from a specific season that carry a type of pollen you&amp;#39;re allergic to (usually birch, grass, or ragweed).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 在大多数汽车上，如果你忘记了，一旦汽车熄火，转动并按住钥匙就会把车窗摇起来。]]></title><description><![CDATA[除了纯粹用钥匙操作的汽车外，把你的钥匙转到门上，就像你要锁门一样。
在锁门的时候，把钥匙放在那里一两秒钟。任何已摇下的车窗
的车窗应该会自动再次卷起。

为什么是YSK：因为在这些较热的日子里，它是非常有用的，可以省去你转动车窗的麻烦。
车子重新启动...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oown5a/ysk_on_most_cars_turning_and_holding_the_key_will/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oown5a/ysk_on_most_cars_turning_and_holding_the_key_will/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 02:56:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other than cars operated purely by a fob, turn your key in the door as if you were locking it yet hold it there for a second or two. Any windows which are rolled down should automatically roll up again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Because it&amp;#39;s super useful on these hotter days and saves you turning the car back on the event you forgot to roll up!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，大多数银行会在180天内兑现支票，即使支票上写着 "90天后无效"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么YSK："个人、企业和工资支票的有效期为6个月（180天）。
天）。) 一些企业的支票上预先印有 "90天后无效 "字样。
大多数银行会在180天内兑现这些支票，而预先印制的
的语言是为了鼓励人们尽早存入支票。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/orcj2r/ysk_that_most_banks_will_honor_checks_up_to_180/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/orcj2r/ysk_that_most_banks_will_honor_checks_up_to_180/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 18:51:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: &amp;quot;Personal, business, and payroll checks are good for 6 months (180 days). Some businesses have &amp;quot;Void after 90 days&amp;quot; pre-printed on their checks. Most banks will honor those checks for up to 180 days and &lt;strong&gt;the pre-printed language is meant to encourage people to deposit a check sooner than later.&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.huntington.com/learn/checking-basics/how-long-is-a-check-good-for#:%7E:text=Personal%2C%20business%2C%20and%20payroll%20checks,a%20check%20sooner%20than%20later.&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你与痤疮斗争了一年多。是时候去看 "医生 "了]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：因为人生苦短。不要再浪费你的时间去寻求建议了。

相信我。

我知道看皮肤科很贵（我住在美国），但计算一下你花了多少 "时间
你花了多少 "时间 "去尝试各种治疗痤疮的产品，但都失败了。有一个
机会，去看皮肤科比继续用药更便宜......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ore86s/ysk_if_you_struggling_with_acne_for_over_a_year/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ore86s/ysk_if_you_struggling_with_acne_for_over_a_year/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 17:34:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Because life is short. Stop wasting your time looking for advice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trust me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I understand it&amp;#39;s expensive to see a derm(I live in US), but calculate how much &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;TIME&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;quot; you&amp;#39;ve spent trying and failing various products for your acne. There&amp;#39;s a chance it&amp;#39;s cheaper to see a derm than continuing to spend money on products aimlessly. In total, from first visiting my dermatologist to curing my acne, it was about $900. I&amp;#39;ve had acne for almost 7 years, I guarantee I&amp;#39;ve spent more than $1000 over those years on acne cures and I had nothing to show for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I deeply regret not going on it earlier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry about the quotation marks from my title...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为使用微波炉的功率设置是重新加热食物的最简单方法]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：大多数重新加热的过程是这样的：用微波炉将食物加热一分钟，搅拌一下。
重复，搅拌，重复。如果您使用一半的功率设置，并以相同的时间甚至更长的时间进行微波加热
的时间，甚至多一分钟，你的食物就会在整个过程中均匀受热。
没有热点或冷点，也不需要在中间搅动。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ora2oc/ysk_that_using_a_microwave_power_setting_is_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ora2oc/ysk_that_using_a_microwave_power_setting_is_the/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 16:44:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: most reheating goes like this: microwave food for a minute, stir, repeat, stir, repeat. If you use a half power setting and microwave for the same amount of time or even a minute longer, your food will heat evenly throughout with no hot or cold spots and no need to stir in the middle of the process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为，将汽车钥匙扣压在太阳穴上或下巴下，可以扩大/增加它对汽车的信号范围。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你拿着你的汽车钥匙扣，把它按在你的太阳穴和或下巴/下巴的皮肤上。
在你的下巴/颌下，你可以有效地将信号的传播范围扩大一倍
传递到你的车上。

为什么YSK会这样。

当你离开你的车，发现你忘了锁车的时候，这很好。
而你通常甚至不...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oqvq0s/ysk_that_pressing_your_car_key_fob_up_against/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oqvq0s/ysk_that_pressing_your_car_key_fob_up_against/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 03:53:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you take your car key fob and press it up to the skin on your temple and or under your chin/jaw, you can effectively double the range to which the signal travels to your car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why YSK this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s great for walking away from your car and realizing you forgot to lock it and you usually don&amp;#39;t even have to turn back around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or if you need to find your car in a giant lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or if in case of an emergency you do need to use the panic button.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s Jeremy Clarkson with an example: &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/_jACSPipPSE&quot;&gt;https://youtu.be/_jACSPipPSE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: just to be clear because people seem to think this will kill you. It will not. The waves emitted from your key fob can not damage your tissue or your hands would have fallen off years ago... I&amp;#39;m surprised this needs to be explained and at the same time not surprised at all.......&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit 2: ok so people are too afraid of common frequency waves here. Here are articles explaining the amplification of the waves due to water molecules and others in your head with no warning of dangers... Because there are non:
-&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apartmenttherapy.com/tech-myth-holding-the-care-rem-83663&quot;&gt;https://www.apartmenttherapy.com/tech-myth-holding-the-care-rem-83663&lt;/a&gt;
-&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2009/02/19/technology/personaltech/19basics.html&quot;&gt;https://www.nytimes.com/2009/02/19/technology/personaltech/19basics.html&lt;/a&gt;
-&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vox.com/xpress/2014/11/22/7259707/car-key-fob&quot;&gt;https://www.vox.com/xpress/2014/11/22/7259707/car-key-fob&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：仅仅因为孩子不想做某件事，并不意味着他们懒惰，可能有一个原因。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK。

他们可能有抑郁症，他们可以在做一项活动时有更好的时间
(就像成年人一样)

有些人在上午工作更好，有些人在下午工作更好，有些人在晚上工作更好。
下午，有些人在晚上工作得更好。所以看看孩子什么时候
更好地提高工作效率。

每...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oqzwzn/ysk_just_because_a_child_doesnt_want_to_do/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oqzwzn/ysk_just_because_a_child_doesnt_want_to_do/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 03:40:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They could have depression, they could have a better time at doing an activity (just like adults)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some people work better in the morning, some people work better in the afternoon, some people work better in the evening. So see when the child is better at being more productive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every adult is different, so it should be safe to say that every child is different as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They could also have a mental disorder or something else entirely that you could look into, as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also: Parents tend to tell kids to do it, instead of explaining why something must be done. So, explain why that something must be done: Outside of just saying: &amp;quot;Because I said so&amp;quot; Would go a long way, as well. And explaining how something is done, as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes kids, just like adults, also just don&amp;#39;t feel like doing xyz at that moment, either. But adults tend to have more discipline in order to do that x thing, even if they don&amp;#39;t want to do it, compared to kids. (Or they (adults) wait until later to do it). So you shouldn&amp;#39;t give a kid such a hard time, when an adult acts the same way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The kids could also be bullied at school as well, or their teachers not care or whatever reason, elsewhere, as well. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read: How to Talk So Kids Will Listen and Listen So Kids Will Talk, for a better understanding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.erikaslighthouse.org/the-parent-handbook-on-childhood-and-teen-depression&quot;&gt;https://www.erikaslighthouse.org/the-parent-handbook-on-childhood-and-teen-depression&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.interiminc.org/2019/03/01/what-are-the-different-types-of-mental-illness/&quot;&gt;https://www.interiminc.org/2019/03/01/what-are-the-different-types-of-mental-illness/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://childmind.org/symptomchecker/&quot;&gt;https://childmind.org/symptomchecker/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check to see if your child has a mental disorder, or any other disability as well. So you can get the proper help for your child if your child does end up having one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为嘴唇开裂是男性和女性缺铁的标志。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：大多数人认为嘴唇开裂只是嘴唇干裂的一种形式。
而实际上，它们可能是缺铁的迹象，可能会导致
其他不利的健康影响。我的初级保健医生注意到我的嘴唇开裂，并要求进行血液测试，以检查我的铁含量。
检查我的铁含量。看吧，我的铁含量很低，可能是...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oquhaa/ysk_that_split_lips_are_a_sign_of_an_iron/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oquhaa/ysk_that_split_lips_are_a_sign_of_an_iron/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 00:24:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Most people think that split lips are simply a form of chapped lips, when in reality they can be a sign of an iron deficiency which could lead to other adverse health effects. My PCP noticed my split lip and ordered a blood test to check my iron levels. Lo and behold, I was quite low likely due to a couple of recent surgeries. Luckily with a daily supplement, my split lips cleared up quickly and haven&amp;#39;t returned.
Sources such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theironclinic.com/symptoms/&quot;&gt;The Iron Clinic&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/nutrition/chapped-lips-vitamin-deficiency&quot;&gt;Healthline&lt;/a&gt; have confirmed that split lips and similar symptoms could be a sign of iron deficiency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如果你想轻松获得苏联时代的电影，你可以在YouTube上免费找到大多数经典作品。]]></title><description><![CDATA[YSK Mosfilm（Mosfilm Cinema Concern）电影工作室将一系列苏联时期的
纪录片在他们的YouTube频道上。其中大部分影片都可以看到高质量的
和英文字幕。你只需要看一个广告就可以欣赏到
不间断的。

频道链接：...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/opi0z4/ysk_if_you_want_to_easily_access_soviet_era_films/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/opi0z4/ysk_if_you_want_to_easily_access_soviet_era_films/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 21:25:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;YSK Mosfilm (Mosfilm Cinema Concern) filmstudio has uploaded an array of Soviet era films to their YouTube channel. Most of them can be seen with high quality and English subtitles. You only need to see one ad before you can enjoy it uninterrupted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Link to channel:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://m.youtube.com/user/mosfilm&quot;&gt;https://m.youtube.com/user/mosfilm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many Soviet era films are life changing experiences, but starting out watching movies in foreign languages is hard especially when those movies are increasingly unavailable. Here&amp;#39;s some of my favourite Soviet films available at the channel:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stalker (1979):
&lt;a href=&quot;https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=TGRDYpCmMcM&amp;amp;t=715s&quot;&gt;https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=TGRDYpCmMcM&amp;amp;t=715s&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mirror (1975):
&lt;a href=&quot;https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=CYZhXm02kN0&quot;&gt;https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=CYZhXm02kN0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Everything made by Andrei Tarkovsky really)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come and see (1985):
&lt;a href=&quot;https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=UkkJZweYaLI&amp;amp;t=49s&quot;&gt;https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=UkkJZweYaLI&amp;amp;t=49s&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kin-Dza-Dza  (1986):
&lt;a href=&quot;https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=EYHv8eJrW2Y&quot;&gt;https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=EYHv8eJrW2Y&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cranes are flying (1957):
&lt;a href=&quot;https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=2OccZQmxKac&quot;&gt;https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=2OccZQmxKac&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WHY YSK Finding legal ways to watch your favorite Soviet films is at times impossible, but Mosfilm studio has slowly been making their films easily accessible on YouTube for ten years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: Just found out YouTube has put ads in the middle of some films. Just a year ago the films only had one ad in the beginning... Reason i didn&amp;#39;t find out is i got YouTube premium&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如果你拥有的三星冰箱的制冰机出现故障，你可以得到一个免费的更换。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：三星的法式门冰箱和制冰机一直存在很多问题。
和制冰机的问题。制冰机会被冻住，导致它不再
制冰机会被冻结，导致它不再制冰，直到被强制解冻，而且冰会在储存器中融化。

如果你与三星公司联系，有这个问题的型号，他们会发...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oqo38u/ysk_if_you_own_a_samsung_refrigerator_with_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oqo38u/ysk_if_you_own_a_samsung_refrigerator_with_a/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 12:53:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: There has been a lot of issues with Samsung’s french door refrigerators and their ice makers. The ice maker will freeze over causing it to no longer make ice until force thawed and ice will melt in the storage holder. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you contact Samsung with a model that has this issue, they’ll send a technician to fix it for free even if it’s outside the warranty period.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK你可以在你的路由器上使用Cloudflare的DNS服务来自动阻止成人和恶意的内容]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：Cloudflare的1.1.1.1[https://1.1.1.1]服务一直是一个简单的方法，以
获得免费、私密、安全的DNS查询（如果是你的移动设备，还可以获得一个
VPN）已经有几年时间了。然而，我今天才发现，他们
他们还提供了两种小型的服务，让你可以使用。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oq6pg8/ysk_you_can_use_cloudflares_dns_service_on_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oq6pg8/ysk_you_can_use_cloudflares_dns_service_on_your/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 10:24:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Cloudflare&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://1.1.1.1&quot;&gt;1.1.1.1&lt;/a&gt; service has been an easy way to get free, private, secure DNS lookups (and in the case of your mobile devices, a VPN too) for a few years now. However, I only just found out today that they also offer two small variants to this service which all you to either 1) block malicious content, or 2) block malicious and adult content, which is very useful for homes with young kids, to stop them from ending up on inappropriate websites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the normal DNS service, you can configure your router to use the following 4 DNS servers for improved performance and privacy:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1.1.1.1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1.0.0.1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2606:4700:4700::1111&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2606:4700:4700::1001&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to also block malicious content, change the final &amp;quot;1&amp;quot; of each address to a &amp;quot;2&amp;quot; (i.e. 1.1.1.2, 1.0.0.2 etc.) and to also block adult content, change each final &amp;quot;1&amp;quot; to a &amp;quot;3&amp;quot;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1.1.1.3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1.0.0.3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2606:4700:4700::1113&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2606:4700:4700::1003&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://developers.cloudflare.com/1.1.1.1/1.1.1.1-for-families&quot;&gt;More details and instructions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK关于微软数学解算器]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK：如果你是一个学生，在数学上有困难，那么你应该使用
Microsoft Maths Solver。它是一个可以解决你大部分数学问题的应用程序。
与传统的计算器不同，它解释并分解了方程式和问题。
问题。我已经使用了一段时间了，你应该...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oq6xbp/ysk_about_microsoft_maths_solver/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oq6xbp/ysk_about_microsoft_maths_solver/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 20:54:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;why YSK: if you are a student and have trouble with maths then you should use Microsoft Maths Solver. it is an app which can solve most of your math problems. Unlike traditional calculators, it explains and breaks down the equations and problems. I have been using this for a while and you should too. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: this is not a sponsored advertisement. i found it useful so i thought i should share with my fellow redditors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK在一段关系中问一些含糊不清的问题可能是灾难性的，很多时候我们都是在不知不觉中这样做的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：那些看似无害但却迫使你的另一半做出不舒服的回答的问题
的问题都是自找麻烦。但我们的天性是问
问题，我们既想从我们的另一半那里得到诚实的反馈，也想得到
验证。相反，表达你对这个话题或问题的感受...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oq4yfq/ysk_asking_loaded_questions_in_a_relationship_can/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/oq4yfq/ysk_asking_loaded_questions_in_a_relationship_can/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 17:36:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: questions that seem harmless but are forcing an uncomfortable answer out of your significant other are asking for trouble. But it&amp;#39;s our nature to ask questions where we want both honest feedback from our SO but also want validation. Instead, express your feelings about the topic or question at hand and request feedback on that emotion. Examples at the end. Also, while this can apply to any relationship, I wanted my focus on this post to be for couples in romantic relationships. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s tough to answer: don&amp;#39;t you absolutely love this new recipe I made right after my long day of work standing on my feet and getting exhausted? Do I look good in this outfit that doesn&amp;#39;t match and is totally inappropriate for the event we are attending? *Do I look fat, BE HONEST? *&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an alternative which will help you get the feedback and validation you need while also receiving constructive criticism that won&amp;#39;t feel like an attack when you&amp;#39;re in need of a self esteem boost, you need to rephrase the question into an open ended statement that encourages a conversation, not a yes or not absolute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hey, I found this new recipe online I wanted to try but I didn&amp;#39;t feel too confident while I was making it. I feel like there may be something missing but what do you think?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m trying something new with this outfit. There&amp;#39;s just something about it I really like but is there anything I should change about it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I &lt;em&gt;know&lt;/em&gt; I haven&amp;#39;t been eating well or exercising as much as I used to. I don&amp;#39;t feel happy with how I look. I just feel like I look fat. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That last one is always difficult to address in any kind way as we have been conditioned to focus on our appearance well beyond any other aspect of our life. But this will at least help your SO take the hint to be encouraging and supportive rather than force them to lie or be awkward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如果你正在慢跑，从后面接近某人，说些什么]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：一个人在没有打招呼的情况下跑到某人身后，真的会引发一些人觉得他们即将受到攻击。
触发一些人觉得他们即将被攻击。女性
尤其是对快速接近她们的脚步声保持高度警惕。
如果一个人特别擅长武术，你实际上可以...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/optu41/ysk_if_you_are_jogging_and_approaching_someone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/optu41/ysk_if_you_are_jogging_and_approaching_someone/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 05:45:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: a person running up behind someone without a greeting can really trigger some individuals into feeling they&amp;#39;re about to be attacked. Women especially are hyper vigilant about footsteps approaching them at a rapid pace. If one is particularly skilled in martial arts, you actually could experience a counter attack simply by failing to announce your presence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：有一个快速、简单、便宜的方法来修复地毯的卷角。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么选择YSK: 地毯的卷角不仅看起来很糟糕，而且会有绊倒的危险。

只需从当地的家庭装修商店买一块可剥落的乙烯基瓷砖，将其切成两半，形成一个三角形。
把它切成两半，形成一个三角形，然后把它贴在卷起的角的下面。
角。胜利！"。超级便宜和容易修复。享受不被绊倒的乐趣...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/opsoa7/ysk_theres_a_fast_easy_and_cheap_way_to_fix/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/opsoa7/ysk_theres_a_fast_easy_and_cheap_way_to_fix/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 04:59:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: Curled corners of rugs not only look bad, but they can be trip hazards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just get a peel and stick vinyl tile from your local home improvement store, cut it in half to form a triangle, and stick it to the underside of the curled up corner. Viola! Super cheap and easy fix. Enjoy not tripping over your rugs!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK认为 "犹太人 "既是一个民族，也是一种宗教（民族宗教）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[为什么是YSK：正如标题所说，某人是犹太人，并不一定意味着他们遵循犹太教。
意味着他们信奉犹太教。而且，仅仅因为某人遵循犹太教，并不代表他们
不一定意味着他们有犹太血统。你可以两者兼备，非此即彼，不必
必须是另一个。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/opqc4u/ysk_that_being_jewish_is_both_an_ethnicity_and_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/opqc4u/ysk_that_being_jewish_is_both_an_ethnicity_and_a/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 02:39:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why YSK: As the title says, just because someone is Jewish, doesn’t necessarily mean they follow Judaism. And just because someone follows Judaism, doesn’t necessarily mean they have Jewish blood. You can be both and either/or without having to be the other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>