<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 19:01:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，如果你在餐廳的等待時間比你想的要長，那麼女主人簡直就是這棟樓裏最不值得被罵的人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：餐廳女主人的首要目標是儘快爲你的聚會安排座位。
餐館女主人的首要目標是儘可能快地安排你的聚會。這符合她自己的最佳利益
爲了她自己的利益，她會讓你直接進入餐廳，所以請你放心，如果她有什麼需要幫助的地方，她會幫助你。
如果她能做什麼來減少您的等待時間，請放心。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rht67a/ysk_that_if_your_wait_at_a_restaurant_is_longer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rht67a/ysk_that_if_your_wait_at_a_restaurant_is_longer/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 18:40:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: The primary goal of the hostess at a restaurant is to seat your party as quickly as possible. It is in her own best interest to move you right on through to the dining room, so please be assured that if there was anything she can do to lower your wait time, she would do it. She does not deserved to be yelled at because your wait is 15 minutes longer than you expected. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Pretty much every restaurant is woefully understaffed right now. Those that survived the last couple of years are trying to operate as lean as possible. Until the restaurant industry has time to recover, this is likely to remain the case. Even then, I imagine they will have a tough time attracting enough workers to become fully staffed unless they make dramatic improvements to how their employees are compensated. The hostess that you are taking your frustrations out on is one of, if not the lowest paid, employees in the restaurant, and in many cases it is their very first job. With the staffing situation the way it is now, she is very likely having to bus tables, answer the phone, pack to-go orders, and do cleanliness checks on the restrooms, as well as manage the waitlist and coordinate the seating of diners. On top of that, she is going to be the first one to get grief from her managers when customers start to pile up waiting to be seated.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The hostess at a restaurant cannot seat you if there isn’t a table available for you. It’s as simple as that. Just because you see an empty table, or a dozen empty tables, doesn’t mean that there are enough servers on duty to work those tables. The hostess cannot put you at a table that doesn’t have a server assigned to it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you MUST yell at someone, first of all, get some psychiatric help at the first opportunity, but until then maybe yell at other diners who loiter for an hour after their meal is finished. Or yell at the manager, who at least to some degree has some control over how the restaurant is staffed at any given time. Maybe write a scathing email or make an irate phone call to the corporate office, if it’s a chain, or the owner if it’s privately owned, and insist that they raise wages or do whatever they need to do to attract more staff.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please, if you are not capable of being patient and showing a little bit of grace, please just eat at home. You never know the battles someone else is fighting in their life, and your harsh words at that particular time may have an impact that on them that you never intended.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：無論你的工作場所如何推崇 "家庭文化"--記住，他們不是你的朋友，它仍然是一個工作場所。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：我的女朋友學到了這一點，她很難受--她在陽光下爲創業公司工作了每一個小時。
她爲一家初創公司工作了每一個小時，當她不工作的時候
會以社交身份與他們共度晚間。她去年被解僱了，原因是
因爲公司有現金流問題，他們所有人都停止了......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhnerx/ysk_no_matter_how_much_your_workplace_pushes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhnerx/ysk_no_matter_how_much_your_workplace_pushes/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 12:43:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: my gf learned this the hard - she worked every hour under the sun for a startup and when she wasn&amp;amp;#39;t working would spend evenings with them in a social capacity. She got fired last year due to the company having cash flow issues and all of them stopped responding to her messages. She put so much work into trying to make the company successful and sacrificed other parts of her life for them, but they didn&amp;amp;#39;t really give a shit about her. I&amp;amp;#39;m not saying go around and be a dick to people for no reason, but it&amp;amp;#39;s better to build relationships outside of work or in places where there aren&amp;amp;#39;t any power imbalances or incentives to screw people over.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK不同類型的性虐待/騷擾/攻擊行爲]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK是因爲我最近剛被性騷擾了。
我想說的是，我最近被性騷擾了，而且沒有得到公正的對待。
所以這裏有一些不同的類型，如果不是所有的類型，只是沒有人和我一樣受到傷害。
所以這裏有一些，如果不是所有不同的類型，只是沒有人遭受和我一樣的痛苦，請務必聯繫......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhh0fc/ysk_the_different_types_of_sexual_abuse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhh0fc/ysk_the_different_types_of_sexual_abuse/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 08:36:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;why YSK is because i recently just got sexually harassed , and no justice came from it . all because people didn’t seem like it was “ a big deal “
so here’s some if not all the different types , just so nobody has to suffer the same as me . make sure to reach out to someone you love or trust :))&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;• rape
• attempted rape 
• unwanted touching or physical contact 
• unwelcome sexual advances
• unwanted sexual photos , texts , emails , etc . ( not just nudes )
• unwanted flashing 
• making conditions of employment or advancement dependent on sexual favors, either explicitly or implicitly.
• remarks of a sexual nature about a persons clothing , personal behavior , clothes , or body .
• purposely brushing up against a person 
• following or standing too close to a person on purpose .
• cat calling
• spreading sexual rumors 
•  taking photos of a person without their consent , especially private parts ( this is what happened to me , he took a photo of my ass and my teacher’s breasts )&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;all types of harassment is important and serious , please never think that it’s not . 
if i missed any on the list please tell me and i’ll add them !&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK在雨中使用你適當的大燈]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: because we can’t see you in our
mirrors. DRLs don’t count.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhcqkz/ysk_to_use_your_proper_headlights_in_the_rain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhcqkz/ysk_to_use_your_proper_headlights_in_the_rain/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 05:51:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: because we can’t see you in our mirrors. DRLs don’t count.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 上癮的循環很容易被預想（你的舊癮第一次出現在你腦海中的時刻）重新點燃。接下來是沉思、決心、行動、維持，最後是復發。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：你可以通過注意到以下幾點來打破成癮性
早期的跡象。如果你可以的話，當你發現你的觸發點時，告訴你的伴侶你的觸發點是什麼，這樣他們就可以和你一起注意。
</p> <p>這正是我個人上癮的模式。
這正是我個人上癮的模式，它完美地遵守了......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhfks8/ysk_the_addiction_cycle_is_easily_reignited_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhfks8/ysk_the_addiction_cycle_is_easily_reignited_by/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: You can break addictions by noticing the early signs. If you can, tell your partner what your trigger is when you find it so that they can be on the lookout with you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is exactly the pattern my personal addiction follows, and it adheres perfectly to the typical model researchers have found. Does it sound familiar?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bonus point for those who made it this far! Advertisements are artificial precontemplation triggers, targeted at ex-addicts.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://addictionresource.com/treatment/stages/&quot;&amp;gt;https://addictionresource.com/treatment/stages/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：男性和女性的中風症狀是不同的]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：我們都被告知要注意什麼？
我們都被告知，當某人發生中風時要注意什麼，但男性和女性實際上有不同的症狀，值得了解。
</p> <p><strong>在中風期間，男性和女性都有不同的症狀，值得了解。
在中風期間，男性和女性通常都會報告出現這些跡象......。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rh93nx/ysk_stroke_symptoms_are_different_for_men_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rh93nx/ysk_stroke_symptoms_are_different_for_men_and/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 03:48:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: We all get told what to look out for when someone is having a stroke but men and women actually have different symptoms and they are worth knowing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;During a stroke, both men and women typically report these signs appearing suddenly:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Numbness or weakness in the face, arm or leg, especially on one side of the body&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Confusion, trouble speaking or trouble understanding&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Trouble seeing in one or both eyes&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Difficulty walking, dizziness, or loss of balance or coordination&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Severe headache with no known cause&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Women, however, may also report these symptoms:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Hiccups&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Nausea&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Chest pain&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Fatigue&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Shortness of breath&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- A racing heartbeat&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s worth knowing in case a friend or a loved one is ever showing any of these signs as you need to act quickly!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK在涉及傷員的事件中，在周圍有很多人的情況下，幫助他們看管好自己的錢包和手機或他們所佩戴的任何貴重物品，或與他們在一起的人確認。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：在許多情況下，這些物品經常被其他人偷走。
</p> <p>不要把他們的物品放在你的口袋裏，除非你與死者有關係。
他們的物品放在你的口袋裏，除非你與該傷亡人員有關係。這可能
這可能會被認爲是你在偷東西。最好把它放在地板上......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgwtsg/ysk_in_an_incident_involving_a_casualty_in_public/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgwtsg/ysk_in_an_incident_involving_a_casualty_in_public/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 17:00:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: In many cases, these items are frequently stolen by other people who pretend to be helping.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Do not keep their items in your pocket unless you are related to that casualty. That may come off as you stealing it. It&amp;amp;#39;s best to leave it on the floor next to the casualty so everyone can see who picks up the wallet.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In a scenario where everyone is gathering around, no one would dare to pick up the casualty&amp;amp;#39;s wallet while it&amp;amp;#39;s very noticeable.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As someone living near a junction where the traffic is confusing and prone to accidents, people stealing money/valuables from the casualty has happened more times than I can count.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK開始爲小動物進入你的房子或汽車做準備]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：越來越冷了
天氣有時會把不受歡迎的客人帶到你的汽車和/或房子裏的溫暖和安全的地方。
和/或房子裏。它們變得飢腸轆轆，會以你的電線、絕緣體和軟管爲食。
造成昂貴的損害。有一輛2022年的MDX說警告......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgq73g/ysk_to_start_preparing_for_small_animals_entering/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgq73g/ysk_to_start_preparing_for_small_animals_entering/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 15:52:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: it’s getting colder and colder weather sometimes brings unwelcome guests into warm and safe spots in your car and/or house. They get hungry and will feed on your wires, insulation, and hoses causing expensive damage. Had a 2022 MDX come in saying warning lights were all on her brand new car. After inspecting it. I found the communication wire to be completely torn apart. Luckily I was able to fix it for less than $100, if not, it would have costed about $6K to replace being as that wire was part of the complete dash harness. However you handle rodents is entirely up to you but know that they can cause lots of damage; most of the time insurance companies and warranty companies will never back you up for that.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK "最低工資 "是法律允許的最低工資。"起始工資 "是僱主提供給新僱員的實際工資。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：我看到很多僱主現在把提供的最低工資稱爲
我看到很多僱主把提供的入門工資稱爲最低工資。雖然我認爲他們可以
我想他們是可以使用這些詞的，但如果在他們宣佈他們的最低工資時造成誤解，那就太可惜了。
當他們宣佈他們提高了最低工資時，這將是一種恥辱。A...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgmkhq/ysk_minimum_wage_is_the_lowest_wage_allowed_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgmkhq/ysk_minimum_wage_is_the_lowest_wage_allowed_by/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 14:38:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;WHY YSK: I see a lot of employers now calling the entry wage offered their &amp;amp;quot;minimum wage&amp;amp;quot;. While I suppose they are allowed to use those words, it would be a shame if it caused misunderstanding when they announce they &amp;amp;#39;raised their minimum wage&amp;amp;#39;. A raise in minimum wage is something currently being urged on government by many as a way to reduce poverty. A wage policy announced by a single employer is not enough.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你應該質疑你在網上看到的一切。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：有這麼多的視頻、圖片和
事實在互聯網平臺上。很多時候，這些視頻都是僞造的，或者是事實
很多時候，這些視頻都是僞造的，或者是將事實歸結到與圖片的原始目的無關的圖像上。
只要看一眼帖子上的評論，你就會發現，這些評論是多麼的......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgycx0/ysk_you_should_question_everything_you_see_online/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgycx0/ysk_you_should_question_everything_you_see_online/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 14:38:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: There are so many videos, images and facts on internet platforms. A lot of the time these videos are staged, or facts are attributed to an image that has no relation to the images original purpose. A glance at the comments on a post will show you just how many people lap it up without question.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The reason you should know is that it’s this blind belief that advertisers and scammers exploit daily. We are living in an age where companies have learnt how easy it is to manipulate us. By taking everything you see at face value you are opening yourself up to this manipulation. And basically opening up your wallet, and in some cases your values and belief systems.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It’s quick and easy to do a quick internet search about anything to find out if something is likely to be true. Don’t be one of the people who comment how impressed you are at a particular post because this just adds to the claim and makes it more difficult for others to determine if something is genuine. It should be obvious not to believe everything you see online but it seems like we have started to take that for granted and have forgotten that lately.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 有可能在同一批衣物中清洗你的白色和彩色。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：許多人把白色和深色的衣服分開洗，以防止染上白色。
衣服分開洗，以防止給白衣服上色，佔用額外的水和時間。
</p> <p><strong>如果你使用的是標有白色的洗衣粉，那麼你就會發現你的衣服是白色的。
</p> <p><strong>如果你使用標有 "對顏色安全 "的增白洗衣粉，並使用冷水洗滌</strong>，那麼大多數人都會選擇用冷水洗滌。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgly9i/ysk_its_possible_to_wash_your_whites_and_colors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgly9i/ysk_its_possible_to_wash_your_whites_and_colors/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 07:42:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Many people wash their whites and darks in seperate loads to prevent coloring their whites, using up extra water and time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;If you use a whitening laundry powder labeled &amp;amp;quot;Safe on colors&amp;amp;quot; AND wash using cold water&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, then most whites will stay white even when washing them with dark or colored clothes. I&amp;amp;#39;ve done this many times using Oxi-clean White Revive and it&amp;amp;#39;s always worked. I believe there&amp;amp;#39;s other brands with similar products.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just be careful not to wash clothes with heavy ink (e.g. Tie-dye or sharpie) in the same load as whites.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT: To clarify, the whitening powder isn&amp;amp;#39;t strictly necessary unless you want to use a whitener. A lot of people do, but if you don&amp;amp;#39;t, then you can skip it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你在美國，YSK--EBT和SNAP福利可以用來在網上訂購食品雜貨，以便送貨或在路邊取貨。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：在美國，使用這些福利的人有這種恥辱感。
使用這些福利的人，這使得一些人在申請時感到擔心。
這使得一些人擔心在第一時間申請。有些人害怕去排隊結賬，冒着被人評頭論足的風險。
說你是如何依靠......的。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgjo1d/ysk_if_you_are_in_the_us_ebt_and_snap_benefits/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgjo1d/ysk_if_you_are_in_the_us_ebt_and_snap_benefits/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 07:42:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: There is this stigma in the US for people who use these benefits and this makes some people worried to apply in the first place. Some fear going to a checkout line and risk someone judging you or making a remark how you are &amp;amp;quot;relying on handouts&amp;amp;quot;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Although these people should just be ignored, it is still there and stopping people from getting food they need. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you&amp;amp;#39;ve ever worked a job, and paid taxes, you&amp;amp;#39;ve already contributed so don&amp;amp;#39;t feel bad. These benefits are a very GOOD thing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anyways, with the help of technology it&amp;amp;#39;s easy to shop online with EBT or SNAP and get curbside delivery, or you can even have your groceries delivered directly to your house.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ll provide a link that details all of the places you can use your benefits. I hope this can help someone who otherwise might not apply.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://foodstampsnow.com/list-of-grocery-stores-that-accept-ebt-online-for-delivery/&quot;&amp;gt;https://foodstampsnow.com/list-of-grocery-stores-that-accept-ebt-online-for-delivery/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK的短信 "741741 "將立即爲你聯繫危機諮詢師，只要你需要，他們就會與你溝通，而且對任何人都是免費的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：隨着假期的臨近，你應該知道。
你應該知道，如果你感到抑鬱，或有自殺傾向，或你需要有人
傾訴，<a href="https://www.crisistextline.org/">這是你可以利用的許多工具之一
</p> <p>你可以利用許多工具</p>。</p> <p>你被通緝，你...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/re9m7u/ysk_that_texting_741741_will_immediately_connect/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/re9m7u/ysk_that_texting_741741_will_immediately_connect/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 21:37:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: With the holidays approaching, you should know that if you are feeling depressed, or suicidal or you need someone to talk to, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crisistextline.org/&quot;&amp;gt;this is one of many tools&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; that are available to you. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You are wanted, you belong, and the world is a better place with you in it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：用現金/借記卡支付實際上是在補貼其他用信用卡支付的顧客。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：信用卡網絡對其服務收取1-3%的手續費。
辦理費，因此，零售商和餐館通常會提高價格，以補償大家的損失。
他們的價格對每個人來說都是一種補償。信用卡持卡人將獲得1-3%的返還
的現金返還或積分，因此，即使零售商提高價格，他們也...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/reuuum/ysk_paying_in_cashdebit_effectively_subsidizes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/reuuum/ysk_paying_in_cashdebit_effectively_subsidizes/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 21:37:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Credit card networks charge a 1-3% processing fee for their services, so retailers and restaurants often mark up their prices for everyone to compensate. Credit card holders will get 1-3% back in cashback or points, so even if a retailer raises prices, they effectively get the fair-market value price for the good. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cash payers, otoh, don&amp;amp;#39;t - so they end up paying 1-3% above the normal asking price to compensate for credit card users.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 冬天來了，給你的輪胎加滿油吧!]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：低溫會使輪胎中的空氣凝結。
你的輪胎，所以即使是那些看起來很好的冬季或全天候輪胎，你的汽車或卡車的
</p> <p>這將增加磨損。
</p> <p>這增加了磨損，影響了行駛，並改變了輪胎與溼滑路面的接觸方式。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rf953q/ysk_winter_is_here_top_up_your_tires/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rf953q/ysk_winter_is_here_top_up_your_tires/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 21:37:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Cold temperatures condense the air in your tires, so even those perfectly OK looking winter or all weather tires on your car or truck can actually be dangerously low.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This increases wear, affects ride, and changes how the tire contacts slippery surfaces, making it potentially much more dangerous on slippery roads for both you, and the other drivers around you if you lose control.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A tire gauge is a cheap investment, check them at least once a month during the cold months of the year, it&amp;amp;#39;ll also give you warning if you develop a slow leak!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你可以很容易地從食譜網站上去除所有雜亂的東西（廣告、生活故事、彈出式窗口），只用OnlyRecipe提取食譜。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼選擇YSK：爲了在博客/網站上找到食譜而略過文字牆可能會讓人感到沮喪。
爲了在博客/網站上找到食譜而瀏覽文字牆，會讓人感到沮喪。作者這樣做是爲了獲得
在谷歌上獲得高排名。</p> <p>You can use <a
href="https://OnlyRecipe.app">OnlyRecipe.app</a> to extract the recipe
information. It works on…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbirw6/ysk_you_can_easily_remove_all_the_clutter_ads/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbirw6/ysk_you_can_easily_remove_all_the_clutter_ads/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 21:37:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: It can get frustrating skimming through text walls just to find the recipe on blogs/sites. Authors do it to get high ranking on Google. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You can use &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://OnlyRecipe.app&quot;&amp;gt;OnlyRecipe.app&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; to extract the recipe information. It works on almost all sites/blogs which follow a recipe standard when they post.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The end result will look like this. for example.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.pinimg.com/previews/E1LeuLp5.png&quot;&amp;gt;Meditarannean Tuna Pasta&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.pinimg.com/previews/4Za6mqQo.png&quot;&amp;gt;Slow cooked Italian Chicken and Peppers&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You can also save it to your phone directly using their app.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 你可以看到並使用Youtube上的不喜歡的東西，這要歸功於這個名爲 "Youtube的增強器 "的很棒的擴展。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：它已經存在很長時間了
他們剛剛更新了它，再次顯示不喜歡的內容...... <a
href="https://i.imgur.com/oKBujCE.png">https://i.imgur.com/oKBujCE.png</p>
<p>使用這個與贊助商屏蔽，你可以在沒有廣告或自我推銷的情況下觀看
廣告，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbpvot/ysk_you_can_see_and_use_youtube_with_dislikes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbpvot/ysk_you_can_see_and_use_youtube_with_dislikes/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 21:37:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: It&amp;amp;#39;s been around for a long time and they just updated it to show the dislikes again... &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/oKBujCE.png&quot;&amp;gt;https://i.imgur.com/oKBujCE.png&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Use this with SponsorBlock and you can watch without ads or self-promotion ads, etc. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I am not affiliated with anyone whatsoever, but after seeing how people are still watching youtube videos and how bad the ads are, etc... I felt the need to send some help out.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Vanced is another extension people will recommend and some of the extensions are also made for mobile devices for certain browsers. Cheers!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 你應該停止將你的簡歷保存爲 "簡歷.pdf"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：每當你送出一份簡歷時，你都應該從以下角度考慮。
你應該從收到簡歷的招聘人員的角度來考慮，因此，你的簡歷格式應該儘可能讓招聘人員容易接受。
因此，在格式上要儘可能地讓他們容易接受。
他們。這包括將其保存爲PDF格式，使信息...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rg7oik/ysk_you_should_stop_saving_your_resume_as/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rg7oik/ysk_you_should_stop_saving_your_resume_as/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:45:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Whenever you send off a resume you should think about it from the point of view of the recruiter receiving it and therefore format it in a way that is going to make it as easy as possible for them. That includes saving it as PDF, making the information clear and saving it in the format of full name followed by job title you&amp;amp;#39;re applying for: &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;FirstLast-JobTitle.pdf&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I see thousands of resumes and so few people remember to do this! It makes it so hard to find and share if you don&amp;amp;#39;t put it in an easily referencable format. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hope this is helpful!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，《時代》雜誌的 "年度人物 "不一定是讚美被選者的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：經常在《時代》宣佈他們的
往往會遇到反彈，因爲人們認爲他們選擇的人不值得稱讚。
他們所選擇的人不值得稱讚，他們建議他們認爲應該成爲年度人物的人。
他們建議用他們認爲應該成爲年度人物的人代替，提供不那麼有影響力的......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfu8j8/ysk_that_time_magazines_person_of_the_year_isnt/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfu8j8/ysk_that_time_magazines_person_of_the_year_isnt/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 03:42:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: often when Time announces their Person of the Year, it&amp;amp;#39;s met with backlash because people think the person they chose is undeserving of praise, and they suggest people they think should have been person of the year instead, providing less influential but morally better options.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Time magazine isn&amp;amp;#39;t always praising the person they select. It is who they think &amp;amp;quot;for better &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;or for worse&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;... has done the most to influence the events of the year&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hitler and Stalin have been person of the year. Elon Musk being person of the year doesn&amp;amp;#39;t mean that time thinks Elon Musk is the greatest person of the year. They think he was the most influential, whether that be good or bad.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：蘋果公司剛剛發佈了一項更新，允許用戶在其死亡後指定一個遺留的聯繫人。這將允許上述聯繫人在他們死後訪問其手機/設備上的信息和照片。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：多年來一直存在的問題是
多年來，擁有iOS設備的父母或親人去世後，他們的親人
由於手機上的安全措施，他們的親人在死後無法訪問他們的手機數據。
手機的安全措施。這導致了許多記憶的丟失，因爲蘋果公司...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfpr2r/ysk_apple_just_released_an_update_that_allows/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfpr2r/ysk_apple_just_released_an_update_that_allows/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 23:40:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: There has been issues for many years with parents or loved ones who have iOS devices and pass away that their loved ones cannot access their phone data after death due to the security measures on the phone. This has caused many memories to be lost as Apple won’t unlock a phone for anyone but the user. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You need to update to iOS 15.2, released today. It is on any phone above iOS 6s. When you do, go to Settings, then tap your name at the top, then tap Password and Security, the you will see Legacy Contact. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you set this up on a parents device, you can help them assign a contact to access the device after their passing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 移除食譜網站上的所有雜物（廣告、生活故事、彈出窗口），只提取使用OnlyRecipe的食譜。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼選擇YSK：爲了在博客/網站上找到食譜而略過文字牆可能會讓人感到沮喪。
爲了在博客/網站上找到食譜而瀏覽文字牆，會讓人感到沮喪。作者這樣做是爲了獲得
</p> <p>你可以使用<a
href="https://onlyrecipe.app/">OnlyRecipe.app</a>來提取菜譜信息。
信息。它可以在...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfkori/ysk_remove_all_the_clutter_ads_life_story_popups/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfkori/ysk_remove_all_the_clutter_ads_life_story_popups/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 23:40:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: It can get frustrating skimming through text walls just to find the recipe on blogs/sites. Authors do it to get high ranking on Google.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You can use &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://onlyrecipe.app/&quot;&amp;gt;OnlyRecipe.app&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; to extract the recipe information. It works on almost all sites/blogs which follow a recipe standard when they post.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The end result will look like this. for example.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.pinimg.com/previews/E1LeuLp5.png&quot;&amp;gt;Meditarannean Tuna Pasta&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.pinimg.com/previews/4Za6mqQo.png&quot;&amp;gt;Slow cooked Italian Chicken and Peppers&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You can also save it to your phone directly using the app. Scan recipe QR code using your phone camera and voila.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Short vid on how recipe camera scanner works :&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ziSNwjv9PXo&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ziSNwjv9PXo&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：更努力的工作並不總是意味着更好的結果。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：在這個世界上有一種態度
認爲努力工作自動意味着你會有一個更好的結果。這並不是
</p> <p>僅僅因爲你在肝臟和洋蔥上花了一個半小時，並不意味着你做出了什麼。
並不意味着你做的東西比普通的烤奶酪更美味....。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfm7du/ysk_harder_work_doesnt_always_mean_a_better_result/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfm7du/ysk_harder_work_doesnt_always_mean_a_better_result/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 21:43:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: There’s an attitude in this world that working hard automatically means you’ll have a better outcome. It’s not true.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just because you spent an hour and half on liver and onions doesn’t mean you made something tastier than a regular grilled cheese. Just because you wrote a song mixing time signatures and changing keys doesn’t mean it sounds better than some rudimentary Green Day tune. Just because you spent 8 years on a degree, doesn’t mean you developed a skill worth more than  $12/hr. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some valuable things in this world take hard work, but not everything that takes hard work is valuable. Before you work hard on something, ask if it’s the best use of your effort.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：當有人告訴你他們的問題時，永遠不要說 "至少"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：說 "至少 "意味着向對方暗示他們的驕傲。
另一個人，他們的問題並沒有那麼糟糕。實際上，他們的問題對他們來說是
對他們來說是糟糕的，這纔是最重要的。</p> <p>這也是對他們的否定，並沒有
讓他們講完它。"至少 "讓他們閉嘴....]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfmlcu/ysk_never_say_at_least_when_someone_is_telling/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfmlcu/ysk_never_say_at_least_when_someone_is_telling/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 21:43:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Saying “at least” implies to the other person that their problem isn’t that bad. In actuality, their problem is bad to them and that’s what matters. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It also dismisses them and does not let them finish speaking about it. “At least” shuts them down. They should not have to defend why their problem is a problem to you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Finally, just because they do not have it the worst or it could be worse, does not mean that they are not experiencing the pain from their own problem. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The example I’ve seen countless times is simple. If someone is telling you about a miscarriage and the emotional/physical pain they are experiencing and you reply, “at least you can have (or already have) children,” you are completely shutting them out.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: here’s a source &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=1Evwgu369Jw&quot;&amp;gt;https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=1Evwgu369Jw&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，對強姦受害者來說，性慾過強是很常見的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：通常情況下，媒體圍繞着一個強姦犯的敘述。
圍繞着強姦受害者的敘述，認爲他們由於創傷性經歷而完全排斥性/性行爲。
在這種情況下，與之相反的另一種情況有時會被人看不起，因爲他們的創傷經歷。
雖然有這種情況發生，但光譜的另一端有時會被看不起，並被徹底地...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfcs7a/ysk_that_being_hypersexual_is_common_for_rape/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfcs7a/ysk_that_being_hypersexual_is_common_for_rape/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 14:41:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Often times the media surrounds the narrative of a rape victim as someone who outright repels sex/sexuality as a result of their traumatic experience, and while that happens, the opposite end of the spectrum is sometimes looked down upon and outright ignored even though it’s highly common amongst rape victims.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Like any traumatic experience, rape has long and lasting impacts to the victim. And due to the unfortunate controversial nature of rape/ rape-culture in itself, stuff like the psychological repercussions of it are often not spoken about enough and swept under the rug.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“Rape trauma syndrome” (RTS) is the name attributed to the disruptions to normal, physical, emotional, and interpersonal behavior as a result of an assault. There are different stages assigned to the time after the assault. Symptoms can range from a complete minimization of the abuse (blaming oneself, watering it down), to dramatization (cannot stop speaking about it). Needless to say the emotional/physical effects of a rape range greatly. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sexual relationships of a rape survivor often become disturbed and they too, range greatly. Some victims shield from contact and develop a fear of intimacy, while others become hyper sexual or “promiscuous” as a subconscious means to reassert a measure of control over their sexual relationships. While this is a documented and common experience, it’s often overshadowed by the depiction of a sex-repulsed survivor. Sometimes due to the shame of it and purity culture in general.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：即使是緩慢流動的水也會帶來難以置信的風險。試圖穿越快速流動的溪流或洪水就是自殺。1米長的水立方是一噸的定義。想象一下，水是1噸的立方體，以這種速度移動，你就會知道汽車是如何被沖走的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：</p> <p>許多人大大地低估了
很多人都低估了小水體所能帶來的力量。
<p>有一個愚蠢的小經驗法則，實際上很有幫助。
如果你把一朵花掉在水裏，你是否有時間彎腰去摘？
它......。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rf59fx/ysk_even_slowmoving_water_presents_incredible/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rf59fx/ysk_even_slowmoving_water_presents_incredible/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 05:40:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Many people vastly underestimate the forces even small bodies of water can impart.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There&amp;amp;#39;s a silly little rule of thumb that&amp;amp;#39;s actually pretty helpful. If you dropped a flower in the water, would you have time to bend down and pick it up, or is flowing away out of reach by the time you did?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you can pick it up, you&amp;amp;#39;re fine.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If not, basically, if the water goes over your ankles you can be taken off your feet at any moment, mind the rocks, but are okayish.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If it goes over your knees, you&amp;amp;#39;re at serious risk of being taken by the stream.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you&amp;amp;#39;re trying to move something with a large surface area, like the wheels of a car, or god help you its deep enough to be pushing on the whole sides of the car, you&amp;amp;#39;re fucked.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Moving bodies of water contain incredible energies, water is really, really dense. I mean just think about picking up a big bucket of the stuff.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I see a lot of people drive cars over roads that have flooded and are in motion, and every time I wish I could scream at them before they go in.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Water is so dense, that whole ass car only weighs as much as 1-2 cubic meters of water. Its surface area can have a LOT more than that pushing on it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Your car absolutely will not win.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 松露油並不含有任何松露，而是使用一種化學物質來拙劣地模仿松露的香氣。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK: 很久以前，松露油是
只是注入了松露的油。<a
href="https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Truffle_oil">現在，它是注入了
2,4-dithiapentane,</a>一種碳氫化合物，其味道可以最好地描述爲
可以被描述爲對...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rf47q6/ysk_truffle_oil_does_not_contain_any_truffles_but/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rf47q6/ysk_truffle_oil_does_not_contain_any_truffles_but/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 04:45:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Once upon a time, truffle oil was just oil infused with truffles. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Truffle_oil&quot;&amp;gt;These days, it is oil infused with 2,4-dithiapentane,&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; a hydrocarbon with a flavor that can best be described as a parody of truffle.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I actually kind of liked truffle oil, until I ate the real deal, which is so much more subtle, deep and pleasant in flavor. It’s also far more expensive, sure—Italian white truffles can be over $200 per oz. But cheaper varieties, like Burgundy black truffles, are about a tenth of that: an expense well worth it in my opinion.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What irks me most is that restaurants will have dishes on their menu described as having truffles—truffle risotto, truffle fries, etc, but are really using truffle oil instead of the real thing. Not only do they use this as an excuse to upcharge the dish by ten dollars because of the “luxury” status, they also overwhelm the food with a pungent chemical inferior to the advertised product.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But don’t take my word for it:
&amp;amp;quot;One of the most pungent, ridiculous ingredients ever known to chef,&amp;amp;quot; Gordon Ramsay once told a competitor on MasterChef.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Reaching for the oil is &amp;amp;quot;a sure sign of someone who doesn&amp;amp;#39;t know what they&amp;amp;#39;re doing,&amp;amp;quot; Joe Bastianich said in the same episode.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;Fake truffle flavoring is one of those things that&amp;amp;#39;s especially upsetting, because not only does it taste like a bad chemical version of the real thing, it&amp;amp;#39;s the flavor that almost everyone now associates with truffles,&amp;amp;quot; Jonathan Gold says.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, if you enjoy truffle oil, power to you. But be aware that it is not truffles that you are tasting and paying big money for. And if you ever get a chance, try some real truffles: they rule.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK月桂葉可以使象鼻蟲和其他害蟲遠離。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK是如果你曾經處理過一個
蟲害，月桂葉能很好地阻止各種害蟲的侵襲。你只需
你只需在你的麪粉和大米中放一兩片月桂葉，就能讓它們遠離
遠離。你也可以將月桂葉散落在櫥櫃周圍，以保持它們...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rf1cph/ysk_bay_leaves_can_keep_weevils_away_along_with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rf1cph/ysk_bay_leaves_can_keep_weevils_away_along_with/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 03:40:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK is if you ever deal with an infestation, bay leaves are great at deterring all kinds of pests. All you have to do is put a bay leaf or two in your flour and rice and it will keep them away. You can also scatter the bay leaves around the cupboard to keep them out. This is an old trick my grandma taught me that I have been using since I was a kid.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: bay leaves lose their potency after awhile so you will have to change the leaves out every so often!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：真的很容易在不知不覺中把客服人員困在他們不想進行的對話中。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：從事客戶服務的人
幾乎不可避免地會與一些客戶進行閒談。
</p> <p>當這種情況發生時。
工人幾乎沒有辦法禮貌地拒絕......。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rebbc6/ysk_its_really_easy_to_unknowingly_trap_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rebbc6/ysk_its_really_easy_to_unknowingly_trap_a/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 19:41:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Someone who works in customer service will almost inevitably have casual conversations with some of the customers, especially if they see the same customers regularly.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When that happens, the worker has almost no way of politely declining the conversation if they don&amp;amp;#39;t feel like talking. For one, it could be considered rude, and the worker probably has to take special care to not hurt customers&amp;amp;#39; feelings.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Second, the worker can&amp;amp;#39;t just say &amp;amp;quot;Hey, I&amp;amp;#39;ve got to go&amp;amp;quot; and walk away. They have to stay, sometimes at the exact spot where you&amp;amp;#39;re having the conversation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The only thing that they can really do is maybe say &amp;amp;quot;Hey, I&amp;amp;#39;ve got a lot of work to do, can we talk later?&amp;amp;quot;, but some people wouldn&amp;amp;#39;t want to lie if they &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;don&amp;amp;#39;t&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; actually have work to do, and it can be awkward even if it&amp;amp;#39;s true.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I work at a hotel and this happens all the time. It&amp;amp;#39;s basically in my job description to be engaged with guests at all times, during conversations both casual and otherwise, which makes them think that I like these talks way more than I actually do.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Even when I try to give hints that I&amp;amp;#39;m not into it by not saying much, shifting my eye contact to my desk, or typing on my computer, they rarely get the hint. It&amp;amp;#39;s a terrible feeling to be all but forced to have a conversation when you really would rather not.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please don&amp;amp;#39;t keep people in long conversations unless you&amp;amp;#39;re &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;sure&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; they&amp;amp;#39;re into it, especially if the other party is at their job.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK i.e.和e.g.是兩個不同的東西]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>i.e.意思是它是其中之一，e.g.意思是
這些都是例子。例如，如果有人說&quot;選擇你最喜歡的
顏色（即藍色或紅色）&quot;他們是說在藍色和紅色之間選擇。如果
有人說&quot;選擇你最喜歡的顏色（如藍色或......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rekljb/ysk_the_ie_and_eg_are_two_separate_things/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rekljb/ysk_the_ie_and_eg_are_two_separate_things/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 13:39:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;i.e. mean it is one of these and e.g. means these are examples. For example, if someone said &amp;amp;quot;Choose your favorite color (i.e. blue or red)&amp;amp;quot; they are saying choose between blue and red. If someone said &amp;amp;quot;Choose your favorite color (e.g. blue or red)&amp;amp;quot; they are saying choose any color, but blue and red are just examples.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: I constantly see people use i.e. where e.g. should be used and e.g. where i.e. should be used and you will need to know this if you are doing something like giving someone instructions because if you say i.e. instead of e.g. then the person will think their options are limited.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To those who call BS: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.merriam-webster.com/words-at-play/ie-vs-eg-abbreviation-meaning-usage-difference&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.merriam-webster.com/words-at-play/ie-vs-eg-abbreviation-meaning-usage-difference&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：當一個零售業工作人員問你是否需要一個尺寸，讓他們幫你拿，他們實際上是要求你不要弄得一團糟，但卻很有禮貌。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：特別是在現在的假日季節
零售店變得非常繁忙，零售工人沒有時間
時間來打掃一整天的衛生。事實上，除了爲你打掃衛生，他們還有很多其他任務要做。
除了打掃衛生之外，他們還有很多其他任務要做，雖然他們正在...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/reja4r/ysk_when_a_retail_worker_asks_if_you_need_a_size/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/reja4r/ysk_when_a_retail_worker_asks_if_you_need_a_size/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 10:39:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Especially in the holiday season now with retail stores getting extremely busy, retail workers just don’t have the time to spend cleaning up all day. They do in fact have a lot of other tasks to do besides clean up after you, and although they are getting paid to keep the store tidy, their job description doesn’t include being your maid. A little mess is fine, but don’t be that person that all the employees will bitch about when you leave. Making all that mess is unnecessary and you’re making their life much harder when it is &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;SO&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; easy to not.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So if a worker asks if you need help with a size, let them get it. They’ll make no mess while getting it, you get the size you want, and then they have more time for the important tasks because they no longer have to clean up your mess. Everyone wins.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT FOR CONTEXT: Majority of this relates to clothing stores, but works for all goods stores. In general though if you’re making a mess looking for something and an employee comes and asks to help you, don’t say no because you can look for it, say yes because they can look for it without making a mess and it makes their life easier.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT AGAIN: Even if you live somewhere where being approached by staff to help is uncommon (which is crazy weird to me), the point is just don’t make a mess. Regardless of which country you’re in, the workers have better shit to do than clean up after people who somehow don’t know how to look through a neatly stacked pile of clothes without making it look like a bomb went off.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 如果有人不想慶祝他們的生日，你就不能強迫他們慶祝，用一些令人尷尬的驚喜來打斷他們的生活，並騷擾他們，直到他們最終讓步。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：你可能會說，你只是想讓他們知道你關心他們。
讓他們知道你關心他們。但你給對方的信息是
你並不關心他們的感受，因爲你所做的正是他們要求你不要做的事。
他們要求你不要做的事。他們最終會怨恨你，並討厭...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rebk9r/ysk_if_someone_doesnt_want_to_celebrate_their/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rebk9r/ysk_if_someone_doesnt_want_to_celebrate_their/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 01:47:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: You may say that you just want them to know you care about them.  But the message you’re sending the person is that you don’t care about their feelings, because you’re doing exactly what they asked you not to do.  They will end up resenting you, and hate celebrating it even more&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：隨着假期的到來，這是你一年一度的提醒。如果有人拒絕喝酒，不要推脫。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：假期是一個非常艱難的時期
對於正在恢復的酗酒者或因不同原因戒酒的人來說，是一個非常艱難的時期。如果有人
如果有人拒絕喝酒，不要大吵大鬧，也不要試圖說服他們喝酒。
</p> <p>玩得開心，不要殺死你的家人，並保持...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/re5ubk/ysk_this_is_your_yearly_reminder_with_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/re5ubk/ysk_this_is_your_yearly_reminder_with_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 20:45:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: the holidays are a really tough time for recovering alcoholics or people who quit for different reasons. If someone declines alcohol, don&amp;amp;#39;t make a scene or try to convince them to drink anyways.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Have fun, don&amp;amp;#39;t kill your family and stay safe&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK在每年的這個時候爲任何快遞或郵件服務留下水瓶/零食，對某人來說意味着很多。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK，每年的這個時候，甚至更多的是
今年更是如此（據我所知，至少在美國），郵件和包裹
服務是完全不堪重負的。這意味着你的郵遞員和包裹
包括像亞馬遜這樣的公司在內的快遞員甚至都...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rdwhij/ysk_leaving_water_bottlessnacks_for_any_delivery/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rdwhij/ysk_leaving_water_bottlessnacks_for_any_delivery/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 15:49:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK, this time of year and even more so this year (at least in the United States as far as I know), the mail and package services are completely overwhelmed. This means your mail carrier and package delivery people including companies like Amazon even are working long hours and are on a strict timeline, and may even get extra work thrown on them if they complete their work quick enough and not really be given notice/time to prepare. Plus they can&amp;amp;#39;t exactly carry and bunch of food/drinks (especially in cities) to last all day. Doing small things like leaving a bottle of water in the mailbox (marked for them, otherwise they may not take it due to a fear of theft claims) or a cooler even clearly marked &amp;amp;quot;help yourself delivery people&amp;amp;quot; can make a huge difference in their day. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My mom worked mail delivery for years and she always would point out the houses with glee as we drive through our small town that she remembered would have a bottle of water or snack waiting for her even when she was just a sub, as in didn&amp;amp;#39;t even have a set route every workday. When she got a set route some customers would even go as far as leaving her home made cookies and gift cards for coffee or lunch occasionally.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TLDR; Appreciate the people who even though are just doing their job, still keep doing it even when it&amp;amp;#39;s not even what they signed up for. You may just be another house if you don&amp;amp;#39;t, but you will probably be a highlight of a strangers day if you do and in today&amp;amp;#39;s world we need more of that!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit; if you are someone delivering please say what country/area of the country/service and what would help you whatever time of the year and any rules you have to follow to accept anything. About to go to sleep, but when I wake up sometime tomorrow I will edit again and add a list as best I can for anyone trying to set up care packages! Obviously water and snacks, but based off a comment I realized I&amp;amp;#39;ve got a bunch of cheap shake to activate hand warmers that could really be nice for someone out all day. I also know some companies have policies where &amp;amp;quot;helping themselves&amp;amp;quot; could be reported in today&amp;amp;#39;s day and age so we could avoid it being a worry I&amp;amp;#39;d like to know how! :) Have a good night/day everyone!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 有一個網站可以免費提供udemy,Coursera,edx等網站的付費課程，並可以合法使用優惠券。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：大多數人都沒有意識到
教育網站提供100%的促銷優惠券，這實際上使
</p> <p>這裏是</p> <p>教育網站提供100%折扣的促銷券，這實際上使這些課程可以免費註冊，並且終身有效。
href="https://coursetime.net/">網站</a>，該網站記錄了這些信息。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rdt0d3/ysk_there_is_an_website_that_offers_paid_courses/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rdt0d3/ysk_there_is_an_website_that_offers_paid_courses/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 10:42:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Most people are unaware that educational sites provide 100% off coupons for promotion which literally make those courses FREE to enroll with lifetime validity.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here is the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://coursetime.net/&quot;&amp;gt;Website&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; that keep a track of those coupons and is updated regularly , which means we can grab courses for FREE.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你的轉向燈快速閃爍，那麼前面或後面的燈泡就燒壞了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：製造商設置了他們的閃光器
繼電器在阻力較小時快速閃爍，例如當燈泡燒燬時
熄滅。許多人認爲這是一個短路或電氣問題，但實際上
</p> </div><!-- SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rddev0/ysk_if_your_turn_signals_blink_quickly_either_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rddev0/ysk_if_your_turn_signals_blink_quickly_either_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 03:39:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Manufacturers set their flasher relays to blink quickly when there is less resistance, such as when a bulb burns out. Many people think there is a short or an electrical issue, when in reality it is simply a burned out bulb.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 抑鬱症與悲傷是不同的]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：人們常常會說&quot;他們有什麼好的？
他們有什麼好鬱悶的？他們有一份好的工作/家庭/家等等。</p>
<p>抑鬱症可能是由導致悲傷的重大事件帶來的，比如悲傷
或創傷。但它也可以在沒有任何明顯的外部因素的情況下存在。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rdky5m/ysk_depression_is_different_from_sadness/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rdky5m/ysk_depression_is_different_from_sadness/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 02:46:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: people will often say &amp;amp;quot;what do they have to be depressed about? They have a good job/family/home/etc. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Depression can be brought on by major events that cause sadness, like grief or trauma. But it can also exist without any obvious external cause. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sadness is like a stubbed toe: it sucks and is temporary in most cases. Depression is like a broken bone: if not properly cared for, it can heal poorly and be debilitating for life. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you&amp;amp;#39;re depressed, stop blaming yourself for not having a &amp;amp;quot;reason&amp;amp;quot; and get the help you need to heal as best you can. If you find yourself thinking this about other people, try and step back to remember that depression is not a choice&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/health/depression/depression-vs-sadness&quot;&amp;gt;How to spot the difference &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m getting some push back on the &amp;amp;quot;chemical imbalance&amp;amp;quot; phrase so I did a quick fact check on myself. It&amp;amp;#39;s an outdated theory. Much research is needed but current thinking is there are many things that cause depression and not all of them are situational, which is my core point. For the scientific report, check the NIH link below or find peer reviewed journals and reliable sources for the most relevant information. 
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3181668/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3181668/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK你當地的圖書館很可能提供附近博物館的大幅折扣門票]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：我&#39;舉個例子。住在
我住在離波士頓不到一小時的地方，我的當地圖書館給所有城市的博物館提供折扣。
城市的博物館。我想帶我的女朋友約會去美術博物館。
美術館，通常每張票是25美元。但通過圖書館，你可以...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rdeqgu/ysk_your_local_library_likely_offers_heavily/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rdeqgu/ysk_your_local_library_likely_offers_heavily/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 22:38:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: I&amp;amp;#39;ll give an example. Living within an hour from Boston my local library gives discounts to all the city&amp;amp;#39;s museums. I wanted to take my girlfriend on a date to the Museum of Fine Arts which is normally $25 per ticket. But through the library you can get them for $10 per ticket. Turning the date from a $50 expense to a $20 expense.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It can make an awesome date/trip with friends much cheaper!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：當Manifestv3實施時，Chrome中的uBlock和其他廣告屏蔽將在一個月內失去大部分功能。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：你的隱私、數據使用和
瀏覽體驗將受到影響。如果你還沒有，請投資於一個
pihole or switch to a non-chromium browser</p> </div><!-- SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rdaz50/ysk_ublock_and_other_adblocks_in_chrome_will_lose/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rdaz50/ysk_ublock_and_other_adblocks_in_chrome_will_lose/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 21:40:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Your privacy, data usage, and browsing experience will be affected. If you haven&amp;amp;#39;t already, invest in a pihole or switch to a non-chromium browser&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK你可以將所有沒有塑料或金屬內襯的食物弄髒的紙和紙板產品堆肥。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：有機材料最終會出現在
埋葬的有機材料可以被回收到自然系統中。
使其生產和使用更具有可持續性。這包括紙巾、衛生紙
這包括紙巾、衛生紙、紙巾、比薩餅盒和其他外賣容器；以及其他一些可回收的材料。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rb853o/ysk_you_can_compost_all_food_soiled_paper_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rb853o/ysk_you_can_compost_all_food_soiled_paper_and/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 19:45:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: organic materials that end up in the landfill can be recycled back into the natural systems from whence that came, making the production and use more sustainable. This includes tissue, toilet paper, paper towels, pizza boxes, and other to go containers; as long as there is no metal or plastic in them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你可能認爲是凱洛格的替代品的品牌可能屬於凱洛格公司的YSK]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：Kellogg&#39;s擁有幾個
子公司和品牌。例如，你可能認爲購買Kashi穀物
而不是Kellogg&#39;s會傷害Kellogg&#39;s；但是，Kashi是Kellogg&#39;s的一個子公司。
然而，Kashi是Kellogg&#39;s的子公司。RXBar、Morningstar、Bear......的情況也是如此。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rd9rfs/ysk_that_brands_you_may_consider_as_alternatives/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rd9rfs/ysk_that_brands_you_may_consider_as_alternatives/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 15:48:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Kellogg&amp;amp;#39;s owns several subsidiaries and brands. For instance, you may think buying Kashi cereals instead of Kellogg&amp;amp;#39;s would hurt Kellogg&amp;amp;#39;s; however, Kashi is a subsidiary of Kellogg&amp;amp;#39;s. The same is true of RXBar, Morningstar, Bear Naked, Natural Touch, Cheez-It, Gardenburger, Eggo, Special K, Nutri-Grain, Krave, Pop-Tarts, Pringles, and Plantation brands.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK手機上的黑色熒光筆功能並不是遮擋圖像或文字的有效方法。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：如果你分享有個人信息的東西
個人信息，並認爲你把個人信息塗黑了。
你可能會不小心將這些信息透露給陌生人。我知道從
經驗告訴我，被塗黑的東西可能看起來很黑......。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcc2xf/ysk_the_black_highlighter_feature_on_phones_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcc2xf/ysk_the_black_highlighter_feature_on_phones_is/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 14:42:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: if you share something that has personal information, and think that you blacked out the personal information, you could accidentally be revealing that information to strangers. I know from experience that something &amp;amp;#39;blacked out&amp;amp;#39; can look jet black on the phone screen without that being the case on other devices; even if it does appear jet black, raising the brightness can reveal the hidden image.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，你的牙齒和牙齦與你的心臟直接相關，通過保持良好的牙齒衛生來保持它們的健康，也有助於保護你的心臟。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p><strong>爲什麼是YSK:</strong>雖然牙齒健康非常重要
往往被忽視的一個原因是，你的牙齒和牙齦與你的心臟直接相關。
牙齒和牙齦與你的心臟直接相關，而不良的牙齒衛生可以
如果不加註意，有可能導致心臟問題。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcw7ap/ysk_that_your_teeth_and_gums_are_linked_directly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcw7ap/ysk_that_your_teeth_and_gums_are_linked_directly/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 04:54:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Why YSK:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; While dental health is very important in general, one reason that often gets overlooked is that your teeth and gums are directly linked to your heart, and poor dental hygiene can potentially lead to heart problems if left unattended.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some of those can include:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Gum disease, which can increase your risk of developing heart disease.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;If you don&amp;amp;#39;t take care of your mouth, you risk developing a bacterial infection in your bloodstream. This, in turn, can potentially affect your heart (specifically heart valves -- be very careful if you&amp;amp;#39;ve had heart surgery to repair/replace them).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Poor dental care can lead to type 2 diabetes, and there&amp;amp;#39;s an apparent link between type 2 and cardiovascular disease.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s worth noting that more research is needed to determine exactly what the links are, why they occur and how prevalent they are. But studies seem to indicate that they do, at the very least, exist in some capacity, and you can never be too careful when it comes to your health (especially not with your heart).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Practice good dental hygiene by doing some or, ideally, all of the following:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Brushing your teeth twice a day for 2 minutes at a time (make sure you are brushing all the way to the back).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Flossing once a day.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Using mouthwash frequently.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;If possible, use toothpaste with or drink water that contains fluoride.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;See a dentist regularly for check-ups and cleanings.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Obviously, you can have heart issues regardless of the state of your teeth. And if you &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;do&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; have heart issues (of any kind, whether congenital or adult), it&amp;amp;#39;s still important to maintain good oral hygiene so that you don&amp;amp;#39;t potentially make those problems worse.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Regardless, it&amp;amp;#39;s still a good idea to brush your teeth twice a day. It keeps more than just your mouth happy!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sources:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/adult-health/expert-answers/heart-disease-prevention/faq-20057986&quot;&amp;gt;Mayo Clinic&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.heart.org/en/news/2018/11/07/bad-tooth-brushing-habits-tied-to-higher-heart-risk&quot;&amp;gt;American Heart Association&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/health/gum-disease-and-heart-disease&quot;&amp;gt;Healthline&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(Disclaimer: I am not a dentist or a doctor, so please let me know if I have misinterpreted any of the sources, or if they are somehow not considered legit.)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK："非品牌 "麥片與 "名牌 "麥片完全一樣，只是它們通常保留了（更好的）經典配方，而且在盲測中，幾乎每次都表現得更好。凱洛格公司解僱了1400名工人，請記住，支付更多的美元並不意味着更好。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK</p> <p>當考慮每份支付0.27美元與0.14美元時
時，你應該知道，大多數品牌與非品牌之間的差異很小（如果有的話）。
大多數品牌與非品牌之間的差異（如果有的話），而且通常情況下，差異在於
不同的是，非品牌保留了更好的產品。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcp9gv/ysk_offbrand_cereals_are_identical_to_name_brand/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcp9gv/ysk_offbrand_cereals_are_identical_to_name_brand/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 21:44:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When considering paying $0.27 per serving vs $0.14 per serving, you should know that there is very little difference (if any) between most brands and their off-brand, and often times the difference is that the &amp;amp;quot;off-brand&amp;amp;quot; retains the better tasting original recipe vs the name brand Cereals cost-cutting, recipe changing, etc;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Name Brand cereal seems better due to their superior marketing, however in almost every instance (depending on the off-brand) the non-name brand cereal beats the name brand cereal in blind taste tests.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This means that their marketing is working, however they are in reality NOT better, in almost every instance.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Note:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; I &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;know&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; there are some cereal off-brands out there which clearly do not match/beat the name brand, however for the most part, the majority of them are identical or better than the original.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And... &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;With Kellogg firing 1400 workers rather than providing better wages or working environment&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, it&amp;amp;#39;s important to remember that, for the most part, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;your extra $ is going toward their superior marketing and trickery to make their brand seem &amp;amp;quot;better&amp;amp;quot;, not a truly better product.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Spend your money in places that share your values, and in this case, on an often identical or superior product. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Paying more $, in this case does not equal a better product, and in fact only gets you a more commonly marketed name, and often a more poorly performing brand in taste tests.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Edit:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; For those looking for taste tests, there are simply too many to link here, depending on which &amp;amp;quot;off brand&amp;amp;quot; you want to see tested vs the big name cereals. Google &amp;amp;quot;off brand cereal taste test&amp;amp;quot; and you&amp;amp;#39;ll find many in-depth reviews and even videos describing the look, and the taste difference (if any) of whatever brand they&amp;amp;#39;re testing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你要減薪了]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>可能只是在僱主中不受歡迎，但是
你應該知道，通貨膨脹率約爲6%，對我們大多數人來說可能要高得多。
對我們大多數人來說，所以如果你今年沒有收到至少6%的加薪
你就會被減薪。你應該要求你的僱主...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcmrzm/ysk_you_are_getting_a_paycut/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcmrzm/ysk_you_are_getting_a_paycut/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 21:44:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Probably only unpopular among employers, but you should know that the inflation rate is around 6% and probably much higher for most of us, so if you are not receiving a raise this year for at least 6% you are getting a pay-cut.  You should ask your employer to explain to you why they think you are worth less now then you were last year.   Why ysk: Inflation generally hits lower income people a lot faster and harder than higher income earners and some owners/employers may not realize how badly it is affecting you.  Also, you have to shoot your shot.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 說外語的一半是瞭解其獨特的音調、旋律和節奏，這可以通過聽母語者的錄音和模仿 "噠噠噠 "等方式進行練習。學習詞彙只是學習外語的一半。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p><strong>爲什麼選擇YSK</strong>: 因爲旅行
因爲旅行和說一門外語，除了基本的流利，沒有濃重的
口音，是很困難的。如果一個短語使用熟悉的輕聲/重聲，講母語的人可以更容易地理解外國人。
如果一個短語使用了熟悉的輕音/旋律/節奏，就可以更容易地理解外國人，這需要...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcjbsp/ysk_half_of_speaking_a_foreign_language_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcjbsp/ysk_half_of_speaking_a_foreign_language_is/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 18:38:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Why YSK&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: Because traveling and speaking a foreign language, beyond rudimentary fluency without a thick accent, is difficult. Native speakers can understand foreigners much easier if a phrase uses the familiar lilt/melody/rhythm, which requires muscle memory of tongue placement and mouth movement.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For example, Spanish and Italian share a lot of the same vocabulary, but the words and phrases themselves are spoken in vastly different ways. Spanish is very staccato, while Italian tends to chain words together with a circular intonation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你在找工作，儘管普遍認爲求職信並不重要，而且會被忽視，但公司絕對會閱讀求職信，如果你至少沒有努力提交求職信，有些公司會放棄你的申請。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼選擇YSK：我曾幫助過好幾年的公司。
1，公司確實使用系統（ATS）來自動過濾非相關的帖子。
1，公司確實使用系統（ATS）來自動過濾掉不相關的帖子，2，當他們真的接觸到
2，當他們接觸到人時，他們尋找的最大東西之一，除了你的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rciits/ysk_if_youre_job_hunting_despite_the_widespread/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rciits/ysk_if_youre_job_hunting_despite_the_widespread/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 16:42:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: I worked for several years helping companies with their recruitment efforts and 1, companies do use systems (ATS) to automatically filter out non-relevant posts and, 2, when they do get to the human, one of the biggest things they look for, beyond your personal work and educational history, is the effort put into applications - someone that has put together a Cover Letter will always stand out over someone that doesn&amp;amp;#39;t. As someone that&amp;amp;#39;s also applied for lots of jobs, I know how shitty companies are at not getting back to candidates, but if you want to win a job, you&amp;amp;#39;ve got to go the extra mile.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，美國各地的工人對加入工會表現出越來越大的興趣，如果你想支持這股暗流，你能做的就是在一家公司表現出採取破壞工會或一般的反工會措施時，抵制該公司的產品。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：過去幾年，階級意識在美國勞動力中迅速增長。
在過去的幾年裏，階級意識在美國的勞動力中迅速增長。最好的辦法是
對這一勢頭做出貢獻的最佳方式是做一個有良心的消費者，並有選擇地購買
在一個人的購買中。許多消費者忘記了他們有這個非常...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rc7j7b/ysk_that_workers_all_over_the_us_are_showing_an/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rc7j7b/ysk_that_workers_all_over_the_us_are_showing_an/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 03:49:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Class consciousness is growing rapidly among the American workforce for the past few years. The best way to contribute to this momentum is to be a conscientious consumer and be selective in one&amp;amp;#39;s purchases. Many consumers forget that they have this very effective tool in their arsenal against bad corporate practices.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：日本沒有公平使用法。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：最近我看到了一些
的聲明，這些人在他們的視頻中不斷地被索賠，或者因爲審查日本產品而面臨日本公司的法律威脅。
的視頻，或者因爲審查日本內容（主要是動漫）而面臨日本公司的法律威脅。
內容（主要是動漫）。這是因爲即使在Youtubes指南中...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbks00/ysk_japan_does_not_have_fair_use_laws/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbks00/ysk_japan_does_not_have_fair_use_laws/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 02:49:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Recenty I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen a few statements about youtubers/influencers who are constantly being claimed on their videos or facing legal threats by Japanese companies for reviewing Japanese content (mostly anime). This is because even though in Youtubes guide lines of fair use, what they post is ok. But fair use doesn&amp;amp;#39;t exist in Japan so big companies like Toei for example would see it just as a copyright violation or stealing products that they made. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Recently Three Japanese men were convinced of violating copyright laws for making and uploading movie reviews for Japanese movies. So this is something companies are willing to sue individuals for and have them sentenced to jail.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;edit (Hopefully I haven&amp;amp;#39;t broken any rules, I&amp;amp;#39;m on mobile so hopefully I&amp;amp;#39;ve covered everything.)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你知道軟件沒有問題，在把筆記本帶到維修店時，不要把硬盤或固態硬盤留在裏面。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：這些公司可能會進行備份和
也許沒有正確地存儲它們。數據是有價值的，你不希望它到處都是。
到處都是。不要把你的數據放在沒有保護的地方！</p> <p>移除你的
硬盤或固態硬盤對大多數筆記本電腦來說並不難，它將...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbry7i/ysk_dont_leave_your_hard_drive_or_ssd_in_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbry7i/ysk_dont_leave_your_hard_drive_or_ssd_in_your/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 22:50:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: These companies may make backups and maybe not store them properly. Data is valuable and you don&amp;amp;#39;t want it to be everywhere. Don&amp;amp;#39;t keep your data somewhere unprotected!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Removing your hard drive or SSD is not hard for most laptops, it will only take a few minutes once you know how to do it and in most cases, it won&amp;amp;#39;t hurt your laptop.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s not always neccesary. Here&amp;amp;#39;s when you should and when you should:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You should when:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You&amp;amp;#39;re bringing it to a local shop that just does repairs(small businesses with just a few people working there)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;There&amp;amp;#39;s something physically broken, like the screen, the keyboard or the charging hole.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You got sensitive data on your laptop(passwords, private media etc)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t when:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You&amp;amp;#39;re sending your laptop back for warranty&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;There&amp;amp;#39;s warranty stickers on screws, and you still have warranty on your laptop(in that case, just send it back)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You don&amp;amp;#39;t have the proper tools to do it&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 在晚上使用止汗劑]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼選擇YSK：作爲一個曾經超級愛出汗的青少年，瞭解到這一點改變了遊戲規則。
患有多汗症的青少年，瞭解到這是一個改變遊戲規則的方法。止汗劑必須要
如果你在洗完澡後直接塗抹止汗劑，而且還是在溼潤的情況下，那麼你的皮膚必須吸收止汗劑才能發揮作用。
如果你在淋浴後直接塗抹，而且還是溼的；或者在早上出汗後塗抹，它就不會起作用......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbvhey/ysk_apply_antiperspirant_at_night/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbvhey/ysk_apply_antiperspirant_at_night/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:51:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: As a formerly super sweaty teenager with hyperhidrosis learning this was a game changer. Anti-perspirant has to absorb into your skin to work and if you apply it directly after a shower while still wet; or in the morning and sweat it out it will not work (and just stain your tees!)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Applying at night, to clean DRY armpits is key. Even if you start getting sweaty before sleep, once you sleep you usually will sweat less which will allow enough time for the active ingredient to absorb. Once built up this will last days at a time and you can often get form to applying only once a week at night.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This was inspired by the EMSKR and how to apply anti perspirant was way too low on list.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: I should probably mention that antiperspirant shouldn’t be used to prevent normal sweating. It’s a natural part of the body that helps you keep cool. If you are however excessively sweaty, first consider seeing your doctor or dermatologist. If you choose to include an anti perspirant in your routine, it’s most effective when used at  night. You also probably don’t need to use it as often as you think. Usually only every other night or a couple nights a week. Continue to apply normal deodorant in mornings as usual.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>