<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 00:18:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：蘋果公司剛剛發佈了一項更新，允許用戶在其死亡後指定一個遺留的聯繫人。這將允許上述聯繫人在他們死後訪問其手機/設備上的信息和照片。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：多年來一直存在的問題是
多年來，擁有iOS設備的父母或親人去世後，他們的親人
由於手機上的安全措施，他們的親人在死後無法訪問他們的手機數據。
手機的安全措施。這導致了許多記憶的丟失，因爲蘋果公司...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfpr2r/ysk_apple_just_released_an_update_that_allows/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfpr2r/ysk_apple_just_released_an_update_that_allows/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 23:40:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: There has been issues for many years with parents or loved ones who have iOS devices and pass away that their loved ones cannot access their phone data after death due to the security measures on the phone. This has caused many memories to be lost as Apple won’t unlock a phone for anyone but the user. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You need to update to iOS 15.2, released today. It is on any phone above iOS 6s. When you do, go to Settings, then tap your name at the top, then tap Password and Security, the you will see Legacy Contact. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you set this up on a parents device, you can help them assign a contact to access the device after their passing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 移除食譜網站上的所有雜物（廣告、生活故事、彈出窗口），只提取使用OnlyRecipe的食譜。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼選擇YSK：爲了在博客/網站上找到食譜而略過文字牆可能會讓人感到沮喪。
爲了在博客/網站上找到食譜而瀏覽文字牆，會讓人感到沮喪。作者這樣做是爲了獲得
</p> <p>你可以使用<a
href="https://onlyrecipe.app/">OnlyRecipe.app</a>來提取菜譜信息。
信息。它可以在...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfkori/ysk_remove_all_the_clutter_ads_life_story_popups/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfkori/ysk_remove_all_the_clutter_ads_life_story_popups/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 23:40:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: It can get frustrating skimming through text walls just to find the recipe on blogs/sites. Authors do it to get high ranking on Google.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You can use &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://onlyrecipe.app/&quot;&amp;gt;OnlyRecipe.app&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; to extract the recipe information. It works on almost all sites/blogs which follow a recipe standard when they post.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The end result will look like this. for example.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.pinimg.com/previews/E1LeuLp5.png&quot;&amp;gt;Meditarannean Tuna Pasta&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.pinimg.com/previews/4Za6mqQo.png&quot;&amp;gt;Slow cooked Italian Chicken and Peppers&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You can also save it to your phone directly using the app. Scan recipe QR code using your phone camera and voila.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Short vid on how recipe camera scanner works :&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ziSNwjv9PXo&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ziSNwjv9PXo&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：更努力的工作並不總是意味着更好的結果。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：在這個世界上有一種態度
認爲努力工作自動意味着你會有一個更好的結果。這並不是
</p> <p>僅僅因爲你在肝臟和洋蔥上花了一個半小時，並不意味着你做出了什麼。
並不意味着你做的東西比普通的烤奶酪更美味....。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfm7du/ysk_harder_work_doesnt_always_mean_a_better_result/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfm7du/ysk_harder_work_doesnt_always_mean_a_better_result/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 21:43:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: There’s an attitude in this world that working hard automatically means you’ll have a better outcome. It’s not true.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just because you spent an hour and half on liver and onions doesn’t mean you made something tastier than a regular grilled cheese. Just because you wrote a song mixing time signatures and changing keys doesn’t mean it sounds better than some rudimentary Green Day tune. Just because you spent 8 years on a degree, doesn’t mean you developed a skill worth more than  $12/hr. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some valuable things in this world take hard work, but not everything that takes hard work is valuable. Before you work hard on something, ask if it’s the best use of your effort.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：當有人告訴你他們的問題時，永遠不要說 "至少"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：說 "至少 "意味着向對方暗示他們的驕傲。
另一個人，他們的問題並沒有那麼糟糕。實際上，他們的問題對他們來說是
對他們來說是糟糕的，這纔是最重要的。</p> <p>這也是對他們的否定，並沒有
讓他們講完它。"至少 "讓他們閉嘴....]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfmlcu/ysk_never_say_at_least_when_someone_is_telling/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfmlcu/ysk_never_say_at_least_when_someone_is_telling/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 21:43:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Saying “at least” implies to the other person that their problem isn’t that bad. In actuality, their problem is bad to them and that’s what matters. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It also dismisses them and does not let them finish speaking about it. “At least” shuts them down. They should not have to defend why their problem is a problem to you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Finally, just because they do not have it the worst or it could be worse, does not mean that they are not experiencing the pain from their own problem. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The example I’ve seen countless times is simple. If someone is telling you about a miscarriage and the emotional/physical pain they are experiencing and you reply, “at least you can have (or already have) children,” you are completely shutting them out.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: here’s a source &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=1Evwgu369Jw&quot;&amp;gt;https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=1Evwgu369Jw&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，對強姦受害者來說，性慾過強是很常見的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：通常情況下，媒體圍繞着一個強姦犯的敘述。
圍繞着強姦受害者的敘述，認爲他們由於創傷性經歷而完全排斥性/性行爲。
在這種情況下，與之相反的另一種情況有時會被人看不起，因爲他們的創傷經歷。
雖然有這種情況發生，但光譜的另一端有時會被看不起，並被徹底地...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfcs7a/ysk_that_being_hypersexual_is_common_for_rape/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfcs7a/ysk_that_being_hypersexual_is_common_for_rape/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 14:41:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Often times the media surrounds the narrative of a rape victim as someone who outright repels sex/sexuality as a result of their traumatic experience, and while that happens, the opposite end of the spectrum is sometimes looked down upon and outright ignored even though it’s highly common amongst rape victims.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Like any traumatic experience, rape has long and lasting impacts to the victim. And due to the unfortunate controversial nature of rape/ rape-culture in itself, stuff like the psychological repercussions of it are often not spoken about enough and swept under the rug.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“Rape trauma syndrome” (RTS) is the name attributed to the disruptions to normal, physical, emotional, and interpersonal behavior as a result of an assault. There are different stages assigned to the time after the assault. Symptoms can range from a complete minimization of the abuse (blaming oneself, watering it down), to dramatization (cannot stop speaking about it). Needless to say the emotional/physical effects of a rape range greatly. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sexual relationships of a rape survivor often become disturbed and they too, range greatly. Some victims shield from contact and develop a fear of intimacy, while others become hyper sexual or “promiscuous” as a subconscious means to reassert a measure of control over their sexual relationships. While this is a documented and common experience, it’s often overshadowed by the depiction of a sex-repulsed survivor. Sometimes due to the shame of it and purity culture in general.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：即使是緩慢流動的水也會帶來難以置信的風險。試圖穿越快速流動的溪流或洪水就是自殺。1米長的水立方是一噸的定義。想象一下，水是1噸的立方體，以這種速度移動，你就會知道汽車是如何被沖走的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：</p> <p>許多人大大地低估了
很多人都低估了小水體所能帶來的力量。
<p>有一個愚蠢的小經驗法則，實際上很有幫助。
如果你把一朵花掉在水裏，你是否有時間彎腰去摘？
它......。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rf59fx/ysk_even_slowmoving_water_presents_incredible/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rf59fx/ysk_even_slowmoving_water_presents_incredible/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 05:40:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Many people vastly underestimate the forces even small bodies of water can impart.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There&amp;amp;#39;s a silly little rule of thumb that&amp;amp;#39;s actually pretty helpful. If you dropped a flower in the water, would you have time to bend down and pick it up, or is flowing away out of reach by the time you did?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you can pick it up, you&amp;amp;#39;re fine.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If not, basically, if the water goes over your ankles you can be taken off your feet at any moment, mind the rocks, but are okayish.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If it goes over your knees, you&amp;amp;#39;re at serious risk of being taken by the stream.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you&amp;amp;#39;re trying to move something with a large surface area, like the wheels of a car, or god help you its deep enough to be pushing on the whole sides of the car, you&amp;amp;#39;re fucked.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Moving bodies of water contain incredible energies, water is really, really dense. I mean just think about picking up a big bucket of the stuff.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I see a lot of people drive cars over roads that have flooded and are in motion, and every time I wish I could scream at them before they go in.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Water is so dense, that whole ass car only weighs as much as 1-2 cubic meters of water. Its surface area can have a LOT more than that pushing on it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Your car absolutely will not win.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 松露油並不含有任何松露，而是使用一種化學物質來拙劣地模仿松露的香氣。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK: 很久以前，松露油是
只是注入了松露的油。<a
href="https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Truffle_oil">現在，它是注入了
2,4-dithiapentane,</a>一種碳氫化合物，其味道可以最好地描述爲
可以被描述爲對...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rf47q6/ysk_truffle_oil_does_not_contain_any_truffles_but/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rf47q6/ysk_truffle_oil_does_not_contain_any_truffles_but/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 04:45:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Once upon a time, truffle oil was just oil infused with truffles. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Truffle_oil&quot;&amp;gt;These days, it is oil infused with 2,4-dithiapentane,&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; a hydrocarbon with a flavor that can best be described as a parody of truffle.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I actually kind of liked truffle oil, until I ate the real deal, which is so much more subtle, deep and pleasant in flavor. It’s also far more expensive, sure—Italian white truffles can be over $200 per oz. But cheaper varieties, like Burgundy black truffles, are about a tenth of that: an expense well worth it in my opinion.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What irks me most is that restaurants will have dishes on their menu described as having truffles—truffle risotto, truffle fries, etc, but are really using truffle oil instead of the real thing. Not only do they use this as an excuse to upcharge the dish by ten dollars because of the “luxury” status, they also overwhelm the food with a pungent chemical inferior to the advertised product.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But don’t take my word for it:
&amp;amp;quot;One of the most pungent, ridiculous ingredients ever known to chef,&amp;amp;quot; Gordon Ramsay once told a competitor on MasterChef.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Reaching for the oil is &amp;amp;quot;a sure sign of someone who doesn&amp;amp;#39;t know what they&amp;amp;#39;re doing,&amp;amp;quot; Joe Bastianich said in the same episode.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;Fake truffle flavoring is one of those things that&amp;amp;#39;s especially upsetting, because not only does it taste like a bad chemical version of the real thing, it&amp;amp;#39;s the flavor that almost everyone now associates with truffles,&amp;amp;quot; Jonathan Gold says.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, if you enjoy truffle oil, power to you. But be aware that it is not truffles that you are tasting and paying big money for. And if you ever get a chance, try some real truffles: they rule.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK月桂葉可以使象鼻蟲和其他害蟲遠離。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK是如果你曾經處理過一個
蟲害，月桂葉能很好地阻止各種害蟲的侵襲。你只需
你只需在你的麪粉和大米中放一兩片月桂葉，就能讓它們遠離
遠離。你也可以將月桂葉散落在櫥櫃周圍，以保持它們...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rf1cph/ysk_bay_leaves_can_keep_weevils_away_along_with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rf1cph/ysk_bay_leaves_can_keep_weevils_away_along_with/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 03:40:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK is if you ever deal with an infestation, bay leaves are great at deterring all kinds of pests. All you have to do is put a bay leaf or two in your flour and rice and it will keep them away. You can also scatter the bay leaves around the cupboard to keep them out. This is an old trick my grandma taught me that I have been using since I was a kid.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: bay leaves lose their potency after awhile so you will have to change the leaves out every so often!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：真的很容易在不知不覺中把客服人員困在他們不想進行的對話中。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：從事客戶服務的人
幾乎不可避免地會與一些客戶進行閒談。
</p> <p>當這種情況發生時。
工人幾乎沒有辦法禮貌地拒絕......。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rebbc6/ysk_its_really_easy_to_unknowingly_trap_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rebbc6/ysk_its_really_easy_to_unknowingly_trap_a/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 19:41:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Someone who works in customer service will almost inevitably have casual conversations with some of the customers, especially if they see the same customers regularly.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When that happens, the worker has almost no way of politely declining the conversation if they don&amp;amp;#39;t feel like talking. For one, it could be considered rude, and the worker probably has to take special care to not hurt customers&amp;amp;#39; feelings.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Second, the worker can&amp;amp;#39;t just say &amp;amp;quot;Hey, I&amp;amp;#39;ve got to go&amp;amp;quot; and walk away. They have to stay, sometimes at the exact spot where you&amp;amp;#39;re having the conversation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The only thing that they can really do is maybe say &amp;amp;quot;Hey, I&amp;amp;#39;ve got a lot of work to do, can we talk later?&amp;amp;quot;, but some people wouldn&amp;amp;#39;t want to lie if they &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;don&amp;amp;#39;t&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; actually have work to do, and it can be awkward even if it&amp;amp;#39;s true.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I work at a hotel and this happens all the time. It&amp;amp;#39;s basically in my job description to be engaged with guests at all times, during conversations both casual and otherwise, which makes them think that I like these talks way more than I actually do.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Even when I try to give hints that I&amp;amp;#39;m not into it by not saying much, shifting my eye contact to my desk, or typing on my computer, they rarely get the hint. It&amp;amp;#39;s a terrible feeling to be all but forced to have a conversation when you really would rather not.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please don&amp;amp;#39;t keep people in long conversations unless you&amp;amp;#39;re &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;sure&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; they&amp;amp;#39;re into it, especially if the other party is at their job.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK i.e.和e.g.是兩個不同的東西]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>i.e.意思是它是其中之一，e.g.意思是
這些都是例子。例如，如果有人說&quot;選擇你最喜歡的
顏色（即藍色或紅色）&quot;他們是說在藍色和紅色之間選擇。如果
有人說&quot;選擇你最喜歡的顏色（如藍色或......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rekljb/ysk_the_ie_and_eg_are_two_separate_things/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rekljb/ysk_the_ie_and_eg_are_two_separate_things/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 13:39:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;i.e. mean it is one of these and e.g. means these are examples. For example, if someone said &amp;amp;quot;Choose your favorite color (i.e. blue or red)&amp;amp;quot; they are saying choose between blue and red. If someone said &amp;amp;quot;Choose your favorite color (e.g. blue or red)&amp;amp;quot; they are saying choose any color, but blue and red are just examples.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: I constantly see people use i.e. where e.g. should be used and e.g. where i.e. should be used and you will need to know this if you are doing something like giving someone instructions because if you say i.e. instead of e.g. then the person will think their options are limited.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To those who call BS: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.merriam-webster.com/words-at-play/ie-vs-eg-abbreviation-meaning-usage-difference&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.merriam-webster.com/words-at-play/ie-vs-eg-abbreviation-meaning-usage-difference&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：當一個零售業工作人員問你是否需要一個尺寸，讓他們幫你拿，他們實際上是要求你不要弄得一團糟，但卻很有禮貌。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：特別是在現在的假日季節
零售店變得非常繁忙，零售工人沒有時間
時間來打掃一整天的衛生。事實上，除了爲你打掃衛生，他們還有很多其他任務要做。
除了打掃衛生之外，他們還有很多其他任務要做，雖然他們正在...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/reja4r/ysk_when_a_retail_worker_asks_if_you_need_a_size/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/reja4r/ysk_when_a_retail_worker_asks_if_you_need_a_size/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 10:39:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Especially in the holiday season now with retail stores getting extremely busy, retail workers just don’t have the time to spend cleaning up all day. They do in fact have a lot of other tasks to do besides clean up after you, and although they are getting paid to keep the store tidy, their job description doesn’t include being your maid. A little mess is fine, but don’t be that person that all the employees will bitch about when you leave. Making all that mess is unnecessary and you’re making their life much harder when it is &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;SO&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; easy to not.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So if a worker asks if you need help with a size, let them get it. They’ll make no mess while getting it, you get the size you want, and then they have more time for the important tasks because they no longer have to clean up your mess. Everyone wins.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT FOR CONTEXT: Majority of this relates to clothing stores, but works for all goods stores. In general though if you’re making a mess looking for something and an employee comes and asks to help you, don’t say no because you can look for it, say yes because they can look for it without making a mess and it makes their life easier.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT AGAIN: Even if you live somewhere where being approached by staff to help is uncommon (which is crazy weird to me), the point is just don’t make a mess. Regardless of which country you’re in, the workers have better shit to do than clean up after people who somehow don’t know how to look through a neatly stacked pile of clothes without making it look like a bomb went off.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 如果有人不想慶祝他們的生日，你就不能強迫他們慶祝，用一些令人尷尬的驚喜來打斷他們的生活，並騷擾他們，直到他們最終讓步。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：你可能會說，你只是想讓他們知道你關心他們。
讓他們知道你關心他們。但你給對方的信息是
你並不關心他們的感受，因爲你所做的正是他們要求你不要做的事。
他們要求你不要做的事。他們最終會怨恨你，並討厭...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rebk9r/ysk_if_someone_doesnt_want_to_celebrate_their/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rebk9r/ysk_if_someone_doesnt_want_to_celebrate_their/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 01:47:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: You may say that you just want them to know you care about them.  But the message you’re sending the person is that you don’t care about their feelings, because you’re doing exactly what they asked you not to do.  They will end up resenting you, and hate celebrating it even more&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：隨着假期的到來，這是你一年一度的提醒。如果有人拒絕喝酒，不要推脫。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：假期是一個非常艱難的時期
對於正在恢復的酗酒者或因不同原因戒酒的人來說，是一個非常艱難的時期。如果有人
如果有人拒絕喝酒，不要大吵大鬧，也不要試圖說服他們喝酒。
</p> <p>玩得開心，不要殺死你的家人，並保持...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/re5ubk/ysk_this_is_your_yearly_reminder_with_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/re5ubk/ysk_this_is_your_yearly_reminder_with_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 20:45:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: the holidays are a really tough time for recovering alcoholics or people who quit for different reasons. If someone declines alcohol, don&amp;amp;#39;t make a scene or try to convince them to drink anyways.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Have fun, don&amp;amp;#39;t kill your family and stay safe&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK在每年的這個時候爲任何快遞或郵件服務留下水瓶/零食，對某人來說意味着很多。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK，每年的這個時候，甚至更多的是
今年更是如此（據我所知，至少在美國），郵件和包裹
服務是完全不堪重負的。這意味着你的郵遞員和包裹
包括像亞馬遜這樣的公司在內的快遞員甚至都...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rdwhij/ysk_leaving_water_bottlessnacks_for_any_delivery/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rdwhij/ysk_leaving_water_bottlessnacks_for_any_delivery/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 15:49:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK, this time of year and even more so this year (at least in the United States as far as I know), the mail and package services are completely overwhelmed. This means your mail carrier and package delivery people including companies like Amazon even are working long hours and are on a strict timeline, and may even get extra work thrown on them if they complete their work quick enough and not really be given notice/time to prepare. Plus they can&amp;amp;#39;t exactly carry and bunch of food/drinks (especially in cities) to last all day. Doing small things like leaving a bottle of water in the mailbox (marked for them, otherwise they may not take it due to a fear of theft claims) or a cooler even clearly marked &amp;amp;quot;help yourself delivery people&amp;amp;quot; can make a huge difference in their day. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My mom worked mail delivery for years and she always would point out the houses with glee as we drive through our small town that she remembered would have a bottle of water or snack waiting for her even when she was just a sub, as in didn&amp;amp;#39;t even have a set route every workday. When she got a set route some customers would even go as far as leaving her home made cookies and gift cards for coffee or lunch occasionally.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TLDR; Appreciate the people who even though are just doing their job, still keep doing it even when it&amp;amp;#39;s not even what they signed up for. You may just be another house if you don&amp;amp;#39;t, but you will probably be a highlight of a strangers day if you do and in today&amp;amp;#39;s world we need more of that!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit; if you are someone delivering please say what country/area of the country/service and what would help you whatever time of the year and any rules you have to follow to accept anything. About to go to sleep, but when I wake up sometime tomorrow I will edit again and add a list as best I can for anyone trying to set up care packages! Obviously water and snacks, but based off a comment I realized I&amp;amp;#39;ve got a bunch of cheap shake to activate hand warmers that could really be nice for someone out all day. I also know some companies have policies where &amp;amp;quot;helping themselves&amp;amp;quot; could be reported in today&amp;amp;#39;s day and age so we could avoid it being a worry I&amp;amp;#39;d like to know how! :) Have a good night/day everyone!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 有一個網站可以免費提供udemy,Coursera,edx等網站的付費課程，並可以合法使用優惠券。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：大多數人都沒有意識到
教育網站提供100%的促銷優惠券，這實際上使
</p> <p>這裏是</p> <p>教育網站提供100%折扣的促銷券，這實際上使這些課程可以免費註冊，並且終身有效。
href="https://coursetime.net/">網站</a>，該網站記錄了這些信息。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rdt0d3/ysk_there_is_an_website_that_offers_paid_courses/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rdt0d3/ysk_there_is_an_website_that_offers_paid_courses/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 10:42:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Most people are unaware that educational sites provide 100% off coupons for promotion which literally make those courses FREE to enroll with lifetime validity.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here is the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://coursetime.net/&quot;&amp;gt;Website&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; that keep a track of those coupons and is updated regularly , which means we can grab courses for FREE.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你的轉向燈快速閃爍，那麼前面或後面的燈泡就燒壞了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：製造商設置了他們的閃光器
繼電器在阻力較小時快速閃爍，例如當燈泡燒燬時
熄滅。許多人認爲這是一個短路或電氣問題，但實際上
</p> </div><!-- SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rddev0/ysk_if_your_turn_signals_blink_quickly_either_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rddev0/ysk_if_your_turn_signals_blink_quickly_either_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 03:39:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Manufacturers set their flasher relays to blink quickly when there is less resistance, such as when a bulb burns out. Many people think there is a short or an electrical issue, when in reality it is simply a burned out bulb.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 抑鬱症與悲傷是不同的]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：人們常常會說&quot;他們有什麼好的？
他們有什麼好鬱悶的？他們有一份好的工作/家庭/家等等。</p>
<p>抑鬱症可能是由導致悲傷的重大事件帶來的，比如悲傷
或創傷。但它也可以在沒有任何明顯的外部因素的情況下存在。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rdky5m/ysk_depression_is_different_from_sadness/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rdky5m/ysk_depression_is_different_from_sadness/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 02:46:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: people will often say &amp;amp;quot;what do they have to be depressed about? They have a good job/family/home/etc. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Depression can be brought on by major events that cause sadness, like grief or trauma. But it can also exist without any obvious external cause. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sadness is like a stubbed toe: it sucks and is temporary in most cases. Depression is like a broken bone: if not properly cared for, it can heal poorly and be debilitating for life. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you&amp;amp;#39;re depressed, stop blaming yourself for not having a &amp;amp;quot;reason&amp;amp;quot; and get the help you need to heal as best you can. If you find yourself thinking this about other people, try and step back to remember that depression is not a choice&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/health/depression/depression-vs-sadness&quot;&amp;gt;How to spot the difference &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m getting some push back on the &amp;amp;quot;chemical imbalance&amp;amp;quot; phrase so I did a quick fact check on myself. It&amp;amp;#39;s an outdated theory. Much research is needed but current thinking is there are many things that cause depression and not all of them are situational, which is my core point. For the scientific report, check the NIH link below or find peer reviewed journals and reliable sources for the most relevant information. 
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3181668/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3181668/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK你當地的圖書館很可能提供附近博物館的大幅折扣門票]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：我&#39;舉個例子。住在
我住在離波士頓不到一小時的地方，我的當地圖書館給所有城市的博物館提供折扣。
城市的博物館。我想帶我的女朋友約會去美術博物館。
美術館，通常每張票是25美元。但通過圖書館，你可以...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rdeqgu/ysk_your_local_library_likely_offers_heavily/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rdeqgu/ysk_your_local_library_likely_offers_heavily/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 22:38:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: I&amp;amp;#39;ll give an example. Living within an hour from Boston my local library gives discounts to all the city&amp;amp;#39;s museums. I wanted to take my girlfriend on a date to the Museum of Fine Arts which is normally $25 per ticket. But through the library you can get them for $10 per ticket. Turning the date from a $50 expense to a $20 expense.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It can make an awesome date/trip with friends much cheaper!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：當Manifestv3實施時，Chrome中的uBlock和其他廣告屏蔽將在一個月內失去大部分功能。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：你的隱私、數據使用和
瀏覽體驗將受到影響。如果你還沒有，請投資於一個
pihole or switch to a non-chromium browser</p> </div><!-- SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rdaz50/ysk_ublock_and_other_adblocks_in_chrome_will_lose/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rdaz50/ysk_ublock_and_other_adblocks_in_chrome_will_lose/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 21:40:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Your privacy, data usage, and browsing experience will be affected. If you haven&amp;amp;#39;t already, invest in a pihole or switch to a non-chromium browser&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK你可以將所有沒有塑料或金屬內襯的食物弄髒的紙和紙板產品堆肥。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：有機材料最終會出現在
埋葬的有機材料可以被回收到自然系統中。
使其生產和使用更具有可持續性。這包括紙巾、衛生紙
這包括紙巾、衛生紙、紙巾、比薩餅盒和其他外賣容器；以及其他一些可回收的材料。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rb853o/ysk_you_can_compost_all_food_soiled_paper_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rb853o/ysk_you_can_compost_all_food_soiled_paper_and/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 19:45:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: organic materials that end up in the landfill can be recycled back into the natural systems from whence that came, making the production and use more sustainable. This includes tissue, toilet paper, paper towels, pizza boxes, and other to go containers; as long as there is no metal or plastic in them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你可能認爲是凱洛格的替代品的品牌可能屬於凱洛格公司的YSK]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：Kellogg&#39;s擁有幾個
子公司和品牌。例如，你可能認爲購買Kashi穀物
而不是Kellogg&#39;s會傷害Kellogg&#39;s；但是，Kashi是Kellogg&#39;s的一個子公司。
然而，Kashi是Kellogg&#39;s的子公司。RXBar、Morningstar、Bear......的情況也是如此。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rd9rfs/ysk_that_brands_you_may_consider_as_alternatives/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rd9rfs/ysk_that_brands_you_may_consider_as_alternatives/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 15:48:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Kellogg&amp;amp;#39;s owns several subsidiaries and brands. For instance, you may think buying Kashi cereals instead of Kellogg&amp;amp;#39;s would hurt Kellogg&amp;amp;#39;s; however, Kashi is a subsidiary of Kellogg&amp;amp;#39;s. The same is true of RXBar, Morningstar, Bear Naked, Natural Touch, Cheez-It, Gardenburger, Eggo, Special K, Nutri-Grain, Krave, Pop-Tarts, Pringles, and Plantation brands.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK手機上的黑色熒光筆功能並不是遮擋圖像或文字的有效方法。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：如果你分享有個人信息的東西
個人信息，並認爲你把個人信息塗黑了。
你可能會不小心將這些信息透露給陌生人。我知道從
經驗告訴我，被塗黑的東西可能看起來很黑......。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcc2xf/ysk_the_black_highlighter_feature_on_phones_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcc2xf/ysk_the_black_highlighter_feature_on_phones_is/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 14:42:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: if you share something that has personal information, and think that you blacked out the personal information, you could accidentally be revealing that information to strangers. I know from experience that something &amp;amp;#39;blacked out&amp;amp;#39; can look jet black on the phone screen without that being the case on other devices; even if it does appear jet black, raising the brightness can reveal the hidden image.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，你的牙齒和牙齦與你的心臟直接相關，通過保持良好的牙齒衛生來保持它們的健康，也有助於保護你的心臟。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p><strong>爲什麼是YSK:</strong>雖然牙齒健康非常重要
往往被忽視的一個原因是，你的牙齒和牙齦與你的心臟直接相關。
牙齒和牙齦與你的心臟直接相關，而不良的牙齒衛生可以
如果不加註意，有可能導致心臟問題。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcw7ap/ysk_that_your_teeth_and_gums_are_linked_directly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcw7ap/ysk_that_your_teeth_and_gums_are_linked_directly/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 04:54:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Why YSK:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; While dental health is very important in general, one reason that often gets overlooked is that your teeth and gums are directly linked to your heart, and poor dental hygiene can potentially lead to heart problems if left unattended.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some of those can include:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Gum disease, which can increase your risk of developing heart disease.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;If you don&amp;amp;#39;t take care of your mouth, you risk developing a bacterial infection in your bloodstream. This, in turn, can potentially affect your heart (specifically heart valves -- be very careful if you&amp;amp;#39;ve had heart surgery to repair/replace them).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Poor dental care can lead to type 2 diabetes, and there&amp;amp;#39;s an apparent link between type 2 and cardiovascular disease.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s worth noting that more research is needed to determine exactly what the links are, why they occur and how prevalent they are. But studies seem to indicate that they do, at the very least, exist in some capacity, and you can never be too careful when it comes to your health (especially not with your heart).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Practice good dental hygiene by doing some or, ideally, all of the following:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Brushing your teeth twice a day for 2 minutes at a time (make sure you are brushing all the way to the back).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Flossing once a day.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Using mouthwash frequently.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;If possible, use toothpaste with or drink water that contains fluoride.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;See a dentist regularly for check-ups and cleanings.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Obviously, you can have heart issues regardless of the state of your teeth. And if you &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;do&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; have heart issues (of any kind, whether congenital or adult), it&amp;amp;#39;s still important to maintain good oral hygiene so that you don&amp;amp;#39;t potentially make those problems worse.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Regardless, it&amp;amp;#39;s still a good idea to brush your teeth twice a day. It keeps more than just your mouth happy!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sources:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/adult-health/expert-answers/heart-disease-prevention/faq-20057986&quot;&amp;gt;Mayo Clinic&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.heart.org/en/news/2018/11/07/bad-tooth-brushing-habits-tied-to-higher-heart-risk&quot;&amp;gt;American Heart Association&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/health/gum-disease-and-heart-disease&quot;&amp;gt;Healthline&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(Disclaimer: I am not a dentist or a doctor, so please let me know if I have misinterpreted any of the sources, or if they are somehow not considered legit.)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK："非品牌 "麥片與 "名牌 "麥片完全一樣，只是它們通常保留了（更好的）經典配方，而且在盲測中，幾乎每次都表現得更好。凱洛格公司解僱了1400名工人，請記住，支付更多的美元並不意味着更好。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK</p> <p>當考慮每份支付0.27美元與0.14美元時
時，你應該知道，大多數品牌與非品牌之間的差異很小（如果有的話）。
大多數品牌與非品牌之間的差異（如果有的話），而且通常情況下，差異在於
不同的是，非品牌保留了更好的產品。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcp9gv/ysk_offbrand_cereals_are_identical_to_name_brand/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcp9gv/ysk_offbrand_cereals_are_identical_to_name_brand/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 21:44:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When considering paying $0.27 per serving vs $0.14 per serving, you should know that there is very little difference (if any) between most brands and their off-brand, and often times the difference is that the &amp;amp;quot;off-brand&amp;amp;quot; retains the better tasting original recipe vs the name brand Cereals cost-cutting, recipe changing, etc;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Name Brand cereal seems better due to their superior marketing, however in almost every instance (depending on the off-brand) the non-name brand cereal beats the name brand cereal in blind taste tests.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This means that their marketing is working, however they are in reality NOT better, in almost every instance.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Note:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; I &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;know&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; there are some cereal off-brands out there which clearly do not match/beat the name brand, however for the most part, the majority of them are identical or better than the original.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And... &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;With Kellogg firing 1400 workers rather than providing better wages or working environment&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, it&amp;amp;#39;s important to remember that, for the most part, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;your extra $ is going toward their superior marketing and trickery to make their brand seem &amp;amp;quot;better&amp;amp;quot;, not a truly better product.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Spend your money in places that share your values, and in this case, on an often identical or superior product. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Paying more $, in this case does not equal a better product, and in fact only gets you a more commonly marketed name, and often a more poorly performing brand in taste tests.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Edit:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; For those looking for taste tests, there are simply too many to link here, depending on which &amp;amp;quot;off brand&amp;amp;quot; you want to see tested vs the big name cereals. Google &amp;amp;quot;off brand cereal taste test&amp;amp;quot; and you&amp;amp;#39;ll find many in-depth reviews and even videos describing the look, and the taste difference (if any) of whatever brand they&amp;amp;#39;re testing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你要減薪了]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>可能只是在僱主中不受歡迎，但是
你應該知道，通貨膨脹率約爲6%，對我們大多數人來說可能要高得多。
對我們大多數人來說，所以如果你今年沒有收到至少6%的加薪
你就會被減薪。你應該要求你的僱主...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcmrzm/ysk_you_are_getting_a_paycut/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcmrzm/ysk_you_are_getting_a_paycut/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 21:44:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Probably only unpopular among employers, but you should know that the inflation rate is around 6% and probably much higher for most of us, so if you are not receiving a raise this year for at least 6% you are getting a pay-cut.  You should ask your employer to explain to you why they think you are worth less now then you were last year.   Why ysk: Inflation generally hits lower income people a lot faster and harder than higher income earners and some owners/employers may not realize how badly it is affecting you.  Also, you have to shoot your shot.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 說外語的一半是瞭解其獨特的音調、旋律和節奏，這可以通過聽母語者的錄音和模仿 "噠噠噠 "等方式進行練習。學習詞彙只是學習外語的一半。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p><strong>爲什麼選擇YSK</strong>: 因爲旅行
因爲旅行和說一門外語，除了基本的流利，沒有濃重的
口音，是很困難的。如果一個短語使用熟悉的輕聲/重聲，講母語的人可以更容易地理解外國人。
如果一個短語使用了熟悉的輕音/旋律/節奏，就可以更容易地理解外國人，這需要...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcjbsp/ysk_half_of_speaking_a_foreign_language_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rcjbsp/ysk_half_of_speaking_a_foreign_language_is/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 18:38:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Why YSK&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: Because traveling and speaking a foreign language, beyond rudimentary fluency without a thick accent, is difficult. Native speakers can understand foreigners much easier if a phrase uses the familiar lilt/melody/rhythm, which requires muscle memory of tongue placement and mouth movement.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For example, Spanish and Italian share a lot of the same vocabulary, but the words and phrases themselves are spoken in vastly different ways. Spanish is very staccato, while Italian tends to chain words together with a circular intonation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你在找工作，儘管普遍認爲求職信並不重要，而且會被忽視，但公司絕對會閱讀求職信，如果你至少沒有努力提交求職信，有些公司會放棄你的申請。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼選擇YSK：我曾幫助過好幾年的公司。
1，公司確實使用系統（ATS）來自動過濾非相關的帖子。
1，公司確實使用系統（ATS）來自動過濾掉不相關的帖子，2，當他們真的接觸到
2，當他們接觸到人時，他們尋找的最大東西之一，除了你的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rciits/ysk_if_youre_job_hunting_despite_the_widespread/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rciits/ysk_if_youre_job_hunting_despite_the_widespread/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 16:42:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: I worked for several years helping companies with their recruitment efforts and 1, companies do use systems (ATS) to automatically filter out non-relevant posts and, 2, when they do get to the human, one of the biggest things they look for, beyond your personal work and educational history, is the effort put into applications - someone that has put together a Cover Letter will always stand out over someone that doesn&amp;amp;#39;t. As someone that&amp;amp;#39;s also applied for lots of jobs, I know how shitty companies are at not getting back to candidates, but if you want to win a job, you&amp;amp;#39;ve got to go the extra mile.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，美國各地的工人對加入工會表現出越來越大的興趣，如果你想支持這股暗流，你能做的就是在一家公司表現出採取破壞工會或一般的反工會措施時，抵制該公司的產品。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：過去幾年，階級意識在美國勞動力中迅速增長。
在過去的幾年裏，階級意識在美國的勞動力中迅速增長。最好的辦法是
對這一勢頭做出貢獻的最佳方式是做一個有良心的消費者，並有選擇地購買
在一個人的購買中。許多消費者忘記了他們有這個非常...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rc7j7b/ysk_that_workers_all_over_the_us_are_showing_an/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rc7j7b/ysk_that_workers_all_over_the_us_are_showing_an/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 03:49:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Class consciousness is growing rapidly among the American workforce for the past few years. The best way to contribute to this momentum is to be a conscientious consumer and be selective in one&amp;amp;#39;s purchases. Many consumers forget that they have this very effective tool in their arsenal against bad corporate practices.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：日本沒有公平使用法。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：最近我看到了一些
的聲明，這些人在他們的視頻中不斷地被索賠，或者因爲審查日本產品而面臨日本公司的法律威脅。
的視頻，或者因爲審查日本內容（主要是動漫）而面臨日本公司的法律威脅。
內容（主要是動漫）。這是因爲即使在Youtubes指南中...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbks00/ysk_japan_does_not_have_fair_use_laws/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbks00/ysk_japan_does_not_have_fair_use_laws/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 02:49:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Recenty I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen a few statements about youtubers/influencers who are constantly being claimed on their videos or facing legal threats by Japanese companies for reviewing Japanese content (mostly anime). This is because even though in Youtubes guide lines of fair use, what they post is ok. But fair use doesn&amp;amp;#39;t exist in Japan so big companies like Toei for example would see it just as a copyright violation or stealing products that they made. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Recently Three Japanese men were convinced of violating copyright laws for making and uploading movie reviews for Japanese movies. So this is something companies are willing to sue individuals for and have them sentenced to jail.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;edit (Hopefully I haven&amp;amp;#39;t broken any rules, I&amp;amp;#39;m on mobile so hopefully I&amp;amp;#39;ve covered everything.)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你知道軟件沒有問題，在把筆記本帶到維修店時，不要把硬盤或固態硬盤留在裏面。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：這些公司可能會進行備份和
也許沒有正確地存儲它們。數據是有價值的，你不希望它到處都是。
到處都是。不要把你的數據放在沒有保護的地方！</p> <p>移除你的
硬盤或固態硬盤對大多數筆記本電腦來說並不難，它將...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbry7i/ysk_dont_leave_your_hard_drive_or_ssd_in_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbry7i/ysk_dont_leave_your_hard_drive_or_ssd_in_your/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 22:50:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: These companies may make backups and maybe not store them properly. Data is valuable and you don&amp;amp;#39;t want it to be everywhere. Don&amp;amp;#39;t keep your data somewhere unprotected!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Removing your hard drive or SSD is not hard for most laptops, it will only take a few minutes once you know how to do it and in most cases, it won&amp;amp;#39;t hurt your laptop.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s not always neccesary. Here&amp;amp;#39;s when you should and when you should:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You should when:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You&amp;amp;#39;re bringing it to a local shop that just does repairs(small businesses with just a few people working there)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;There&amp;amp;#39;s something physically broken, like the screen, the keyboard or the charging hole.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You got sensitive data on your laptop(passwords, private media etc)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t when:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You&amp;amp;#39;re sending your laptop back for warranty&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;There&amp;amp;#39;s warranty stickers on screws, and you still have warranty on your laptop(in that case, just send it back)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You don&amp;amp;#39;t have the proper tools to do it&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 在晚上使用止汗劑]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼選擇YSK：作爲一個曾經超級愛出汗的青少年，瞭解到這一點改變了遊戲規則。
患有多汗症的青少年，瞭解到這是一個改變遊戲規則的方法。止汗劑必須要
如果你在洗完澡後直接塗抹止汗劑，而且還是在溼潤的情況下，那麼你的皮膚必須吸收止汗劑才能發揮作用。
如果你在淋浴後直接塗抹，而且還是溼的；或者在早上出汗後塗抹，它就不會起作用......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbvhey/ysk_apply_antiperspirant_at_night/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbvhey/ysk_apply_antiperspirant_at_night/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:51:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: As a formerly super sweaty teenager with hyperhidrosis learning this was a game changer. Anti-perspirant has to absorb into your skin to work and if you apply it directly after a shower while still wet; or in the morning and sweat it out it will not work (and just stain your tees!)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Applying at night, to clean DRY armpits is key. Even if you start getting sweaty before sleep, once you sleep you usually will sweat less which will allow enough time for the active ingredient to absorb. Once built up this will last days at a time and you can often get form to applying only once a week at night.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This was inspired by the EMSKR and how to apply anti perspirant was way too low on list.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: I should probably mention that antiperspirant shouldn’t be used to prevent normal sweating. It’s a natural part of the body that helps you keep cool. If you are however excessively sweaty, first consider seeing your doctor or dermatologist. If you choose to include an anti perspirant in your routine, it’s most effective when used at  night. You also probably don’t need to use it as often as you think. Usually only every other night or a couple nights a week. Continue to apply normal deodorant in mornings as usual.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：有一個瀏覽器擴展，將 "不喜歡 "按鈕重新整合到YouTube中。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：因爲它使瀏覽更快樂
清楚地知道你可以顯示你對某些內容的潛在不屑。
</div><!-- SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rak6pw/ysk_there_is_a_browser_extension_that_integrates/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rak6pw/ysk_there_is_a_browser_extension_that_integrates/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 11:48:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Because it makes for happier browsing knowing full well you can show your potential disdain for certain content.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在進行基因檢測之前，你要購買人壽、殘疾和長期護理保險。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>YSK：人壽、殘疾和長期護理
保險公司可以根據基因測試結果進行歧視。健康
</p> <p>爲什麼YSK：健康保險公司被禁止根據基因測試結果進行歧視。
</p> <p>爲什麼YSK：健康保險公司被禁止以遺傳學爲由進行歧視。其他保險公司--如人壽保險、...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbhh2k/ysk_you_want_to_get_your_life_disability_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rbhh2k/ysk_you_want_to_get_your_life_disability_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 05:42:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;YSK: Life, disability, and long-term care insurance providers can discriminate based on genetic testing results. Health insurance providers can&amp;amp;#39;t.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Health insurers are forbidden to discriminate on the basis of genetics. Other insurers--like life, disability, and long-term care--aren&amp;amp;#39;t. So if you think you&amp;amp;#39;ll want genetic testing--and odds are you will someday--it&amp;amp;#39;s wise to get your life, disability, and long-term care policies set up first.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在美國，你可以通過在IRS數據庫中搜索一個組織，來檢查它是否真的是一個非營利組織。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：特別是每年的這個時候，有很多公司試圖假裝自己是慈善機構，而他們卻不知道。
有很多公司試圖假裝他們是慈善機構，而實際上他們是盈利公司。
實際上是營利性公司。美國國稅局有一個完整的數據庫向公衆開放。
公衆在線<a href="https://apps.irs.gov/app/eos/">這裏</a>...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rb1s93/ysk_that_in_the_us_you_can_check_if_an/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rb1s93/ysk_that_in_the_us_you_can_check_if_an/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 02:49:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: especially this time of year, there are plenty of companies that try to pretend that they are charities when they are actually for profit companies. The IRS keeps a full database open to the public online &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.irs.gov/app/eos/&quot;&amp;gt;here&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; where you can simply search for an organization to see if its a real non profit.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Further, if it is a nonprofit, both the organization and the IRS are required to disclose their 990 tax form, which provides their financial statements including the salary of their directors and chief officers, so you can see if half of your donation is simply going into the chairperson&amp;amp;#39;s pocket.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如何區分緊張性頭痛和偏頭痛，因爲它們的治療方法是非常不同的]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：偏頭痛和緊張性頭痛之間有着巨大的區別。
偏頭痛和緊張性頭痛有很大的區別。緊張性頭痛是最常見的頭痛類型。
緊張性頭痛是最常見的頭痛類型，但大多數人在不知情的情況下將其稱爲緊張性頭痛並將其視爲
偏頭痛。</p> <p>偏頭痛是一個神經系統問題，而緊張性頭痛則是一個神經系統問題。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rajzla/ysk_how_to_tell_the_difference_between_tension/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rajzla/ysk_how_to_tell_the_difference_between_tension/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 17:57:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: There is a HUGE difference between migraines and tension headaches. Tension headaches are the most common type of headache though most people unknowingly refer to them and treat them as migraines. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Migraines are a neurological problem and tension headaches are more of a muscular problem. Of course it is much more complicated than this but I’m trying to keep it as basic as possible.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ve suffered from tension headaches for the past 7 years that have been so bad they cost me friendships, relationships, and multiple jobs. Because of this I am very educated on tension headaches (but not so much migraines).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here’s how you can tell if you have tension headaches (and not migraines):&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Next time you have a headache take a muscle relaxer than contains ibuprofen (this is usually the purple coloured bottle). Robax platinum or any store brand version will work.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you find relief from the muscle relaxer, you likely have tension headaches, not migraines.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There are many other ways to test it such as using ice and heat as those tend to do good for tension headaches but they can also help some people with migraines, so it’s not a definite answer. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If the muscle relaxer does not relieve your pain you either have migraines or another type of headaches such as cluster headaches. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here are somethings to consider if you have tensions headaches as these are common factors in those that do. Consider fixing them as they can be the cause of your pain:
- do you grind your teeth? 
- are you low on magnesium?
- do you sleep on your side or stomach?
- do you have poor posture? 
- do you have proper tongue posture/where does your tongue sit in your mouth (it’s should be firmly pressed against the roof of your mouth). &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;not&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; relaxed. I used  to grind my teeth at night and would try to relax my whole mouth during the day to stop it. In reality this was causing more damage as one of the most important parts of good posture is having your tongue pressing against the roof of your mouth as frequently as possible) &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I have so much more advice but I don’t want to make this post too long. I hope I can help at least one person with this info :)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 如果你的車被撞壞了，告訴你的保險公司在市場上找三輛類似的車，以他們提供的金額爲準。你不必接受他們的第一個報價，也不必同意修理一輛往往不應該修理的汽車。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK:</p> <p><strong>1.)</strong> Insurance
始終試圖首先提供低價，有時會讓你在舊的車輛貸款上欠下餘額，或讓你無法更換車輛。
貸款，或者讓你無法用類似價值的車輛來替換你的車輛。
vehicle of similar value.</p> <p><strong>2.)</strong> They may…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/raro9d/ysk_if_your_car_is_totaled_tell_your_insurance/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/raro9d/ysk_if_your_car_is_totaled_tell_your_insurance/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 08:46:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;1.)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Insurance will ALWAYS try to offer low first, sometimes leaving you with a balance owed on your old vehicle loan or leaving you unable to replace your vehicle with a vehicle of similar value.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;2.)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; They may also try to force you to repair a vehicle which is so damaged that it will be nearly worthless &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;(or dangerous)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; after the repair.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With the price of used (and new) vehicles skyrocketing, insurance companies are pushing heavily to &amp;amp;quot;repair&amp;amp;quot; vehicles with fire damage, frame damage, firewall damage, etc; due to the high cost of replacing your vehicle often leaving you with something unsafe and also worthless to any potential buyer in the future.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What to do:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Situation 1.)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Ask the insurance company to provide you with a list of 3 of the exact same trim of vehicle, in the same condition, with the same mileage for the $ they&amp;amp;#39;re giving you. They will be forced to give you a proper amount, in order to replace the vehicle you were paying them to insure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Situation 2.)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Get an &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;independent estimate&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; from a reputable body shop, and if you believe your vehicle is beyond repair and ask the body shop if it were their car, would they repair it? If the answer is &amp;amp;quot;no&amp;amp;quot;, then fight your insurance company because you&amp;amp;#39;re about to get a raw deal..and possibly end up with a vehicle that&amp;amp;#39;s now dangerous and also possibly worthless to any lender or any future buyer (or any future insurance payout..)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在穿新衣服之前要先洗乾淨。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：許多紡織品都經過化學處理，包括甲醛樹脂。
包括甲醛樹脂，以防止衣服在運輸過程中發生黴變和黴菌生長。
在運輸過程中防止衣服發黴和發黴，以及染料固定劑、阻燃劑和抗菌處理。
抗菌處理，以及爲防止起皺和起皺而進行的處理。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rap5y5/ysk_wash_your_new_clothes_before_wearing_them/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rap5y5/ysk_wash_your_new_clothes_before_wearing_them/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 06:40:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Many textiles are treated with chemicals including formaldehyde resins to prevent mildew and mold growth on clothes during transport as well as dye fixatives, fire retardant and antibacterial treatments, and treatments to prevent wrinkling and shrinkage.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You may be able to smell it on your new clothes. It&amp;amp;#39;s recommended that you wash all garments that will come into direct contact with your skin. Any remaining resins will come out as you wash them. At the acceptable levels present in clothing, the main risk to you is contact dermatitis. But you should still wash your new clothes.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m sharing this because I bought new pajamas and they reek.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.co.in/books/edition/Principles_of_Textile_Finishing/p_9PCwAAQBAJ?hl=en&amp;amp;amp;gbpv=1&amp;amp;amp;dq=finishing+textiles&amp;amp;amp;printsec=frontcover&quot;&amp;gt;Principles of Textile Finishing&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gao.gov/assets/gao-10-875.pdf&quot;&amp;gt;Formaldehyde in Textiles&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007%2Fs40521-019-0197-5&quot;&amp;gt;Textile Contact Dermatitis&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2010/12/11/your-money/11wrinkle.html&quot;&amp;gt;NYT Formaldehyde Fumes&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK政府管理的無人認領財產項目持有你所欠的錢。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：它是免費的，它是合法的，而且
它是你的錢</p> <p><strong>這個項目在美國、加拿大和英國都存在。
至少，所以雖然我說的是美國，但你的國家可能也有一個
也有</strong></p> <p>假設8年前你辭去了一份工作....]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/raizy7/ysk_the_govrun_unclaimed_property_program_holds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/raizy7/ysk_the_govrun_unclaimed_property_program_holds/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 04:42:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: it&amp;amp;#39;s free, it&amp;amp;#39;s legit, and it&amp;amp;#39;s your money&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;This program exists in the US, Canada, and UK AT LEAST, so while I&amp;amp;#39;m talking about the US, your country probably has one too&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Let&amp;amp;#39;s say 8 years ago you quit a job. Later, that business discovered you were owed $50 in overtime. Legally, they have to get it to you, but realistically they aren&amp;amp;#39;t going to hire a PI to find &amp;amp;amp; verify your identity. Maybe you inherited some stocks/bonds and weren&amp;amp;#39;t notified. Where does the money go? Why, the Unclaimed Property Program! &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://unclaimed.org/search/&quot;&amp;gt;https://unclaimed.org/search/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Government-run and totally legitimate, it&amp;amp;#39;s free to search your name, your business name, your sister&amp;amp;#39;s name....anyone&amp;amp;#39;s name, and see if they are owed money. I found I was owed hundreds of dollars from my college apartment. My best friend was owed about $75 from an old gig. My current employer had cash from an overpaid utility bill.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s your money and it&amp;amp;#39;s free to get it back. There are BILLIONS OF DOLLARS left unclaimed in the US every year.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is not a scam. I get nothing from this. You won&amp;amp;#39;t be asked to pay a dime - if you are, it&amp;amp;#39;s a scam website. Every state has its own. You can search anywhere - make sure to search in states you&amp;amp;#39;ve lived in the past.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Steps:
Search name - find $$$ - fill out form - get a check in the mail a few weeks later&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;GET YOUR MONEY Y&amp;amp;#39;ALL!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在計劃參觀國家森林/公園的行程時，森林/公園管理員可以提供大量關於附近住宿或交通的信息。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：計劃去另一個州旅行可能是令人生畏的。
是令人生畏的。所有的國家森林和公園都是由其中一個森林/公園管理局經營的。
所有的國家森林和公園都由其中一個森林/公園服務機構運營。所有這些服務都有帶聯繫表格的網站。護林員
護林員就像圖書管理員一樣，但卻是爲土地服務的。</p> <p>他們擁有所有的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rad2oo/ysk_when_planning_a_trip_to_see_a_national/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rad2oo/ysk_when_planning_a_trip_to_see_a_national/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 23:45:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Planning a trip to another state can be daunting. All national forests and parks are operated by one of the forest/park services. All of these services have sites with contact forms. The rangers are like librarians but for the land.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They have all been in the area for a long time and are very familiar with tourism to their park. And they typically are very kind and informative and don&amp;amp;#39;t mind helping you out with the info.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It makes planning a trip so much easier to have all of that information up front.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK直截了當地切割指甲，以防止嵌甲。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：不正確的修剪指甲是導致嵌甲的一個原因。
ingrown nails.</p> <p><a
href="https://puretherapyclinic.files.wordpress.com/2017/01/infection-after-ingrown-toenail-1.png">Here&#39;s
an example of how to cut them</a></p> <p>Causes:</p> <p>The etiology of…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rabskj/ysk_cut_nails_straight_across_to_prevent_ingrown/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rabskj/ysk_cut_nails_straight_across_to_prevent_ingrown/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 18:42:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Improper nail trimming is 1 cause of ingrown nails.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://puretherapyclinic.files.wordpress.com/2017/01/infection-after-ingrown-toenail-1.png&quot;&amp;gt;Here&amp;amp;#39;s an example of how to cut them&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Causes:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The etiology of ingrown toenails includes direct trauma to the toe that forces the nail corners into the surrounding nail fold, genetic predisposition, improper nail trimming, poorly fitting shoes, and constant and repetitive microtrauma from normal day-to-day activities. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After a painful procedure this afternoon and now typing this with throbbing pain, I wish I have knew about this MUCH SOONER.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC1472971/&quot;&amp;gt;Source&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/d5qh3a/&quot;&amp;gt;Old YSK post&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://theawkwardyeti.com/comic/ingrown-nail/&quot;&amp;gt;Comic&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK有一個名爲Be My Eyes的應用程序，可以讓視障人士通過視頻呼叫志願者，請求提供視覺援助。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼選擇YSK：該應用程序是免費下載的，你可以作爲志願者或視障/盲人註冊。
你可以以志願者或視障/盲人的身份註冊。如果你需要
視覺幫助（舉例說明挑選正確的衣服顏色。
或在購物時選擇正確的產品品牌），並且你是...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r9lzqz/ysk_there_is_an_app_called_be_my_eyes_that_allows/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r9lzqz/ysk_there_is_an_app_called_be_my_eyes_that_allows/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 04:48:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: The app is free to download and you can sign up as a volunteer or a visually impaired / blind person. If you need visual help (examples given are picking the right colour of an item of clothing, or the right brand of product when shopping) and you are visually impaired, you press a button on the app. The app will call multiple volunteers (volunteers do not need to have the app open to recieve a call, they just have to be logged in) , and whoever picks up the quickest is connected by video call. The volunteer can then assist you in whatever task you need help with.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thought it was a great idea and a helpful app. Currently there are over 4 million volunteers signed up, but only 310, 000 visually impaired or blind people. Thought I&amp;amp;#39;d share in case anyone would find this useful.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你應該定期將白醋倒入馬桶的蓄水池/水箱中，以避免鈣質在馬桶的沖水系統中堆積，從而損壞它。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：自來水是用來填充馬桶水箱的。
廁所的水箱，其中可能含有大量的鈣質硬度。如果不加處理
如果不加以控制，隨着時間的推移，鈣質堆積物會在馬桶的幾乎所有地方形成
馬桶的沖水系統，這將損害墊圈......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r9tj6r/ysk_you_should_regularly_pour_white_vinegar_into/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r9tj6r/ysk_you_should_regularly_pour_white_vinegar_into/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 02:52:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Tap water, which is used to fill a toilet&amp;amp;#39;s water tank, can contain a lot of calcium hardness in it. If left unchecked, over time, calcareous buildups will form pretty much everywhere in the toilet&amp;amp;#39;s flushing system, which will damage the gaskets and other components in it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This also goes for pretty much anything that has tap water running through it in your home. Faucets, dishwasher, washing machine, kettle, shower head, etc. A little bit of vinegar is very efficient at getting rid of calcium deposits.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Steps:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Turn off the water&amp;amp;#39;s supply to the toilet&amp;amp;#39;s water tank, there&amp;amp;#39;s usually a knob or valve on the wall next to your toilet that you have to turn.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Open up the water tank/cistern by removing the top lid. (You may need a screwdriver to do this, depending on the model of your toilet)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;If the water tank is full, flush the water and empty it. (Because you&amp;amp;#39;ve turned off the water&amp;amp;#39;s supply, it shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t fill back up again)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Pour white vinegar all over the flushing system and fill half of the tank with it.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Fill the remaining half of the tank with hot water (not boiling, slightly hot, max 50°C/120°F temp) and let the mixture do its thing for 15-20 minutes. You should be able to see small bubbles, that&amp;amp;#39;s a result of the white vinegar dissolving the deposits.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;If you have thick hard deposits, wear latex gloves and use a sponge to scrape off the deposits.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Once all the deposits have dissolved, flush it all down the toilet.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Turn the water&amp;amp;#39;s supply to the toilet&amp;amp;#39;s tank back on and put the lid back on.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Do this once a month, or maybe even once a week, depending on how calcareous your tap water is.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ve just had to clean mine thoroughly because my toilet&amp;amp;#39;s flushing system stopped working properly, the water kept flushing/running. When I opened up the lid of the water tank, I was pretty horrified by the state of the flushing system. I had to replace the gaskets and had to scrape a lot of thick deposits. It was a real pain to clean... So, I now have a reminder in my phone to pour white vinegar into the toilet&amp;amp;#39;s water tank once a month to prevent this.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hopefully this is useful to someone!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：漂白劑過期，幾乎無用]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：漂白劑會隨着時間的推移降解成其
組成的部分。它不會變得更危險，但它絕對會
它不會變得更危險，但絕對會失去效力，從而限制了它的清潔能力。如果你
如果你很難讓漂白劑像你期望的那樣發揮作用，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r9ef6v/ysk_bleach_expires_and_becomes_almost_useless/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r9ef6v/ysk_bleach_expires_and_becomes_almost_useless/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 14:44:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Bleach degrades over time into its constituent parts. It doesn&amp;amp;#39;t become more dangerous but it will absolutely lose its potency, thus limiting it&amp;amp;#39;s cleaning capabilities. If you&amp;amp;#39;re having a hard time getting bleach to work as you&amp;amp;#39;d expect, think back to how long ago you bought it, as it could be almost completely inert if it&amp;amp;#39;s a few years old.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：阿芙樂可導致一種嚴重的醫學症狀，稱爲反跳性充血]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：&quot;雖然它不被視爲一種
在通常意義上，你的身體<em>可以</em>變得依賴
對藥物的依賴。醫生稱這種現象爲&#39;反彈性充血,&#39;或<a
href="https://www.jacionline.org/article/S0091...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r92nwx/ysk_afrin_can_cause_a_serious_medical_condition/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r92nwx/ysk_afrin_can_cause_a_serious_medical_condition/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 13:46:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:  &amp;amp;quot;While it’s not considered an &amp;amp;#39;addiction&amp;amp;#39; in the usual sense, your body &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;can&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; become dependent on the drug. Doctors call this phenomenon &amp;amp;#39;rebound congestion,&amp;amp;#39; or &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jacionline.org/article/S0091-6749(06&quot;&amp;gt;rhinitis medicamentosa&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;01370-4/fulltext), and it is a very real problem. In fact, it could be responsible for up to 9% of visits to allergists and ENT doctors. &amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.singlecare.com/blog/rebound-congestion-nasal-spray-addiction/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.singlecare.com/blog/rebound-congestion-nasal-spray-addiction/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：吊扇有一個冬季設置。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：大多數吊扇能夠
暖房間，這是很反常的。很多風扇上都有一個開關。
側面的某個地方有一個開關，可以是向上或向下的，翻開這個開關將
切換葉片的旋轉，所以不是向下吹風，而是......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r91xer/ysk_ceiling_fans_have_a_winter_setting/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r91xer/ysk_ceiling_fans_have_a_winter_setting/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 09:26:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Most ceiling fans are capable of warming a room which is counterintuitive. On a lot a fans there&amp;amp;#39;s a switch somewhere on the side that can be either up or down, flipping this switch will switch the blades rotation so instead of blowing air down, it sucks air up (so having some space between the fan blades and the ceiling is ideal) which moves the cool air from below disturbing the warm air above which warms the room. (This is probably common knowledge that is worth repeating for those who didn&amp;amp;#39;t know)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: Really important point not in my original post brought up by a smart comment: Vacuum/dust the top of your blades before doing this! (thank you aquaman67!)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：教孩子們如何安全、適當地與狗相處。被狗咬傷是兒童時期最容易預防的一些傷害。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：作爲一個照顧者，保護兒童安全是非常重要的。
照顧兒童的安全是非常重要的。如果你想在你的家庭中養狗，那麼教孩子們如何與狗安全互動是非常重要的。
</p> <p>編輯：是的!
人們應該訓練他們的狗! 但是，這也是非常重要的，孩子們...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r911j3/ysk_teach_children_how_to_be_around_dogs_safely/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r911j3/ysk_teach_children_how_to_be_around_dogs_safely/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 00:56:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: as a caregiver it is incredibly important to keep children safe. If you want to have a dog in your family it is important to teach kids how to interact with dogs safely.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT: Yes! People should train their dogs! But also it’s really important kids are taught certain elements of how to protect themselves. These are what I teach kids with families with dogs to work on safety. I am never excusing untrained dogs. I became a dog trainer because I care about dog training and well trained dogs. I am not blaming children for dog bites at all. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;One thing I routinely see as a dog trainer is how many dogs are absolutely terrified of children. It’s not necessarily due to bad experience. Rather, kids move sporadically and unpredictably; they vocalize in unusual patterns. Dogs are used to human movement but children do not move in ways dogs can easily read. Many dogs will not chase an adult out for a run but will chase a child that is skipping or sprinting down the side walk. This is partially due to the unpredictable nature of the way kids move; when dogs see those kinds of movement patterns instincts to herd/chase can be activated. To keep children in your care safe around dogs here are a few simple rules I used to explain to children I worked with:
1) If you see a dog, stop running. Try not to run or skip around dogs. A lot of dogs have herding and chasing instincts, and they may see these sudden movements an invitation to run towards you. They do not want to hurt you but they may also not want to play with you. It is safest for you to never run around when you see a dog. 
2) If a dog is scared of you, it does not mean you have done something wrong. Lots of dogs have had different experiences and do not know whether strangers will be nice to them. 
3) Do not scream or shout near or at dogs, try to lower your voice if you are playing with a dog. Screaming may scare them and many dogs will act defensively when scared. They do not want to hurt you but they may be concerned that you may hurt them.
4) If you want to say hi to a dog and the owner says it is okay, make sure the dog can see your hand. Instead of reaching for the top of their head see if they will let you pet them under the chin. Instead of approaching them from the front, you can try approaching the dog from the side with your hand extended. Dogs will approach each other from the side to indicate non threatening and friendly behavior.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：大多數公司和ISP通過DNS追蹤你，通過使用Adguard DNS這樣的開源服務器，你可以阻止整個設備上的廣告/追蹤器/惡意軟件。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：任何人都需要DNS服務器來連接互聯網。
連接到互聯網。公司和ISP喜歡在法律允許的範圍內儘可能多地追蹤你。
在法律允許的範圍內儘可能地跟蹤你。他們主要是通過DNS服務器來做到這一點
他們自動配置你的設備來使用。通過切換到...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8wdhg/ysk_most_corporations_and_isps_track_you_through/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8wdhg/ysk_most_corporations_and_isps_track_you_through/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:42:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: DNS servers are required for anyone to connect to the internet. Corporations and ISPs like to track you as much as humanly possible within the law. They do this mostly through the DNS servers they automatically configure your devices to use. By switching to an encrypted dns server with filters that block these tracking/ad domains you won&amp;amp;#39;t see any more on your entire device. DNS is being used for tracking/ads more than any time previously in the last twenty years. It&amp;amp;#39;s only a few numbers, it&amp;amp;#39;s an easy and effortless switch. Adguard is open source and free to use like Bitcoin and Ethereum, Linux, Firefox and Tor for example.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit (for no confusion): &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://adguard-dns.com/en/public-dns.html&quot;&amp;gt;https://adguard-dns.com/en/public-dns.html&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit 2: May not work with streaming services or youtube on phones or xboxes, play stations. Google loads all their ads on one domain, so to block those domains you&amp;amp;#39;d be blocking youtube itself, alas. You can sideload cercube youtube through altstore on IOS or use youtube vanced on Android to get premium for free though (I myself use altstore, also have spotify premium for free)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你能證明你的收入很低，美國的一些醫院會提供大幅折扣。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：美國的醫療保健可能是非常難以負擔的。
負擔不起，並有可能在經濟上毀掉人們。沒有多少人
沒有多少人知道<em>一些</em>醫院會對你的賬單提供折扣。你必須
你必須要求這些折扣，它們不會像其他醫院那樣被分發出去。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8qwut/ysk_some_hospitals_in_the_usa_will_offer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8qwut/ysk_some_hospitals_in_the_usa_will_offer/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 20:36:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Healthcare in the USA can be very unaffordable and has the potential to financially ruin people. Not many people are aware that &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;some&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; hospitals will offer discounts to your bill. You MUST ASK for these discounts, they aren&amp;amp;#39;t handed out like candy. Some discounts may be applied simply because you asked and were polite in doing so. Other potentially larger discounts may be applied if you can prove your income is relatively low and you are unable to pay in a timely fashion. Generally speaking, some hospitals will prefer to lower your bill and get you to pay that amount rather than send the full bill to collections. You might want to seek out hospitals that offer these discounts as opposed to ones that do not. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As an anecdote, I had low wages and a hospital bill a number of years ago. I asked for a discount and got 45% off the bill, as well as 35% off any future bills for a whole year. I did have sign a document attesting to my wages. I had insurance at the time but the bill was slightly less than my deductible.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK, wary, weary, leery都是不同的詞。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK，警覺和警惕都意味着
對一個潛在問題的謹慎&quot;。疲憊是指&quot;疲憊&quot;。
</p> <p>你一次又一次地看到人們說他們對一個問題感到厭煩。
問題，那是因爲他們把 "警覺 "和 "警惕 "這兩個詞混爲一談......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r5rb87/ysk_wary_weary_leery_are_all_different_words/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r5rb87/ysk_wary_weary_leery_are_all_different_words/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 18:37:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK, wary and leery both mean &amp;amp;quot;cautious about a potential problem&amp;amp;quot;. Weary means &amp;amp;quot;tired&amp;amp;quot;. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Over and over you see people say they are &amp;amp;quot;weary&amp;amp;quot; of a problem, that&amp;amp;#39;s because they are conflating wary and leery, two words that means roughly the same thing, but combining those words leaves you with &amp;amp;quot;weary&amp;amp;quot;, which, again, just means tired. You are not tired of the problem, you are sceptical of the problem, so either wary or leery is what you mean. 
Unless the issue has exhausted you, you aren&amp;amp;#39;t &amp;amp;quot;weary&amp;amp;quot; of it, you&amp;amp;#39;re &amp;amp;quot;wary&amp;amp;quot; or &amp;amp;quot;leery&amp;amp;quot; of it. Learn the difference and you won&amp;amp;#39;t sound like a tool.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：大多數洗碗皁（如黎明）都是在裝滿水的水槽中使用的，而不是直接用在海綿上。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：一些肥皂公司正在改變配方。
一些肥皂公司正在改變他們的配方，因爲現在很多人都是一個一個地洗碗，把洗碗劑放在海綿上，然後用流水擦洗。
肥皂放在海綿上，然後用流動的水擦洗，而不是在水槽裏填滿。
水槽。如果你沒有一個兩部分的水槽，那就很難...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8f5fq/ysk_most_dish_soaps_like_dawn_are_designed_to_be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/r8f5fq/ysk_most_dish_soaps_like_dawn_are_designed_to_be/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 04:58:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Some soap companies are changing their formula because so many people wash dishes now one by one, by putting dish soap on the sponge and then scrubbing with running water, rather than filling the sink. If you don’t have a 2 part sink, it makes it harder to wash by hand (maybe consider using a tub), but if you do have 2 sides, fill one side w water and soap, soak dishes, scrub them while submerged, and then rinse them in the other side of the sink. It not only saves on both water and soap, but will get your dishes cleaner.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>