<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 12:16:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲腰高比（WtHR）是比BMI更強的預測體重相關健康問題的因素。理想情況下，你的腰圍大約是你身高的一半。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：</p> <p>與體重有關的疾病是一些最具毀滅性的疾病。
一些最具破壞性的疾病，也是一些最容易預防的疾病，而且
BMI（可能是最受歡迎的指標）實際上在預測與體重有關的疾病方面做得很差。
</p> <p>這篇文章的目的不是要...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmppwp/ysk_that_waist_to_height_ratio_wthr_is_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmppwp/ysk_that_waist_to_height_ratio_wthr_is_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 11:38:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Weight related illnesses are some of the most devastating and also some of the most preventable diseases, and BMI (likely the most popular metric) actually does a poor job of predicting weight-related illnesses.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This post is not intended to body shame anyone. No measure is perfect.  It is simply meant to inform people of an easy, high-predictive-power way to assess your own risk for weight-related illnesses.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/14674615/&quot;&amp;gt;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/14674615/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，你身體中95%的5-羥色胺（穩定情緒的荷爾蒙，負責健康的感覺）是在你的腸道中產生。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：你腸道中的菌羣負責生產許多重要的激素，包括血清素。
腸道菌羣負責生產許多重要的激素，包括血清素。
保持健康的腸道微生物羣在降低壓力水平、保持身體健康方面起着巨大作用。
壓力水平，保持抑鬱症，獲得足夠的睡眠，等等。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmjnod/ysk_that_95_of_your_bodys_serotonin_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmjnod/ysk_that_95_of_your_bodys_serotonin_the/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 05:36:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: The flora in your gut is responsible for the production of a lot of important hormones, including serotonin. Maintaining a healthy intestinal micro-biome plays a huge role in lowering stress levels, keeping depression at bay, getting enough sleep, and so many other things that can improve your quality of life. Eating a balanced diet not only keeps you healthy physically, but it promotes a healthy mental state too.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TLDR: A lot of mental health issues can potentially be treated by eating a balanced, healthy diet. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/health/irritable-bowel-syndrome/serotonin-effects&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.healthline.com/health/irritable-bowel-syndrome/serotonin-effects&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apa.org/monitor/2012/09/gut-feeling&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.apa.org/monitor/2012/09/gut-feeling&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，如果你與服務行業的好工人交往，給他們工作的公司打電話表揚該工人，通常會給這個人的生活帶來切實的好處。只是不要提到折扣或偷工減料。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：</p> <ol> <li><p>它使你的生活更美好，讓他們付出額外的努力對你好。
讓他們付出額外的努力對你好，所以讓他們的生活變得更好是很好的
讓他們的生活更美好。Usually they don&#39;t see a ton of reward.</p></li>
<li><p>it costs you nothing to call, and only 5 minutes of…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmheie/ysk_that_if_you_interact_with_a_nice_worker_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmheie/ysk_that_if_you_interact_with_a_nice_worker_in/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 02:52:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;it makes your life better to have them put in the extra effort to be nice to you, so it&amp;amp;#39;s nice to make their life better. Usually they don&amp;amp;#39;t see a ton of reward.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;it costs you nothing to call, and only 5 minutes of time usually. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s a powerful statement, because people usually just call to complain. A compliment speaks loudly. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s good for the businesses too, to have workers that are pleasant. Everyone benefits from them rewarding solid and friendly employees. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Tip: don&amp;amp;#39;t mention them giving you discounts etc. Do mention the solid experience they provided you as a customer, and how friendly they were.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 用激光瞄準飛機是非法的，可能導致罰款和/或監禁。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：在美國上空飛行的飛機受到
受聯邦法律的管轄和保護。干擾飛行中的飛機是
是一項聯邦罪行。當飛行員從地面上看到激光時，會使他或她失明幾分鐘。
當飛行員從地面上看到激光時，會使他或她失明數分鐘，嚴重危害到他或她的安全。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmbarc/ysk_targeting_an_aircraft_with_a_laser_is_illegal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmbarc/ysk_targeting_an_aircraft_with_a_laser_is_illegal/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 21:37:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Aircraft flying over the US are governed and protected by federal law. Interfering with an aircraft in flight is a federal offense. When a pilot sees a LASER from the ground it can blind him or her for several minutes, seriously endangering the safety of the flight, the aircraft, the pilots, and all passengers onboard the aircraft.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.avweb.com/aviation-news/mississippi-man-faces-prison-time-for-targeting-aircraft-with-a-laser/&quot;&amp;gt;Here&amp;amp;#39;s an example of a recent penalty&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你在美國爲非營利組織或政府全職工作，你可能能夠通過PSLF計劃擺脫你的一些學生貸款。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：學生債務在美國是巨大的。
任何能夠幫助人們擺脫一些債務的東西都是偉大的。美國教育部
美國教育部於10月6日宣佈臨時擴大PSLF的範圍。
計劃。趁着這個機會，趕快行動吧！</p> <p>美國的全職非營利組織和...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmafgj/ysk_if_you_work_fulltime_in_the_us_for_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmafgj/ysk_if_you_work_fulltime_in_the_us_for_a/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 19:34:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Student debt is HUGE in the US, and anything that can help people get rid of some of that debt is great. The U.S. Department of Education announced a temporary expansion on Oct. 6 for the PSLF program. Get it while you can!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;US full-time nonprofit and government workers that have Federal Direct Loans student debt may be eligible for loan forgiveness, cancellation and/or consolidation of federal student loans under the Public Service Loan Forgiveness (PSLF) program. You could have your outstanding debt forgiven tax-free, after making 120 qualifying monthly payments under a qualifying repayment plan. Go to the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://studentaid.gov/pslf/&quot;&amp;gt;PSLF Help Tool&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; to find out if you&amp;amp;#39;re eligible.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK。貿易工作並不適合所有人。來自一個有13年工作經驗的商人]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK；我聽到很多人淡化了學校，炒作了交易。
我聽到很多人貶低學校，炒作貿易。雖然對某些人來說，貿易可能是通往成功未來的最佳途徑。
雖說對某些行業來說，可能是通往成功未來的最佳途徑，但這並不適合於所有人。</p> <p>我已經培訓了
至少有80％的人在聲稱他們已經成功後被淘汰。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlicqy/ysk_trade_work_isnt_for_everyone_coming_from_a_13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlicqy/ysk_trade_work_isnt_for_everyone_coming_from_a_13/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 23:41:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK;  I hear a lot of people downplay school and hype up trades. While for some trades may be the best way to a successful future, this does not hold true for everyone. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ve trained dozens of people and watched at least %80 wash out after claiming they could handle it. Why? It’s hard, depressing, you’re going to miss your family get no thanks, and it’s out right demoralizing until you’ve mastered it unless you’re a true die hard country boy or handy man. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you or your child considers trade work you have to be In perfect physical condition to even have a shot at the big bucks(some, or most tbh, forego that for hard drugs to cope). There is no I’m tired or hungry when you’re at the mercy of people that have done this for years. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I will not quit my trade although I am in the process of getting an education. I take pride in building. Aliens didn’t build the pyramids people like you and I  did. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Concrete finisher here. The broken bones, missing time with my family and pissing blood from dehydration was enough to make me reconsider my choice. 2022 college freshman at age 28&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TLDR; do your research before joining trade work. You may be in for a surprise.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你在面試中被問到是否打算生孩子，你不必回答，你可以直接說不。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：最近在一次採訪中被問到這個問題。
採訪中被問到了這個問題，作爲最後的問題之一，他們爲什麼要問我這個問題，這一點非常明顯。
我很清楚他們爲什麼要問我這個問題。作爲一個主要由男性組成的行業中的女性，我感到
因爲我確信他們不會問男人的問題。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlgusb/ysk_if_you_get_asked_in_an_interview_whether/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlgusb/ysk_if_you_get_asked_in_an_interview_whether/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 19:40:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: was recently asked this in an interview as one of the final questions and it was super obvious why they were asking me it. As a women in an industry that is made mostly of men, I felt slightly unfairly treated as I&amp;amp;#39;m sure they don&amp;amp;#39;t ask men going for the role that question. I&amp;amp;#39;ve also read that it is illegal to ask that question in some countries. Has anyone else been asked this in interviews? Or is it just me?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，你從僱主那裏收到的 "廉價 "禮物實際上可能是從你的經理的口袋裏掏出來的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：我知道現在是拉屎的季節。
我知道現在是拉屎的季節，我也很支持，因爲這些錢確實是來自於企業的預算。
但在你收到禮物時點燃你的火把之前
但在你收到禮物時點燃火把之前，考慮一下你收到的東西是由......支付的。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlhqbh/ysk_that_the_cheap_gifts_that_you_receive_from/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlhqbh/ysk_that_the_cheap_gifts_that_you_receive_from/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 18:37:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: I know it&amp;amp;#39;s the season to shit on shitty corporate gifts, and I&amp;amp;#39;m all for it in the event that the money does come out of the corporate budget, but before you light your torches when you get your present, consider that what you received was paid from the pocket of someone not too far removed from you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;25 years ago, when we all got our first &amp;amp;#39;real jobs&amp;amp;#39; out of college, I remember many of my mates bragging about their company-funded golf games and company-expensed dinners and amazing Christmas bonuses. In retrospect I think most of them were exaggerating/lying, but I always wondered why I never had those perks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Come Christmas, my immediate manager (we were a team of 12) went around and gave envelopes to everyone. &amp;amp;#39;Here&amp;amp;#39;s the fat Christmas bonus I hear everyone talk about&amp;amp;#39;, I thought to myself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I open the envelope and see a $15 gift certificate to a retail store. &amp;amp;#39;That&amp;amp;#39;s it?&amp;amp;#39; I thought to myself &amp;amp;#39;I bust my chops all day for $15?&amp;amp;#39; I was livid.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I was livid all the way home. Livid that evening. Livid that weekend. I told my gf how livid I was. I expected her to be livid along with me.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Instead, she said &amp;amp;quot;That was nice of her, spending her own money like that.&amp;amp;quot; That&amp;amp;#39;s when I realized that this wasn&amp;amp;#39;t a cheap gift, but an amazing, thoughtful gift. I was so obsessed with myself, that I didn&amp;amp;#39;t realize that we were the only team to get something.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My manager - who wasn&amp;amp;#39;t getting paid much more than us, but who had way more financial responsibilities than us - took it upon herself to go out and get each of her team something with her own money - almost $200.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I felt terrible for feeling the way I did, but it taught me a valuable lesson in life.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Happy holidays, everyone!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，能量飲料的酸度很高，因此對你的牙齒/胃酸倒流有害。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：飲料可能是酸性的，即使它們喫起來不酸不苦。
飲料可能是酸性的，即使它們的味道不是酸或苦。</p> <p>一般能量飲料的PH值爲2.8。
實際上與蘇打水相同。</p> <p>The acidity of energy drinks can contribute to
enamel degradation and/or acid reflux.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rkubb0/ysk_that_energy_drinks_are_very_acidic_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rkubb0/ysk_that_energy_drinks_are_very_acidic_and/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 02:53:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Drinks can be acidic even if they don’t taste sour or bitter. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The average energy drink has a PH of 2.8, really the same as soda. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The acidity of energy drinks can contribute to enamel degradation and/or acid reflux.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在美國，沒有無鋁止汗劑這種東西。它們被認爲是藥物，美國食品和藥物管理局只批准在止汗劑中使用源自鋁的活性成分。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：FDA認爲止汗劑是藥物，因爲它們可以防止出汗。
因爲它們可以防止出汗。在美國的OTC專著中，唯一被批准的活性成分
美國的OTC專著中批准的唯一活性成分都是鋁製的。所以在美國
因此，在美國，任何 "不含鋁 "的產品都是除臭劑，而且...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rk7hkf/ysk_in_the_united_states_there_is_no_such_thing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rk7hkf/ysk_in_the_united_states_there_is_no_such_thing/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 21:36:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: The FDA considers antiperspirants as drugs as they prevent perspiration. The only active ingredients approved in the United States in the OTC monograph are all aluminum derived. So in the United States, anything that is “aluminum-free” is a deodorant and will only cover up the scent, but does nothing for sweat prevention, which causes the bad smell in the first place. Any company that tells you their aluminum-free deodorant is an antiperspirant is making either a mislabeled claim, or might be adulterated depending on the situation the FDA deems fit.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://ecfr.io/Title-21/Section-350.10&quot;&amp;gt;OTC monograph active ingredients&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你在加油站加油時，燃料流被點燃，不要將噴嘴從接收器上移開。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>如果你遇到這種情況，請將噴嘴保持在原位。
如果發生這種情況，請將噴嘴留在原地，用開關或緊急開關關閉泵的燃料，並告訴服務員。
告知服務員，服務員將關閉主泵並呼叫緊急服務。
爲什麼是YSK：我已經看到了大約69個視頻，這些人經歷了...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rki013/ysk_if_youre_pumping_at_a_gas_station_and_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rki013/ysk_if_youre_pumping_at_a_gas_station_and_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 12:52:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If this happens to you, keep the nozzle in place, shut off the fuel at the pump with the on/off or emergency switch, and tell the attendant who will shut off the main pump and call emergency services.  Why YSK:  I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen about 69 videos of people who experience this and immediately remove the nozzle and wave the stream of fire around. This will be your first instinct and it is WRONG. To lower the chance this happening, ground yourself when you exit your car by touching the door frame.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，刪除你的數據並不總是刪除它]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：你的數據往往仍然可以被恢復
你的數據經常可以被恢復，並被黑客攻擊，甚至在你要求刪除數據的請求被公司確認後也是如此。
</p> <p>我曾在大技術領域擔任數據科學家，並觀察到數據刪除是一件棘手的事情。
數據刪除是一件棘手的事情。數據治理法律因人而異。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rkf6e1/ysk_that_deleting_your_data_doesnt_always_delete/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rkf6e1/ysk_that_deleting_your_data_doesnt_always_delete/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 10:39:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: your data can often still be recovered, and hacked, even after your request that it be deleted was confirmed by a company.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I worked as a data scientist in big tech, and observed that data deletion is tricky business. Data governance laws vary by country and even state, and range quite widely. In some jurisdictions, there are no requirements: a company owns the data generated through your interactions with its services. Other countries/states do have data ownership/privacy requirements, but even the most stringent laws often require that data not be actually deleted.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Many large companies retain data for &amp;amp;quot;compliance&amp;amp;quot; reasons. A request to delete personal data, while often honored for marketing purposes by companies seeking to operate legally (not all do), is often considered legally compliant if a company only locks your data away rather than deletes it. Data access in these cases is usually limited to a handful of people dedicated to the data privacy compliance effort, but the data is often kept for months and even years. This is not a company&amp;amp;#39;s fault, but rather is mandated by other laws--ones that help identify corruption, market manipulation, anti-consumer actions, etc.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;While retaining data is useful for the above reasons, this legal mess can create confusion for ordinary people. In practice, your data is often accessible even after a company &amp;amp;quot;deletes&amp;amp;quot; it. Given that data breaches in today&amp;amp;#39;s world are effectively only a matter of time at any given company, you can pretty much assume that any online interaction you make can one day surface. Companies do have an obligation to try to keep this from happening, but can seldom be counted on as software often relies on hundreds and thousands of other pieces of software as dependencies--consistently updating all of which is incredibly difficult.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK TurboTax今年不再爲低收入的美國人延續其免費文件計劃]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：許多賺取&lt;$72,000的人使用
TurboTax來免費報稅。今年，他們將需要找到另一個
供應商。請看<
href="https://www.irs.gov/filing/free-file-do-your-federal-taxes-for-free">https://www.irs.gov/filing/free-file-do-your...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rigvha/ysk_turbotax_is_not_renewing_its_free_file/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rigvha/ysk_turbotax_is_not_renewing_its_free_file/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 19:34:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Many people who make &amp;amp;lt;$72,000 use TurboTax to file taxes for free. This year, they will need to find another provider. Check out &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.irs.gov/filing/free-file-do-your-federal-taxes-for-free&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.irs.gov/filing/free-file-do-your-federal-taxes-for-free&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; for more information about which companies will have partnered with the IRS for free file this year (currently this information is not available yet).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK戶外的寵物貓和野貓是一個巨大的捕食問題。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：讓你的貓在外面活動可能對它們的心理健康有好處。
對它們的心理健康有好處，但對當地的生態系統卻不利。貓咪
是天然的捕食者，因此，它是美國最大和最多的鳥類入侵者。
在美國，貓是天然的捕食者，因此是最大和最豐富的鳥類入侵捕食者。</p> <p>野貓的數量超過5000萬隻。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rihl9w/ysk_pet_cats_outdoors_and_feral_cats_are_a_huge/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rihl9w/ysk_pet_cats_outdoors_and_feral_cats_are_a_huge/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 19:34:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Letting your cats outside may be great for their mental health, but it is worse for your local ecosystem. Cats are natural predators, and as a result are the largest and most abundant invasive predator of birds in the US. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Feral cats number over 50M in the US, equating to about &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;8 billion&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; small game hunts per year, most of which are small song birds.(2.4 billion) &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why is this important to me?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;a single mating pair of cats can produce 400,000 offspring in 7 years&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;cats kill about 50% of songbird fledglings (baby birds)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; they will never recover at this rate&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;a UNebraska study has pinned 33 bird extinction events on cat predation&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Humans&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, almost 8 billion of us and our cars, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;are responsible for about 400M deaths of song-birds annually, cats are 2.4 billion&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This issue is 100% to blame on irresponsible cat owners because they are an invasive species brought here by pet trade. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source:&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wintuaudubon.org/feral-cats-drive-songbird-decline/&quot;&amp;gt;Wintu Audubon Society - Feral cats drive songbird decline&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲納洛酮（Narcan）可以逆轉阿片類藥物過量的影響。它使用起來很安全，而且不需要專門的培訓。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：阿片類藥物的過量使用導致[每年10萬名美國人]。
美國人每年]。如果足夠早的話，納洛酮可以逆轉阿片類藥物過量的影響，並使其成爲一種新的治療方法。
阿片類藥物過量的影響，並恢復正常呼吸。它的作用是關閉大腦中的阿片類藥物受體。
它的作用是關閉大腦中的阿片類受體，這意味着它對一個人沒有影響。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfsybl/ysk_that_naloxone_narcan_can_reverse_the_effects/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfsybl/ysk_that_naloxone_narcan_can_reverse_the_effects/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 19:34:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Opioid overdoses kit [100,000 Americans per year]. If given early enough, Naloxone can reverse the effects of an opioid overdose and restore normal breathing. It works by turning off opioid receptors in the brain, meaning it has no effects on someone who isn&amp;amp;#39;t being affected by opioids.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In my home state of Minnesota, most pharmacies give it out for free. No special training is required.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Note that it is a controlled substance, so you will need a prescription in some states. More info below. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How Does Naloxone Work?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Naloxone is an opioid receptor antagonist meaning it binds to opioid receptors and reverses or blocks the effects of other opioids. Giving naloxone rapidly reverses the effects of opioid drugs, restoring normal respiration. It can be administered by injection or through a nasal spray.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Is Naloxone Safe?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Yes. There is no evidence of significant adverse reactions to naloxone. Administering naloxone in cases of opioid overdose can cause withdrawal symptoms when the person is dependent on opioids; this is uncomfortable without being life threatening. The risk that someone overdosing on opioids will have a serious adverse reaction to naloxone is far less than their risk of dying from overdose. Naloxone works if a person has opioids in their system and has no harmful effect if opioids are absent. Naloxone should be given to any person who shows signs of an opioid overdose or when an overdose is suspected.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.drugabuse.gov/publications/naloxone-opioid-overdose-life-saving-science&quot;&amp;gt;Source - drugabuse.gov&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;hr/&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Additional Sources:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preventionsolutions.edc.org/services/resources/state-naloxone-access-laws&quot;&amp;gt;State Naloxone Access Laws - Education Development Center&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://doseofreality.mn.gov/need-help/naloxone.asp&quot;&amp;gt;General information on Naloxone - doseofreality.mn.gov&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，AFL-CIO保持着美國所有活躍工人罷工的最新地圖]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: if you&#39;re trying to avoid
crossing picket lines this should aid you greatly.</p> <p><a
href="https://aflcio.org/strike-map">Strike Map</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/risckt/ysk_that_the_aflcio_keeps_an_updated_map_of_all/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/risckt/ysk_that_the_aflcio_keeps_an_updated_map_of_all/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 19:34:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: if you&amp;amp;#39;re trying to avoid crossing picket lines this should aid you greatly.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://aflcio.org/strike-map&quot;&amp;gt;Strike Map&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：白色手杖並不是只有全盲的人才會使用。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：</p> <p>全白的手杖可以被用於
任何視力障礙者都可以使用。它們經常被用作向他人發出的信號。我的
我的父親是法律上的盲人，但一般不需要手杖來行走。
然而，他在外面用它來使過馬路更容易....。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfyrub/ysk_white_canes_arent_only_used_by_fully_blind/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rfyrub/ysk_white_canes_arent_only_used_by_fully_blind/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 19:34:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Fully white canes can be used by any visually impaired person. They are often used as a signal to others. My dad is legally blind, but doesn&amp;amp;#39;t need the cane to generally walk around. However, he uses it outside to make crossing the street easier. In most places, you are required to stop for people with a white cane (or guide dog).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also, white canes with a red tip are for people who are deaf blind.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know this was posted 6 years ago, but I saw some thread of people arguing about if a person with a white cane could see someone in front of them. Sometimes they can !&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：鋁不是除臭劑的成分]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：除臭劑和止汗劑是兩回事。
不同的東西。止汗劑通常含有鋁這一成分。
除臭劑，在大多數情況下，不包含。我看到人們購買更昂貴的
品牌的除臭劑，因爲標籤上說它不含鋁....。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rjxrki/ysk_aluminum_is_not_an_ingredient_in_deodorants/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rjxrki/ysk_aluminum_is_not_an_ingredient_in_deodorants/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 17:45:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Deodorant and antiperspirant are two different things. Antiperspirants usually contain aluminum as an ingredient. Deodorants, for the most part, do not. I’m seeing people buy the more expensive brand of deodorant, because the label says it’s aluminum free. Aluminum was never an ingredient in deodorant to begin with, don’t pay extra for “Aluminum free” deodorant. If anything, pay extra for the Aluminum free antiperspirants. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goodhousekeeping.com/beauty/anti-aging/a37272089/is-deodorant-aluminum-bad-for-you/&quot;&amp;gt;source&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/health/what-to-know-about-aluminum-in-deodorant&quot;&amp;gt;source2&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，你在網上找到的相當多的建議只適用於美國。特別是帶有文化成分的建議幾乎不具有普遍性。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：在這個星球上，並不是每個地方都有相同的社會或法律規範來辭去你的工作或組建公司。
辭職、買車或撰寫簡歷的社會或法律規範不盡相同。
簡歷。因此，請確保用你自己的語言和來自你自己國家的消息來源來仔細檢查。
你自己的國家的消息來源。使用常識，並嘗試將你的想法與你的國家聯繫起來。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rjkjq5/ysk_that_a_fair_amount_of_advice_you_find_online/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rjkjq5/ysk_that_a_fair_amount_of_advice_you_find_online/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 14:39:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Not every place on this planet has the same social or legal norms for quitting your job, buying a car or formating a CV. So make sure to double check with a source in your own language and from your own country. Use common sense, and try to relate what you read in thus sub to expercieas from your life before taking any advice at face value.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，無限制的PTO/Vacation不是一項福利，儘管在招聘過程中，它經常被公司作爲一個賣點。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：在傳統的PTO套餐中，每年有固定的天數。
在傳統的PTO套餐中，每年有固定的天數，你的休假時間在每個發薪期都會被累積。
基本上創造了一個假期銀行。有些公司甚至會讓你將一定數量的休假時間
一些公司甚至會讓你將一定數量的天數結轉到下一年......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rjnkl2/ysk_that_unlimited_ptovacation_is_not_a_perk_even/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rjnkl2/ysk_that_unlimited_ptovacation_is_not_a_perk_even/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 08:47:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: in a traditional PTO package with a set number of days per year, your vacation time is accrued each payroll period essentially creating a bank of days off. Some companies will even let you carry over a certain amount of days into the following year (although that is becoming increasingly rare these days). If you are allowed 3 weeks per year and you are allowed to carry over 1 week per year, over the course of 5 years, you could build up a pretty substantial amount of accrued PTO. If you leave the company, they have to make you whole… in other words, that company is required to pay back all your accrued vacation time at the end of your employment. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, with an unlimited vacation policy, no vacation time is accrued at any point throughout the year. So if you had a really stressful year which didn’t allow you to take PTO and the company lays you off in December, you receive nothing. In the 3 week PTO example, the company would have to comp you almost 3 weeks of accrued vacation time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also, there is a psychological component in play as well. If employees are given unlimited PTO, most take less time off throughout any given year. If a company says you HAVE to take 3 weeks this year (no carryover), you’re going to plan out that time off. If unlimited, you always think that you’ll get around to planning time off but then that always gets delayed. As one who can speak from experience in my current company, I make sure to assign myself X number of days off per year and track to that. Believe me, it helps.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just remember, a lot of companies are not “cool” or progressive with these perks that make them seem more attractive, they are usually tactics that somehow benefit their bottom lines in the end.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(Seeing a lot of comments about policies outside of US. Apologies, I should have clarified that all my experience is within US based companies. I am not surprised for a second that other countries take better care of their workforce)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，送餐公司不僅收取送餐費，而且還擡高菜單價格，收取服務費、最小推車費等等。平均而言，35美元的食物成本在美國的外賣應用程序上要花費55美元以上]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：你可以通過更多的信息來省錢
你可以通過更多瞭解食品配送費用來節省開支。你經常看到的那些 "免費送貨 "的廣告，實際上是指 "沒有送貨費"。
你經常看到的那些 "免費送貨 "的廣告，實際上是指 "沒有送貨費"。還有15-20%的服務費，他們
他們擡高菜單價格，並增加激增費用和最低購物車費用。銷售...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rjl2f5/ysk_that_food_delivery_companies_not_only_charge/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rjl2f5/ysk_that_food_delivery_companies_not_only_charge/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 05:40:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: You can save money by being more informed about food delivery fees. Those ads you see all the time for “free delivery” really mean “no delivery fee.” There’s also 15-20% service fees, they inflate menu prices, and add surge fees and minimum cart fees. Sales taxes are also calculated differently from app to app! One item that’s $10 on the menu could very well be $17 on a delivery app. I usually avoid these fees by either 1. Picking up the food myself or 2. Using a food delivery aggregator like FoodBoss or MealMe. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foodboss.net/&quot;&amp;gt;Foodboss&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; has a website, but only operates in a few cities and compares 2 major services. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.apple.com/us/app/mealme-doordash-grubhub-etc/id1460140965&quot;&amp;gt;MealMe&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; works in every city and compares all the apps, but is only on iOS. Whatever you choose, make sure to always tip!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲寵物是一個可怕的禮物。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK: 照顧寵物是一項巨大的工作。
大量的工作。節後，動物收容所經常充斥着不需要的動物。
</p> <p>如果你想讓你的朋友們知道你在做什麼，那麼你就會知道你在做什麼。</p> <p>如果有人想養寵物，請給他們玩具或食物。
他們的玩具或食物來代替。他們可以自己去挑選動物....。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rjd476/ysk_that_a_pet_is_a_terrible_gift/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rjd476/ysk_that_a_pet_is_a_terrible_gift/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 20:40:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Caring for a pet is an enormous amount of work. Animal shelters are often flooded with unwanted animals after the holidays as people figure this out. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If someone wants a pet, give them toys or treats instead. They can pick out an animal on their own. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please don&amp;amp;#39;t give someone a puppy because it looks like they need one. Animals aren&amp;amp;#39;t for everyone. They may not have the time, resources or living situation to support it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If your child wants a pet, bring them to a shelter to pick one out instead. Also be ready to care for it when your child slacks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你的衣櫃推拉門很難移動嗎？你有沒有給它上過潤滑油？]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>我們的房子有30多年的歷史了，大多數
櫥櫃的滑動門都很難打開和關閉。我看到一個視頻，顯示
技巧，他們用凡士林（Vaseline）來潤滑門。
他們用凡士林來潤滑門，現在（2年後）它們仍然可以滑動...。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rj56k7/ysk_is_your_sliding_closet_door_hard_to_move_have/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rj56k7/ysk_is_your_sliding_closet_door_hard_to_move_have/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 16:44:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Our house is 30+ years old and most the sliding closet doors were hard to open and close. I saw a video showing household tips &amp;amp;amp; tricks and they used petroleum jelly (Vaseline) to lubricate the doors and now (2 years later) they still slide along effortlessly. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You have to be tall enough to reach the top of the door. There are usually a two brackets up on top with a small wheel that rides along a rail. If you can&amp;amp;#39;t see it you can move your door back &amp;amp;amp; forth slowly and feel around with your finger until you come across a little wheel spinning. Take some petroleum jelly on the end of your finger and touch it to the wheel as you move the door slowly. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The wheel will spread the jelly on the rail and use it up, which is what you want to happen. You should  have to use about 3 dabs to cover the rail &amp;amp;amp; wheel really well. Move the door as far as you can one way then the other. Repeat with the other bracket. Then repeat on the two brackets on the other door. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When you are done with the jelly just use the door handle to move the doors back &amp;amp;amp; forth as far as you can about a dozen times. This makes sure the lubricant is spread the entire length of the rails. You should already notice how easily it is gliding along. If not, then you have other problems. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: A sliding door has moving pieces just like hinges move on swinging doors and need lubrication. Most people don&amp;amp;#39;t think about lubricating the moving pieces because they are hidden. You won&amp;amp;#39;t believe how easily some will open &amp;amp;amp; shut afterwards.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：快餐業的可怕之處]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：你可以通過避免快餐工作來拯救你自己的許多痛苦
你可以避免從事快餐工作，我將告訴你發生在你身上的故事。
我告訴你一些食物的故事，會讓你不想再去那裏喫飯。
<p>&#x200B;</p> <p>作爲一個做過無數快餐工作的人，...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rivgly/ysk_the_horrors_of_the_fast_food_industry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rivgly/ysk_the_horrors_of_the_fast_food_industry/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 09:40:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: You can save yourself a lot of misery by avoiding fast food jobs, and the stories I will tell you about what happened to some of the food will make you not want to eat there anymore.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As someone who has worked numerous fast food jobs, I can tell you these are some of the absolute worst working conditions in America. I have worked at Popeye&amp;amp;#39;s, Jack in the Box, and Burger King. Do you like being tremendously under-compensated for your work? Then fast food is for you. Popeye&amp;amp;#39;s paid $10/hr, Burger King paid $9.50, Jack in the Box paid $9. Now imagine you work an 8 hour shift at Jack in the Box and come away with $70 for your efforts. They&amp;amp;#39;re making $70 in sales &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;within 100 seconds.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; Seriously, it takes them 2-3 sales to earn what you get paid over an entire 8 hour shift. The pay is insulting and impossible to live off of.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Oh, and that&amp;amp;#39;s not all. While the tasks may be &amp;amp;quot;easy&amp;amp;quot;, they are CONSTANT. Imagine making dozens and dozens and dozens of sandwiches in  a row, and the line never slows down or ceases. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;I have made food poorly out of spite, and so have my coworkers. You should know that if you join an already long line, thus putting more stress on grossly underpaid workers, they may make your food poorly out of frustration.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; And that&amp;amp;#39;s not all. Most fast food places don&amp;amp;#39;t offer a break. You&amp;amp;#39;re expected to work 8 hours straight, only getting to rest when the line stops.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And that&amp;amp;#39;s not all either. The conditions are poor. You&amp;amp;#39;re surrounded by multiple fryers, causing the air in the restaurant to get hot and humid, causing you to sweat. Not only that, but the air is filled with grease and you will feel gross by the end of your shift. Not to mention that eating the unhealthy food on a daily basis can lead to weight gain and health problems. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Not here&amp;amp;#39;s another kicker. Because you are working in a low-paying industry that will basically hire anyone, you are going to meet some bad people.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; I worked with a man who would literally clock in, go to the manager&amp;amp;#39;s office (This was the overnight so there was no manager there), and just go to sleep. Then he&amp;amp;#39;d wake up, call his girlfriend, and start screaming at her. This was a nightly occurrence. Another guy I worked with frequently went to the bathroom to do meth and crack. He was homeless, spent his checks on drugs, and would get so high he would spend the entire shift talking to himself. He called women &amp;amp;quot;Skynet&amp;amp;quot; and said he needed to take them out, and asked me where to get a gun. Another woman and her boyfriend quit after his repeated abuse. There are plenty of bad people in fast food.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Ok, ok, I get it, you don&amp;amp;#39;t care about the working conditions. All you want is a decent meal. Let me tell you about the things I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen sandwich buns dropped on the floor, and instead of throwing them away, the employee will continue to make the sandwich with those buns. I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen entire buckets of raw chicken dropped onto the ground, only to be thrown in the fryer instead of the garbage. I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen swarms and swarms of flies in the kitchen, both at Popeye&amp;amp;#39;s and Burger King. Most of the time, employees didn&amp;amp;#39;t wear gloves, they made the food with their bare hands. Those are just a few examples, and I&amp;amp;#39;m sure I could think of more if I tried.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你有一隻貓，並且一直在半夜醒來，這可能不是失眠。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：這可能只是你的貓是一個可愛的混蛋。
</p> <p>在過去的一年半里，我一直在半夜醒來。
在過去的一年半里，我不斷地在半夜醒來，被嚇得睜大了眼睛。我以爲我的失眠症已經翻轉了 --
沒有。(我通常是難以入睡的類型)原來我的貓...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/riqjic/ysk_if_you_have_a_cat_and_keep_on_waking_up_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/riqjic/ysk_if_you_have_a_cat_and_keep_on_waking_up_in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 07:41:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: it might just be your cat being a loveable jerk.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For the past year and a half, I kept waking up in the middle of the night, wide awake startled. I thought my insomnia had flipped- nope. (I usually have the hard to fall asleep type) Turns out my cat just smacks my face in the middle of the night or bites my nose or toes when he is lonely or cold to wake me up. Caught him a couple of times, and now that I have gotten a bigger blanket that covers my head and feet, it doesn&amp;amp;#39;t happen anymore.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：談論你的工資並不違法，你應該這樣做，因爲這更有可能使你獲得更好的工資/薪水。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：圍繞討論你的工資/薪水的恥辱是不可能的。
僱主想要利用同工不同酬的優勢，對你的工資/薪水進行討論，這是毫無道理的，是由僱主驅動的。
僱主想利用同樣的工作向僱員支付不同的金額。你完全有權利
你有權利討論你的工資，並可能受到法律的保護，這取決於...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rinvl6/ysk_talking_about_your_wages_is_not_against_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rinvl6/ysk_talking_about_your_wages_is_not_against_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 04:46:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: the stigma around discussing your wages/salary is unjustified and is driven by employers wanting to take advantage of paying employees different amounts for the same work. You have every right to discuss your wages and may be protected by law depending on what country/ state you are in.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：某人在邪教中的跡象]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：嗯，2021年教會了我，它非常
很容易被洗腦進入邪教。你知道這些跡象嗎？1. 領袖是
如果你不允許批評你的領袖，即使批評是真實的。
批評是真實的，那麼你可能是在一個邪教中。2. 2.團體...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rijkbx/ysk_signs_someone_is_in_a_cult/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rijkbx/ysk_signs_someone_is_in_a_cult/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 03:40:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Well 2021 taught me that it’s very easy to get brainwashed into a cult. 
Do you know the signs?
1. The leader is the ultimate authority
If you’re not allowed to criticize your leader, even if the criticism is true, you’re probably in a cult.
2. The group suppresses skepticism
If you’re only allowed to study your organization through approved sources, you’re probably in a cult. Cults view critical thinking as an infectious disease and every effort is made to suppress it. Doubting members are encouraged to isolate themselves from outside influences and focus solely on the doctrine of the cult
4. The group is paranoid about the outside world
5. The group relies on shame cycles
6. The leader is above the law 
7. The group uses “thought reform” methods
If your serious questions are answered with cliches, you’re probably in a cult.
8. The group is elitist
If your group is the solution for all the world’s problems, you’re probably in a cult.
Cults see themselves as the enlightened, chosen, and elect organization tasked with radically transforming individual lives and the entire world.
9. Tell you to stay away from friends and family with different views.
10. No financial transparency&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 超速行駛幾乎從來不值得冒險。在60英里的車程中，時速90英里而不是70英里，只能爲你節省11分鐘。在10英里的車程中，它將爲你節省不到2分鐘。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：超速是非法的，而且很危險。它
它幾乎不能爲你節省任何時間，卻極大地增加了事故的風險。
傷害和法律後果。順着交通流走是最安全的。
而且發生任何問題的風險要低得多。</p>...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rilppc/ysk_speeding_almost_never_is_worth_the_risk_on_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rilppc/ysk_speeding_almost_never_is_worth_the_risk_on_a/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:41:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Speeding is illegal and dangerous. It barely saves you any time while dramatically increasing the risk of accidents, injuries, and legal consequences.  Going with the flow of traffic is the safest and has much lower risk of any trouble. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://mindyourdecisions.com/blog/2011/09/30/how-much-time-does-speeding-save/&quot;&amp;gt;How much time does speeding save?&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，大多數人都誤解了 "下雨機率 "的實際含義；50%的下雨機率並不意味着那天有50%的機會會下雨。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：因爲它是一個常見的錯誤觀念
這可能會影響我們如何安排我們的一天。</p> <p>用簡單的術語來說。50%的機會
意思是說，預計某個地區有50%的地方會下雨。
</p> <p>計算降水概率的公式是......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/riqpw9/ysk_that_most_people_misunderstand_what_chance_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/riqpw9/ysk_that_most_people_misunderstand_what_chance_of/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 22:41:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: because its a common misperception that can affect how we organize our day. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In simplistic terms: 50% chance of rain means that it is expected that 50% of a certain area is expected to see rain.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The formula to calculate Precipitation Chance (%) = Confidence of Precipitation Developing x Percent of Area Affected.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If the confidence level is 100% then a 30% chance of rain means that 30% of the coverage area will see precipitation. If the confidence level is 50% and only 40% of the coverage area will see precipitation, then the math is (0.50 x 0.40) x 100 = 20 or 20% chance of rain. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Check out more: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nwahomepage.com/weather/weather-101/weather-101-what-does-a-30-chance-of-rain-really-mean/amp/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.nwahomepage.com/weather/weather-101/weather-101-what-does-a-30-chance-of-rain-really-mean/amp/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你習慣於從一個地方的幾個員工那裏獲得交易或折扣，這並不意味着你有權每次都從所有人那裏獲得。如果你說你習慣於從經理那裏得到上述優惠，那麼你就是在坑害那些一直爲你提供服務的員工。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：他們在幫你的忙，但這並不意味着其他員工會幫你。
並不意味着其他員工會這樣做。如果你逼得太緊，你就不會
你不會再從那些員工那裏得到你的交易，而且你很可能會被
你很可能會危及他們的就業，所以請閉上你的嘴，並...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rifffo/ysk_if_youre_used_to_getting_a_deal_or_discount/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rifffo/ysk_if_youre_used_to_getting_a_deal_or_discount/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 17:47:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: They&amp;amp;#39;re doing you a favour but it doesn&amp;amp;#39;t mean other employees will. And if you push too hard, you won&amp;amp;#39;t get your deal from those employees anymore, and you could very well be jeopardizing their employment there, so just keep your mouth shut and be happy with what you get.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：當你在工作中進行績效評估時，你不應該爲想要談判薪酬而感到內疚]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：我最近離開了一份工作，因爲我的老闆
我最近離開了一份工作，因爲我的老闆拒絕給我加薪，儘管我在兩年的績效評估中達到了所有的目標。
我最近離開了一份工作，因爲我的老闆拒絕給我加薪，儘管我在兩年的績效評估中達到了所有的目標。他甚至讓我爲要求加薪而感到內疚。
他甚至讓我爲要求加薪而感到內疚，說我很幸運能擁有這個職位，而且...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ridzij/ysk_you_shouldnt_feel_guilty_for_wanting_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ridzij/ysk_you_shouldnt_feel_guilty_for_wanting_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 14:41:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: I recently left a job because my boss refused to increase my salary even though I had met every target set over two years of performance reviews. He even made me feel guilty for asking for a salary increase saying that I was lucky to have the position and that there were plenty of other people out there that would love the opportunity I had. At the end of the day, if a company is growing and you are contributing to that growth, you should never feel guilty for knowing your worth and asking for a salary increase. If your manager can&amp;amp;#39;t see your worth, there will always be another company that will be able to.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: I recently changed jobs and got a 20% payrise - sent my boss an email after I left my previous job saying &amp;amp;quot;thanks for not believing in me and making me realise that others did&amp;amp;quot; lol&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：記住這個聖誕節，如果有人爲你買了一份25美元的禮物，而他們賺的是最低工資，他們付出了2-3個小時的生命來給你買這個禮物。要謙虛，禮物不一定要花很多錢纔有價值。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：朋友或家人可能經歷了艱難的一年，可能爲我付出了很多努力/思考。
你的朋友或家人可能度過了艱難的一年，他們可能爲你的禮物付出了很多努力/思考，所以即使可能不是幾百美元，也要記得善待他們。
</p> </div><!
SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rie4ga/ysk_remember_this_christmas_if_someone_buys_a_25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rie4ga/ysk_remember_this_christmas_if_someone_buys_a_25/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 12:50:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Friends or family might have had a tough year and might have put a lot of effort/thought into your gift so even though it may not be hundreds of dollars, remember to be kind!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK如果你已經更新了你的iPhone iOS 15或更大，並且討厭底部的搜索欄，你可以點擊搜索欄左邊的AA，將搜索欄移回頂部。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>在底部看不到欄杆是很痛苦的，因爲你已經習慣了它在頁面的頂部。
因爲你已經習慣了它在頁面的頂部，這就是爲什麼YSK的這個技巧！希望它能幫助你。
希望能有所幫助。</p> </div><!--SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ri5z9l/ysk_if_youve_updated_your_iphone_ios_15_or/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ri5z9l/ysk_if_youve_updated_your_iphone_ios_15_or/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 07:10:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Aggravating not seeing the bar at the bottom because you’re so use to it being on the top of the page is why YSK this trick! Hope it helps.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你更新到最新版本的iOS 15，不喜歡Safari瀏覽器中生活在用戶界面底部的搜索欄，你可以點擊 "aA "符號，將其移回頂部。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：有些人不喜歡這種變化，而且不知道有一個回到location的選項。
不知道有一個選項可以返回到傳統的佈局。這個小
這個小提示將允許你在兩種佈局之間來回切換，並使你能夠自己選擇。
you to choose for yourself.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhxvsx/ysk_if_you_updated_to_the_latest_version_of_ios/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhxvsx/ysk_if_you_updated_to_the_latest_version_of_ios/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 23:36:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Some people don’t like the change and don’t know that there’s an option to return to the legacy layout.  This little tip will allow you to toggle back and forth between the layouts and will empower you to choose for yourself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲吼叫、尖叫、罵人等是不正常的，而且很少存在於健康的關係中。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：如果你像我一樣，大喊大叫是你家裏唯一的溝通方式。
是你家裏唯一的溝通方式。許多人可能沒有意識到的是
這種行爲的影響對一個人的自尊、對人際關係的看法、對人際關係的看法、對人際關係的看法、對人際關係的看法都會產生長期的影響。
自尊心、對人際關係的看法、心理健康（負面的核心自我評價）。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhxqn1/ysk_that_yelling_screaming_namecalling_etc_is_not/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhxqn1/ysk_that_yelling_screaming_namecalling_etc_is_not/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 21:40:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: If you&amp;amp;#39;re like me, yelling was the only form of communication in your household. What many may not realize is the impact of that kind of behavior has long term effects on one&amp;amp;#39;s self esteem, view of relationships, mental health (negative core self beliefs, trauma, PTSD/CPTSD, anxiety, depression, etc etc) and needs as a person. Thats why its important to stop the cycle and learn to communicate properly. Healing is definitely possible.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It doesn&amp;amp;#39;t matter how well they treat you after or how sincerely they apologize. It doesn&amp;amp;#39;t matter if they are your parents or guardians. This is not normal healthy behavior. Healthy relationships involve talking about problems and working things out. There is no hurtful name-calling or blaming things on the other person. If they are willing to call you names to get a rise out of you on purpose, how do you think that will work out with children or years down the line?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Its hard enough to find a relationship, I get it, but yelling and screaming happen when there is not enough healthy communication. 9/10 times situations that involve yelling or screaming could be solved by a calm, emotionally mature, and honest conversation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you know you do this, own it. Talk to a therapist about why and work on it. You will be so much happier and healthier when you can communicate your feelings through talking rather than the less effective and more hurtful mode of verbal violence&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，如果你在餐廳的等待時間比你想的要長，那麼女主人簡直就是這棟樓裏最不值得被罵的人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：餐廳女主人的首要目標是儘快爲你的聚會安排座位。
餐館女主人的首要目標是儘可能快地安排你的聚會。這符合她自己的最佳利益
爲了她自己的利益，她會讓你直接進入餐廳，所以請你放心，如果她有什麼需要幫助的地方，她會幫助你。
如果她能做什麼來減少您的等待時間，請放心。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rht67a/ysk_that_if_your_wait_at_a_restaurant_is_longer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rht67a/ysk_that_if_your_wait_at_a_restaurant_is_longer/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 18:40:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: The primary goal of the hostess at a restaurant is to seat your party as quickly as possible. It is in her own best interest to move you right on through to the dining room, so please be assured that if there was anything she can do to lower your wait time, she would do it. She does not deserved to be yelled at because your wait is 15 minutes longer than you expected. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Pretty much every restaurant is woefully understaffed right now. Those that survived the last couple of years are trying to operate as lean as possible. Until the restaurant industry has time to recover, this is likely to remain the case. Even then, I imagine they will have a tough time attracting enough workers to become fully staffed unless they make dramatic improvements to how their employees are compensated. The hostess that you are taking your frustrations out on is one of, if not the lowest paid, employees in the restaurant, and in many cases it is their very first job. With the staffing situation the way it is now, she is very likely having to bus tables, answer the phone, pack to-go orders, and do cleanliness checks on the restrooms, as well as manage the waitlist and coordinate the seating of diners. On top of that, she is going to be the first one to get grief from her managers when customers start to pile up waiting to be seated.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The hostess at a restaurant cannot seat you if there isn’t a table available for you. It’s as simple as that. Just because you see an empty table, or a dozen empty tables, doesn’t mean that there are enough servers on duty to work those tables. The hostess cannot put you at a table that doesn’t have a server assigned to it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you MUST yell at someone, first of all, get some psychiatric help at the first opportunity, but until then maybe yell at other diners who loiter for an hour after their meal is finished. Or yell at the manager, who at least to some degree has some control over how the restaurant is staffed at any given time. Maybe write a scathing email or make an irate phone call to the corporate office, if it’s a chain, or the owner if it’s privately owned, and insist that they raise wages or do whatever they need to do to attract more staff.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please, if you are not capable of being patient and showing a little bit of grace, please just eat at home. You never know the battles someone else is fighting in their life, and your harsh words at that particular time may have an impact that on them that you never intended.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：無論你的工作場所如何推崇 "家庭文化"--記住，他們不是你的朋友，它仍然是一個工作場所。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：我的女朋友學到了這一點，她很難受--她在陽光下爲創業公司工作了每一個小時。
她爲一家初創公司工作了每一個小時，當她不工作的時候
會以社交身份與他們共度晚間。她去年被解僱了，原因是
因爲公司有現金流問題，他們所有人都停止了......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhnerx/ysk_no_matter_how_much_your_workplace_pushes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhnerx/ysk_no_matter_how_much_your_workplace_pushes/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 12:43:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: my gf learned this the hard - she worked every hour under the sun for a startup and when she wasn&amp;amp;#39;t working would spend evenings with them in a social capacity. She got fired last year due to the company having cash flow issues and all of them stopped responding to her messages. She put so much work into trying to make the company successful and sacrificed other parts of her life for them, but they didn&amp;amp;#39;t really give a shit about her. I&amp;amp;#39;m not saying go around and be a dick to people for no reason, but it&amp;amp;#39;s better to build relationships outside of work or in places where there aren&amp;amp;#39;t any power imbalances or incentives to screw people over.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK不同類型的性虐待/騷擾/攻擊行爲]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK是因爲我最近剛被性騷擾了。
我想說的是，我最近被性騷擾了，而且沒有得到公正的對待。
所以這裏有一些不同的類型，如果不是所有的類型，只是沒有人和我一樣受到傷害。
所以這裏有一些，如果不是所有不同的類型，只是沒有人遭受和我一樣的痛苦，請務必聯繫......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhh0fc/ysk_the_different_types_of_sexual_abuse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhh0fc/ysk_the_different_types_of_sexual_abuse/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 08:36:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;why YSK is because i recently just got sexually harassed , and no justice came from it . all because people didn’t seem like it was “ a big deal “
so here’s some if not all the different types , just so nobody has to suffer the same as me . make sure to reach out to someone you love or trust :))&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;• rape
• attempted rape 
• unwanted touching or physical contact 
• unwelcome sexual advances
• unwanted sexual photos , texts , emails , etc . ( not just nudes )
• unwanted flashing 
• making conditions of employment or advancement dependent on sexual favors, either explicitly or implicitly.
• remarks of a sexual nature about a persons clothing , personal behavior , clothes , or body .
• purposely brushing up against a person 
• following or standing too close to a person on purpose .
• cat calling
• spreading sexual rumors 
•  taking photos of a person without their consent , especially private parts ( this is what happened to me , he took a photo of my ass and my teacher’s breasts )&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;all types of harassment is important and serious , please never think that it’s not . 
if i missed any on the list please tell me and i’ll add them !&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK在雨中使用你適當的大燈]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: because we can’t see you in our
mirrors. DRLs don’t count.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhcqkz/ysk_to_use_your_proper_headlights_in_the_rain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhcqkz/ysk_to_use_your_proper_headlights_in_the_rain/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 05:51:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: because we can’t see you in our mirrors. DRLs don’t count.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 上癮的循環很容易被預想（你的舊癮第一次出現在你腦海中的時刻）重新點燃。接下來是沉思、決心、行動、維持，最後是復發。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：你可以通過注意到以下幾點來打破成癮性
早期的跡象。如果你可以的話，當你發現你的觸發點時，告訴你的伴侶你的觸發點是什麼，這樣他們就可以和你一起注意。
</p> <p>這正是我個人上癮的模式。
這正是我個人上癮的模式，它完美地遵守了......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhfks8/ysk_the_addiction_cycle_is_easily_reignited_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rhfks8/ysk_the_addiction_cycle_is_easily_reignited_by/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 04:57:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: You can break addictions by noticing the early signs. If you can, tell your partner what your trigger is when you find it so that they can be on the lookout with you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is exactly the pattern my personal addiction follows, and it adheres perfectly to the typical model researchers have found. Does it sound familiar?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bonus point for those who made it this far! Advertisements are artificial precontemplation triggers, targeted at ex-addicts.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://addictionresource.com/treatment/stages/&quot;&amp;gt;https://addictionresource.com/treatment/stages/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：男性和女性的中風症狀是不同的]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：我們都被告知要注意什麼？
我們都被告知，當某人發生中風時要注意什麼，但男性和女性實際上有不同的症狀，值得了解。
</p> <p><strong>在中風期間，男性和女性都有不同的症狀，值得了解。
在中風期間，男性和女性通常都會報告出現這些跡象......。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rh93nx/ysk_stroke_symptoms_are_different_for_men_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rh93nx/ysk_stroke_symptoms_are_different_for_men_and/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 03:48:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: We all get told what to look out for when someone is having a stroke but men and women actually have different symptoms and they are worth knowing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;During a stroke, both men and women typically report these signs appearing suddenly:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Numbness or weakness in the face, arm or leg, especially on one side of the body&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Confusion, trouble speaking or trouble understanding&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Trouble seeing in one or both eyes&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Difficulty walking, dizziness, or loss of balance or coordination&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Severe headache with no known cause&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Women, however, may also report these symptoms:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Hiccups&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Nausea&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Chest pain&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Fatigue&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Shortness of breath&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- A racing heartbeat&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s worth knowing in case a friend or a loved one is ever showing any of these signs as you need to act quickly!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK在涉及傷員的事件中，在周圍有很多人的情況下，幫助他們看管好自己的錢包和手機或他們所佩戴的任何貴重物品，或與他們在一起的人確認。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：在許多情況下，這些物品經常被其他人偷走。
</p> <p>不要把他們的物品放在你的口袋裏，除非你與死者有關係。
他們的物品放在你的口袋裏，除非你與該傷亡人員有關係。這可能
這可能會被認爲是你在偷東西。最好把它放在地板上......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgwtsg/ysk_in_an_incident_involving_a_casualty_in_public/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgwtsg/ysk_in_an_incident_involving_a_casualty_in_public/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 17:00:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: In many cases, these items are frequently stolen by other people who pretend to be helping.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Do not keep their items in your pocket unless you are related to that casualty. That may come off as you stealing it. It&amp;amp;#39;s best to leave it on the floor next to the casualty so everyone can see who picks up the wallet.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In a scenario where everyone is gathering around, no one would dare to pick up the casualty&amp;amp;#39;s wallet while it&amp;amp;#39;s very noticeable.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As someone living near a junction where the traffic is confusing and prone to accidents, people stealing money/valuables from the casualty has happened more times than I can count.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK開始爲小動物進入你的房子或汽車做準備]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：越來越冷了
天氣有時會把不受歡迎的客人帶到你的汽車和/或房子裏的溫暖和安全的地方。
和/或房子裏。它們變得飢腸轆轆，會以你的電線、絕緣體和軟管爲食。
造成昂貴的損害。有一輛2022年的MDX說警告......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgq73g/ysk_to_start_preparing_for_small_animals_entering/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgq73g/ysk_to_start_preparing_for_small_animals_entering/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 15:52:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: it’s getting colder and colder weather sometimes brings unwelcome guests into warm and safe spots in your car and/or house. They get hungry and will feed on your wires, insulation, and hoses causing expensive damage. Had a 2022 MDX come in saying warning lights were all on her brand new car. After inspecting it. I found the communication wire to be completely torn apart. Luckily I was able to fix it for less than $100, if not, it would have costed about $6K to replace being as that wire was part of the complete dash harness. However you handle rodents is entirely up to you but know that they can cause lots of damage; most of the time insurance companies and warranty companies will never back you up for that.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK "最低工資 "是法律允許的最低工資。"起始工資 "是僱主提供給新僱員的實際工資。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：我看到很多僱主現在把提供的最低工資稱爲
我看到很多僱主把提供的入門工資稱爲最低工資。雖然我認爲他們可以
我想他們是可以使用這些詞的，但如果在他們宣佈他們的最低工資時造成誤解，那就太可惜了。
當他們宣佈他們提高了最低工資時，這將是一種恥辱。A...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgmkhq/ysk_minimum_wage_is_the_lowest_wage_allowed_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgmkhq/ysk_minimum_wage_is_the_lowest_wage_allowed_by/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 14:38:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;WHY YSK: I see a lot of employers now calling the entry wage offered their &amp;amp;quot;minimum wage&amp;amp;quot;. While I suppose they are allowed to use those words, it would be a shame if it caused misunderstanding when they announce they &amp;amp;#39;raised their minimum wage&amp;amp;#39;. A raise in minimum wage is something currently being urged on government by many as a way to reduce poverty. A wage policy announced by a single employer is not enough.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你應該質疑你在網上看到的一切。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：有這麼多的視頻、圖片和
事實在互聯網平臺上。很多時候，這些視頻都是僞造的，或者是事實
很多時候，這些視頻都是僞造的，或者是將事實歸結到與圖片的原始目的無關的圖像上。
只要看一眼帖子上的評論，你就會發現，這些評論是多麼的......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgycx0/ysk_you_should_question_everything_you_see_online/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgycx0/ysk_you_should_question_everything_you_see_online/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 14:38:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: There are so many videos, images and facts on internet platforms. A lot of the time these videos are staged, or facts are attributed to an image that has no relation to the images original purpose. A glance at the comments on a post will show you just how many people lap it up without question.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The reason you should know is that it’s this blind belief that advertisers and scammers exploit daily. We are living in an age where companies have learnt how easy it is to manipulate us. By taking everything you see at face value you are opening yourself up to this manipulation. And basically opening up your wallet, and in some cases your values and belief systems.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It’s quick and easy to do a quick internet search about anything to find out if something is likely to be true. Don’t be one of the people who comment how impressed you are at a particular post because this just adds to the claim and makes it more difficult for others to determine if something is genuine. It should be obvious not to believe everything you see online but it seems like we have started to take that for granted and have forgotten that lately.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 有可能在同一批衣物中清洗你的白色和彩色。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：許多人把白色和深色的衣服分開洗，以防止染上白色。
衣服分開洗，以防止給白衣服上色，佔用額外的水和時間。
</p> <p><strong>如果你使用的是標有白色的洗衣粉，那麼你就會發現你的衣服是白色的。
</p> <p><strong>如果你使用標有 "對顏色安全 "的增白洗衣粉，並使用冷水洗滌</strong>，那麼大多數人都會選擇用冷水洗滌。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgly9i/ysk_its_possible_to_wash_your_whites_and_colors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgly9i/ysk_its_possible_to_wash_your_whites_and_colors/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 07:42:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Many people wash their whites and darks in seperate loads to prevent coloring their whites, using up extra water and time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;If you use a whitening laundry powder labeled &amp;amp;quot;Safe on colors&amp;amp;quot; AND wash using cold water&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, then most whites will stay white even when washing them with dark or colored clothes. I&amp;amp;#39;ve done this many times using Oxi-clean White Revive and it&amp;amp;#39;s always worked. I believe there&amp;amp;#39;s other brands with similar products.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just be careful not to wash clothes with heavy ink (e.g. Tie-dye or sharpie) in the same load as whites.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT: To clarify, the whitening powder isn&amp;amp;#39;t strictly necessary unless you want to use a whitener. A lot of people do, but if you don&amp;amp;#39;t, then you can skip it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你在美國，YSK--EBT和SNAP福利可以用來在網上訂購食品雜貨，以便送貨或在路邊取貨。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：在美國，使用這些福利的人有這種恥辱感。
使用這些福利的人，這使得一些人在申請時感到擔心。
這使得一些人擔心在第一時間申請。有些人害怕去排隊結賬，冒着被人評頭論足的風險。
說你是如何依靠......的。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgjo1d/ysk_if_you_are_in_the_us_ebt_and_snap_benefits/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rgjo1d/ysk_if_you_are_in_the_us_ebt_and_snap_benefits/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 07:42:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: There is this stigma in the US for people who use these benefits and this makes some people worried to apply in the first place. Some fear going to a checkout line and risk someone judging you or making a remark how you are &amp;amp;quot;relying on handouts&amp;amp;quot;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Although these people should just be ignored, it is still there and stopping people from getting food they need. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you&amp;amp;#39;ve ever worked a job, and paid taxes, you&amp;amp;#39;ve already contributed so don&amp;amp;#39;t feel bad. These benefits are a very GOOD thing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anyways, with the help of technology it&amp;amp;#39;s easy to shop online with EBT or SNAP and get curbside delivery, or you can even have your groceries delivered directly to your house.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ll provide a link that details all of the places you can use your benefits. I hope this can help someone who otherwise might not apply.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://foodstampsnow.com/list-of-grocery-stores-that-accept-ebt-online-for-delivery/&quot;&amp;gt;https://foodstampsnow.com/list-of-grocery-stores-that-accept-ebt-online-for-delivery/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK的短信 "741741 "將立即爲你聯繫危機諮詢師，只要你需要，他們就會與你溝通，而且對任何人都是免費的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：隨着假期的臨近，你應該知道。
你應該知道，如果你感到抑鬱，或有自殺傾向，或你需要有人
傾訴，<a href="https://www.crisistextline.org/">這是你可以利用的許多工具之一
</p> <p>你可以利用許多工具</p>。</p> <p>你被通緝，你...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/re9m7u/ysk_that_texting_741741_will_immediately_connect/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/re9m7u/ysk_that_texting_741741_will_immediately_connect/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 21:37:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: With the holidays approaching, you should know that if you are feeling depressed, or suicidal or you need someone to talk to, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crisistextline.org/&quot;&amp;gt;this is one of many tools&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; that are available to you. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You are wanted, you belong, and the world is a better place with you in it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：用現金/借記卡支付實際上是在補貼其他用信用卡支付的顧客。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：信用卡網絡對其服務收取1-3%的手續費。
辦理費，因此，零售商和餐館通常會提高價格，以補償大家的損失。
他們的價格對每個人來說都是一種補償。信用卡持卡人將獲得1-3%的返還
的現金返還或積分，因此，即使零售商提高價格，他們也...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/reuuum/ysk_paying_in_cashdebit_effectively_subsidizes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/reuuum/ysk_paying_in_cashdebit_effectively_subsidizes/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 21:37:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Credit card networks charge a 1-3% processing fee for their services, so retailers and restaurants often mark up their prices for everyone to compensate. Credit card holders will get 1-3% back in cashback or points, so even if a retailer raises prices, they effectively get the fair-market value price for the good. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cash payers, otoh, don&amp;amp;#39;t - so they end up paying 1-3% above the normal asking price to compensate for credit card users.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 冬天來了，給你的輪胎加滿油吧!]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：低溫會使輪胎中的空氣凝結。
你的輪胎，所以即使是那些看起來很好的冬季或全天候輪胎，你的汽車或卡車的
</p> <p>這將增加磨損。
</p> <p>這增加了磨損，影響了行駛，並改變了輪胎與溼滑路面的接觸方式。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rf953q/ysk_winter_is_here_top_up_your_tires/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rf953q/ysk_winter_is_here_top_up_your_tires/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 21:37:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Cold temperatures condense the air in your tires, so even those perfectly OK looking winter or all weather tires on your car or truck can actually be dangerously low.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This increases wear, affects ride, and changes how the tire contacts slippery surfaces, making it potentially much more dangerous on slippery roads for both you, and the other drivers around you if you lose control.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A tire gauge is a cheap investment, check them at least once a month during the cold months of the year, it&amp;amp;#39;ll also give you warning if you develop a slow leak!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>