<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[你应该知道的事]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Reddit小组 You Should Know 的热门内容]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 04:01:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[如果你喜歡用大量的香料做飯，當地的亞洲/印度/外國雜貨店往往有香料，價格和數量都比只賣麥考密克之類的傳統雜貨店低得多。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：用6美元我買了一大瓶芝麻。
種子。麥考密克的小瓶子差不多是4美元。
多花2美元就能買到50多倍的種子。他們還支持當地人
</p> <p>我用了一整瓶。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rropag/ysk_if_you_enjoy_cooking_with_lots_of_spices/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rropag/ysk_if_you_enjoy_cooking_with_lots_of_spices/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 03:42:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: For $6 I got a large bottle of sesame seeds. The tiny bottle of McCormick is almost $4. The quantity difference might be over 50x the seeds for an extra 2 dollars. They also support local people better than your regional chain.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I used an entire bottle of cumin and other Indian spices for 1 recipe of butter chicken totalling $10-$15 in spices. The Indian store near me sold near gallon sized bags of it for less than $10.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you like to cook, buy from them and then transfer extras into old glass jars for safe keeping since they don&amp;amp;#39;t usually come in resealable bags. It&amp;amp;#39;s a great way to save some money and try new fun products.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在爭論中利用別人的弱點來對付他們並不聰明]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：基本上，它是一個愚蠢的舉動
特別是當它是你身邊的人的時候，因爲它打破了你們之間的信任。
因爲它在一個完全不同的層面上打破了你們之間的信任。它導致人們不再向你傾訴
在你身上。不要這樣做，即使對方是你的朋友。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rrko0w/ysk_using_someones_vulnerability_against_them_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rrko0w/ysk_using_someones_vulnerability_against_them_in/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 01:49:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: basically it&amp;amp;#39;s a d*ck move to make, especially when it&amp;amp;#39;s someone close to you because it shatters the trust between you on a whole different level. It causes people to stop confiding in you. Don&amp;amp;#39;t do it, even if the other person is the one in the wrong.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你的谷歌搜索可以通過包括你不希望它找到的東西來嚴重改善。例如，搜索燒烤食譜--牛肉，就會剔除牛肉的結果。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：在尋找你想要的信息時，最困難的部分往往是擺脫你不想要的信息。
你想要的信息的最難部分是擺脫你不想要的信息。知道
這個技巧可以讓你更快地找到這些信息，並定製顯示的內容。
</p> <p>編輯：爲了清晰起見，添加減號將...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rrleto/ysk_that_your_google_searches_can_be_seriously/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rrleto/ysk_that_your_google_searches_can_be_seriously/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 00:43:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: often the hardest part of finding the information you want is getting rid of the information you don’t want. Knowing this trick can get you to that information a lot quicker and customise what is shown.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: for clarity, adding the minus sign will exclude that word from results.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK大多數兒童玩具在發貨時處於 "Try Me "模式，必須打開 "On "才能完全使用所有功能。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：能發出聲音的兒童玩具有一個嘗試的過程。
我模式，用於商店展示。如果你不把它轉到 "開"，大部分的短語和聲音就不能發揮作用。
和聲音將無法發揮作用。這對那些讓你嘗試的幼兒玩具來說尤其如此。
讓你在展示時嘗試它們。開/關/試我模式的按鈕是...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rrgmbe/ysk_most_kid_toys_are_shipped_in_a_try_me_mode/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rrgmbe/ysk_most_kid_toys_are_shipped_in_a_try_me_mode/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 21:42:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Kid toys that make sound have a try me mode for store display. If you don’t shift it to “On”, most of the phrases and sounds will not function. This is especially true for toddler toys that let you try them on display. The On/Off/Try Me mode buttons are usually next to the battery compartment.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你的銀行是一個比CoinStar更好的地方，可以把你的零錢變成有用的東西。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：我理解的是，在沃爾瑪的方便。
我理解沃爾瑪的機器很方便，但如果你也是附近銀行或信用社的成員，他們不應該對你用硬幣計數收取費用。
但如果你是附近銀行或信用社的成員，他們不應該收取費用，用機器來計算你的硬幣，並將其存入或給你。
他們不應該收取用機器清點硬幣的費用，並把它們存入或給你現金。CoinStar要麼...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rr0632/ysk_your_bank_is_a_better_place_than_a_coinstar/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rr0632/ysk_your_bank_is_a_better_place_than_a_coinstar/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 08:47:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: I understand the convenience of the machines in Walmart, but if you are a member of a bank or credit union also in your neighborhood, they shouldn’t charge a fee to count your coins with a machine and either deposit them or give you cash. CoinStar either charges a percentage or forces you to get a gift card at the store you’re in.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你的遺傳學可能使你在雜草叢生的時候容易發作精神病]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：很多人都會把解離或在興奮時聽到的聲音斥爲 "糟糕的旅行"。
很多人都會把解離或在興奮時聽到的聲音當作是 "糟糕的旅行"，但是
但實際上，它可能是一個孤立的<a
href="https://www.psychiatrictimes.com/view/cannabis-induced-psychosis-review">大麻...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rqqz56/ysk_your_genetics_can_predisposition_you_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rqqz56/ysk_your_genetics_can_predisposition_you_to/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 05:17:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: a lot of people will dismiss dissociation or hearing voices during a high as &amp;amp;quot;just a bad trip&amp;amp;quot; but it can actually be an isolated episode of &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychiatrictimes.com/view/cannabis-induced-psychosis-review&quot;&amp;gt;cannabis-induced psychosis (CIP)&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; or a precursor to mental illness.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;Recent research (see &amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.drugabuse.gov/publications/research-reports/marijuana/there-link-between-marijuana-use-psychiatric-disorders#akt1&quot;&amp;gt;AKT1 Gene Variations and Psychosis&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;) has found that people who use marijuana and carry a specific variant of the &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;AKT1&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; gene, which codes for an enzyme that affects dopamine signaling in the &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;striatum&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;, are at increased risk of developing psychosis&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;If you have 23andme or some other genome sequencing product, you can look up AKT1 and see if you have this marker.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4872423/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Specifically, you&amp;amp;#39;re looking to see if you have C/C genotype.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲存在着買賣成癮者的隱性經濟，人們因此而死亡。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>我在成癮治療領域工作了20年。
和YSK，在所有這些組織的背景中，有一個準合法的病人販賣經濟。
販賣病人的準法律經濟。一個涉及非營利組織
表面上是教育和支持公衆，然後轉身......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rqtp1u/ysk_that_there_is_a_hidden_economy_of_buying_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rqtp1u/ysk_that_there_is_a_hidden_economy_of_buying_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 01:36:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I have worked in addiction treatment for 20 years, and YSK that in the background of all of these organizations is a quasi-legal economy of patient trafficking. One involes non-profit organizations that ostensibly educate and support the public, then turn around and &amp;amp;quot;sell&amp;amp;quot; referrals to treatment centers for personal profit (sometimes laundered as &amp;amp;quot;you can buy advertising on our website&amp;amp;quot; or &amp;amp;quot;you can sponsor our events financially for a certain number of patients per quarter&amp;amp;quot;). This violates numerous ethical rules and means that the community organizations that claim to be working in the public interest, but some who benefit from the non-profit tax status also have thriving direct income from selling your loved ones into centers that may not be the right fit for their needs. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The other more publicized version are the internal and external &amp;amp;quot;treatment loops&amp;amp;quot; maintained between inpatient and outpatient centers. Essentially either one owner holds both centers, and they count on you relapsing in the lower level of care to send you back up to the higher level of care in and endless loop that ends in your death, or the inpatient facility partners with a series of poorly-run outpatient facilities or &amp;amp;quot;recovery homes&amp;amp;quot; that are either negligently or in some cases intentionally inviting relapse, then rushing you back through to the feeder system of inpatient care...is you survive. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Because this can contribute to the relapse and death of you or a loved one. America has a complicated and complex issue with addiction, but this aspect is a part of the problem, and is not nearly well-known enough and gets ignored when the federal government releases millions of dollars in new grants, that then sadly often go to those exact organizations that continue to prop up more of the same kinds of cyclical addiction factories. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please, do your own research and choose the centers that specialize in the kids of issues you or your loved one suffer from, and don&amp;amp;#39;t blindly take the word of community outreach personnel that may or may not have a vested financial interest in treatment failure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.natlawreview.com/article/addiction-treatment-facilities-patient-shuffling-scheme-exposed&quot;&amp;gt;Florida Addiction Treatment Scam&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：2022年的3G頻譜淘汰將影響某些設備]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：某些醫療設備、平板電腦。
智能手錶、車輛SOS服務、家庭安全系統和其他聯網產品。
產品可能正在使用3G網絡服務。不要忘記那些
當有線網絡出現問題時，使用手機連接作爲備用的設備。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rnsq1p/ysk_the_3g_spectrum_phaseout_in_2022_will_affect/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rnsq1p/ysk_the_3g_spectrum_phaseout_in_2022_will_affect/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 21:50:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Certain medical devices, tablets, smart watches, vehicle SOS services, home security systems, and other connected products may be using 3G network services. Don&amp;amp;#39;t forget about devices that use cellular connectivity as a back-up when a wired internet connection goes down. If the device is not labeled, contact the monitoring company or other service provider to confirm how the device connects and whether your device may be impacted.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[大多數零售商，特別是奢侈品牌，有一些商品是打折的，只是爲了讓你認爲你得到了便宜貨。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：爲了使其合法化，他們在網上以較高的價格出售。
他們在網上短時間內以較高的價格銷售，比如說一袋700美元，然後他們在賣場或以350美元的價格出售
他們把它放在賣場或以350美元的價格出售，並在標籤上打了個大大的五折。
</p> <p>他們從未爲主線商店或主...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rqhagw/ysk_that_most_retailers_especially_the_luxury/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rqhagw/ysk_that_most_retailers_especially_the_luxury/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 16:58:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;WHY YSK: To make this legal, they sell it online for a short period of time a higher price, let’s say $700 for a bag, then they put it in outlets or on sale for $350 and smack a big 50% off on the label. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They were never made for mainline stores or main collections. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sadly, there’s no way to tell which items they are unless you know someone who works on the inside.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如何用大蒜烹飪。你把大蒜切得越小，味道就越濃。切片的味道會比較淡，而糊狀的味道會最濃。你煮得越多，味道就會流失得越多。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：我知道有很多人總是說
"三倍於食譜建議 "的大蒜。但是，我看到他們只是把大蒜切成
大蒜切成毫米級的片狀，在他們的菜譜中。對......找到了問題所在。大多數情況下
大多數情況下，配方是好的，你只需要準備...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rqgygv/ysk_how_to_cook_with_garlic_the_tinier_you_mince/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rqgygv/ysk_how_to_cook_with_garlic_the_tinier_you_mince/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 16:58:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: I know so many people who always say “triple the recipe recommendation” for garlic. But then I see them just slicing garlic into millimeter slices in their recipe. Right.. found the problem. Most of the time the recipe is fine, you just have to prepare the garlic correctly in order to get the right amount of flavor you want. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The way you chop and cook garlic affects the strength of the flavor in your dish. If you mince garlic you will release much more flavor compared to slices. A paste will be even stronger (you get a paste by mincing first and then smearing it on the cutting board using a knife repeatedly) &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also, cooking garlic less will retain more of its flavor. If your garlic is being sautéed until brown, you won’t taste it as much. If you want a strong flavor make sure you add it late and keep it white.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.recipetips.com/kitchen-tips/t%E2%80%941263/all-about-garlic.asp&quot;&amp;gt;Here&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; is a link about this topic. Scroll down for more detailed info and graphics on what I’m talking about in this post!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在向災民或一般的食品銀行發送救濟物資時，盒裝牛奶常常被忽視。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：災區，如在
肯塔基州、阿肯色州、伊利諾伊州和周邊地區通常沒有電力。
鮮奶供應稀少。盒裝牛奶，如Gossner, Horizon, 或
盒裝牛奶，如Gossner、Horizon或Parmalat，貨架穩定，是一種急需的替代品。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rqfr96/ysk_when_sending_relief_supplies_to_disaster/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rqfr96/ysk_when_sending_relief_supplies_to_disaster/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 16:58:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Disaster areas, such as the ones in Kentucky, Arkansas, Illinois, and surrounding areas are usually without power, and fresh milk is in scarce supply. Boxed milk, such as Gossner, Horizon, or Parmalat are shelf stable, and a much needed alternative to fresh.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I remembered reading about this a while back, on a Reddit post regarding food banks. The thought came to me as I was watching news about a relief shipment headed to Kentucky, and saw cases of beer. The kids need shelf stable milk more than mom &amp;amp;amp; dad need beer...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你有一個新的年度決議，現在和今天就去做。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK : If you wait for 1st January 2022,
its just another form of procrastination delaying your wonderful journey, happy
new year everyone!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rq9enz/ysk_if_you_have_a_new_years_resolution_do_it_now/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rq9enz/ysk_if_you_have_a_new_years_resolution_do_it_now/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 14:41:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK :  If you wait for 1st January 2022, its just another form of procrastination delaying your wonderful journey, happy new year everyone!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，如果你在開會或打電話時及時醒來，你的聲音會讓你離開]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：如果你剛剛醒來，你有一個
早晨的聲音，無論你是否聽到它，通常其他人都能看出來。它
這可能使你看起來不那麼專業，特別是如果你在家裏工作。</p>
<p>我的建議是，在你上路之前，先跟着歌曲唱一唱。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rpt9i9/ysk_that_if_you_wake_up_just_in_time_for_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rpt9i9/ysk_that_if_you_wake_up_just_in_time_for_a/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 20:39:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: if you just wake up you have a morning voice and whether you hear it or not, usually other people can tell. It might make you seem less professional especially if you work from home. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My suggestion is to sing along to a song before you get on your first call, and usually that will warm up your vocal chords enough to get rid of your sleepy creaky voice.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;edit: I think a lot of people dislike this post because they’re conflating how things should be with how things are. When you work from home people don’t have all the same data as they do if they can see you, read your body language, and see how hard you’re working. They don’t know what kind of day you’ve had. All people have to go off of is what you type, how you sound, and what work you get done. I genuinely believe how you sound is important if you’re customer-facing. I’m trying to help you!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你是一個多雪氣候下的新房主，如果可以的話，最理想的是擁有各種不同類型的鏟子。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p><strong>爲什麼YSK：不是所有雪鏟都是
不是所有的雪鏟都是一樣的。有的鏟子是用來擡的，有的鏟子是用來推的，還有的鏟子是用來做的。
</p> <p>對於較小的降雪量，您將會很感激。
</p> <p>對於較小的降雪，你會喜歡有一個更寬的(30&quot;...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rpsvi7/ysk_if_you_are_a_new_homeowner_in_a_snowy_climate/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rpsvi7/ysk_if_you_are_a_new_homeowner_in_a_snowy_climate/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 19:51:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Why YSK: Not all snow shovels are created equal. There are shovels built to lift, shovels built to push, and those made to do both&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; (like the Head &amp;amp;amp; Shoulders of shovels).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For lighter snowfall, you will appreciate having a wider (30&amp;amp;quot; or 36&amp;amp;quot;) snow pusher that is lower profile and allows you to easily move light snow and cover more ground quickly.  These shovels are best in 3&amp;amp;quot; or less.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For the end of the driveway after the plow has come through, use a bucket style (or &amp;amp;quot;combination&amp;amp;quot;)  shovel to lift heavier and more compact snow that you need to lift &amp;amp;amp; carry to it&amp;amp;#39;s spot.  If there is big-time accumulation, you&amp;amp;#39;ll be happy to have a scooping shovel (similar to what you may see on a farm) that can more easily grab deep snow. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There are plenty of other designs as well for ergonomics,  bad backs and dual-hand placement and even one I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen with wheels, so do a little research to find whatever is right for you.  But my message is about owning &amp;amp;amp; having an assortment of 2-3 different shovels for different types of snow accumulation throughout the season.  Shoveling snow is wildly easier for me these days than my first year of homeownership when I just had one basic combination shovel I bought on the cheap.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：壁爐中的木火對室內空氣質量有極大的毒性，研究表明它們對我們的健康造成了多大的破壞，尤其是對婦女和兒童。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>與親人擠在可愛的暖爐旁的想法
的想法在文化上是如此根深蒂固，以至於人們很難接受它對健康的危害。
很難接受它對健康有多麼可怕。但是，健康風險是明確的。
木柴火的煙霧會損害你的呼吸系統。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rph9el/ysk_a_wood_fire_in_the_fireplace_is_extremely/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rph9el/ysk_a_wood_fire_in_the_fireplace_is_extremely/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 18:48:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The idea of huddling around a lovely warm fire with loved ones is so deeply and culturally ingrained that it can be very difficult to accept just how terrible it is for health. But the health risks are clear, and smoke from a wood fire damages your respiratory system and heart in a similar fashion to cigarette smoking. Light fires frequently enough and it can become much worse.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fireplace#Health_effects&quot;&amp;gt;Wikipedia&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; summary perfectly describes how bad it is:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With regard to adults, studies show that prolonged inhalation of &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wood_smoke&quot;&amp;gt;wood smoke&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; contributed to &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bronchitis#Chronic_bronchitis&quot;&amp;gt;chronic bronchitis&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, chronic interstitial &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lung_disease&quot;&amp;gt;lung disease&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pulmonary_arterial_hypertension&quot;&amp;gt;pulmonary arterial hypertension&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/w/index.php?title=Corpulmonale&amp;amp;amp;action=edit&amp;amp;amp;redlink=1&quot;&amp;gt;corpulmonale&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; (Pulmonary heart disease), and altered pulmonary immune defense mechanisms. While adverse effects on adults are notable, children appear to be at greatest risk. Many studies that focused specifically on RWC [Residential Wood Combustion] have concluded that young children living in homes heated by a wood-burning stove had a greater occurrence of moderate and severe chronic respiratory symptoms than children of the same age and sex who did not live in homes heated with a wood burning stove. Exposure of preschool children living in homes heated with wood burning stoves or in houses with open fireplaces yielded these effects: decreased pulmonary &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lung&quot;&amp;gt;lung&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; function in young &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Asthmatics&quot;&amp;gt;asthmatics&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;; increased incidence of acute &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bronchitis&quot;&amp;gt;bronchitis&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and severity/frequency of &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wheezing&quot;&amp;gt;wheezing&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Coughing&quot;&amp;gt;coughing&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;; and increased incidence, duration, and possibly severity of acute &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Respiratory_infections&quot;&amp;gt;respiratory infections&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. Residential wood combustion &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Exhaust_gas&quot;&amp;gt;emissions&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; also contain &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lower_sulfur_oxides&quot;&amp;gt;sulfur oxides&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nitrogen_oxides&quot;&amp;gt;nitrogen oxides&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Carbon_monoxide&quot;&amp;gt;carbon monoxide&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and potentially &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Carcinogenic&quot;&amp;gt;carcinogenic&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; compounds including &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Polycyclic_aromatic_hydrocarbons&quot;&amp;gt;polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Benzene&quot;&amp;gt;benzene&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Formaldehyde&quot;&amp;gt;formaldehyde&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dioxins_and_dioxin-like_compounds&quot;&amp;gt;dioxins&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. Some of these pollutants are known to cause cancer but their effects on human health via exposure to wood smoke have not been extensively studied.&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fireplace#cite_note-9&quot;&amp;gt;[9]&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;The Washington State Department of Ecology also published a booklet explaining why wood smoke can be dangerous. It explains that human lung and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Respiratory_system&quot;&amp;gt;respiratory systems&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; are unable to filter &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Particulates&quot;&amp;gt;particulates&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; emitted by wood combustion, which penetrate deeply into the lungs. For months, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Carcinogen&quot;&amp;gt;carcinogens&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; can continue to cause changes and structural damage within the respiratory system. Young children, seniors, pregnant women, smokers and individuals with &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Respiratory_disease&quot;&amp;gt;respiratory diseases&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; are most vulnerable. Wood smoke can cause disease and even death in children, because it is associated with &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lower_respiratory_tract_infection&quot;&amp;gt;lower respiratory tract infections&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fireplace#cite_note-Ecology-3&quot;&amp;gt;[3]&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; Home fireplaces have caused fatal &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Carbon_monoxide_poisoning&quot;&amp;gt;carbon monoxide poisoning&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fireplace#cite_note-10&quot;&amp;gt;[10]&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.epa.gov/burnwise/wood-smoke-and-your-health&quot;&amp;gt;EPA&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The smoke from wood burning is made up of a complex mixture of gases and fine particles (also called particle pollution, particulate matter, or PM). In addition to particle pollution, wood smoke contains several toxic air pollutants including: benzene, formaldehyde, acrolein, polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons (PAHs)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://heart.org/&quot;&amp;gt;Heart.org&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3685524/&quot;&amp;gt;2013 study&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; in the journal &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Particle and Fibre Toxicology&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; found exposure to wood smoke causes the arteries to become stiffer, which raises the risk of dangerous cardiac events. For pregnant women, a &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/30253313&quot;&amp;gt;2019 study&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; in &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Environmental Research&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; connected wood smoke exposure to a higher risk of hypertensive disorders of pregnancy, which include preeclampsia and gestational high blood pressure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: I thought that this would be a good YSK since it is the winter holidays, and a wood fire is anchored in our mind as a part of a picture-perfect holiday evening. But the truth is that they are completely awful, and many of us in modern society are still completely naïve to this fact. Just like led-based paint, asbestos, and smoking around children, it needs to be on its way out. Some states are already offering tax incentives to replace old fireplaces. Please just use an alternative method of heating if you have it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK黃瓜並不是唯一被醃製的美味。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Why YSK: other good for yous like mushrooms,
onions, carrots, asparagus and even cauliflower taste amazing when pickled. </p>
<p>An oft forgotten yet delicious way to get fiber and nutrients.</p> </div><!--
SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rpa51p/ysk_cucumbers_arent_the_only_delicious_thing_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rpa51p/ysk_cucumbers_arent_the_only_delicious_thing_that/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 03:51:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: other good for yous like mushrooms, onions, carrots, asparagus and even cauliflower taste amazing when pickled. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;An oft forgotten yet delicious way to get fiber and nutrients.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 如何節省現金以擺脫與在經濟上控制你的人的關係。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：對於控制你的人來說，離開似乎是不可能的。
這條建議可以幫助你節省資金，幫助你離開。
幫忙離開。</p> <p>如果你需要節省現金來離開有財務控制權的施暴者
如果你需要節省現金來離開有財務控制權的伴侶--利用雜貨店旅行來放...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rpakw2/ysk_how_to_save_cash_to_get_out_of_a_relationship/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rpakw2/ysk_how_to_save_cash_to_get_out_of_a_relationship/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 02:51:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: with someone who is controlling your finances leaving may seem impossible- this advice could help you save funds to help with leaving. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you need to save cash to get away from an abusive partner who has financial control- use grocery trips to put away money a little at a time. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If your partner will not see/check the itemized receipt, just get cash back when checking out and save that cash somewhere safe. Bank statements will show the total grocery store bill without showing any cash was withdrawn. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If your partner does check the itemized receipt, many stores now have free apps to clip digital coupons- my local store (giant) will give cash back for any digital coupons that did not properly come off during check out. Any coupons not “clipped” at least 30 minutes before a check out have to be manually paid out. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I got $15 cash back from customer service today that will not show up on any receipt or bank statement. Thankfully this is not something I need to worry about , but I thought it may help someone in a difficult situation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：清潔廁所後，清潔你的廁所]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：許多人（包括清潔工）在使用馬桶後沒有想到用抹布和水擦拭馬桶。
很多人（包括清潔工）在使用清潔液或清潔抹布後，沒有想到用抹布和水來擦拭馬桶蓋。
清潔液或清潔溼巾（如來蘇爾溼巾）。剩餘的清潔劑
殘留物會灼傷你的屁股，使你感到癢癢的。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rp1ekx/ysk_clean_your_toilet_after_a_cleaning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rp1ekx/ysk_clean_your_toilet_after_a_cleaning/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 18:47:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Many people (Including cleaners) don&amp;amp;#39;t think to wipe toilet seats down with a rag and water after using cleaning solution or cleaning wipes (like lysol wipes). The remaining cleaner residue will burn your bottom prompting you to have an itchy bottom.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你的體重太大，晨起後/plan b藥丸就會失去效力。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：晨起後/plan b藥片，是最有效的，如果你的體重平均低於170磅。
如果你的體重平均低於170磅，那麼它是最有效的。體重限制
所以在購買時一定要向藥劑師詢問體重限制。
這並不意味着它不會起作用。無論如何，它可能會起作用...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rodxlz/ysk_the_morning_afterplan_b_pill_looses/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rodxlz/ysk_the_morning_afterplan_b_pill_looses/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 01:38:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: The morning after/plan b pill, is the most effective if you weigh ON AVERAGE less than 170lbs. The weight limit does very by brand so always ask the pharmacist about the weight limit when you buy. This doesn&amp;amp;#39;t mean it WON&amp;amp;#39;T work. It may work anyway and it won&amp;amp;#39;t hurt you to take it.  Just don&amp;amp;#39;t rely on it as a sure thing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.plannedparenthood.org/learn/teens/ask-experts/whats-the-weight-limit-for-plan-b&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.plannedparenthood.org/learn/teens/ask-experts/whats-the-weight-limit-for-plan-b&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: 流行的藍牙追蹤器公司Tile最近被Life360收購了，這家公司的商業模式主要源於出售包括兒童在內的3100萬客戶的位置數據。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p><a
href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/12/9/22820381/tile-life360-location-tracking-data-privacy">Source</a></p>
<p><strong>Why YSK</strong>: Many people bought Tiles over the years because
他們希望有一個質量好、方便的藍牙跟蹤設備，以滿足他們的需求。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rofvya/ysk_the_popular_bluetooth_tracker_company_tile/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rofvya/ysk_the_popular_bluetooth_tracker_company_tile/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 21:34:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2021/12/9/22820381/tile-life360-location-tracking-data-privacy&quot;&amp;gt;Source&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Why YSK&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: Many people bought Tiles over the years because they wanted a good quality convenient bluetooth tracking device for their keys or valuables. With the introduction of Apple&amp;amp;#39;s Airtags and Galaxy SmartTags, Tile has been under a lot of pressure with their extremely limited network. Now that their parent company has switched to one whose philosophy is radically different, those who bought Tiles in the past should reconsider if they want to continue using those products and potentially lose out on a large part of their privacy.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also something Tile customers may want to know is that Mark Zuckerberg&amp;amp;#39;s sister sits on Life360&amp;amp;#39;s &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://investors.life360.com/investor-relations/?page=board-of-directors&quot;&amp;gt;board of directors&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It is worth noting that when asked about the parent company change, a Tile representative stated, &amp;amp;quot;Tile does not sell/monetize personal data and we have Life360’s full support and commitment to continue that,&amp;amp;quot; but that remains to be seen.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK講述了基本歸因錯誤，這是心理學中的一個關鍵概念，我們根據他人的行爲來判斷他們，而根據我們的意圖來判斷自己。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：如果有人惹惱了你，或者做了什麼
你不同意的事情，請記住，你無法看到他們的內心世界。
思想。</p> <p>當你在交通中攔截別人時，那是因爲你心不在焉。
因爲你心不在焉，或者因爲你遲到了，要給你的朋友唱搖籃曲。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rob9kl/ysk_about_the_fundamental_attribution_error_a_key/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rob9kl/ysk_about_the_fundamental_attribution_error_a_key/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 17:46:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: if someone is annoying you or does something that you disagree with, remember that you can’t see inside their thoughts.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When you cut someone off in traffic, it’s because you were being absentminded or because you’re late to sing lullabies to your newborn, right? But when someone cuts YOU off, it’s because they’re a jerk. You don’t know their inner thoughts, just the result of their actions in the world.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So: take it easy on your fellow people this holiday season, and remember the fundamental attribution error. You’ll be less stressed, less annoyed, and maybe even happier!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：儘可能通過Google Play/Apple App商店訂閱 "難以取消 "的服務，如《紐約時報》，以便以後能夠輕鬆取消，而無需與現場代理交談。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：像《紐約時報》這樣的服務機構是衆所周知的。
諸如《紐約時報》這樣的服務是臭名昭著的，它讓你與一個現場代理交談，並經歷了一個艱鉅的過程來取消你在網上輕鬆註冊的服務。
</p> <p>像這樣的服務並不罕見，而且與日俱增。
並不罕見，而且與日俱增，但許多服務允許你...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ro54uv/ysk_subscribe_to_difficult_to_cancel_services/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ro54uv/ysk_subscribe_to_difficult_to_cancel_services/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 11:42:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Services such the NY Times are notorious for making you speak to a live agent and go though an arduous process to cancel the service you easily signed up for online.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Services like this are not rare and growing day by day, however many allow you to sign up through the Google Play/ Apple App Store if you do so via their mobile apps instead of the websites.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you do this, you can easily cancel these subscriptions on your phone in just a few clicks without having to bother with each service&amp;amp;#39;s customer care.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK："無暇受孕 "指的是瑪麗的出生，而不是耶穌。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：這似乎只是一個超級常見的
誤解。</p> <p>這個想法是，瑪麗生來就沒有罪。</p>
<p>考慮到每年的時間，我認爲澄清一下可能會有幫助。
</div><！--SC_ON-->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ro33cf/ysk_the_immaculate_conception_refers_to_the_birth/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/ro33cf/ysk_the_immaculate_conception_refers_to_the_birth/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 09:18:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: this just seems like a super common misconception. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The idea is that Mary was born free from sin. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Given the time of year I thought it might be helpful to clarify.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你對飛機事故和事件感興趣，請查一下 "航空先驅報"。一旦有事情發生，你就會知道了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：名爲 "航空先驅 "的網站是對商業航空感興趣的人絕對不能錯過的。
的網站，是對商業航空事件和事故感興趣的人絕對不能錯過的。
</p> <p>對於那些對商業航空事件和事故感興趣的人來說，這絕對是必不可少的。</p> <p>它是由一個人管理的，他只發布事實和可覈實的信息。
它是由一個人經營的，他只發布有關任何事實和可覈實的信息。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmm2nk/ysk_if_youre_interested_in_airplane_accidents_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmm2nk/ysk_if_youre_interested_in_airplane_accidents_and/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 03:22:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: The website called &amp;amp;quot;The Aviation Herald&amp;amp;quot; is an absolute must for people interested in commercial aviation incidents and accidents and avgeeks. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s ran by a single person who posts only factual and verifiable information about any commercial aviation incident or accident with incredible speed and accuracy.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s incredibly interesting to scroll through and see what&amp;amp;#39;s happening out there.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://avherald.com/&quot;&amp;gt;https://avherald.com/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK--每年清潔你的烘乾機排氣管，包括內部和外部。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p><strong>Why YSK</strong> lint buildup happens
in the exhaust <em>no matter how religiously you clean it in the dryer</em> and
can create a fire hazard if not cleaned. The excess lint accumulates in the
exhaust (the tube in the wall that goes outside) and due to…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlk62c/ysk_clean_your_dryer_exhaust_yearly_both_inside/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlk62c/ysk_clean_your_dryer_exhaust_yearly_both_inside/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 01:48:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Why YSK&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; lint buildup happens in the exhaust &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;no matter how religiously you clean it in the dryer&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; and can create a fire hazard if not cleaned. The excess lint accumulates in the exhaust (the tube in the wall that goes outside) and due to moisture, will build up fairly quickly, so if you clean it once a year, it keeps the buildup to a minimum. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;-Especially if you rent, you never know when the last time was the line was cleaned so it should be one of the first things done before connecting your dryer.-&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In states that go below freezing, and in homes where the exhaust line is low, remember to check to ensure the ice buildup is not getting close to the line. The ice accumulates from the ground up, so if it gets too close, knock it over. Most building codes require new construction to be well off the ground but older homes can have lines close enough that ice buildup can accumulate enough that it reaches the line and you can quickly asphyxiate once the dryer is engaged. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We use the new year as our reminder to change smoke detector batteries, clean furnace and dryer exhausts, etc., and thought it might also help someone else. If you’re uncomfortable performing this task, it is recommended to clean your furnace exhaust bi-yearly and if you ask, an HVAC company will gladly clean your dryer vent, as well.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你的銀行賬單支付系統給你的 "接收日期 "幾乎不可能是實際收到支票的時間。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<！--SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：該日期通常只是
他們從你的賬戶中提取資金。然後他們打印支票並
最終郵寄。它可能需要2-3周的時間，才能真正被你的人/公司收到。
你要支付的人/公司收到。</p> <p>來源。我爲一家公司工作。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmyevn/ysk_the_receive_by_date_that_your_banks_bill_pay/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmyevn/ysk_the_receive_by_date_that_your_banks_bill_pay/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 20:41:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: That date is usually just the date they withdraw the funds from your account. Then they print the check and eventually mail it. It could take 2-3 weeks for it to actually be received by the person/ company you&amp;amp;#39;re paying. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source: I work for a company that performs Home maintenance services, and it&amp;amp;#39;s not uncommon to receive packets of bill payment checks. It appears that when banks have multiple clients sending payments to the same company, they will hold the checks and send them all in the same envelope. I regularly receive packets of bill payment checks, with the checks themselves having dates ranging over a space of two weeks. The number of clients who get angry with me for telling him I haven&amp;amp;#39;t received their payment yet, when the bank has given them a date and already withdrawn their funds makes me realize that people don&amp;amp;#39;t understand how bill payment seems to work. The funds don&amp;amp;#39;t come out of your account when the checks are received, they come out of your account when the checks are printed, which is not necessarily even when they are mailed out.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Note that this may not apply to all bank bill pay systems and you should contact your individual bank for more details.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK VHS錄像帶會隨着時間的推移而退化。在平均條件下，磁帶的預期壽命約爲30年。那些躺在90年代的帶有珍貴家庭記憶的磁帶已經明顯退化了。你應該現在就把你家裏所有的VHS磁帶數字化。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：許多人都有舊的VHS錄像帶躺在身邊
很多人都有舊的VHS錄像帶在身邊，沒有意識到它們很快就會退化得沒有用處。這些
could be the only video of loved ones, etc. If you want to keep these memories,
you must convert these to digital ASAP.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rnr906/ysk_vhs_video_cassettes_degrade_over_time_under/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rnr906/ysk_vhs_video_cassettes_degrade_over_time_under/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 19:41:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Many people have old VHS tapes laying around, not realizing that they will soon be degraded  beyond usefulness.  These could be the only video of loved ones, etc.  If you want to keep these memories, you must convert these to digital ASAP.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在專業場合，不要給別人起未經要求的可愛的暱稱。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：這並不有趣或令人喜愛，它是
貶低和不可接受，而且會使你顯得非常不專業。稱呼
在一個專業的環境中，叫某人寶貝、親愛的、女孩、男孩、年輕人或類似的稱呼是不敬的。
在專業環境中顯然是不尊重人的，以前是可以的...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/riov6j/ysk_do_not_give_people_unasked_for_cutesy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/riov6j/ysk_do_not_give_people_unasked_for_cutesy/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 17:38:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: It is not funny or endearing, it is demeaning and unacceptable and will make you appear very unprofessional.  Calling someone baby, honey, dear, girl, boy, youngster or the like is disrespectful in a professional setting apparently used to be OK for previous generations but I can tell you that I for one will not work with you if you refuse to use my name and give me a child’s nickname. Sure, you will find people who will work with you but it will not be the A team or anyone with self respect.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK: Youtube最近一直在降低你的分辨率以節省流媒體數據。以下是如何解決這個問題。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：你是否注意到視頻的加載速度爲
440p，即使你的網絡連接是正常的？安裝tampermonkey
擴展，然後安裝<
href="https://greasyfork.org/en/scripts/23661-youtube...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmemil/ysk_youtube_has_been_lowering_your_resolution/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmemil/ysk_youtube_has_been_lowering_your_resolution/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 17:14:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Have you noticed videos loading in at 440p even though your internet connection is fine? Install the tampermonkey extension for your browser and then install &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://greasyfork.org/en/scripts/23661-youtube-hd&quot;&amp;gt;https://greasyfork.org/en/scripts/23661-youtube-hd&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You can set your preferred maximum resolution in the editor.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：你的貓咪經常嘔吐是不正常的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：</p> <p>我經常看到人們隨意地
提到他們的貓在地板上嘔吐的不便，彷彿這是貓咪行爲的一個正常部分。
</p> <p>其實不然。</p> <p>貓咪偶爾也會嘔吐--通常是因爲它的毛髮。
偶爾會嘔吐--通常是因爲毛球或吃了東西......。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rnmy9v/ysk_it_isnt_normal_for_your_cats_to_be_vomiting/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rnmy9v/ysk_it_isnt_normal_for_your_cats_to_be_vomiting/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 16:53:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I often see people causally mentioning the inconvenience of their cat vomiting on their floor, as if it is a normal part of cat behaviour.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It isn&amp;amp;#39;t.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cats will throw up occasionally - typically because of a fur ball or having eaten too quickly, but it isn&amp;amp;#39;t normal for them to be doing it as frequently as &amp;amp;quot;once every few weeks&amp;amp;quot;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cats can often vomit because:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You aren&amp;amp;#39;t grooming your cat enough, therefore fur balls are forming and will eventually be expelled (a complete brush once a week should be sufficient in minimising this)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It is eating too quickly, playing too soon after eating, or both&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You are changing their food too frequently - you should find a food that works (ask your vet) and stick with it&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If none of these reasons sound like they could be the cause of your cat vomiting, then you should take it to the vet and get it checked out - it could be a sign of an underlying illness, intolerance to a specific food, or exposure to something toxic (some houseplants can be culprits).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also, for goodness sake, don&amp;amp;#39;t give your cat chocolate or anything that isn&amp;amp;#39;t strictly edible for cats (Google if in doubt).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：谷歌密碼管理器無法與第三方管理器相提並論]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：我想我要爲別人省去了
我目前正在經歷的頭痛問題。你應該知道谷歌密碼
是一個基於瀏覽器的管理器，與你的瀏覽器數據相聯繫，如
歷史記錄/cookies/緩存，所以它可以意外地被清除，而且......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlolbn/ysk_google_password_manager_is_not_comparable_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlolbn/ysk_google_password_manager_is_not_comparable_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 10:43:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: I figured I&amp;amp;#39;d save someone else the headache I&amp;amp;#39;m currently going though. You should know google password manager is a browser-based manager and linked to your browser&amp;amp;#39;s data like history/cookies/cache, so it can be cleared accidentally and easily. A third party app (lastpass, keeper, 1password, etc.) is a true password manager and much better choice. Other things to note if you&amp;amp;#39;re new to tech-security and want to be better: Google&amp;amp;#39;s auto-generating feature only creates relatively simple passwords and you cannot change the requirements/length. It is &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;only&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; available with chrome, while third party managers are separate entities and have apps/extensions. Being linked to google, someone would only need one password on one of your devices to access them &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;all&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How did I learn this? Well, I absent-mindedly cleared my history along with all other data in the advanced settings to help try and debug an app. Next thing I know, the entirety of 2+ years of saved passwords, most of which are auto-generated, are gone! Don&amp;amp;#39;t be like me. But if you do want to stick with google pw manager, make sure to back them up. There is an option to download a .csv file with all your passwords if you want to move them to another manager. That introduces a whole other layer of risk, so be careful.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK讓女孩喝得酩酊大醉，以便她與你發生性關係是強姦。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：它可以影響受害者很長一段時間
潛在地使你陷入很多困境</p> <p>在我看來，根據我所看到的電影，許多人都在不知不覺中宣揚強姦文化。
在我所看到的電影中，許多人都在不知不覺地促進強姦文化。在
我最近重新觀看的一部非常受歡迎的電影（《超級大壞蛋》），喬納...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rn27jx/ysk_getting_a_girl_really_drunk_so_shell_have_sex/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rn27jx/ysk_getting_a_girl_really_drunk_so_shell_have_sex/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 07:54:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: it can effect the victim for a long time and could potentially land you in a lot of shit&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It seems to me based on films I have seen, many of them are unknowingly promoting rape culture. In one very popular film I rewatched recently (Superbad), Jonah hill jokes that parties are for getting girls really drunk so they’ll sleep with you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With recent personal events this shocked me that such a popular film would joke about something like that and normalise it. If you sleep with someone (whether it’s a man/woman) who is blackout drunk and likely would never even consider sleeping with you sober THAT IS RAPE, there was no consent.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you’re still reading also please read up on symptoms of Rohypnol/ GHB (date rape drugs). Many people think being spiked looks like you’re really drunk, unable to speak or walk but the reality is often VERY different. They can make you euphoric, lose inhibition, increase sense of connection with others, influence decision making and increase libido. If the spiker knows what they’re doing it can be so hard to spot and it’s so important to look out for your friends and ANY indication they may have been spiked GET TESTED ASAP. These drugs only stay in your system for a few hours and we need to start catching these bastards!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Take care, have a good Christmas for those who celebrate it :)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please stop making this a gender thing, I literally say man/woman&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My post has actually shocked me seeing this level of hatred in the comments and comments saying “well what about &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;insert men’s issue&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;” NOT EVERYTHING IS A MENS VS WOMEN COMPETITION &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I don’t comment on posts about men’s mental health and suicide rates saying “oh yeah well women are more likely to get raped so that’s the real issue”ygm?? They’re BOTH issues, let them both exist&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：一氧化碳（CO）中毒的症狀]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：一個簡單的缺乏症狀知識的人可能是你和/或你的家人死亡的全部原因。
症狀可能就是你和/或你的朋友/親人死亡的全部原因。
</p> <p>我的姐姐和她的丈夫可能已經死了。
</p> <p>我無意中聽到我妹妹告訴我們的媽媽，她仍然在脫髮，而且......。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rn6dl3/ysk_the_symptoms_of_carbon_monoxide_co_poisoning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rn6dl3/ysk_the_symptoms_of_carbon_monoxide_co_poisoning/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 01:47:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: A simple lack in knowledge of symptoms could be all that is required for the death of you and/or your friends/loved ones.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My sister and her husband could&amp;amp;#39;ve died.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I overheard my sister telling our mom that she is still losing hair and can&amp;amp;#39;t figure out why - this is red flag #1, but it didn&amp;amp;#39;t click in my brain at that point.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Several hours later, my sister was having a discussion with our dad.  For the sake of brevity, here are the important parts:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Dad (joking): &amp;amp;quot;It sounds like your house is haunted!&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sister: &amp;amp;quot;It literally is haunted.  I see ghosts all the time.&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;click&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Me: &amp;amp;quot;Do you have a CO detector in your house?&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sister: &amp;amp;quot;No.  Why?&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Long story short, her house did indeed have a CO leak.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Other symptoms her and her husband were experiencing:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Dull headache&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Weakness&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Dizziness&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Nausea&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;These symptoms had gone on for so long that they just accepted them as a normal part of life.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Additional symptoms can be found &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/carbon-monoxide/symptoms-causes/syc-20370642&quot;&amp;gt;here&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://whippleplumbing.com/low-exposure-carbon-monoxide-poisoning/&quot;&amp;gt;here&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you or someone you know are inexplicably experiencing any of these symptoms: get the hell out of the house IMMEDIATELY and pick up a CO detector, then call a plumber if it goes off.  You could potentially save lives.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit:  Forgot to mention - Symptoms go away after leaving the house for a while, such as visiting family.  My sister and her husband said they feel great when they aren&amp;amp;#39;t in the house.  This is another significant indicator of CO poisoning.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你買了房子或爲你的抵押貸款再融資，你可能會收到一大堆關於你的契約和抵押貸款文件的垃圾郵件，你應該忽略所有這些郵件。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK:</p> <p>取決於你所在州的公共房地產記錄和法律。
的公共房地產記錄和法律，掠奪性公司可能能夠看到
購房時，你的新房契或抵押貸款被歸入公共記錄。
</p><p>根據你所在的州的公共房地產記錄和法律，掠奪性公司可能會看到你的新契約或抵押貸款在你購買房產或再融資時的公開記錄。他們有一套算法。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmkqzd/ysk_that_if_you_buy_a_house_or_refinance_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmkqzd/ysk_that_if_you_buy_a_house_or_refinance_your/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 20:40:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;-depending on your state&amp;amp;#39;s public real estate records and laws, predatory companies may be able to see whenever your new deed or mortgage is filed into public record when you purchase a property or refinance a mortgage. They have algorithms set up to comb through newly filed public records and automatically send mailers to every new homeowner or newly refinanced borrower. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;-these predatory companies will spam mail you with offers to send copies of your documents for an exorbitant price which you can otherwise get for free or very inexpensively&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;-(by the way, other predatory companies will spam mail you with life insurance offers to pay off your new mortgage (even if you refinance) if you die. I just refinanced and got no less than 12 mailers across 2 weeks.) &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;-you should never pay any 3rd party company for copies of your deed and mortgage if you buy or refinance a house. Your title company should send copies to you free of charge or for a few dollars. You can also obtain them from the local public record authority for a small charge compared to the insane fees charges by the predatory mail companies. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is so insidious because most people don&amp;amp;#39;t know how real estate records work. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There&amp;amp;#39;s nothing illegal about what these companies do, but it&amp;amp;#39;s very unethical. It costs them 50 cents to mail you a letter, makes you think you need to get the service from them, and if you give them hundreds of dollars for their &amp;amp;quot;service&amp;amp;quot; then they just made 99.9% profit. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you need any paperwork after your closing, contact your title company, bank, insurance company, or whatever service provider you&amp;amp;#39;ve already engaged. Don&amp;amp;#39;t fall victim to the public record profiteers.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And if you need life insurance to pay off your mortgage if you die-- don&amp;amp;#39;t buy it from them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，"你的（空白）是你名字的第一個字母和你的生日 "的帖子是人們弄清你身份的好辦法。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：人們總是評論他們 "得到 "什麼。
如果你對他們的評論足夠多，就很容易找出你的名字縮寫和出生日期以及你的各種細節。
如果你在足夠多的評論上發表評論，就很容易知道你的名字縮寫和出生日期以及關於你的各種細節。將這些與
你在你的帖子歷史中所說的話，他們可能知道更多......]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmprv9/ysk_that_the_your_blank_is_the_first_letter_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmprv9/ysk_that_the_your_blank_is_the_first_letter_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 20:40:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: People always comment what they ‘get’ and if you comment on enough of them it’s easy to work out your initials and date of birth as well as various details about you. Combine that with anything you’ve said in your post history and they probably know more than you want them to.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：聯邦調查局分享據稱參與制作兒童色情製品的人、房間、物品和物體的圖像。任何信息都是有幫助的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p><a
href="https://www.fbi.gov/wanted/ecap">https://www.fbi.gov/wanted/ecap</a></p>
</div><!-- SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmmeno/ysk_the_fbi_shares_images_of_people_rooms_items/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmmeno/ysk_the_fbi_shares_images_of_people_rooms_items/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 17:07:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fbi.gov/wanted/ecap&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.fbi.gov/wanted/ecap&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲腰高比（WtHR）是比BMI更強的預測體重相關健康問題的因素。理想情況下，你的腰圍大約是你身高的一半。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK：</p> <p>與體重有關的疾病是一些最具毀滅性的疾病。
一些最具破壞性的疾病，也是一些最容易預防的疾病，而且
BMI（可能是最受歡迎的指標）實際上在預測與體重有關的疾病方面做得很差。
</p> <p>這篇文章的目的不是要...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmppwp/ysk_that_waist_to_height_ratio_wthr_is_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmppwp/ysk_that_waist_to_height_ratio_wthr_is_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 11:38:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Weight related illnesses are some of the most devastating and also some of the most preventable diseases, and BMI (likely the most popular metric) actually does a poor job of predicting weight-related illnesses.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This post is not intended to body shame anyone. No measure is perfect.  It is simply meant to inform people of an easy, high-predictive-power way to assess your own risk for weight-related illnesses.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/14674615/&quot;&amp;gt;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/14674615/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，你身體中95%的5-羥色胺（穩定情緒的荷爾蒙，負責健康的感覺）是在你的腸道中產生。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：你腸道中的菌羣負責生產許多重要的激素，包括血清素。
腸道菌羣負責生產許多重要的激素，包括血清素。
保持健康的腸道微生物羣在降低壓力水平、保持身體健康方面起着巨大作用。
壓力水平，保持抑鬱症，獲得足夠的睡眠，等等。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmjnod/ysk_that_95_of_your_bodys_serotonin_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmjnod/ysk_that_95_of_your_bodys_serotonin_the/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 05:36:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: The flora in your gut is responsible for the production of a lot of important hormones, including serotonin. Maintaining a healthy intestinal micro-biome plays a huge role in lowering stress levels, keeping depression at bay, getting enough sleep, and so many other things that can improve your quality of life. Eating a balanced diet not only keeps you healthy physically, but it promotes a healthy mental state too.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TLDR: A lot of mental health issues can potentially be treated by eating a balanced, healthy diet. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.healthline.com/health/irritable-bowel-syndrome/serotonin-effects&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.healthline.com/health/irritable-bowel-syndrome/serotonin-effects&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apa.org/monitor/2012/09/gut-feeling&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.apa.org/monitor/2012/09/gut-feeling&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，如果你與服務行業的好工人交往，給他們工作的公司打電話表揚該工人，通常會給這個人的生活帶來切實的好處。只是不要提到折扣或偷工減料。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：</p> <ol> <li><p>它使你的生活更美好，讓他們付出額外的努力對你好。
讓他們付出額外的努力對你好，所以讓他們的生活變得更好是很好的
讓他們的生活更美好。Usually they don&#39;t see a ton of reward.</p></li>
<li><p>it costs you nothing to call, and only 5 minutes of…]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmheie/ysk_that_if_you_interact_with_a_nice_worker_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmheie/ysk_that_if_you_interact_with_a_nice_worker_in/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 02:52:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;it makes your life better to have them put in the extra effort to be nice to you, so it&amp;amp;#39;s nice to make their life better. Usually they don&amp;amp;#39;t see a ton of reward.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;it costs you nothing to call, and only 5 minutes of time usually. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s a powerful statement, because people usually just call to complain. A compliment speaks loudly. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s good for the businesses too, to have workers that are pleasant. Everyone benefits from them rewarding solid and friendly employees. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Tip: don&amp;amp;#39;t mention them giving you discounts etc. Do mention the solid experience they provided you as a customer, and how friendly they were.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK 用激光瞄準飛機是非法的，可能導致罰款和/或監禁。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：在美國上空飛行的飛機受到
受聯邦法律的管轄和保護。干擾飛行中的飛機是
是一項聯邦罪行。當飛行員從地面上看到激光時，會使他或她失明幾分鐘。
當飛行員從地面上看到激光時，會使他或她失明數分鐘，嚴重危害到他或她的安全。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmbarc/ysk_targeting_an_aircraft_with_a_laser_is_illegal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmbarc/ysk_targeting_an_aircraft_with_a_laser_is_illegal/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 21:37:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Aircraft flying over the US are governed and protected by federal law. Interfering with an aircraft in flight is a federal offense. When a pilot sees a LASER from the ground it can blind him or her for several minutes, seriously endangering the safety of the flight, the aircraft, the pilots, and all passengers onboard the aircraft.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.avweb.com/aviation-news/mississippi-man-faces-prison-time-for-targeting-aircraft-with-a-laser/&quot;&amp;gt;Here&amp;amp;#39;s an example of a recent penalty&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你在美國爲非營利組織或政府全職工作，你可能能夠通過PSLF計劃擺脫你的一些學生貸款。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：學生債務在美國是巨大的。
任何能夠幫助人們擺脫一些債務的東西都是偉大的。美國教育部
美國教育部於10月6日宣佈臨時擴大PSLF的範圍。
計劃。趁着這個機會，趕快行動吧！</p> <p>美國的全職非營利組織和...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmafgj/ysk_if_you_work_fulltime_in_the_us_for_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rmafgj/ysk_if_you_work_fulltime_in_the_us_for_a/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 19:34:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Student debt is HUGE in the US, and anything that can help people get rid of some of that debt is great. The U.S. Department of Education announced a temporary expansion on Oct. 6 for the PSLF program. Get it while you can!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;US full-time nonprofit and government workers that have Federal Direct Loans student debt may be eligible for loan forgiveness, cancellation and/or consolidation of federal student loans under the Public Service Loan Forgiveness (PSLF) program. You could have your outstanding debt forgiven tax-free, after making 120 qualifying monthly payments under a qualifying repayment plan. Go to the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://studentaid.gov/pslf/&quot;&amp;gt;PSLF Help Tool&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; to find out if you&amp;amp;#39;re eligible.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK。貿易工作並不適合所有人。來自一個有13年工作經驗的商人]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼是YSK；我聽到很多人淡化了學校，炒作了交易。
我聽到很多人貶低學校，炒作貿易。雖然對某些人來說，貿易可能是通往成功未來的最佳途徑。
雖說對某些行業來說，可能是通往成功未來的最佳途徑，但這並不適合於所有人。</p> <p>我已經培訓了
至少有80％的人在聲稱他們已經成功後被淘汰。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlicqy/ysk_trade_work_isnt_for_everyone_coming_from_a_13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlicqy/ysk_trade_work_isnt_for_everyone_coming_from_a_13/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 23:41:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK;  I hear a lot of people downplay school and hype up trades. While for some trades may be the best way to a successful future, this does not hold true for everyone. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ve trained dozens of people and watched at least %80 wash out after claiming they could handle it. Why? It’s hard, depressing, you’re going to miss your family get no thanks, and it’s out right demoralizing until you’ve mastered it unless you’re a true die hard country boy or handy man. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you or your child considers trade work you have to be In perfect physical condition to even have a shot at the big bucks(some, or most tbh, forego that for hard drugs to cope). There is no I’m tired or hungry when you’re at the mercy of people that have done this for years. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I will not quit my trade although I am in the process of getting an education. I take pride in building. Aliens didn’t build the pyramids people like you and I  did. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Concrete finisher here. The broken bones, missing time with my family and pissing blood from dehydration was enough to make me reconsider my choice. 2022 college freshman at age 28&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TLDR; do your research before joining trade work. You may be in for a surprise.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：如果你在面試中被問到是否打算生孩子，你不必回答，你可以直接說不。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：最近在一次採訪中被問到這個問題。
採訪中被問到了這個問題，作爲最後的問題之一，他們爲什麼要問我這個問題，這一點非常明顯。
我很清楚他們爲什麼要問我這個問題。作爲一個主要由男性組成的行業中的女性，我感到
因爲我確信他們不會問男人的問題。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlgusb/ysk_if_you_get_asked_in_an_interview_whether/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlgusb/ysk_if_you_get_asked_in_an_interview_whether/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 19:40:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: was recently asked this in an interview as one of the final questions and it was super obvious why they were asking me it. As a women in an industry that is made mostly of men, I felt slightly unfairly treated as I&amp;amp;#39;m sure they don&amp;amp;#39;t ask men going for the role that question. I&amp;amp;#39;ve also read that it is illegal to ask that question in some countries. Has anyone else been asked this in interviews? Or is it just me?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK，你從僱主那裏收到的 "廉價 "禮物實際上可能是從你的經理的口袋裏掏出來的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：我知道現在是拉屎的季節。
我知道現在是拉屎的季節，我也很支持，因爲這些錢確實是來自於企業的預算。
但在你收到禮物時點燃你的火把之前
但在你收到禮物時點燃火把之前，考慮一下你收到的東西是由......支付的。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlhqbh/ysk_that_the_cheap_gifts_that_you_receive_from/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rlhqbh/ysk_that_the_cheap_gifts_that_you_receive_from/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 18:37:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: I know it&amp;amp;#39;s the season to shit on shitty corporate gifts, and I&amp;amp;#39;m all for it in the event that the money does come out of the corporate budget, but before you light your torches when you get your present, consider that what you received was paid from the pocket of someone not too far removed from you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;25 years ago, when we all got our first &amp;amp;#39;real jobs&amp;amp;#39; out of college, I remember many of my mates bragging about their company-funded golf games and company-expensed dinners and amazing Christmas bonuses. In retrospect I think most of them were exaggerating/lying, but I always wondered why I never had those perks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Come Christmas, my immediate manager (we were a team of 12) went around and gave envelopes to everyone. &amp;amp;#39;Here&amp;amp;#39;s the fat Christmas bonus I hear everyone talk about&amp;amp;#39;, I thought to myself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I open the envelope and see a $15 gift certificate to a retail store. &amp;amp;#39;That&amp;amp;#39;s it?&amp;amp;#39; I thought to myself &amp;amp;#39;I bust my chops all day for $15?&amp;amp;#39; I was livid.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I was livid all the way home. Livid that evening. Livid that weekend. I told my gf how livid I was. I expected her to be livid along with me.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Instead, she said &amp;amp;quot;That was nice of her, spending her own money like that.&amp;amp;quot; That&amp;amp;#39;s when I realized that this wasn&amp;amp;#39;t a cheap gift, but an amazing, thoughtful gift. I was so obsessed with myself, that I didn&amp;amp;#39;t realize that we were the only team to get something.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My manager - who wasn&amp;amp;#39;t getting paid much more than us, but who had way more financial responsibilities than us - took it upon herself to go out and get each of her team something with her own money - almost $200.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I felt terrible for feeling the way I did, but it taught me a valuable lesson in life.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Happy holidays, everyone!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，能量飲料的酸度很高，因此對你的牙齒/胃酸倒流有害。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：飲料可能是酸性的，即使它們喫起來不酸不苦。
飲料可能是酸性的，即使它們的味道不是酸或苦。</p> <p>一般能量飲料的PH值爲2.8。
實際上與蘇打水相同。</p> <p>The acidity of energy drinks can contribute to
enamel degradation and/or acid reflux.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON -->]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rkubb0/ysk_that_energy_drinks_are_very_acidic_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rkubb0/ysk_that_energy_drinks_are_very_acidic_and/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 02:53:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Drinks can be acidic even if they don’t taste sour or bitter. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The average energy drink has a PH of 2.8, really the same as soda. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The acidity of energy drinks can contribute to enamel degradation and/or acid reflux.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK：在美國，沒有無鋁止汗劑這種東西。它們被認爲是藥物，美國食品和藥物管理局只批准在止汗劑中使用源自鋁的活性成分。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：FDA認爲止汗劑是藥物，因爲它們可以防止出汗。
因爲它們可以防止出汗。在美國的OTC專著中，唯一被批准的活性成分
美國的OTC專著中批准的唯一活性成分都是鋁製的。所以在美國
因此，在美國，任何 "不含鋁 "的產品都是除臭劑，而且...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rk7hkf/ysk_in_the_united_states_there_is_no_such_thing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rk7hkf/ysk_in_the_united_states_there_is_no_such_thing/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 21:36:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: The FDA considers antiperspirants as drugs as they prevent perspiration. The only active ingredients approved in the United States in the OTC monograph are all aluminum derived. So in the United States, anything that is “aluminum-free” is a deodorant and will only cover up the scent, but does nothing for sweat prevention, which causes the bad smell in the first place. Any company that tells you their aluminum-free deodorant is an antiperspirant is making either a mislabeled claim, or might be adulterated depending on the situation the FDA deems fit.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://ecfr.io/Title-21/Section-350.10&quot;&amp;gt;OTC monograph active ingredients&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你在加油站加油時，燃料流被點燃，不要將噴嘴從接收器上移開。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>如果你遇到這種情況，請將噴嘴保持在原位。
如果發生這種情況，請將噴嘴留在原地，用開關或緊急開關關閉泵的燃料，並告訴服務員。
告知服務員，服務員將關閉主泵並呼叫緊急服務。
爲什麼是YSK：我已經看到了大約69個視頻，這些人經歷了...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rki013/ysk_if_youre_pumping_at_a_gas_station_and_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rki013/ysk_if_youre_pumping_at_a_gas_station_and_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 12:52:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If this happens to you, keep the nozzle in place, shut off the fuel at the pump with the on/off or emergency switch, and tell the attendant who will shut off the main pump and call emergency services.  Why YSK:  I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen about 69 videos of people who experience this and immediately remove the nozzle and wave the stream of fire around. This will be your first instinct and it is WRONG. To lower the chance this happening, ground yourself when you exit your car by touching the door frame.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK認爲，刪除你的數據並不總是刪除它]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：你的數據往往仍然可以被恢復
你的數據經常可以被恢復，並被黑客攻擊，甚至在你要求刪除數據的請求被公司確認後也是如此。
</p> <p>我曾在大技術領域擔任數據科學家，並觀察到數據刪除是一件棘手的事情。
數據刪除是一件棘手的事情。數據治理法律因人而異。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rkf6e1/ysk_that_deleting_your_data_doesnt_always_delete/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rkf6e1/ysk_that_deleting_your_data_doesnt_always_delete/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 10:39:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: your data can often still be recovered, and hacked, even after your request that it be deleted was confirmed by a company.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I worked as a data scientist in big tech, and observed that data deletion is tricky business. Data governance laws vary by country and even state, and range quite widely. In some jurisdictions, there are no requirements: a company owns the data generated through your interactions with its services. Other countries/states do have data ownership/privacy requirements, but even the most stringent laws often require that data not be actually deleted.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Many large companies retain data for &amp;amp;quot;compliance&amp;amp;quot; reasons. A request to delete personal data, while often honored for marketing purposes by companies seeking to operate legally (not all do), is often considered legally compliant if a company only locks your data away rather than deletes it. Data access in these cases is usually limited to a handful of people dedicated to the data privacy compliance effort, but the data is often kept for months and even years. This is not a company&amp;amp;#39;s fault, but rather is mandated by other laws--ones that help identify corruption, market manipulation, anti-consumer actions, etc.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;While retaining data is useful for the above reasons, this legal mess can create confusion for ordinary people. In practice, your data is often accessible even after a company &amp;amp;quot;deletes&amp;amp;quot; it. Given that data breaches in today&amp;amp;#39;s world are effectively only a matter of time at any given company, you can pretty much assume that any online interaction you make can one day surface. Companies do have an obligation to try to keep this from happening, but can seldom be counted on as software often relies on hundreds and thousands of other pieces of software as dependencies--consistently updating all of which is incredibly difficult.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK TurboTax今年不再爲低收入的美國人延續其免費文件計劃]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：許多賺取&lt;$72,000的人使用
TurboTax來免費報稅。今年，他們將需要找到另一個
供應商。請看<
href="https://www.irs.gov/filing/free-file-do-your-federal-taxes-for-free">https://www.irs.gov/filing/free-file-do-your...]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rigvha/ysk_turbotax_is_not_renewing_its_free_file/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rigvha/ysk_turbotax_is_not_renewing_its_free_file/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 19:34:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Many people who make &amp;amp;lt;$72,000 use TurboTax to file taxes for free. This year, they will need to find another provider. Check out &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.irs.gov/filing/free-file-do-your-federal-taxes-for-free&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.irs.gov/filing/free-file-do-your-federal-taxes-for-free&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; for more information about which companies will have partnered with the IRS for free file this year (currently this information is not available yet).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YSK戶外的寵物貓和野貓是一個巨大的捕食問題。]]></title><description><![CDATA[<! -- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>爲什麼YSK：讓你的貓在外面活動可能對它們的心理健康有好處。
對它們的心理健康有好處，但對當地的生態系統卻不利。貓咪
是天然的捕食者，因此，它是美國最大和最多的鳥類入侵者。
在美國，貓是天然的捕食者，因此是最大和最豐富的鳥類入侵捕食者。</p> <p>野貓的數量超過5000萬隻。]]></description><link>https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rihl9w/ysk_pet_cats_outdoors_and_feral_cats_are_a_huge/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://know.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/YouShouldKnow/comments/rihl9w/ysk_pet_cats_outdoors_and_feral_cats_are_a_huge/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 19:34:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why YSK: Letting your cats outside may be great for their mental health, but it is worse for your local ecosystem. Cats are natural predators, and as a result are the largest and most abundant invasive predator of birds in the US. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Feral cats number over 50M in the US, equating to about &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;8 billion&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; small game hunts per year, most of which are small song birds.(2.4 billion) &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why is this important to me?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;a single mating pair of cats can produce 400,000 offspring in 7 years&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;cats kill about 50% of songbird fledglings (baby birds)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; they will never recover at this rate&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;a UNebraska study has pinned 33 bird extinction events on cat predation&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Humans&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, almost 8 billion of us and our cars, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;are responsible for about 400M deaths of song-birds annually, cats are 2.4 billion&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This issue is 100% to blame on irresponsible cat owners because they are an invasive species brought here by pet trade. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source:&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wintuaudubon.org/feral-cats-drive-songbird-decline/&quot;&amp;gt;Wintu Audubon Society - Feral cats drive songbird decline&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>